<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/isabelle_zhang/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/isabelle_zhang/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix 2019 General Election Poll: Results</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-felix-general-election-poll-results-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-felix-general-election-poll-results-2019/</guid>
        <description></description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union Council Votes 36:1 to Reject Increase in Halls Rent Price</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-union-council-votes-reject-increase-halls-rent/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-union-council-votes-reject-increase-halls-rent/</guid>
        <description>The Union and College are currently in negotiations over the price of rent in first-year accommodation, which College is proposing to increase by 12.2% overall in order to match a break-even model as calculated by Campus Services. On Tuesday, December 3rd, the Union President and Deputy President …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chemical Kitchen: Leading the Charge on Innovation</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-Chemical-Kitchen-Leading-Charge-on-Innovation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-Chemical-Kitchen-Leading-Charge-on-Innovation/</guid>
        <description>Chemical Kitchen, a new course rolled out within the Department of Chemistry, aims to introduce students to laboratory skills and practical experience via a more approachable and unconventional method. In groups of fifteen at a time, students spend three hours a day for three days in a newly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>General Election Time</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-general-election-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,Harvey Dolton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-general-election-time/</guid>
        <description>Above: General Election 2017 constituency map
It would be impossible to discuss any politics in the UK without stumbling upon Brexit. Brexit has been the key political issue of the last three years, a problem that successive governments have been unable to satisfactorily resolve.
The calling of this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Election Section: Canada’s Trudeau Wins Minority Government</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-election-section-canadas-trudeau-wins-minority-government/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,Harvey Dolton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-election-section-canadas-trudeau-wins-minority-government/</guid>
        <description>When first elected as the Canadian Prime Minister in 2015, Justin Trudeau was a breath of fresh air for a country that for 9 years had been governed by the Conservative Stephen Harper. He was young, charismatic, progressive, and completely unlike the traditionally understated style of politics …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Highs and Lows: Parliamentary Votes Prolong Brexit Uncertainty</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-25-10-highs-lows-parliamentary-votes-prolong-brexit-uncertainty/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,Harvey Dolton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-25-10-highs-lows-parliamentary-votes-prolong-brexit-uncertainty/</guid>
        <description>Last week and Monday 21st October
Boris Johnson reaches a withdrawal agreement with the European Union, a 115 page Withdrawal Agreement Bill was published. The bill outlines the terms on which Britain will leave the EU and includes an exit fee, the price sum has not yet been established, to be paid …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>If You Don’t Already Know: Why an Impeachment Inquiry against Trump has Been Opened</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-if-you-dont-already-know-why-impeachment-against-trump-has-opened/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-if-you-dont-already-know-why-impeachment-against-trump-has-opened/</guid>
        <description>For months, Speaker of the House Nancy Pelosi has been resisting calls from progressive members of her party to open an impeachment inquiry into President Donald Trump. But within days of breaking news about a whistle-blower complaint about Trump, she has come out in support of it. On September …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Staff excellence is celebrated at the Annual Imperial Garden Party</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-staff-excellence-is-celebrated-at-the-annual-imperial-garden-party/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-staff-excellence-is-celebrated-at-the-annual-imperial-garden-party/</guid>
        <description>On Tuesday 18th June, Felix was in attendance at the annual Imperial Garden Party, a ceremony to honour staff who have made outstanding contributions to research and academic excellence, public engagement and outreach, teaching and student support, and to Imperial’s culture and community.
Staff …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Policy View of Abortion</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-a-policy-view-of-abortion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-a-policy-view-of-abortion/</guid>
        <description>Last week, the Alabama State legislature approved a bill that would limit a woman’s access to abortion at every stage of pregnancy and make it a criminal offence for doctors who provide the service. This measure has been the most drastic move by American pro-lifers to challenge a woman’s right to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Do you sometimes feel like you’re in China?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-do-you-sometimes-feel-like-you-re-in-china/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-do-you-sometimes-feel-like-you-re-in-china/</guid>
        <description>Do you sometimes feel like you’re in China? That’s what Suburban Express, a bus company based in Illinois, promises their customers will not feel when on their buses. The Urbana-Champaign campus of the University of Illinois (UIUC) has drawn a surging population of Chinese students to the area, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Green New Deal: the less realistic the better</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-the-green-new-deal-the-less-realistic-the-better/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-the-green-new-deal-the-less-realistic-the-better/</guid>
        <description>A revolutionary set of policies called the New Deal was enacted by Franklin Roosevelt, in response to the Great Depression. The policies were incredibly successful in providing economic relief and financial reform through public work projects, laying the foundation for the upcoming era of Democratic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Move Out Day Concerns Addressed by College</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-move-out-day-concerns-addressed-by-college/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-move-out-day-concerns-addressed-by-college/</guid>
        <description>Concerns have been raised by students about the Move Out Day for first year hall residents. In previous years, Move Out Day has always fallen on the last Saturday of term (which would be 29th June), but this year it has been pushed up to Thursday 27th June.
This will not affect the schedules of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>500 Women Scientists</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-500-women-scientists/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-500-women-scientists/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday, 27th February, Dr. Kelly Ramirez visited Imperial College London to give a talk on “Transforming scientific institutions through crowdsourcing and gritty determination”. The theme of the discussion was “empowering women scientists through public engagement and advocation”.
In late …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Anti-Vax movement</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-the-anti-vax-movement/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-the-anti-vax-movement/</guid>
        <description>Ethan Lindenberger is an American high-school senior who, on Tuesday, testified before the US Senate Committee on Health, Education, Labor and Pensions. He got himself vaccinated after asking on Reddit how to do so against the wishes of his anti-vax mother.
In his testimony, he attributed his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LSE Festival – An Exhibition of Policy and Social Science Research</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-lse-festival-an-exhibition-of-policy-and-social-science-research/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-lse-festival-an-exhibition-of-policy-and-social-science-research/</guid>
        <description>The LSE Festival, running from 25 February to 2 March, is a week-long series of events aimed at engaging the public with social science hot topics. This year’s theme is New World (Dis)Orders and focuses on the changing global situation: a new emergent world order where the US is no longer the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lauren Dennis to be honoured at We Innovate Final</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-01-lauren-dennis-to-be-honoured-at-we-innovate-final/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-01-lauren-dennis-to-be-honoured-at-we-innovate-final/</guid>
        <description>The WE Innovate program, a part of the Imperial Enterprise Lab, will be hosting its Final Showcase next Thursday, March 7th, from 18.20 – 21.00 in the City &amp;amp; Guilds Building. WE Innovate is Imperial’s flagship female entrepreneurship education program and, since its inception, 253 women have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Meet the Candidates!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-01-meet-the-candidates/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-01-meet-the-candidates/</guid>
        <description>Whenever you have bought food or drinks on campus, attended any society or sports club, or just used any non-College facility in the last year, you have engaged with the Union.
Imperial College Union is the organisation that aims to represent the views and interests of all Imperial College students, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College settles bursary saga</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-college-settles-bursary-saga/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-college-settles-bursary-saga/</guid>
        <description>The 2015-2016 cohort bursary scheme saga is coming to a patchy end, with affected students having been contacted on Monday 18th February about new available opportunities being funded.
The affected students were notified of the opportunities that they would be eligible for, funded by the £250,000 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Future Developments to the South Kensington Campus</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-future-developments-to-the-south-kensington-campus/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-future-developments-to-the-south-kensington-campus/</guid>
        <description>The South Kensington Campus has a rich history. The campus today, founded mid-19th Century, has buildings with diverse origins – the Queen’s Tower built during Victorian times; the Royal School of Mines built in the Edwardian era; constructions in the 1950s that nearly doubled the size of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College Chemistry students to be offered cooking classes next autumn</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-imperial-college-chemistry-students-to-be-offered-cooking-classes-next-autumn/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-imperial-college-chemistry-students-to-be-offered-cooking-classes-next-autumn/</guid>
        <description>Whether or not you are a chemist, you definitely have some experience with reacting chemicals – in the kitchen. On a molecular level, cooking is simply chemistry. The Imperial College London Department of Chemistry agrees, and will be advancing this notion by introducing a new module: “Introduction …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>DramaSoc presents: And Then There Were None</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-11-dramasoc-presents-and-then-there-were-none/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-11-dramasoc-presents-and-then-there-were-none/</guid>
        <description>If you were hoping for a warm evening in at the theatre, in refuge from the cold London night, you may have found that DramaSoc’s performance of And Then There Were None was not the hearty bonfire you expected – but for the best possible reasons. The murder mystery based on Agatha Christie’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Central Library re-opens Group Study Space</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-central-library-re-opens-group-study-space/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-central-library-re-opens-group-study-space/</guid>
        <description>The Group Study Area on the first floor of Central Library has reopened after refurbishment began in mid-October. Over the past month, the Group Study space has been re-carpeted, furniture has been installed, and power has been brought to all desks.
The refurbishments is the latest stage in Central …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An ‘exploding’ political atmosphere</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-an-exploding-political-atmosphere/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-an-exploding-political-atmosphere/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday 24th October, news broke of suspicious packages containing explosives mailed to former President Barack Obama and former Secretary of State Hillary Clinton. Similar packages were quickly discovered, addressed to:
George Soros: billionaire investor and Democratic mega-donor
John Brennan: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College Business School launches first live hologram lectures</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-imperial-college-business-school-launches-first-live-hologram-lectures/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-imperial-college-business-school-launches-first-live-hologram-lectures/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Business School has become the first institution in the world to use live holograms as part of its lectures.
The technology was unveiled during a “Women in Tech: The Inside Story” event. In a panel featuring four speakers, two were present on stage and two appeared as holograms from …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
