<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/gta/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/gta/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The best and the worst of GTA-ing
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-the-best-and-the-worst-of-gta-ing/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 14:42:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>The GTA,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-the-best-and-the-worst-of-gta-ing/</guid>
        <description> Almost every memorable moment as a GTA (Graduate Teaching Assistant) is both wonderful and terrible. Some are so bad that they’re good in retrospect (though some are just bad), and sometimes being a GTA makes you so happy that you can’t help but love your job. It’s been a rollercoaster first year …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Confessions of a GTA: Part 17
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-12-confessions-of-a-gta-part-17/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 16:44:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>The GTA,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-12-confessions-of-a-gta-part-17/</guid>
        <description>I expected to enjoy invigilating undergraduate exams, and to be honest, I did. There is something very satisfying about getting paid to watch other people going through the hell you have lived for three years. One thing I did notice there is a specific pattern to every exam. From a GTA perspective …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Confessions of a GTA: Part 15
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-16-confessions-of-a-gta-part-15/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 01:58:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>The GTA,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-16-confessions-of-a-gta-part-15/</guid>
        <description>GTAs can be pretty cool people: we’re trying to save the world with the power of our minds, we know an awful lot of answers to tutorial questions, and we drink quite a lot. We also quite like to know the undergrads, as they drink a lot too and they seem to like it when we try to help them with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Confessions of a GTA: Part 14
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-confessions-of-a-gta-part-14/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 01:02:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>The GTA,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-confessions-of-a-gta-part-14/</guid>
        <description>In the early days of my GTAing I thought it strange that all the other GTAs became twitchy when there was a quiet tutorial. I mean what is better than getting paid a decent wage just to stand there, literally sometimes for hours. Some of the longer labs can be up to three, not a bad little break …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Confessions of a GTA: Part 13
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-28-confessions-of-a-gta-part-13/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 07:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>The GTA,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-28-confessions-of-a-gta-part-13/</guid>
        <description>In GTA work, a lot depends on trust from your student. Sometimes this simply depends on perceived authority, i.e. you are older and wrinklier than them and you’ve been introduced by their lecturer, therefore you must know something, right? The nicest times are when it depends on a relationship built …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Confessions of a GTA: Part 11
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-confessions-of-a-gta-part-11/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 03:27:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>The GTA,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-confessions-of-a-gta-part-11/</guid>
        <description>Presenting as an undergraduate was always horrific. A lot of it had to do with that we (were all given the same project. Having to sit through at least 10 presentations on exactly the same thing, whilst noticing everything the other groups had done better, was not only boring but galling all at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Confessions of a GTA: Part 11
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-17-confessions-of-a-gta-part-11/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 17:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>The GTA,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-17-confessions-of-a-gta-part-11/</guid>
        <description>As one of the more strapped for cash GTAs I teach a lot of classes in my department. This includes some outside my speciality meaning I have taught pretty much every year of the undergraduates and as detailed last week, some of the MScs. This is great as I have a broad spectrum of topics and an even …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Confessions of a GTA: Part 10
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-confessions-of-a-gta-part-10/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>The GTA,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-confessions-of-a-gta-part-10/</guid>
        <description>For most of my time as a GTA here, I have stuck very securely to the undergrads. These are people I may not always like but at least I know where they are coming from. I have been there. I have experienced the peaks and troughs (or more likely deep underwater trenches) of undergrad life. With the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Confessions of a GTA: Part 9
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-confessions-of-a-gta-part-9/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 17:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>The GTA,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-confessions-of-a-gta-part-9/</guid>
        <description>This week’s confession is pretty bad. Most of the time I enjoy GTAing. The students are nice and unusually polite, but in every class there are always students you try to avoid. These have been getting more frequent and must stop for our sanity. So here are a few you might recognise:
The Safety …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Confessions of a GTA: Part 8
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-confessions-of-a-gta-part-8/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 09:54:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>The GTA,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-confessions-of-a-gta-part-8/</guid>
        <description>Lecturers as a profession are very hard to say no to. In general they control your life from the moment you enter college. They set coursework and will demand you spend time on it, even when it is worth 0.1% of your grade. They will set field trips or labs at times that completely don’t work for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Confessions of a GTA: Part Seven
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-confessions-of-a-gta-part-seven/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 03:33:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>The GTA,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-confessions-of-a-gta-part-seven/</guid>
        <description>Awkward moments in a GTA’s life come pretty thick and fast. I had hoped to start a new term off well, but 3 months of GTA experience had taught me better. I have several times marked something as completely wrong only to realise five minutes later it is a perfect solution and had to cross out all my …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Christmas Confessions of a GTA
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-christmas-confessions-of-a-gta/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 04:04:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>The GTA,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-christmas-confessions-of-a-gta/</guid>
        <description>Christmas at Imperial as an undergrad quite literally sucks. All I can remember was all my friends from alternative universities having a fantastic time with mulled wine, carols, slightly questionable decisions at the Christmas dinners, and retiring home to make snowmen with all their lovely family. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Confessions of a GTA: Part 6
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-confessions-of-a-gta-part-6/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 16:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>The GTA,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-confessions-of-a-gta-part-6/</guid>
        <description>As an undergraduate, if you had asked me what the worst thing was about Imperial it was obvious: The exams. After working all those hours to be hit with the striking realisation that I did not, in fact, understand the topic even a little bit caused me to doubt many a life decision. I also came to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Confessions of a GTA: Part 5
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-confessions-of-a-gta-part-5/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 02:28:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>The GTA,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-confessions-of-a-gta-part-5/</guid>
        <description>Week 6 in a GTA calendar is filled with the undergraduates’ horror of fifth week mid-term tests. I honestly never thought that marking papers could be worse than sitting them. I was certain that this would be the subject of my confession today. However, on Monday I was highly irritated, which I know …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Confessions of a GTA: Part 4
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-4-confessions-of-a-gta-part-4/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 11:03:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>The GTA,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-4-confessions-of-a-gta-part-4/</guid>
        <description>As an undergrad, field trips were always best in hindsight. Those hours on a windblown moor in the back of beyond in the pouring rain seemed later like quite a laugh and that time you nearly got impaled on machinery by an irate Scottish factory worker who did not care how interested you were in the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
