<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/cf107/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/cf107/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Fenimism with flair
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-18-fenimism-with-flair/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 08:28:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christina Flanagan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-18-fenimism-with-flair/</guid>
        <description>My first impressions on entering the Finborough Theatre, having climbed the stairs from the wine bar below, were dubious. The middle of the theatre was covered in earth, liberally strewn with potatoes, the room hummed with eerie folky music and for a good five minutes an actress in farmer’s garb …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Afghanistan’s magnificent heirlooms
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-afghanistans-magnificent-heirlooms/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 20:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christina Flanagan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-afghanistans-magnificent-heirlooms/</guid>
        <description>Afghanistan. What images are conjured up in your mind? The sad reality is that, for many of us, 3000 years of history has been eclipsed by 30 years of chaos. Fortunately the aim of the British Museum’s exhibition Afghanistan: Crossroads of the Ancient World is to remind us of the country’s crucial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Untethered
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-untethered/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 19:24:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christina Flanagan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-untethered/</guid>
        <description>The Untethered installation is the best use of the space in Imperial’s Blyth Gallery that I have seen since I started occasionally visiting four years ago. The normally minimalist gallery let go and featured a flock of origami birds surging out from one corner to finally disappear up into the spaces …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get hot at pole dancing class
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-11-get-hot-at-pole-dancing-class/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 06:43:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christina Flanagan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-11-get-hot-at-pole-dancing-class/</guid>
        <description>Apparently, Imperial is one of the few universities in the country not to already have a pole dancing society (I wonder why…). Even Cambridge University is better catered for! Given the growing interest in all forms of erotic dancing – the much hyped Burlesque the movie has recently been released – …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Enchanting glass memories
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-enchanting-glass-memories/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 20:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christina Flanagan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-enchanting-glass-memories/</guid>
        <description>The Glass Menagerie enfolds us in the memories of Tom, a young poet trapped by his dependent family, who both appears in each scene and narrates the play from his present. This is the play that made Tennessee Williams famous and aside from an occasionally dodgy Southern accent (Deborah Findlay as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s new about Cézanne?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-whats-new-about-czanne/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 18:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christina Flanagan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-whats-new-about-czanne/</guid>
        <description>Best known for his instantly recognisable still lifes, the Courtauld’s latest exhibition instead focuses on Cézanne’s depictions of people at play. His models were peasant farmers from his own estate, about whom the exhibition provides some intriguing snippets of information. They are pictured …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
