<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Julio_perez on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/julio_perez/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Julio_perez on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/julio_perez/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The End of a Decade: Spain</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-end-of-decade-spain/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-end-of-decade-spain/</guid>
        <description>The last decade has been a period of historical changes in Spain that have transformed its political culture and society forever. This historical phase is parallel to the European economic crisis and its aftermath, which were particularly intense in Southern European countries like Spain. Arguably, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flag Patriotism: Vox in the November elections and the Rise of the Far Right in Spain</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-flag-patriotism-vox-november-elections-rise-far-right-spain/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-flag-patriotism-vox-november-elections-rise-far-right-spain/</guid>
        <description>Some political scientists argue that the far right comes in “waves”, and that Europe is currently being swept up by one of them. Most European countries have witnessed the rise (and sometimes fall) of parties representing this radical mindset in the last century; but Spain has been an exception, or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>EUphoria and the EU’s Role in the People’s Vote</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-euphoria-and-eu-role-in-peoples-vote/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-euphoria-and-eu-role-in-peoples-vote/</guid>
        <description>Brexit has been the main object of political attention for the past year, dividing UK’s population in half: pro-Brexit and pro-EU. The latter is interclass, constituted by voters mainly ranging from centre to left from all ages. In 2018, a pro-EU campaign group aiming to hold another referendum was …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
