<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sh1207/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sh1207/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Armchair Techno
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-armchair-techno/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 00:31:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Hunter,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-armchair-techno/</guid>
        <description>For a guy who has had such a spectacular rise to musical prominence, Nicolas Jaar’s choice of the Barbican as the venue for a one off gig last weekend should perhaps not be too surprising. In many ways the concert hall is perfectly suited to Jaar’s delicate, jazz-infused melodies and masterful …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Punky Reggae Party
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-a-punky-reggae-party/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 02:05:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Hunter,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-a-punky-reggae-party/</guid>
        <description>On Monday night I spent the evening in the Millennium Dome and came to the conclusion that it should be levelled. It may no longer be called the Millennium Dome and it may now have an array of soulless bars/restaurants, but the fact remains: it’s a large tent with the character to match.
This was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Long Live the Radio Star
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-long-live-the-radio-star/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 22:47:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Hunter,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-long-live-the-radio-star/</guid>
        <description>http://rinse.fm/At the end of last year I tried to put together a mixtape containing my favourite tunes of 2012. But I couldn’t do it. My iTunes library just didn’t do 2012 justice, and this got me wondering why that was. It’s not that I’ve gone ‘cold’ on new music; I’m probably listening to more …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Return of The Duke
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-return-of-the-duke/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 22:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Hunter,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-return-of-the-duke/</guid>
        <description>This week, just as all the music journo’s had finished having their “what to look forward to in 2013” articles published, a fuck-off metaphorical anvil fell from the clouds and smashed them to pieces; all of them made irrelevant. No-one expected David Bowie to return with new material; his last …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Soul hero Terry Callier passes on
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-soul-hero-terry-callier-passes-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 14:06:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Hunter,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-soul-hero-terry-callier-passes-on/</guid>
        <description>Two weeks ago Terry Callier’s name was added to the ever increasing list of great soul artists who are no longer with us. Callier, born in 1940’s Chicago released his first record in 1968 to little commercial success. This was followed, in the first half of the 70’s, with two more albums, including …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gonzales at the Barbican
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-gonzales-at-the-barbican/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 23:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Hunter,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-gonzales-at-the-barbican/</guid>
        <description>In the full flow of a performance Chilly Gonzales is a sight to behold. Dressed in a black satin dressing gown and wasabi green slippers his unkempt, sweaty hair hangs across his face as he hammers the keys of a beautiful Steinway. This is a man who loves to let his wild imagination gallop and two …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hot Chip are hot
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-hot-chip-are-hot/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 03:12:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Hunter,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-hot-chip-are-hot/</guid>
        <description>I’ve never really understood where Hot Chip fit in. Having shot to musical prominence during the years of ‘nu-rave’ (terrible clothes, a lot of dick heads but hell, the music was fun), the band mix catchy pop riffs and delicate vocals with synths that time and again slay the dancefloor. This …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Diggidy Dawg! Felix Music Night
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-22-diggidy-dawg-felix-music-night/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 16:21:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Hunter,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-22-diggidy-dawg-felix-music-night/</guid>
        <description>Last Saturday saw the return of Felix Music Night for their final party of the year and boy, was it a party. Things were kicked off with an uplifting jazz &amp;amp; bass set from Phrij. Accompanying his selection, Gabor Kerekes shone the hypnotic motion of oils, colours and washing up liquid swirling …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Techno Nonsense: Hyperdub
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-techno-nonsense-hyperdub/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 21:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Hunter,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-techno-nonsense-hyperdub/</guid>
        <description>Regular readers of my column probably need little introduction to the label that I concern myself with this week. Hyperdub has, with not a hint of exaggeration, been the most influential electronic music label to have come out of London in a long, long time. Why then, you may ask, has it taken me so …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reviewed in 60 Seconds
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-reviewed-in-60-seconds/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 21:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Hunter,Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,Alexandra Ramadan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-reviewed-in-60-seconds/</guid>
        <description>David Bowie - The Rise And Fall of Ziggy Stardust and the Spiders from Mars
Having been released 40 years ago, this review is probably a bit late. For those of you who are less than familiar with the work of David Bowie this album is a great place to start.
_The Rise and Fall of Ziggy Stardust and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Blacks Keys rock a heart at the Ally Pally
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-blacks-keys-rock-a-heart-at-the-ally-pally/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 21:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Hunter,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-blacks-keys-rock-a-heart-at-the-ally-pally/</guid>
        <description>Like most people who spent the better half of their teenage years during the mid-noughties, my music tastes were fairly rigidly constrained to the world of indie rock. My iTunes library was full of guitar bands and the ideal school night involved necking a few tins, getting on the train and sweating …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Techno Nonsense: Stones Throw
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-techno-nonsense-stones-throw/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 11:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Hunter,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-techno-nonsense-stones-throw/</guid>
        <description>I started this column last year but any recent input has been massively lacking. The feature started off highlighting electronic music labels that were either doing big things at that time or labels that should just be known due to their impact on music. I suppose this one falls into both …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Camping in an Old Street basement
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-camping-in-an-old-street-basement/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 21:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Hunter,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-camping-in-an-old-street-basement/</guid>
        <description>As acronyms go, the one belonging to the _City Arts &amp;amp; Music Project _is a bit awkward. The same goes for the name of its nightclub: CAMP Basement.
A small club just off Old Street roundabout and unlike a lot of its neighbouring establishments, there’s nothing pretentious about this place; in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Techno Nonsense: Boiler Room
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-techno-nonsense-boiler-room/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 20:56:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Hunter,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-techno-nonsense-boiler-room/</guid>
        <description>For those of you paying any attention to the underground dance music scene here in London, there has been one true star to emerge over the past year, and that is the Boiler Room; yet describing it isn’t easy. It’s not a club night because to get in you need an invite and it’s usually all over by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Interview with Chilly Gonzales
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-interview-with-chilly-gonzales/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 21:29:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Hunter,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-interview-with-chilly-gonzales/</guid>
        <description>Last month I was able to have a chat with musician, comedian and all-round entertainer Chilly Gonzales. Currently jetting around the world promoting his latest foray into film-making and putting the finishing touches to a new album, I caught him in the airport waiting for a flight. The latest string …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Techno Nonsense: Ramp Recordings
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-techno-nonsense-ramp-recordings/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 20:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Hunter,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-techno-nonsense-ramp-recordings/</guid>
        <description>The underground dance music scene in the UK is the healthiest it has been for a number of years. London is, as ever, a melting pot for musicians from a myriad of backgrounds who push the boundaries of what becomes many peoples’ 4am soundtrack. It is in testament to this that I devote a second label …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Techno Nonsense: Turbo Records
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-techno-nonsense-turbo-records/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2010 20:45:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Hunter,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-techno-nonsense-turbo-records/</guid>
        <description>As you’ve probably gathered by now I enjoy contrast. Traversing the musical spectrum from disco Permanent Vacation style, to Night Slugs’ grimiest bass music in the space of a fortnight has set my stall out nicely I think. This week I introduce to you: Turbo Recordings.
Unlike new boys on the scene …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Techno Nonsense: Night Slugs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-techno-nonsense-night-slugs/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 21:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Hunter,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-techno-nonsense-night-slugs/</guid>
        <description>In this, my second installment of Techno Nonsense, a feature dedicated to highlighting the big players in electronic dance music right now, I’m going to hit you with Night Slugs.
Traversing the entire length of the musical spectrum from last week’s Disco feature, Night Slugs is one of the hottest …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Techno Nonsense: Permanent Vacation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-techno-nonsense-permanent-vacation/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 19:36:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Hunter,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-techno-nonsense-permanent-vacation/</guid>
        <description>Over the coming issues of Felix I will embark on a quest to dispel the popular belief that electronic dance music begins with Tiesto and finishes with David Guetta. I will try and dip into as many genres as possible; highlighting what’s big at the moment, what was big 20 years ago and just generally …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
