<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/scc114/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/scc114/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Wolf of Wall Street - An Attempt at High-octane Fun Burns out Quickly</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-wolf-wall-street/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-wolf-wall-street/</guid>
        <description>2 stars
The Wolf of Wall Street is the latest immersive offering from director Alexander Wright, based on the 2013 film about unscrupulous stockbroker Jordan Belfort. The premise is that we - the audience - are all new employees at Belfort&amp;rsquo;s cash-swindling firm Stratton Oakmont. Right from the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Harry Potter in Concert: A Magical Musical Evening</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-harry-potter-concert-magical-musical-evening/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-harry-potter-concert-magical-musical-evening/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
Imagine your favourite movie – any movie. Now, imagine it again without the music and its iconic soundtrack: it would simply not be the same. Music is a huge part of creating a film’s atmosphere, creating the right ambience and enhancing the emotional tug of the moment. And what better way …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Mikado - Stylish Set, Passé Plot</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-mikado-stylish-set-passe-plot/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-mikado-stylish-set-passe-plot/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
The Mikado is perhaps the most well-known of Gilbert and Sullivan’s Victorian-era comic operas, famously set in Japan. Why Japan, one might wonder? Back in 1885, it was all about keeping political satire hidden in plain sight. By setting their scenes in fantastical or wildly foreign …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Red Palace</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-red-palace/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-red-palace/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
A masked ball at the Prince’s Palace, for the thousandth day of his reign. There’s a rumour going around that the Prince will be dead by morning. We are left to wander through the palace’s rooms, tasked with finding out just what is going on.
Such is the premise of Shotgun Carousel’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Up Pompeii - An Audio Revival</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-up-pompeii-audio-revival/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-up-pompeii-audio-revival/</guid>
        <description>3 stars
One quick look around the audience and I soon realise my companion and I are easily the youngest in the room. I’m also the only non-white person there (unless we’re counting the ushers). We’re at a live radio recording of Up Pompeii, that BBC comedy classic about a ne’er-do-well slave in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Arts Editor Intro: Claire - The Culture Vulture</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-arts-editor-intro-claire-culture-vulture/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-arts-editor-intro-claire-culture-vulture/</guid>
        <description>This is my second year as Arts section editor. It’s a role that never gets boring – London really is one of the best cities in the world for culture. It’s a wonderful mix of things old and new. Van Gogh and Warhol. Russian classical ballet and Merce Cunningham’s contemporary choreography. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don Giovanni</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-don-giovanni/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-don-giovanni/</guid>
        <description>Kasper Holten&amp;rsquo;s tech-heavy Don Giovanni has been trotted out on the ROH stage for the third time. The eye-catching set is unquestionably the most remarkable thing about this production. Unfortunately, it detracts from, rather than adds to, the performance, leaving one wondering where Holten’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Whisk Desserts: A delightfully decadent all-dessert pop-up in Angel</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-whisk-desserts-a-delightfully-decadent-all-dessert-pop-up-in-angel/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-whisk-desserts-a-delightfully-decadent-all-dessert-pop-up-in-angel/</guid>
        <description>As term ends (at last!) and summer makes its approach, we can all take a well-deserved break from the daily grind of revision and exams. Holidays abroad, lazing around in the sun, ice cream in the park - what could be better? On your list of indolent summer indulgence should definitely be Whisk …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stanley Kubrick: The Exhibition</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-26-stanley-kubrick-the-exhibition/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-26-stanley-kubrick-the-exhibition/</guid>
        <description>What an opening. As the dramatic music of Also Sprach Zarathustra thunders in the background, the psychedelic hexagonal carpet from The Shining rolls underfoot. We enter a bright corridor of screens, Stanley Kubrick’s most iconic scenes flashing by as we get closer and closer to the main screen …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London Coffee Festival 2019 | Enter caffeinated heaven</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-london-coffee-festival-2019-enter-caffeinated-heaven/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,Elizabeth Thong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-london-coffee-festival-2019-enter-caffeinated-heaven/</guid>
        <description>For any hectic Londoner, and especially the sleep-deprived Imperial student, coffee is a staple - if not a necessity - of daily existence. Now in its 9th year running, the London Coffee Festival is a massive celebration of everyone&amp;rsquo;s favourite stimulant. And when I say massive, I mean massive. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Picture of Dorian Gray</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-the-picture-of-dorian-gray/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-the-picture-of-dorian-gray/</guid>
        <description>The Picture of Dorian Gray is one of Oscar Wilde’s best-known works, and certainly the most controversial. Published in 1890, it immediately attracted criticism for the hedonism and immorality promulgated in its pages, with Wilde accused of ‘offending public morals’. The story is of Dorian Gray, a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gary Nicholls: The Imaginarium</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-14-gary-nicholls-the-imaginarium/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-14-gary-nicholls-the-imaginarium/</guid>
        <description>Corsets and cogwheels, leather and lace: what would the Victorian era have looked like if electricity hadn’t been discovered and steam technology had prevailed? Throw in a little fantasy, a little science fiction, and you have the steampunk movement – a weirdly intriguing combination of Victorian …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Eva von Schnippisch won WWII</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-14-how-eva-von-schnippisch-won-wwii/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-14-how-eva-von-schnippisch-won-wwii/</guid>
        <description>Who is Eva von Schnippisch and what does she have to do with WWII? You might be forgiven for wondering if you’d fallen asleep one too many times in history class, but Stephanie Ware’s one-woman cabaret has very, very little to do with the actual affairs of WWII at all.
It’s an unashamedly salacious, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is it #TimesUp for #MeToo?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-01-is-it-timesup-for-metoo/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-01-is-it-timesup-for-metoo/</guid>
        <description>It’s fair to say that the #MeToo movement has been the most significant social upheaval of recent times. Triggered by the much-publicised downfall of Harvey Weinstein, the tremendous outpouring of stories of both sexual assault and everyday sexism faced by women on a regular basis became a force too …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Justice Syndicate</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-the-justice-syndicate/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-the-justice-syndicate/</guid>
        <description>In The Justice Syndicate, an interactive 12-person game created by theatre company fanSHEN, we’re on a jury deciding the fate of a top paediatric neurosurgeon who’s been accused of sexual assault by the mother of one of his patients. It’s almost like 12 Angry Men when we walk in: twelve desks …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Surreal and beautiful: The Good Person of Szechwan</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-13-surreal-and-beautiful-the-good-person-of-szechwan/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-13-surreal-and-beautiful-the-good-person-of-szechwan/</guid>
        <description>How can a good person survive in a world which is intrinsically evil? This is the question Bertolt Brecht poses to us in his play The Good Person of Szechwan. Set in Sichuan, it tells the story of how the gods reward a poor prostitute Shen Te, ‘the only good person in the city’, with enough money to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dior: Designer of Dreams</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-11-dior-designer-of-dreams/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-11-dior-designer-of-dreams/</guid>
        <description>‘In the world today, haute couture is one of the last repositories of the marvellous,’ said Christian Dior in 1957. The dresses of the House of Dior combine fantasy and futurism – the exoticism of far-flung countries, the allure of delicate flowers, and the old-world grandeur of eras long past. It …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Witness for the Prosecution</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-03-witness-at-the-prosecution/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-03-witness-at-the-prosecution/</guid>
        <description>Who doesn’t remember reading Agatha Christie’s books as a child? Murder mysteries, full of suspense and intrigue, invariably with an unexpected twist or surprising revelation in the dénouement. Her enduring popularity has seen a plethora of film, stage and West End adaptations of her stories, such …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Manon: A triumph of expressiveness in ballet</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-manon-a-triumph-of-expressiveness-in-ballet/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-manon-a-triumph-of-expressiveness-in-ballet/</guid>
        <description>What a brilliant night. Being quite a novice to the ballet world, English National Ballet’s production of Manon was my first introduction to two of its stars – the choreographer Sir Kenneth Macmillan and the ballerina Alina Cojocaru. It was ballet like I’d never seen it before, and it was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Queen of Spades: ROH disappoints</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-the-queen-of-spades-roh-disappoints/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-the-queen-of-spades-roh-disappoints/</guid>
        <description>It’s been a long while since I’ve found an opera more enjoyable with my eyes shut than open. But with a director who says things like ‘Opera is not about giving people a good time,’ perhaps I shouldn’t have been surprised. Stefan Herheim’s gamble with Tchaikovsky’s The Queen of Spades tries too hard …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pinter Six: Money can’t buy you love</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-pinter-six-money-can-t-buy-you-love/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-pinter-six-money-can-t-buy-you-love/</guid>
        <description>Now past the halfway mark, Jamie Lloyd’s season of Pinter plays continues to astonish with each new installment. What’s impressive is the curation – the plays are grouped by subject matter, rather than chronology, showcasing the themes that Pinter revisited multiple times throughout his career as a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>La Bohème | One of opera’s great classics</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-la-boh-me-one-of-opera-s-great-classics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,Helen Money-Kyrle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-la-boh-me-one-of-opera-s-great-classics/</guid>
        <description>The romanticised notion of the struggling artist – impoverished but ingenious, penniless but praiseworthy – was a big hit with the public when La Bohème first premiered in 1896. As a uni student living on a budget, the plight of Rodolfo (Jonathan Tetelman), Marcello (Nicholas Lester), Colline (David …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NYT Rep’s Macbeth</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-nyt-rep-s-macbeth/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-nyt-rep-s-macbeth/</guid>
        <description>Having had a chat with both Macbeth (Olivia Dowd) and Lady Macbeth (Isabel Adomakoh Young) a fortnight prior, I was particularly excited to see them on stage for the National Youth Theatre’s production of Macbeth. Moira Buffini’s abridged version results in a snappy, intense play which runs straight …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pinter Three: Love and longing</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-pinter-three-love-and-longing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-pinter-three-love-and-longing/</guid>
        <description>One way of looking at speech is to say that it is a constant stratagem to cover nakedness.” This statement by Harold Pinter sums up excellently the motif that is characteristic of his work, and which makes his plays so powerful. In them, what is said is but a flimsy covering for the things that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imagined Touch</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-imagined-touch/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-imagined-touch/</guid>
        <description>Imagine losing your sense of sight. Then imagine losing your sense of hearing too. What is it like to inhabit a world of silence and darkness? In their immersive performance piece Imagined Touch, deafblind artists Heather Lawson and Michelle Stevens seek to open up to audiences their world – a world …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>National Youth Theatre’s genderfluid Macbeth: Interview with the star couple</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-national-youth-theatre-s-genderfluid-macbeth-interview-with-the-star-couple/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-national-youth-theatre-s-genderfluid-macbeth-interview-with-the-star-couple/</guid>
        <description>The National Youth Theatre Rep company is finishing up an exciting performance season with their new, genderfluid version of Macbeth. Abridged by Moira Buffini and directed by Natasha Nixon, it certainly is an intriguing premise! I had the opportunity to sit down with Olivia and Isabel and find out …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Monkey King and The Crossroads Inn</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-the-monkey-king-and-the-crossroads-inn/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-the-monkey-king-and-the-crossroads-inn/</guid>
        <description>The Crossroads Inn, a classic of Peking opera, begins with Jiao Zan, an unjustly exiled general, being led onstage in handcuffs by two soldiers. By the end of the scene the handcuffs are on one of the soldiers and Jiao Zan (played by Liu Kuikui) is bossing the other around - the audience is in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>William Carlos Williams: poet, doctor, writer</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-william-carlos-williams-poet-doctor-writer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-william-carlos-williams-poet-doctor-writer/</guid>
        <description>Family doctor, poet, novelist, playwright and occasional translator – William Carlos Williams wore many hats in his life as both a man of medicine and a man of letters. There seems to be a strange compulsion amongst doctors to write, as though their creative energies need some outlet which medicine …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Wider Earth: a magical voyage of scientific discovery</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-the-wider-earth-a-magical-voyage-of-scientific-discovery/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-the-wider-earth-a-magical-voyage-of-scientific-discovery/</guid>
        <description>Two years old, fresh out of uni and off on a five-year journey circumnavigating the world. That’s the story of Charles Darwin and his historic odyssey on the HMS Beagle – a fantastic tale that receives an enthralling dramatisation in The Wider Earth.
The Wider Earth takes us back to an age of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Definitive Guide to Autumn in the Capital</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-the-definitive-guide-to-autumn-in-the-capital/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Helen Money-Kyrle,Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-the-definitive-guide-to-autumn-in-the-capital/</guid>
        <description>Now until 7 October 2018
Frieze London and Frieze Masters art fairs in Regents Park.
Now until 13 October 2018
The Globe is still running open air performances; with £5 standing tickets it’s not to be missed!
Now until December 2018
Caledonian Express at the Pleasance – the best shows of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BBC Proms</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-bbc-proms/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-bbc-proms/</guid>
        <description>The Proms concerts are an annual tradition dating back to the late 1800s, when open-air ‘promenade concerts’ had become popular in London’s pleasure gardens. Rather than sitting stiffly down to listen to music, concertgoers would stroll, or promenade, through the gardens while enjoying fresh air and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imagine Moscow | A melancholy reminder of what could have been
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-23-imagine-moscow-a-melancholy-reminder-of-what-could-have-been/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 16:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-23-imagine-moscow-a-melancholy-reminder-of-what-could-have-been/</guid>
        <description>With Imagine Moscow, the newly-opened Design Museum makes its contribution to the range of events marking the centennial of Russia’s October Revolution. The concept is certainly an interesting one: Imagine Moscow focuses on six architectural landmarks around Moscow’s Red Square, conceptualised in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Partenope | A brilliantly off-piste version of a little-performed classic
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-22-partenope-a-brilliantly-off-piste-version-of-a-little-performed-classic/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 17:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-22-partenope-a-brilliantly-off-piste-version-of-a-little-performed-classic/</guid>
        <description>Can 18th century humour still be relevant today? This is the question the ENO are attempting to answer, with the first reprisal of Christopher Alden’s production of Partenope. First performed in 1730, Partenope is an opera not often found on the operatic stage today. Opera in the early 18th century …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Julie Cunningham | Dance as Performance Art
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-12-julie-cunningham-dance-as-performance-art/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 21:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-12-julie-cunningham-dance-as-performance-art/</guid>
        <description>Julie Cunningham | Dance as performance art
3.5 out of 5 stars
“Classical dance is about confirmation, while contemporary dance is about exploration.” Classical ballets are drawn from well-known tales; the characters fall into easily recognisable roles – the princess, the knight-errant, the evil …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Danza Contemporánea de Cuba | Electrifying dance with a Cuban flavour
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-danza-contempornea-de-cuba-electrifying-dance-with-a-cuban-flavour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 15:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-danza-contempornea-de-cuba-electrifying-dance-with-a-cuban-flavour/</guid>
        <description>Cuba’s premier dance company stopped by London for one night last week during their whirlwind tour of the UK. Founded in 1959, Danza Contemporánea de Cuba has had over half a century to develop its distinct aesthetic – contemporary dance and classical ballet, with Spanish and Afro-Caribbean …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Blanca Li&#39;s Robot | A confusing hodgepodge of man and machine
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-blanca-lis-robot-a-confusing-hodgepodge-of-man-and-machine/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 17:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-blanca-lis-robot-a-confusing-hodgepodge-of-man-and-machine/</guid>
        <description>There is little doubt that technology has pervaded every inch of our modern lives. From people plugged in on their daily commutes, to the seas of smartphones at concerts, we seem to be constantly immersed in gadgetry. But is that a good or bad thing? This question has become something of a hot topic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC Dance slays at Southern Universities
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-ic-dance-slays-at-southern-universities/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 16:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-ic-dance-slays-at-southern-universities/</guid>
        <description>Dancing is a sport? Of course! After months of intense training, IC Dance’s Ballroom and Latin Dancesport teams travelled to Cardiff last weekend for a clash of the southern universities. This is one of the most eagerly anticipated competitions of the year, a crucial step before the UK-wide …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Revolution: Russian Art 1917 – 1932 | A terrible festival of dead leaves
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-revolution-russian-art-1917-1932-a-terrible-festival-of-dead-leaves/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-revolution-russian-art-1917-1932-a-terrible-festival-of-dead-leaves/</guid>
        <description>The Royal Academy’s ambitious new exhibition chronicles a troubled period in Russian history, from the overthrowing of the tsarist regime in 1917, through the years of civil war, to the consolidation of power by Stalin after death. In this window of time, art in Russia experienced a brief burgeoning …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>¡Caliente! Burning up the stage with Tango Fire
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-caliente-burning-up-the-stage-with-tango-fire/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 15:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-caliente-burning-up-the-stage-with-tango-fire/</guid>
        <description>Tango – the word alone conjures images of passion, seduction, and power play. German Cornejo and his sizzling dance crew return to London with Tango Fire to set the stage ablaze. The first part of the show harks back to tango’s roots in the milongas of Buenos Aires. Impossibly glamorous, the five …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reading Drawings
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-reading-drawings/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 15:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-reading-drawings/</guid>
        <description>    Courtauld Gallery   Marginalia are the annotations one finds scribbled in the margins of a text; they can be insightful, witty or rude depending on the commentator in question. Reading Drawings is a new collection at the Courtauld Gallery that aims to showcase the equivalent in drawings – …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rigoletto | Singers outshined by set
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-rigoletto-singers-outshined-by-set/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 15:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-rigoletto-singers-outshined-by-set/</guid>
        <description>It’s never a good sign when the set outshines the main cast. Unfortunately for the ENO’s latest rendition of Jonathan Miller’s superbly conceptualised Rigoletto, this is very much the case. Miller takes us back to 1950s New York City, in the shadier Mafia-dominated parts of Little Italy. It is a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>La Traviata
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-la-traviata/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 17:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-la-traviata/</guid>
        <description>An exhibition of harlotry upon the public stage!” denounced The Times when La Traviata was first staged in London in 1856. Although it is now the most frequently staged opera worldwide, La Traviata’s beginnings were plagued by stern censorship and moral outrage. That a common prostitute should be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ruth Wilson breathes new life into Hedda Gabler
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-ruth-wilson-breathes-new-life-into-hedda-gabler/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 15:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-ruth-wilson-breathes-new-life-into-hedda-gabler/</guid>
        <description>Unpredictable, beautiful, haughty, callous – Hedda Gabler is one of Ibsen’s best-known anti-heroines. Trapped in a life devoid of meaning, she desires freedom and power, but is unable to seize it for herself. She is stifled and unfulfilled; the people around her bore her, from her insipid husband …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Il trovatore | Melodrama and musical beauty
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-il-trovatore-melodrama-and-musical-beauty/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 15:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-il-trovatore-melodrama-and-musical-beauty/</guid>
        <description>Il trovatore is a classic opera by Verdi, one of the most regularly performed in the operatic repertoire today. It is the sort of opera that has fuelled the caricatures of the art form – it is confusing, extravagant, and filled with impassioned singing, known as much for its convoluted plotline as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hooked on Peter Pan
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-hooked-on-peter-pan/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 12:37:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-hooked-on-peter-pan/</guid>
        <description>The story of Peter Pan, popularised by Disney in 1953, hardly needs any introduction. However, not everyone knows of its darker history. J.M. Barrie first invented the character in 1902 in The Little White Bird, a semi-autobiographical story about a small boy who is befriended by a lonely London …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Manon Lescaut raises some questions
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-manon-lescaut-raises-some-questions/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 14:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-manon-lescaut-raises-some-questions/</guid>
        <description>Despite the pre-existing Manon by Jules Massenet, Puccini chose to write another opera based on the story of Manon Lescaut, defending his decision thus: “a woman like Manon can have more than one lover.” The sentiment is not untrue; by turns passionate, coquettish, and mercenary, Manon is a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is this even the right theatre? | Oreste disappoints
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-is-this-even-the-right-theatre-oreste-disappoints/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 15:11:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-is-this-even-the-right-theatre-oreste-disappoints/</guid>
        <description>As Oreste started, I thought for a fleeting moment that I was in the wrong place. Had I gotten lost among the twisting alleyways of East London? Why was a mascara-streaked, hammer-wielding teenage girl butchering a hapless prisoner on stage?
Then the orchestra struck up the opening chords, and I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cymbeline
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-14-cymbeline/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 14:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-14-cymbeline/</guid>
        <description>Cymbeline is one of Shakespeare’s lesser known plays. On reading it before going for the production at the Barbican, I could understand why. There is a tangle of plot lines: star-crossed lovers, kidnapped royal babes, attempted seduction, attempted assassination, and topping it all off, a war …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oneiric landscapes of strange enchantment
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-oneiric-landscapes-of-strange-enchantment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 14:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-oneiric-landscapes-of-strange-enchantment/</guid>
        <description>Paul Nash was an artist best known for two things: his portrayal of English landscapes, and his work as an official artist in both World Wars.
Nature and war - two seemingly irreconcilable themes, are portrayed by Nash in his own distinctive style. Born in Kensington, he spent his early years …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>International dance championships
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-international-dance-championships/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 22:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-international-dance-championships/</guid>
        <description>What is it about ballroom dancing that so enthrals us? The public’s fascination with ballroom dancing began years ago in Hollywood, with Fred Astaire and Ginger Rogers lighting up the silver screen. And as the wild success of TV programs like Strictly Come Dancing and Dancing With The Stars shows, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A not-so shabby shocker
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-10-a-not-so-shabby-shocker/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 14:40:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Felix Arts,Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-10-a-not-so-shabby-shocker/</guid>
        <description>Puccini’s Tosca is well-known for being a melodramatic opera. After its premiere in 1900, it received mixed reviews from critics despite its popularity with the public - the musicologist Joseph Kerman famously dismissed it as “a shabby little shocker”.
The plot centres on Cavaradossi, a painter who …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
