<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/aoz15/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/aoz15/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Epic battle sees 1st XV score bonus point win against BARTS</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-epic-battle-sees-1st-xv-score-bonus-point-win-against-barts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aleksei Zaboronsky,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-epic-battle-sees-1st-xv-score-bonus-point-win-against-barts/</guid>
        <description>Last Wednesday saw a vital match for Imperial 1st XV against fellow bottom-of-the-league dwellers BARTS. Still searching for our first win of the season at the end of November, this was a must-win occasion, and a loss would almost certainly subject us to relegation at the end of the season. An …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICRUFC: Stunning 2nd XV top League table</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-icrufc-stunning-2nd-xv-top-league-table/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aleksei Zaboronsky,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-icrufc-stunning-2nd-xv-top-league-table/</guid>
        <description>This week’s game was a big one, a clash between the top two teams in the league. We got onto the pitch and began the warm up with a sense of intensity and hunger. Everyone knew what was at stake. As UEL made their way out to warm up we did notice that a few of their players looked older than our …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brave 1st XV challenge ends in narrow loss against Brunel</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-brave-1st-xv-challenge-ends-in-narrow-loss-against-brunel/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aleksei Zaboronsky,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-brave-1st-xv-challenge-ends-in-narrow-loss-against-brunel/</guid>
        <description>Last Wednesday saw a grudge match for the first team against their old foe Brunel. After two close losses last season, the squad was in the mood for revenge. Kicking off at a delayed time of 15:00, the match started perfectly: a reclaimed kick off, followed by a barrelling run by resident …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>1st XV Rugby Woes Continue Against Surrey</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-1st-xv-rugby-woes-continue-against-surrey/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aleksei Zaboronsky,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-1st-xv-rugby-woes-continue-against-surrey/</guid>
        <description>Last week’s fixture against Surrey saw a determined Imperial 1st XV turn up in force, ready to put the previous week’s fixture against Reading behind them and get some points in the league table. A sharp, no-messing-about warm up reflected this mood, as did the start of the match; after kicking off, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Rugby kick off this year with trials and pints</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-imperial-rugby-kick-off-this-year-with-trials-and-pints/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aleksei Zaboronsky,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-imperial-rugby-kick-off-this-year-with-trials-and-pints/</guid>
        <description>Imperial rugby preseason kicked off on Monday 18th September, resulting in a rag-tag crew of motley looking seniors and fresh-faced freshers gathering at Ethos. Among the new faces were reliable fellas such as Amin, Michael, and Jacob, as well as a Lord Farquaad impersonator and a nervous young …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICURFC take on Movember
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-icurfc-take-on-movember/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 15:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aleksei Zaboronsky,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-icurfc-take-on-movember/</guid>
        <description>As rugby players we are all about stash. By this we usually mean rugby kit. However, this month the focus is on cultivating a different kind of ‘stache. A Movember one. “Classic, another group of people idly taking part in a fruitless activity whilst trying to justify it with the pretence of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Phaal from grace
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-a-phaal-from-grace/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 09:46:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aleksei Zaboronsky,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-a-phaal-from-grace/</guid>
        <description>Imperial travelled to Royal Holloway last Wednesday to start what they hoped would be a long cup run culminating in some silverware. Falling on Remembrance Day and being followed by the club curry night, there was a lot to play for to ensure that IC got back on track after an unmentionable loss to …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
