<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fashion on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/fashion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fashion on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/fashion/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Shoes: Pleasure and Pain
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-18-shoes-pleasure-and-pain/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2015 21:01:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecile Borkhataria,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-18-shoes-pleasure-and-pain/</guid>
        <description>The V&amp;amp;A’s latest fashion exhibition takes a look at the extremes of footwear from around the world, ranging from Cinderella’s glass slippers featured in the recent Disney live action movie, to tiny lotus shoes used to bind women’s feet in 19th century China. The exhibition focuses on the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Life on Foot’: Discovering Spanish shoe brand Camper
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-life-on-foot-discovering-spanish-shoe-brand-camper/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 12:54:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecile Borkhataria,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-life-on-foot-discovering-spanish-shoe-brand-camper/</guid>
        <description>After arriving at the Design Museum soaking wet from London’s pelting rain, I joined a group of journalists ready to be guided through the Museum’s latest exhibition entitled Life on Foot: Camper at the Design Museum. The exhibition marks the 40th anniversary of the Spanish footwear Brand Camper, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pioneers of Plus-Size
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-pioneers-of-plus-size/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 12:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-pioneers-of-plus-size/</guid>
        <description>Tess Munster, also known as Tess Holliday, has recently become the largest model ever to be signed to a major modelling agency, MiLK Model Management. Her size being a UK 22-24, and 5’5”, she describes herself as a “body-positive activist”, and is most well known for her #effyourbeautystandards …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Music’s biggest night: the best and worst outfits of the 2015 Grammy’s
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-musics-biggest-night-the-best-and-worst-outfits-of-the-2015-grammys/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 23:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecile Borkhataria,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-musics-biggest-night-the-best-and-worst-outfits-of-the-2015-grammys/</guid>
        <description>Beyoncé killed it in this all black Proenza Schouler dress at Sunday’s Grammy’s. She wore an equally beautiful white dress on stage whilst performing Take My Hand, Precious Lord, which featured in the popular movie Selma about the civil rights movement in the United States. Her performance was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chanel haute couture spring/summer 2015: the luxe rebirth of the beanie
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-chanel-haute-couture-springsummer-2015-the-luxe-rebirth-of-the-beanie/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 13:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecile Borkhataria,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-chanel-haute-couture-springsummer-2015-the-luxe-rebirth-of-the-beanie/</guid>
        <description>On Tuesday, Karl Lagerfeld pushed the boundaries of haute couture fashion yet again at the Chanel haute couture fashion show. The exclusive catwalk event was held at the Grand Palais in Paris, with attendees ranging from the likes of Hollywood starlets like Kristen Stewart, to French femme fatales …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Victoria’s Secret fashion show – landing on home turf
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-11-the-victorias-secret-fashion-show-landing-on-home-turf/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 21:33:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecile Borkhataria,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-11-the-victorias-secret-fashion-show-landing-on-home-turf/</guid>
        <description>Angel: Alessandra Ambrosio
The Fantasy Bra
This year, Alessandra Ambrosio and Adriana Lima had the honour of modeling a Fantasy Bra this year. Normally, only one angel wears a fantasy bra each year, but for this year’s show, two were made for the angels who have been modelling for Victoria’s Secret …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fashion Rules: regal fashion at Kensington Palace
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-fashion-rules-regal-fashion-at-kensington-palace/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 21:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-fashion-rules-regal-fashion-at-kensington-palace/</guid>
        <description>Almost every girl has dreamt of being a princess at some point in her life. Being able to live in a fairy-tale castle, enjoy the privileges and most of all, the dresses and beautiful outfits that come with it. Look at Cinderella; she got a dress from her fairy god mother and the next thing you know, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wedding Dresses: An Exhibition at the V&amp;A
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-wedding-dresses-an-exhibition-at-the-va/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 20:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecile Borkhataria,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-wedding-dresses-an-exhibition-at-the-va/</guid>
        <description>Today, brides of many faiths and nationalities wear white to celebrate their marriages, even in countres where it is not traditional to do so. The globalisation phenomenon and the influence and strength of the wedding industry have contributed to this homogenisation in wedding trends. The white …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Best Dressed Stars of the 2014 Met Gala: Beyond Fashion
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-the-best-dressed-stars-of-the-2014-met-gala-beyond-fashion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 15:03:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecile Borkhataria,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-the-best-dressed-stars-of-the-2014-met-gala-beyond-fashion/</guid>
        <description>On Monday night the most exclusive fashion event of the year took place in New York City, and its famous guests wowed us with their style.
This years Met Gala theme, Charles James: Beyond Fashion, gave guests the opportunity to dress over the top! From Lupita Nyong’o’s flapper girl Prada ensemble to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The cutest spring 2014 trends
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-the-cutest-spring-2014-trends/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 01:35:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecile Borkhataria,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-the-cutest-spring-2014-trends/</guid>
        <description>Spring is slowly starting to set in in London, and although we’re not feeling the mini-skirt wearing heat yet, these trends work for the transiton stage between winter and summer. On a cooler day, carry around a chunky knit sweater to ward off the occasional chills of the British spring time, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Autumn Week 13/14 highlights
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-autumn-week-1314-highlights/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 01:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Yang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-autumn-week-1314-highlights/</guid>
        <description>Dolce and Gabbana
This season’s golden collection goes to Milan Fashion Week’s Dolce and Gabbana as the pair turned to the traditional treasures of Italy for inspiration, concocting glittering mosaics and jewelled montages. Relaxed womanly shapes and dangling golden crosses, each saintly piece was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A luxurious death
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-a-luxurious-death/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 01:45:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Yang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-a-luxurious-death/</guid>
        <description>Common knowledge to anyone who actually wants to embark upon a career in the near future, the world economy is dragging its feet along the ground and practically all global growth has been brought to a grinding halt. The unfortunate result from all of this, besides the lack of money each and every …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tim Walker: Story Teller
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-tim-walker-story-teller/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 02:18:47 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Yang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-tim-walker-story-teller/</guid>
        <description>There has long existed a debate in regards to the reasons behind fashion photography. Do photographers pick up their Hasselblads solely under the direction of Devil Wears Prada-esque editors, and do models pose nonchalantly just to put the seemingly un-wearable catwalk designs to use? Or perhaps it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New term, new season and a new colour palette to match
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-new-term-new-season-and-a-new-colour-palette-to-match/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:21:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,Alice Yang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-new-term-new-season-and-a-new-colour-palette-to-match/</guid>
        <description>Red
Red has always held a special place in the hearts of women as a symbol of power, confidence and sensuality – an eye-catching scarlet lipstick for seduction, chic red nails for timeless elegance and, of course, scarlet-soled Louboutins for a woman truly in control.
Red is a colour for turning …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A guide to blagging fashion month
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-a-guide-to-blagging-fashion-month/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 20:54:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-a-guide-to-blagging-fashion-month/</guid>
        <description>For those unfamiliar, fashion month is a bi-annual occasion made up of fashion weeks in the four fashion capitals, where the fashion community (editors, buyers, bloggers and celebrities alike) collects to view the major designers’ collections for the following season. This September saw the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Festival Fashion
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-festival-fashion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 12:03:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Fashion,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-festival-fashion/</guid>
        <description>This summer Felix hit up the east coast of Spain, on a mission to discover the summer styles at Benicàssim Music Festival (Festival Internacional de Benicàssim).
A summer pilgrimage to a music festival is essential and Benicàssim is the place to go. Pay no heed to worries of mud, the rain and the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bag to basics
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-7-16-bag-to-basics/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 12:03:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Yang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-7-16-bag-to-basics/</guid>
        <description>So summer has finally arrived and it’s time to pack up our precious belongings and start travelling. Whether it’s lugging a heavy laptop to the office, or, for those more fortunate, a chance to explore the world with SLRs slung around our necks, there’s no doubt that expensive pieces of technology …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Essential Reads
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-22-essential-reads/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 10:46:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Yang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-22-essential-reads/</guid>
        <description>THE DRESS With the summer quickly settling in, there’s no doubt that the most talked about show come September will be Raf Simons’ inauguration at the House of Christian Dior. Up your fashion credentials for the inevitable discussions by taking a swirl through the House’s overflowing couture …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fashion week highlights for autumn/winter 2012
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-fashion-week-highlights-for-autumnwinter-2012/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 20:55:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,Alice Yang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-fashion-week-highlights-for-autumnwinter-2012/</guid>
        <description>Alexander McQueen
Once again, the organic references at McQueen were seared with a modern intricacy, the shoes heel-less and the models’ eyes hidden behind mirrored visors. It was curious to watch the clothes move, each shaggy twist of Mongolian lamb fur, ostrich feather and goat fur undulating and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fashion’s big re-shuffle
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-9-fashions-big-re-shuffle/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 00:54:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Yang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-9-fashions-big-re-shuffle/</guid>
        <description>As a month of high-fashion draws to an end with yards of lace, cashmere and leather erupting lavishly off the Paris catwalks, the unavoidable fact is that a tornado of names is what belies the centre of its storm.
There has been an explosion in terms of change at the top of fashion this season, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fashion Week frenzy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-fashion-week-frenzy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 21:28:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Yang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-fashion-week-frenzy/</guid>
        <description>To Do: London Fashion Weekend
23–26 February, Tickets start at £12.50
Once again Somerset House has opened its doors to the great British public, inviting in all those among us that yearn for the fashion week experience. The hoards of models, photographers and editors that have swarmed London this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dazed, confused and just a little hungry
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-dazed-confused-and-just-a-little-hungry/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 21:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Yang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-dazed-confused-and-just-a-little-hungry/</guid>
        <description>Born in Hertfordshire in 1996, John Rankin Waddell has come much further than most ex-accounting students, inspiring millions of people worldwide with his renowned collection of portraits. From top models and famous celebrities to the Queen, all the way to the less glamorous Mugunga refugee camp in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Embracing diversity in fashion
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-embracing-diversity-in-fashion/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 21:39:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Munim Islam,Alice Yang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-embracing-diversity-in-fashion/</guid>
        <description>A fashion industry expert for over 30 years having co-edited i-D magazine, renowned for its rebellion to conventional views towards art, fashion and music, and presented BBC’s The Clothes Show for over a decade, Caryn Franklin is anything but your ordinary fashion journalist. With no less than four …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The forgotten designer
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-the-forgotten-designer/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 22:49:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Yang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-the-forgotten-designer/</guid>
        <description>As unlikely as it may seem, I have found myself swapping the glossy pages of Vogue for the less conveniently sized Financial Times this week as the recently realised flurry of financial figures drag my attention away from the conventional pre-fashion-week buzz.
Instead of delighting in the prospect …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Suit Up: an idiot’s guide to the who, what, where, and how of formalwear
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-suit-up-an-idiots-guide-to-the-who-what-where-and-how-of-formalwear/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 20:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Yang,Saskia Verhagen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-suit-up-an-idiots-guide-to-the-who-what-where-and-how-of-formalwear/</guid>
        <description> Double-Breasted Suit The Man
The double-breasted suit was once thought to be reserved for a particular type of imperious middle-aged bore, chortling at something distinctly unfunny at a gentleman’s club or boating event of some description. Thankfully, this stereotype no longer applies. A favourite …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fashion faux pas to avoid
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-fashion-faux-pas-to-avoid/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 19:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Yang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-fashion-faux-pas-to-avoid/</guid>
        <description> GIRLS: Bin those Uggs Understandably, after seasons of toe-crunching towering stilettos, the female population are seeking out more practical and cosy footwear. Yet regardless of how appealing a shearling lined boot may sound, we must remember and endeavour to live through the famous quote: ‘no …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Give your gifts in style
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-give-your-gifts-in-style/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 21:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,Alice Yang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-give-your-gifts-in-style/</guid>
        <description>UNDER £20 Girls: Body-chain (£12-15)
 A completely unique gift inspired by Leonardo himself, and beautifully crafted by one of our own (Annabel St John-Lyle, Year 4 MechEng), these cross-body necklaces lend a downtown-chic touch to the plainest of outfits. Worn over a white tee, or a black dress, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Interview Dressing: Womenswear
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-interview-dressing-womenswear/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 20:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-interview-dressing-womenswear/</guid>
        <description>Informal Interviews
Here we’re talking about a company dinner with a few executives, or perhaps a casual interview for a cool media post somewhere you’ll find yourself fetching everyone’s tea order for your first six months of employment. This type of interview means deciphering the impossible …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Men: How to dress for an interview
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-men-how-to-dress-for-an-interview/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 21:19:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Fashion,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-men-how-to-dress-for-an-interview/</guid>
        <description>Shirt and Tie
This is the one area where you can really put your personality into business dress. Well, not quite – if you are interviewing for city positions, forget any shirt that’s not blue or white.
It’s generally best to go for solid twill or poplin cotton as it can provide you with more …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2012 Spring/Summer highlights hot from the catwalks
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-12-2012-springsummer-highlights-hot-from-the-catwalks/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2011 17:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,Alice Yang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-12-2012-springsummer-highlights-hot-from-the-catwalks/</guid>
        <description>Alexander McQueen
Surely those most critical of critics in the fashion industry must get tired of singing the praises of a woman who has slipped so perfectly into the 8-inch sculpted platforms of a designer whose shoes they claimed could ne’er be filled. Alas, no dice. Sarah Burton’s latest aquatic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Having a fashion fling online
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-having-a-fashion-fling-online/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 22:09:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laura Johnston,Saskia Verhagen,Alice Yang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-having-a-fashion-fling-online/</guid>
        <description>Style Bubble
Susanna Lau (aka Susie Bubble) is undoubtedly Britain’s most followed fashion blogger. The London-based 28-year-old, who once wrote about sneaking into fashion week shows, claiming, “If you’re ballsy enough to act like you’re somebody, SOMEONE’s gonna fall for it eventually,” now graces …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fashion through the decades, the good and the bad
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-fashion-through-the-decades-the-good-and-the-bad/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 21:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Yang,Saskia Verhagen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-fashion-through-the-decades-the-good-and-the-bad/</guid>
        <description>1940s
Iconic: Dior&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;New Look&amp;rsquo;
“In 1947, my first collection was successful beyond my wildest dreams,” remarked Christian Dior after he showcased a catwalk so revolutionary that it not only defined the 40s by majorly changing the way women dressed, but is still constantly referred …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Man’s Shoe Haven
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-a-mans-shoe-haven/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 10:24:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-a-mans-shoe-haven/</guid>
        <description>I rather like shoes, which is a problem because buying shoes is usually the low point of any shopping trip, especially for men. I guess we buy fewer shoes and don’t spend as much money on them, and thus as inferior customers get massively inferior treatment in shoe shops.
Your average ‘Office’ will …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Designer Horcrux
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-a-designer-horcrux/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 10:22:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,Federica Amato,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-a-designer-horcrux/</guid>
        <description>Which girl, provided she has already satisfied all primary concerns (food, water, shelter etc.) doesn’t dream of a clothing collection on the scale of, say, Blair Waldorf or Carrie Bradshaw? And within those ladies’ swoon-inducing wardrobes, which does not contain their essential Louis Vuitton …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Winter is coming, time to go coat crazy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-winter-is-coming-time-to-go-coat-crazy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 22:15:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Yang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-winter-is-coming-time-to-go-coat-crazy/</guid>
        <description>Fur
What better way to combat the winter chills than to wrap up warm in a fluffy fur coat? From Paris to Milan, fur was seen in a rainbow of colours, lengths and cuts leaving us spoilt for choice. Sleek glamour shone through with a seventies vibe at Gucci in the form of rich, gem coloured, bulging …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Post-summer accessories update
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-post-summer-accessories-update/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 12:26:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Yang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-post-summer-accessories-update/</guid>
        <description>Hats
Eyes were drawn up and beyond the faces of this season’s models to the hats that flew across the catwalk for AW11/12. Marc Jacobs presented fun plastic berets with a hint of fetish, whilst Dolce and Gabbana strutted sharp androgynous trilbies, adding an edge to their fun and glittery show. Wide …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tisci to replace disgraced Galliano?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-tisci-to-replace-disgraced-galliano/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 20:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-tisci-to-replace-disgraced-galliano/</guid>
        <description>After allegations of anti-semitic and racial slurs against a couple in a Parisian café, and the release of a damning video evidencing yet more abusive behaviour, John Galliano was dismissed from his role as designer for Christian Dior last Thursday. Although the fashion world has been rocked by the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Boutique du jour: One, Two, Three...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-boutique-du-jour-one-two-three/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 19:33:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-boutique-du-jour-one-two-three/</guid>
        <description>Tucked away in Shoreditch, lives one of London’s most exciting concept stores. 123. Offering beautifully crafted, locally sourced British clothing and accessories, as well as homeware and other trinkets, the main ethos of 123 is anti-mass production: British and vintage sourcing and recycling. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Menswear in Milan: Trendwatch
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-menswear-in-milan-trendwatch/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 19:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-menswear-in-milan-trendwatch/</guid>
        <description>Crayola Bright Colour
Unusually for the Autumn/Winter menswear collections, the runways were rather jolly - credited to the flashes of colour seen especially at Burberry Prorsum, Jil Sander and Bottega Veneta. There was none of the jewel-hued colour blocking we saw over at womenswear, but just pops …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The rise and rise of the Fashion Blog
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-the-rise-and-rise-of-the-fashion-blog/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 20:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-the-rise-and-rise-of-the-fashion-blog/</guid>
        <description>The fashion industry has always been deemed inaccessible, elitist and perhaps slightly indimidating by general consensus. It seems only natural, then, for people to start taking fashion into their own hands, and out of the perfectly manicured talons of the fashion editrixes at Vogue and the like. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An iconic life in pictures: Audrey Hepburn by Bob Willoughby
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-an-iconic-life-in-pictures-audrey-hepburn-by-bob-willoughby/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 20:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-an-iconic-life-in-pictures-audrey-hepburn-by-bob-willoughby/</guid>
        <description>Yet another photographic tome on the ubiquitous Ms Audrey Hepburn – there are so many out there now that if you didn’t know better, this one, by the late renowned Hollywood photographer Bob Willoughby is just another one on the shelf.
I would beg to differ. Bob Willoughby’s favourite subject, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Santi: A South Kensington sanctuary
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-santi-a-south-kensington-sanctuary/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 20:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-santi-a-south-kensington-sanctuary/</guid>
        <description>There is a place, inconspicuous and elusive to the untrained eye, where the weathered creatures of West London emerge calm, bright and restored. A spa, in South Kensington, which offers the most advanced techniques to enhance and perfect the skin. Only what they don’t tell you, is that it all goes a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Search of the Perfect Winter Boot.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-the-search-of-the-perfect-winter-boot/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 20:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-the-search-of-the-perfect-winter-boot/</guid>
        <description>As seen on the Autumn/Winter 2010 catwalks of Milan, CAT’s shearling-lined work boots are quickly becoming the hot fashion trend of this winter. With an eclectic mix of designs for men and women, CAT presents an ideal footwear solution for those seeking a boot encapsulating functionality and vintage …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fashion’s final frontier: Techno-Couture
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-fashions-final-frontier-techno-couture/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 20:33:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gabriella Yongue,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-fashions-final-frontier-techno-couture/</guid>
        <description>Many of us think that Imperial could not be further removed from the world of fashion, however I’d like to persuade you otherwise. Both fashion and technology are constantly evolving industries; fickle and always in search of the new ‘it’ product to entice buyers into yet another superfluous …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to London
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-welcome-to-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 19:09:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-welcome-to-london/</guid>
        <description>London is a quintessential fashion capital. Though we don’t have the edgy cool of New York, the elegant chic of Paris or the classic luxury of Milan, we have quirkiness and an extraordinary propensity to seek originality, using every sartorial tool in the box to illustrate exactly who we are, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mario Testino vs. Kate Moss
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-10-mario-testino-vs-kate-moss/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 15:43:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gabriella Yongue,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-10-mario-testino-vs-kate-moss/</guid>
        <description>When one of the most renowned fashion photographers collaborates with his muse, it is unsurprising that they should create the most exclusive photographic tome since Helmut Newton’s gargantuan, and aptly named, Sumo. Kate Moss by Mario Testino, printed in extremely limited edition and retailing at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Renaissance of the Chino
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-10-renaissance-of-the-chino/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 15:41:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-10-renaissance-of-the-chino/</guid>
        <description>Good news medic boys! Your favourite sports night style staple and go-to firms-wear has found itself on the hottest catwalks of London, Paris, Milan and New York: yes, chinos are actually in vogue.
Admittedly, the modest chino is somewhat underrated; it is the male equivalent of the trusty black …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
