<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Arts on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/arts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Arts on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/arts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>After the Collapse of Man Comes… Jellyfish?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-after-collapse-man-jellyfish/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Amanda Hertzberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-after-collapse-man-jellyfish/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
How art interacts with and depicts the changing climate is pivotal to how we think about climate change. This is the underlying idea of Eco-visionaries running right now at the Royal Academy of Arts. Very much a multimedia exhibition, it features works from DeepMind, AntFarm and Olafur …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cyrano de Bergerac: Love Letters to Language</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-cyrano-bergerac-love-letters-language/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-cyrano-bergerac-love-letters-language/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
I had no idea of what kind of show to expect, Swayed to attend by media buzz and the prospect Of seeing James McAvoy - live on stage! A welcome break from his golden age Of threequels and reboots, Green screens and CGI substitutes, Blockbuster, record-buster, So-called cinematic filibuster. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Midsummer in Midwinter</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-midsummer-in-winter/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-midsummer-in-winter/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
For those unfamiliar with the plot, A Midsummer Night’s Dream is a classic Shakespearean comedy. In this adaptation by the National Youth Theatre (NYT), several changes to the plot and setting have been made. The most obvious setting change was that instead of the traditional Athens of, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Christmas Carol</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-a-christmas-carol/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laura Casas,Aya Hayakawa,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-a-christmas-carol/</guid>
        <description>3 stars
This ‘musical play’ is an original adaptation of a well-known and loved novella, thanks to the fresh use of music and direction. The use of carol-singing and handbell performances to break up the well-known narrative play a role in creating a Christmassy and joyful environment on stage, but …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wolf of Wall Street - An Attempt at High-octane Fun Burns out Quickly</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-wolf-wall-street/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-wolf-wall-street/</guid>
        <description>2 stars
The Wolf of Wall Street is the latest immersive offering from director Alexander Wright, based on the 2013 film about unscrupulous stockbroker Jordan Belfort. The premise is that we - the audience - are all new employees at Belfort&amp;rsquo;s cash-swindling firm Stratton Oakmont. Right from the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Amelie: A Warm Hug in this Cruel World</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-amelie-warm-hug-in-cruel-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-amelie-warm-hug-in-cruel-world/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
Adapted from the five-time Oscar nominated French language movie of the same name, Amelie tells the story of a girl with a wild imagination who takes pleasure in performing “small, but extraordinary acts of kindness” with the goal of bringing joy to those around her. What must she do to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hunger - The Battle Between the Self and the City</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-hunger-battle-between-self-and-city/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Byron Gamble,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-hunger-battle-between-self-and-city/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
Simply titled “Hunger”, director Fay Lomas delves into the psychological turmoil as this primal instinct comes face-to-face with ambition. What sacrifices are we willing to make for our dreams? Although the production is based on the 1890 novel written by modernist Knut Hamsun, it displays …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is It Art if Everybody Hates It?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-art-everyone-hates-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laura Casas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-art-everyone-hates-it/</guid>
        <description>Van Gogh, while alive (1853-1890), only sold one painting. Though we all agree that The Starry Night (1889) and Sunflowers (1888) are artworks, people of the time detested or at least ignored these canvases. Thus, was it not art then and it is now? Was it always art?
In contrast, other masterpieces …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pop Hits Take the West End: &amp; Juliet</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-pop-hits-take-west-end-juliet/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-pop-hits-take-west-end-juliet/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
Romeo and Juliet, is probably one of history’s most famous love stories which (spoiler alert) tragically ends in death. This modern retelling considers what could have happened if Juliet (Miriam-Teak Lee) was given a life beyond Romeo. She travels to Paris with an entourage consisting of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sun, Sex and Suspicous Parents: 1920s Edition</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-sun-sex-suspicious-parents-1920s-edition/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-sun-sex-suspicious-parents-1920s-edition/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
In a few weeks’ time we will be in a new decade, the 2020s. If it’s anything like the 1920s, it should be a blast! The Boy Friend gives a little glimpse into what life back then was like.. for young, pretty socialites at a finishing school on the French Riviera that is!
If you fit this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Surrealist Superstars</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-surrealist-superstars/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-surrealist-superstars/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
Brussels’s Place Royale is a mecca of art, like a small, art-oriented brother to the museums surrounding our beautiful campus. The Royal Museums that flank it comprise some of the finest works of the European canon, from the Flemish masters to the modern genius of Magritte. The latter’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tepid Reviews for Dear Evan Hansen?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-tepid-reviews-dear-evan-hansen/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-tepid-reviews-dear-evan-hansen/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
It was rather surprising to me that the majority of the professional reviews for Dear Evan Hansen, the Broadway juggernaut that just made its way to the West End stage, have been rather tepid. Unlike its Broadway counterpart, which was showered with endless praise and a plethora of five …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Arrival: Two Brothers Reunited</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-the-arrival-two-brothers-reunited/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-the-arrival-two-brothers-reunited/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
Samad (Irfan Shamji) and Tom (Scott Karim) have lived very different lives. Different upbringings, different parents, different friends, different schools. Social, geographic and cultural barriers have divided them for over thirty years. But they have one thing in common, they are brothers, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Greatest Play in the History of the World</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-greatest-play-in-history-of-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Deniz Ak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-greatest-play-in-history-of-world/</guid>
        <description>3 stars
A man wakes in the middle of the night to discover that the world has stopped. It was exactly 04:40. The title, intriguing and vague, leaves you wondering what the greatest play in the history of the world could possibly be.
The Greatest Play in the History of the World written by Ian …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Illusion of Accessible Theatre: How Far Have we Come and How Far do we Have Left to Go?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-illusion-accessible-theatre/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-illusion-accessible-theatre/</guid>
        <description>Ever since my stint as a Felix arts editor began, I’ve been preaching the importance of making theatre more accessible. For the most part, the baby-boomer leaning demographics at the theatre astonish me. I strongly believe this medium of arts can be a formative part of a young person’s development. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Wind of Heaven: From Bethlehem to Blestin</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-wind-of-heaven-bethlehem-to-blestin/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Swift Roberts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-wind-of-heaven-bethlehem-to-blestin/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
The greatest objection to God has always been emotional. While it is true that the debate over divine non-presence is clothed in the mild-breathed language of logicism and rationality, what stirs in us feeling enough to slacken faith and scorn perdition is the atrociousness of evil and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Troy: Myth and Reality</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-troy-myth-reality/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-troy-myth-reality/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
Legend has it that the goddess of discord threw a golden apple into a crowd, bearing the inscription ‘for the most beautiful’. It was claimed by three goddesses, Athena, Hera and Aphrodite, and Zeus asked The Trojan prince Paris to make the final judgement. He chose Aphrodite, who promised …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>War Horse: A Year Later</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-war-horse-a-year-later/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-war-horse-a-year-later/</guid>
        <description>Last year, I was lucky enough to watch War Horse at the National Theatre, its return to the original National Theatre venue a celebration of the centenary of Armistice Day.I loved it so much the first time that I grabbed a different friend the next evening and ended up queueing for return tickets to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your Union is Standing Firm</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-dramsoc-macbeth-scores-macb/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-dramsoc-macbeth-scores-macb/</guid>
        <description>2 stars
I don’t remember much about Macbeth, having only studied it briefly in my early secondary school days. While I may have forgotten the plot and the characters’ names, I could never forget the feeling of empowerment I experienced after learning of my king-slayer potential wrought from the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your Union is Standing Firm</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-let-me-be-your-star-mtsoc-revue-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-let-me-be-your-star-mtsoc-revue-review/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
Sometimes all it takes to fall in love with a musical is that one special song or moment. MTSoc’s medley of musical classics hopes to scratch that itch with over fifteen musicals represented! With more than 45 performers taking part in the show in small groups, the audience was transported …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hyde Park Winter Wonderland Comedy Club</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-hyde-park-winter-wonderland-comedy-club/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Manfredi Castelli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-hyde-park-winter-wonderland-comedy-club/</guid>
        <description>2 stars
Between November and December of every year, Winter Wonderland opens its doors to Londoners and tourists alike as one of the most visited attractions. It has the perfect atmosphere for just going around the Christmas markets and enjoying the rides (of course while drinking mulled wine) but …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Shook: Becoming a Father Behind Bars</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-shook-becoming-father-behind-bars/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-shook-becoming-father-behind-bars/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
Shook is as close to a perfect play that I think I have ever seen. Set in a prison classroom, three convicts, all with pregnant girlfriends, are receiving lessons on how to be fathers. Opening with rapid wit and banter the play first comes across as an entertaining but fundamentally shallow …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Tiger Will See You Now</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-tiger-will-see-you-now/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-tiger-will-see-you-now/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
I live with medics, and from the way they go on, one could be forgiven for thinking that the last thing that any of them want is to be a doctor. Which is why it is so funny that the ICSM medics chose to put on Tiger Country last week as their autumn play. This is a play based on the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>#WeAreArrested - The Brutal Reality</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-we-are-arrested-brutal-reality/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Byron Gamble,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-we-are-arrested-brutal-reality/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
#WeAreArrested poses some very important questions. What is the power of the press? How do we protect its freedom when its own government acts outside its legal jurisdiction? This is a deeply personal account of a globally relevant story. In such strange times where lies and truth are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Crisis? What Crisis?: How to Save a Minority Government or Die Trying</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-crisis-what-crisis-how-to-save-minority-government-die-trying/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Swift Roberts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-crisis-what-crisis-how-to-save-minority-government-die-trying/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
The government has no working majority, millions are protesting on the street and economic catastrophe seems imminent. Sound familiar? Well, the year is 1979: in the midst of mass industrial action and the coldest winter in two decades, the Labour Party’s grip on power hangs in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I Will Still Be Whole (When You Rip Me in Half)/ Before I Was a Bear</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-I-will-still-be-whole-when-you-rip-me-in-half-before-i-was-a-bear/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kestrel Maio,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-I-will-still-be-whole-when-you-rip-me-in-half-before-i-was-a-bear/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
I Will Still Be Whole (When You Rip Me in Half) harnesses you from the offset, the two characters stand facing outwards towards the audience, hands by their sides and speaking with urgency. It describes the events that take place for a young woman, EJ (Aoife Hinds), and her estranged mother, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College DramSoc Presents: 11 Miles</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-imperial-college-dramsoc-presents-11-miles/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aya Hayakawa,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-imperial-college-dramsoc-presents-11-miles/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
Based on the real journal entries, 11 Miles follows Captain Scott’s journey to the South Pole with his four companions: Evans, Wilson, Bowers, and Oates. The audience comes to understand the meaning behind “11 miles” during the play as they hear about the tragedies that struck the team on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>La Clique: A Cabaret Show</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-la-clique-cabaret-show/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-la-clique-cabaret-show/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
Underbelly’s vaudeville cabaret show, La Clique has finally returned to London after ten years of coasting in Spiegeltents across UK, now offering a magnificent, jaw-dropping and titillating escapade. Bernie Dieter’s vivifying performance is somehow both salubrious and salacious, promising …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Leonardo: A journey through Da Vinci’s mind</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-leonardo-journey-through-da-vincis-mind/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ambika Bharadwaj,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-leonardo-journey-through-da-vincis-mind/</guid>
        <description>Leonardo Da Vinci was a man ahead of his time; only he could bring his brushstrokes &amp;amp; muted pencil shading to life. The exhibition, which opened in November at the National Gallery allows the public to have an immersive Da Vinci experience, unveiling hidden sketch &amp;amp; fingerprints. Although Da …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Touching the Void Review</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-touching-void-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aya Hayakawa,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-touching-void-review/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
Based on Joe Simpson’s mountaineering memoir and adapted by David Greig, Touching the Void is a story about the adventures of Joe and Simon to Siula Grande in the Peruvian Andes. As the double meaning of the title infers, the significant factor of the play are the feelings of the characters …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Death of a Salesman</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-death-salesman/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-death-salesman/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
Written by the iconic Arthur Miller, Death of a Salesman is often hailed as one of the best plays of the 20th century. Adding to its fame, the play recently made the news when the roof of the theatre ‘collapsed’ on the audience twenty minutes into the show, a mere 48 hours after my own …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>DramSoc Presents: Macbeth</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-dramsoc-presents-macbeth/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-dramsoc-presents-macbeth/</guid>
        <description>Shakespeare is the eternal snake. Just when you think you have him pinned down, he writhes away, changes shape or just turns to smoke in your hands. His texts, so well trod, in the hands of successive centuries of directors retain the ability to shock generation after generation.
Dramatists and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Harry Potter in Concert: A Magical Musical Evening</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-harry-potter-concert-magical-musical-evening/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-harry-potter-concert-magical-musical-evening/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
Imagine your favourite movie – any movie. Now, imagine it again without the music and its iconic soundtrack: it would simply not be the same. Music is a huge part of creating a film’s atmosphere, creating the right ambience and enhancing the emotional tug of the moment. And what better way …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I Love You, You’re Perfect, Now Change</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-i-love-you-youre-perfect-now-change/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-i-love-you-youre-perfect-now-change/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
Love is at the centre of all good tales. Every story ever told, every piece of art, is propelled by this strange notion of an attractive force between individuals, a force that can neither be defined nor explained. And yet that’s what I Love You… attempts to do by showcasing the almost …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Mikado - Stylish Set, Passé Plot</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-mikado-stylish-set-passe-plot/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-mikado-stylish-set-passe-plot/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
The Mikado is perhaps the most well-known of Gilbert and Sullivan’s Victorian-era comic operas, famously set in Japan. Why Japan, one might wonder? Back in 1885, it was all about keeping political satire hidden in plain sight. By setting their scenes in fantastical or wildly foreign …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Music of the Night</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-music-of-the-night/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aya Hayakawa,Laura Casas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-music-of-the-night/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
In theatrical performances, the orchestra has a supporting function, often lacking the appreciation that it deserves. In this one-night-only show of hit songs from the most famous musicals, the orchestra is on stage alongside the singers, as opposed to being in the pit. This unusual …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Taming of the Shrew: It’s Shakespeare… but Woke</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-taming-shrew-shakespeare-woke/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Preet Lalli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-taming-shrew-shakespeare-woke/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
The Royal Shakespeare Company return to the Barbican this winter with As You Like It, Measure for Measure and The Taming of the Shrew. Justin Audibert’s electrifying production of Shrew is a gender-flipped version of the original, where, instead of a rich gentleman looking for suitors for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Magic Flute - Mozart’s classic</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-magic-flute-mozarts-classic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aya Hayakawa,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-magic-flute-mozarts-classic/</guid>
        <description>It isn’t easy to picture a more magical setting than sitting in the historical auditorium of the Royal Opera House as you listen to the overture, eagerly waiting for the curtain to rise.
Back for its seventh revival at Covent Garden, Mozart’s Die Zauberflöte (The Magic Flute) manages to retain the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A fairytale on Old Compton Street - Soho Cinders</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-a-fairytale-on-old-compton-street-soho-cinders/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-a-fairytale-on-old-compton-street-soho-cinders/</guid>
        <description>After an initial run back in 2012, Soho Cinders is back off the west end at the Charing Cross Theatre, and its unique narrative and warm characters are more relevant than ever. Set on the iconic Old Compton Street in the beating heart of the West End, this modern Cinderella sees young Robbie (Luke …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BEAT: A breath of fresh air</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-BEAT-breath-fresh-air/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sid Basetti,Maria Greca,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-BEAT-breath-fresh-air/</guid>
        <description>BEAT is at the forefront of contemporary dance, choreographed by Igor and Moreno, performed by Margarita Elliot. This production has taken four years to reach fruition and is the second piece from this duo. The choreography encourages introspection and plunges into the millennial psyche. It will …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Birmingham Royal Ballet Mixed Bill: A three-course meal</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-birmingham-royal-ballet-mixed-bill-three-course-meal/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Deniz Ak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-birmingham-royal-ballet-mixed-bill-three-course-meal/</guid>
        <description>Birmingham Royal Ballet is on tour at Sadler’s Wells with a three-part mixed bill to suit anyone’s taste. Three separate pieces by different minds to dive into.
The first piece, A Brief Nostalgia (directed by Jack Lister) is unsettling. Two large slates. One dancer. Her shadow cast on the wall …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Arts: Interview with Anita-Joy Uwajeh</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-interview-with-anita-joy-uwajeh/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-interview-with-anita-joy-uwajeh/</guid>
        <description>Cyrano de Bergerac is a French verse-play written in 1897, telling the fictionalised story of the eponymous nobleman., whose large nose prevents him from winning his love, Roxane. Despite its somewhat peculiar plot, the play has proven surprisingly timeless through the ages. There are at least five …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Frankenstein: Resurrected for the Modern Day</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-frankenstein-resurrected-for-modern-day/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-frankenstein-resurrected-for-modern-day/</guid>
        <description>It’s been a long time since Frankenstein was first published. Written in 1818 by Mary Shelley, the gothic novel swiftly became a cultural icon. Widely regarded as one of the first science fiction novels ever written, Frankenstein follows the tragic tale of Dr Victor Frankenstein and his destructive …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title> Hogarth After Hours – A Rushed Masterpiece</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-hogarth-after-hours-a-rushed-masterpiece/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Evlyn Forsyth-Muris,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-hogarth-after-hours-a-rushed-masterpiece/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
On a cold and slightly wet October Friday night, I made my way to the Sir John Soane Museum in Holborn. Located in the late John Soane’s house, the museum is a rabbit warren of impressively decorated rooms and secret cupboards; mirrors, artwork and sculpture line every wall and surface. Look …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gaslight- A Play About Mental Delusion</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-gaslight-play-mental-delusion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-gaslight-play-mental-delusion/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
I had always assumed that ‘gaslighting’, a form of psychological manipulation which systematically breaks down another person’s grip on reality, was a very modern phenomenon. Imagine my surprise when I found out that its etymology derives from a play first written in 1938. Gaslight tells the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Great Expectations</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-great-expectations/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-great-expectations/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
My week began this Monday with Great Expectations. I was richly rewarded by a play that was wonderfully acted and brought to life the world of Pip, Miss Havisham and Magwitch.
For those of you unfamiliar with the plot, it follows the life of Pip, an adopted blacksmith’s son. Pip, whilst …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lungs: Royalty Takes Over the Old Vic</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-lungs-royalty-takes-old-vic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-lungs-royalty-takes-old-vic/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
Running for a mere three weeks at The Old Vic, Lungs promised to recapture the magic that Claire Foy and Matt Smith brought to the first two seasons of The Crown on Netflix to the stage. I’m not one to blindly buy tickets for the sake of the play’s star power (I made that mistake once with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Meet Me at Dawn: Stun Me at Dusk</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-meet-me-at-dawn-stun-me-at-dusk/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tesni Haddon-Mcmillan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-meet-me-at-dawn-stun-me-at-dusk/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
According to Greek myth, Orpheus loses his lover, Eurydice, and laments so painfully for her that the gods themselves weep and help him on the terrible quest to reclaim Eurydice from the underworld.
This tale of longing and devastation was the source of inspiration for playwright, Zinnie …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Lovely Bones: A Different Viewpoint on Death</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-lovely-bones-different-viewpoint-death/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aya Hayakawa,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-lovely-bones-different-viewpoint-death/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
The first thing to capture your attention when entering the theatre is the great mirror which extends above the stage. The reflective structure is only one of many creative tools present in this production through which the main character’s unique story-telling is done. The minimal but …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Translations – Mythical Ireland speaks the Common Tongue</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-translations-mythical-ireland-speaks-common-tongue/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Waleed A El-Geresy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-translations-mythical-ireland-speaks-common-tongue/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
Director Ian Rickson’s new production of Brian Fiel’s play Translations is staging at The National Theatre. Set in an 1833 hedge school in Baile Beag (English: Ballybeg), an Irish speaking community in County Donegal, the play explores the lingual boundaries that divide us and define us.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>[Blank]- Giving Justice to Women’s Voices</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-blank-giving-justice-womens-voices/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Poppy Hayes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-blank-giving-justice-womens-voices/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
A mother who excitedly enters into a new alluring relationship is later horrifically murdered by her new lover. Another mother navigates the demands of her eldest daughter who desperately appeals to her to help fund her habits. Two young girls, who meet in foster care, struggle over the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don Pasquale: A Modern Opera</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-don-pasquale-modern-opera/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mehreen Ishaque,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-don-pasquale-modern-opera/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
Michieletto reworks Donizetti’s classic comedy, Don Pasquale (Dom Pa-Skwah-Lay), at the Royal Opera House. The opera buffa stays true to its origins with a largely untouched storyline but successfully brings its characters into 2019. The result is fabulous: think traditional opera singing, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Inside the Flashy Mind of Tim Walker</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-inside-flashy-mind-tim-walker/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Amanda Hertzberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-inside-flashy-mind-tim-walker/</guid>
        <description>2 stars
Dolls larger than humans. Hokusai’s The Great Wave inside of a room. A living mermaid floating in a box. In Tim Walker’s world everything is possible. As I walk through the door into the exhibition, I hear Tchaikovsky’s music playing in the background. On the walls hang Lewis Carroll-like …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Moving to Mars</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-moving-mars/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-moving-mars/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
Space travel and design go hand in immaculately engineered glove. Rockets and rovers, space stations and satellites, the unique environmental challenges that extra-terrestrial exploration must solve are fascinating. The exhibition, “Moving to Mars,” is the engrossing result of the human …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pretty Fly for a Sci-fi</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-pretty-fly-for-sci-fi/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-pretty-fly-for-sci-fi/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
Based on the 1961 book of the same name by Polish author Stanisław Lem, Solaris recounts the events that occur on a research station hovering in orbit above the titular ocean planet. Orbiting between two stars, Solaris defies scientific explanation, behaving not as a planet but more like a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>South Africa, France, Dance: An Unexpected Trio</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-south-africa-unexpected-trio/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-south-africa-unexpected-trio/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
Pioneering South African choreographer and dance, Maqoma created “Cion: Requiem of Ravel’s Boléro” a few years ago, imaginatively setting his story inspired by South African literature against the music of Ravel’s famed orchestral piece, Boléro. Maqoma founded Vuyani Dance Theatre in 1999 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stranger Things Called, they want their ’80s Gimmick Back</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-stranger-things-called-want-80s-gimmick-back/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-stranger-things-called-want-80s-gimmick-back/</guid>
        <description>3 stars
Three thieves all with different motivations try to break into a gallery to steal a famous painting. As they work their way through the gallery, they unknowingly affect each other’s progress before finally meeting. Of course only one of them can actually end up with the painting&amp;hellip;
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Distortion of Orientalist Art</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-distortion-orientalist-art/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-distortion-orientalist-art/</guid>
        <description>2 stars
This tone is set by the very first piece in the exhibition, the Prayer. This painting by Frederick Arthur Bridgman, is supposed to capture two individuals in a mosque, engaged in the act of prayer (salat). The subject in the foreground stands with both hands outstretched at his sides, face …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Soviet Still Life in Eight Chapters - Theatre of Nations</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-soviet-still-life-eight-chapters-theatre-nations/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-soviet-still-life-eight-chapters-theatre-nations/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
The themes of the stories are centred mostly on the everyday aspects of social life. The characters are not extraordinary in their feats of achievement but shine through with their touching realness. When the curtains part, a bench is revealed, which takes up most of the stage, and will …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dutchman - A Discomforting Enlightenment</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-dutchman-discomforting-enlightenment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Preet Lalli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-dutchman-discomforting-enlightenment/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
The playwright Amiri Baraka, a famous American Civil Rights activist known by the name of LeRoi Jones, wrote and produced Dutchman in 1964, a time when African Americans were not afforded the same constitutional rights as white people. Racial segregation, discrimination and violence were …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gauguin Portraits</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-gauguin-portraits/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-gauguin-portraits/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
As you enter the exhibition, the first room is filled with self-portraits of Gauguin. To walk into any room of self-portraits would give the impression of a self-centred creator, but Gauguin’s portraits strike one as particularly narcissistic, given there are several oil paintings where he …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Giselle: A Bold Reimagination of a Classic Ballet</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-giselle-bold-reimagination-classic-ballet/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xiuchen Xu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-giselle-bold-reimagination-classic-ballet/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
Dada Masilo is famous for her works which rework the plots of well-known classical ballet pieces. Her previous works include her interpretation of Swan Lake which included twists such as a homosexual Siegfried, and social commentary on sexism and homophobia. Her vision for Giselle is equally …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ian McKellen On Stage</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-ian-mckellen-stage/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elizabeth Thong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-ian-mckellen-stage/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
Sir Ian McKellen: the mere prospect of seeing him live would stir up excitement in any Lord of the Rings or Shakespeare fan. And that was very much how I felt – I mean, who wouldn’t want to see Gandalf live? McKellen’s one-man show is a tribute to his 80th birthday and 50 years of acting, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Live it Up with the Modernists at Barbican’s New Show</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-live-up-with-modernists-barbicans-new-show/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-live-up-with-modernists-barbicans-new-show/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
In contrast to last year’s wildly popular Modern Couples, which offered an intimate view into how interpersonal relationships of artists shaped their work, this offers a different view. It portrays some of the most influential artists of modernism as entertainers: uproarious and devilish …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Love, Me and Compost: A Double Bill of Love and Trash</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-love-me-compost-double-bill-love-trash/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-love-me-compost-double-bill-love-trash/</guid>
        <description>Love, Me: 3.5 stars
Compost: 4 stars
Teaming up for a double-billed show, our very own MTSoc and Dramsoc have put together an original musical titled Love, Me, and an original play titled Compost, the latter of which was recently performed at the Edinburgh Fringe Festival over the summer.
Love, Me …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Meet the Editors: Ozbil - The Fanatical One</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-meet-editors-ozbil-fanatical-one/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-meet-editors-ozbil-fanatical-one/</guid>
        <description>Having joined Felix Arts as a writer last year, I often think about how different life would have been had I joined sooner. I first heard about Felix Arts from my housemate, and quickly realised that this would be one of the best ways to enjoy the London theatre scene on a student budget – and enjoy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Noises Off</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-noises-off/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-noises-off/</guid>
        <description>2 stars
Hailed as ‘iconic’ and as ‘the funniest farce ever written’, I thought I was in for a treat when I went to see Noises Off at the Garrick Theatre. Having been revived on Broadway various times, I was sure that the play would be nothing short of magnificent. Oh, boy, was I wrong.
Noises Off is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Red Palace</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-red-palace/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-red-palace/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
A masked ball at the Prince’s Palace, for the thousandth day of his reign. There’s a rumour going around that the Prince will be dead by morning. We are left to wander through the palace’s rooms, tasked with finding out just what is going on.
Such is the premise of Shotgun Carousel’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Watsons: Jane Austen Spin-off Fiction Fan Club</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-18-10-watsons-jane-austen-spin-off-fiction-fan-club/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maria Portela,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-18-10-watsons-jane-austen-spin-off-fiction-fan-club/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
Laura Wade set herself up for a difficult task: to finish, as a play, a novel that Jane Austen couldn’t complete. It follows the story of Emma Watson, a young woman used to a luxurious lifestyle, who finds herself dumped back home, and financially dependent on her family. Several suitors …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tick, Tick… BOOM!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-28-tick-tick-boom/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-28-tick-tick-boom/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
Before there was Rent, there was 30&amp;frasl;90. Wait a second. Let me start again. Before there was Rent there was Boho Days, a… solo rock monologue? Ah, here we go. Before there was Rent, there was 30&amp;frasl;90, which was renamed to Boho Days and finally to tick, tick… BOOM!, an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Up Pompeii - An Audio Revival</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-up-pompeii-audio-revival/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-up-pompeii-audio-revival/</guid>
        <description>3 stars
One quick look around the audience and I soon realise my companion and I are easily the youngest in the room. I’m also the only non-white person there (unless we’re counting the ushers). We’re at a live radio recording of Up Pompeii, that BBC comedy classic about a ne’er-do-well slave in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Arts Editor Intro: Claire - The Culture Vulture</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-arts-editor-intro-claire-culture-vulture/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-arts-editor-intro-claire-culture-vulture/</guid>
        <description>This is my second year as Arts section editor. It’s a role that never gets boring – London really is one of the best cities in the world for culture. It’s a wonderful mix of things old and new. Van Gogh and Warhol. Russian classical ballet and Merce Cunningham’s contemporary choreography. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Glass. Kill. Bluebeard. Imp.</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-glass-kill-bluebeard-imp/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-glass-kill-bluebeard-imp/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
As the title implies, this performance was comprised of four different plays, each increasing in length – the final play, ‘Imp’, was one hour long. ‘Glass’ tells the story of a girl made of glass, discussing important themes of abuse. However, this aspect didn’t seem to quite fit in as I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Interview with the Makers of Now is the Time to Say Nothing</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-interview-makers-now-time-say-nothing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-interview-makers-now-time-say-nothing/</guid>
        <description>Would you mind briefly summarising your stories?
Caroline Williams: This is the story of Syrian artist Reem Karssli’s life during the Syrian conflict. It follows the story of what happens when a group of teenagers from London tries to contact her. It is about how we can stay connected to the people …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Love and Loss, Music and Mourning</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-love-loss-music-mourning/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-love-loss-music-mourning/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
This Autumn, the English National Opera is presenting an “Orpheus” series with four operas from different historical periods that retell the myth. The first of these comes from the mid-eighteenth century: ‘Orfeo ed Euridice’, by Gluck. It is of particular importance in the history of music …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Manon</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-manon/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-manon/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
Manon, based on the 1731 novel L’histoire du chevalier des Grieux et de Manon Lescaut by Abbé Prévost, was reimagined by Kenneth Macmillan in 1974 as a ballet and remains a captivating story to this day. It tells the tale of Manon who, though in love with Des Grieux, agrees to be mistress …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Me too in Mount Olympus</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-me-too-mount-olympus/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maria Portela,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-me-too-mount-olympus/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
Jacques Offenbach composed his world-famous operetta Orphée aux enfers in late 19th century France, satirizing the society of his time, the ruling classes and their vices. Now, in the second opera of this season’s ENO’s Orpheus Series, director Emma Rice adapts this comic masterpiece to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nara: Sacred Images from Early Japan</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-nara-sacred-images-early-japan/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Adderley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-nara-sacred-images-early-japan/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
The city of Nara in Japan is perhaps best-known today for the large number of deer found roaming in Nara park. However, make your way through these creatures once regarded as divine and you’ll find Todaiji temple, one of Japan’s largest and most historically significant Buddhist temples. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Now is the Time to Say Nothing</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-now-time-say-nothing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-now-time-say-nothing/</guid>
        <description>3 stars
This article was followed by an interview with the makers, available in the Arts section.
What to say for Now is the Time to Say Nothing? Now is the Time&amp;hellip;, is primarily a piece of artwork about relationships. Although there is a focus on the relationship between one group of Western …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ONE: Rough Edged Insights to the State We’re In</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-ONE-rough-edged-insights-state-were-in/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calvin Nesbitt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-ONE-rough-edged-insights-state-were-in/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
Reconciliation, compromise &amp;amp; understanding. These are words one would be hard pushed to find mentioned in modern British political discourse. So evident is their absence that the more hopeless among us may feel they have been forever barred from the British psyche. Here in One, a show …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Beginner&#39;s Guide to the West End: how to score cheap (or even free) tickets</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-a-beginners-guide-to-the-west-end-how-to-score-cheap-tickets/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-a-beginners-guide-to-the-west-end-how-to-score-cheap-tickets/</guid>
        <description> Studying at such a science-based university, it is often easy to forget that London is one of the world’s art capitals, with an endless number of plays, musicals, and exhibitions at our doorstep. Unfortunately, the theatre has a bit of a reputation for being expensive, and therefore inaccessible …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dogfight</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-dogfight-when-camaraderie-and-debauchery-are-confused/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Disha Bandyopadhyay,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-dogfight-when-camaraderie-and-debauchery-are-confused/</guid>
        <description>It is intriguing how a musical with such a fierce name can be so gentle and sensitive. Amidst the brash soldiers and their swearing, Dogfight shines light on the importance of not being judgmental and accepting each others’ differences to work together. Dogfight, in a youth production by the British …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don Giovanni</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-don-giovanni/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-don-giovanni/</guid>
        <description>Kasper Holten&amp;rsquo;s tech-heavy Don Giovanni has been trotted out on the ROH stage for the third time. The eye-catching set is unquestionably the most remarkable thing about this production. Unfortunately, it detracts from, rather than adds to, the performance, leaving one wondering where Holten’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fame the Musical</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-fame-the-musical/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marena Gray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-fame-the-musical/</guid>
        <description>Who doesn’t want to be famous? Fame the Musical is all about that desire to be recognised, to be known, to not fade out of existence when death takes hold. While based on a film from the 1980s, that desire is just as relevant today. “I’m Gonna Live Forever” is the refrain of our protagonists - …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Manga Exhibition at the British Museum</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-manga-exhibition-british-museum/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-manga-exhibition-british-museum/</guid>
        <description>Ask the uninitiated what manga is, and they’ll probably tell you something about “Japanese cartoons with the big eyes and crazy hair” or, if you’re my mum, “Japanese nerd stuff that’ll turn you into a shut-in NEET pervert”. For me, manga and anime were one of few cultural touchstones that I could …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Meet the Editors: Eamon - the cool one</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-meet-the-editors-eamon-the-cool-one/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-meet-the-editors-eamon-the-cool-one/</guid>
        <description>So you’ve come to London, rents are high, a pint costs £500 and you basically can’t step out of the house without breaking the bank. But it’s all worth it right? London is a city of endless possibilities with a very vibrant arts and theatre scene&amp;hellip; But where to start?
That’s where I come in. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rouge</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-rouge/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elizabeth Thong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-rouge/</guid>
        <description>Hailing from a stellar run at the Edinburgh Fringe Festival is ‘Rouge: A Circus for Grown Ups’. And it is a truly spectacular show. The award-winning Australian production is a celebration of jaw-dropping acrobatics, cheeky burlesque and charming cabaret that was both sensual and gorgeous. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Son</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-the-son/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-the-son/</guid>
        <description>The Son completes a loosely related trilogy in which each standalone play focuses on a member of the family. The first, The Father, examines the effects of dementia, and The Mother discusses middle-aged angst and loneliness. This final play’s focus is, teen depression. Nicolas, two years ago a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Werther at the Royal Opera House</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-werther-at-royal-opera-house/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bernadette Fernandes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-werther-at-royal-opera-house/</guid>
        <description>The opening night of Werther was a beautiful masterpiece, however it was underwhelming at times. Massenet’s Werther, based on Goethe’s Die Leiden des Jungen (The Sorrows of Young Werther), is a classic story of two star-crossed lovers – whose love brings sorrow to both themselves and the people …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Girls Are Made Of</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-what-girls-are-made-of/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mehreen Ishaque,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-what-girls-are-made-of/</guid>
        <description>‘What Girls are Made of’ is a deeply introspective and yet refreshingly playful performance written by and starring Cora Bissett: the (almost famous) lead singer of the 90s indie-band ‘Darlingheart’. Fresh from its sold-out run in the Edinburgh Fringe and now being performed in the Soho Theatre, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Truth Isn&#39;t Always Satisfying</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-23-the-truth-isnt-always-satisfying/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 21:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Amanda Hertzberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-23-the-truth-isnt-always-satisfying/</guid>
        <description>There’s no doubt that a large chunk of the population are at least fascinated by conspiracy theories. Youtuber Shane Dawson has compilations of them on his youtube channel, each video with almost as many views as the British population. And we all have that friend who stays up at night listening to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Midsummer night’s dream</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-a-midsummer-night-s-dream/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maria Portela,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-a-midsummer-night-s-dream/</guid>
        <description>There is no line between audience and stage at The Bridge. Or rather, there are multiple lines, but they are constantly changing, with raising platforms, movable staircases and rolling beds; the actors jumping to the middle of the crowd or shouldering an unsuspecting audience member. The action …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cinderella: sculpture of a fleeting magical moment</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-cinderella-sculpture-of-a-fleeting-magical-moment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Disha Bandyopadhyay,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-cinderella-sculpture-of-a-fleeting-magical-moment/</guid>
        <description>Christopher Weeldon creates magic right next to Imperial’s main campus at the Royal Albert Hall, in Cinderella, performed by the English National Ballet Philharmonic. A retelling of the Brothers Grimm fairy-tale, over ninety dancers and a live orchestra unfold a dream-like sequence with resplendent …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rosmersholm</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-rosmersholm/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marena Gray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-rosmersholm/</guid>
        <description>Ibsen wrote Rosmersholm (pronounced Ros-mers-home) in 1886, and it is considered to be his masterpiece, over The Wild Duck and A Doll’s House. Yet it is rarely staged. The day I saw Rosmersholm was ironically the day of the European Elections, and the parallels were astonishing, regardless of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Life, Love and Robots: A Conversation</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-life-love-and-robots-a-conversation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Amanda Hertzberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-life-love-and-robots-a-conversation/</guid>
        <description>The exhibition ‘AI: More Than Human’ (explored in the previous issue of Felix) is taking place at the Barbican right now, where visitors can explore the topic of artificial intelligence and machine learning, spanning back to the Middle Ages, then jumping to 1940’s Alan Turing to today’s newest …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AI: More than Worth It</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-ai-more-than-worth-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-ai-more-than-worth-it/</guid>
        <description>It has almost been seventy years since Alan Turing published the hugely influential paper ‘Computing Machinery and Intelligence’ where he first posits the basis of what we now know as the Turing test. In a mere lifetime, computers have gone from purely machines of calculation to pocket-sized marvels …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An interview with Anna Ridler, the artist behind Mosaic Virus and Myriad (Tulips)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-an-interview-with-anna-ridler-the-artist-behind-mosaic-virus-and-myriad-tulips/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-an-interview-with-anna-ridler-the-artist-behind-mosaic-virus-and-myriad-tulips/</guid>
        <description>For those unfamiliar with your work, how would you introduce yourself and describe your artwork?
I’m an artist. I like to work with technology, but not just because it is there. I think about what it can do and how it can add to what I’m making, about its associations and the connotations of using …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dog Without Feathers</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-22-dog-without-feathers/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elizabeth Thong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-22-dog-without-feathers/</guid>
        <description>Transport yourself to the dried-out Capibaribe River in north-eastern Brazil, where ‘crab men’ covered in mud desperately try to survive the harsh, violent environment. Where water is scarce and life is returned to its primal origins, Dog Without Feathers is a virtuostic dance production by the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Avalanche: A Love Story</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-avalanche-a-love-story/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-avalanche-a-love-story/</guid>
        <description>Hope springs eternal; that is both a blessing and curse for Julie Leigh’s protagonist, the Woman (Maxine Peake), in Avalanche: A Love Story. We meet Peake’s nameless character at a psychic’s gathering, which is really something of a supernaturally tinged group therapy session. Everyone there is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Class</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-class/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-class/</guid>
        <description>What begins as a simple parent-teacher meeting between recently separated Brian (Stephen Jones) and Donna (Sarah Morris), and teacher Mr McAfferty (Will O’Connell), to talk about their son Jayden’s literacy struggles in school, spirals quickly as tension bubbles about social and cultural divides …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
