<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mh3210/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mh3210/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>News from around the world
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-news-from-around-the-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 22:12:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie-Laure Hicks,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-news-from-around-the-world/</guid>
        <description>Obama, the new Nixon?
Obama has found himself in some trouble over the past few weeks. After being accused of sexism for calling the new attorney general the “best-looking”, Obama faced embarrassment as his gun background check bill was defeated in the Senate, a strong victory for gun lobbies.
More …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Riding through Europe
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-21-riding-through-europe/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 13:52:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie-Laure Hicks,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-21-riding-through-europe/</guid>
        <description>The horse meat scandal is revealing the intricacies and complexities of the European food industry. When disconcerting discoveries were made in Ireland in November 2012 and finally the scandal erupted in the UK mid-January, no one expected it to blow up in such a dramatic way. Since then, three …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Eco-Terrorism
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-eco-terrorism/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 23:22:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie-Laure Hicks,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-eco-terrorism/</guid>
        <description>Classed as the number one domestic threat in the US since 2001, eco-terrorism is estimated to have cost $300million between 2003 and 2008. Organisations like EarthFirst!, the Earth Liberation Front (ELF), the Animal Liberation Front, GreenPeace and PETA have been accused of radical environmentalism …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All around the world, elections
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-all-around-the-world-elections/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 22:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie-Laure Hicks,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-all-around-the-world-elections/</guid>
        <description>Americans have chosen the man to lead them for the next four years. China is easing its way to a new leadership. How are other countries doing?
Jordan
23 January 2013
 In reaction to public discontent and pressure for reform, King Abdullah dissolved parliament in October, calling for early …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Republicans’ Last Chance to Win?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-the-republicans-last-chance-to-win/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:22:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie-Laure Hicks,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-the-republicans-last-chance-to-win/</guid>
        <description>Throughout the campaign, Obama has been depicted as having two advantages: the incumbent advantage and the demographic advantage. Since 1948, only three incumbent presidents have failed to be re-elected, with seven successful bids. As an incumbent, the candidate has already gone through the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Short Stories of the Week
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-short-stories-of-the-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 20:53:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie-Laure Hicks,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-short-stories-of-the-week/</guid>
        <description>Missing Women After being accused of spying on employees in France, Ikea has issued an apology concerning its catalogue available in Saudi Arabia. In the Saudi version of the catalogue, women have been airbrushed out of pictures, including a woman standing in her pyjamas and an Ikea designer. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sex Scandal in Chongqing (and more important news)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-sex-scandal-in-chongqing-and-more-important-news/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 13:04:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie-Laure Hicks,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-sex-scandal-in-chongqing-and-more-important-news/</guid>
        <description>China is one of the largest and fastest growing economies in the world and (to an extent) the country that gave us Jacqui Chan (I’m totally going to watch Rush Hour now – Tim). At a time when the rest of the world, especially the Eurozone, is turning towards China to solve their (money) problems, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Sexism Survey
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-24-felix-sexism-survey/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 23:40:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie-Laure Hicks,Silvia Araguas Rodriguez,Philip Kent,Jonathan Kim,Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-24-felix-sexism-survey/</guid>
        <description>Over the past year, 10 articles and 231 comments have been written about sexism in science and at Imperial. Stephen Smith’s “Sexism at Imperial College” has been viewed over 7,500 times on the Felix website. Sexism is clearly an issue that concerns the Imperial community and 631 of you gave us your …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Twinkle, twinkle, little star
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-twinkle-twinkle-little-star/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 21:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie-Laure Hicks,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-twinkle-twinkle-little-star/</guid>
        <description>Every student faces the eternal dilemma: balancing work, having a social life and sleep. On average, we humans spend a third of our lives sleeping. So what is sleep and is it really that important?
There are two main types of sleep. The first type is composed of four stages. Stage I is called light …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New autism diagnosis in infants
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-new-autism-diagnosis-in-infants/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 20:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie-Laure Hicks,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-new-autism-diagnosis-in-infants/</guid>
        <description>Autistic Spectrum Disorder (ASD) affects approximately 1% of the population. The main characteristics of ASD are difficulties in social interaction, communication, and repetitive behaviours. It is a difficult condition to diagnose, especially in young children, but researchers at Birkbeck College …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Medics in BBC3 reality show
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-imperial-medics-in-bbc3-reality-show/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 22:49:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie-Laure Hicks,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-imperial-medics-in-bbc3-reality-show/</guid>
        <description>Junior Doctors: Your Life in their Hands is back! After a first series in Newcastle General Hospital and the Royal Victoria Infirmary, eight newly-qualified doctors hit the wards of the Chelsea and Westminster Hospital. After getting their MBBS, for the first time, they have to deal with real life …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Dulce Et Decorum Est Pro Patria Mori”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-dulce-et-decorum-est-pro-patria-mori/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 22:03:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie-Laure Hicks,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-dulce-et-decorum-est-pro-patria-mori/</guid>
        <description>Following Sherlock and Great Expectations, another one of Britain’s favourite novels, Birdsong has been adapted for the small screen by the BBC. The first part was broadcast last Sunday. The book, written by Sebastian Faulks, is considered a modern retelling of the Great War. Set in pre-war Amiens …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The brain is king
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-the-brain-is-king/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 20:10:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie-Laure Hicks,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-the-brain-is-king/</guid>
        <description>As the economic crisis continues, companies are developing new methods to make you buy, by going straight to the source: your brain. Marketing and advertisement have generally relied on focus groups and surveys to determine the efficiency of a campaign. This method poses a problem as it is difficult …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>There’s a New Girl on Channel 4!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-theres-a-new-girl-on-channel-4/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 22:57:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie-Laure Hicks,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-theres-a-new-girl-on-channel-4/</guid>
        <description>Blue Monday (the statistically most depressing day of the year) is approaching. The weather is ever gloomier. Work starts to pile up. Festive feelings slowly disintegrate into utter misery. In a desperate attempt to cheer yourself up, you splash your student loan in the sales, fill your house with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Feminists need to man up
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-feminists-need-to-man-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 21:44:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie-Laure Hicks,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-feminists-need-to-man-up/</guid>
        <description>I am writing from the kitchen, the place where my family believe I belong, having given me an apron, tea towels, cookbooks and sponges for Christmas. Feminism is committing suicide. Last week, the BBC’s adaptation of Arthur Conan Doyle’s Sherlock was criticised for being sexist. In my opinion, this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Paper days are over
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-the-paper-days-are-over/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 20:03:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie-Laure Hicks,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-the-paper-days-are-over/</guid>
        <description>Take the tube and read a newspaper. Most people there are doing the same, but their number is in rapid decline. Between 2007 and 2009, newspaper circulation dropped by 25% in the UK. Only the US saw a heavier decline. This $50bn business, employing 400,000 people in the US alone, is in trouble. In …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Modern Family – A Family Portrait
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-modern-family-a-family-portrait/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 20:36:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie-Laure Hicks,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-modern-family-a-family-portrait/</guid>
        <description>I have a completely insane family. So when I heard about Modern Family, I didn’t think much of it. The advert on TV just made me cringe. That was until I watched an episode. American comedies can sometimes disappoint, but this show is fantastic. I would venture to say it’s because it has a hint of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Time to deal, innit bruv
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-time-to-deal-innit-bruv/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 21:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie-Laure Hicks,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-time-to-deal-innit-bruv/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to Summerhouse, fam. Here, food (the kind you smoke) is sold on the streets by 10-year olds, snakes (traitors) get stabbed and adults run farms (not the kind that grow fruit and veg). In the shadow of the mighty Canary Wharf, this Hackney estate is the centre of Dushane and Sully’s drug …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Place of the week: Soho Joe
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-place-of-the-week-soho-joe/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 21:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie-Laure Hicks,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-place-of-the-week-soho-joe/</guid>
        <description>Soho Joe is the product of a husband and wife team who both have more than twenty years experience in the catering industry. Open from early morning until late at night, Soho Joe is an exciting new venture situated in the heart of Soho, serving a range of food and drinks at extremely affordable …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Thought the Government were in trouble?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-thought-the-government-were-in-trouble/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 20:22:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie-Laure Hicks,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-thought-the-government-were-in-trouble/</guid>
        <description>After three different Waterstones (ironically, nobody could find the single copy supposedly in stock) and two failed Amazon deliveries, I finally got my hands on the book: “The Thick of It: The Missing DoSAC Files”. Bringing to the paper Armando Iannucci’s BAFTA-winning comedy, this brilliant set of …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
