<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rj408/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rj408/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Freedom to Fornicate
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-freedom-to-fornicate/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 21:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rajat Jain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-freedom-to-fornicate/</guid>
        <description> This week, Felix releases the full results of the much-anticipated sex survey. This typically makes for depressing reading in a university concerned with its high levels of “geekiness” and obsessed with a less than ideal gender ratio. Beyond the statistics and the innuendo, there is, however, a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fresh protests in Senegal
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-fresh-protests-in-senegal/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 19:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rajat Jain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-fresh-protests-in-senegal/</guid>
        <description>Police have been deployed in towns across Senegal, and are reported to have killed two people in the northern town of Podor, as protests intensify. Rallies have been organised after President Abdoulaye Wade declared his intention to stand for a third term.
Senegal has long been seen as a relatively …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Smack your kids up
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-smack-your-kids-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 19:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rajat Jain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-smack-your-kids-up/</guid>
        <description>MP David Lammy has blamed anti-smacking laws for the lack of discipline that led to riots in London last summer.
Mr Lammy is the MP for the North London constituency of Tottenham, where the riots originated and some of the worst violence was experienced. He became a regular on our screens for his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Recent elections and scandals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-recent-elections-and-scandals/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 21:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rajat Jain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-recent-elections-and-scandals/</guid>
        <description>Russian Election
 The number in brackets shows the number of seats – 226 is a majority   The number in brackets shows the number of seats – 226 is a majority   Vladimir Putin’s party looks set to lose its two thirds majority in the 450 seat State Duma, Russia’s lower house. The two thirds of seats …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Palestinian students visit Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-palestinian-students-visit-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 20:28:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rajat Jain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-palestinian-students-visit-imperial/</guid>
        <description>On Tuesday, Imperial was visited by a group of six Palestinian university students spending eleven days in London as part of a cultural exchange. Felix took the opportunity to speak to them.
In particular, I spoke to Haifa Ansari, a final year law student and Zacharia Zanoon, a second year dentistry …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Long live a Queen
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-long-live-a-queen/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 20:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rajat Jain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-long-live-a-queen/</guid>
        <description>A couple of weeks ago, at the Commonwealth summit in Perth, the sixteen leaders of countries where Elizabeth II is head of state unanimously agreed to change the succession laws to give women equal priority as men. This means should the Duke and Duchess of Cambridge (aka Wills and Kate) have a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>News from the outside world
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-news-from-the-outside-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 20:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rajat Jain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-news-from-the-outside-world/</guid>
        <description>More resignations in the Eurozone
The socialist Prime Minister of Greece, George Papandreou, finally made a deal with opposition conservatives for a unity government and acceptance of the European bailout deal, in exchange for him standing down. His previous decision to call a referendum on the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Conservatives in Europe
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-the-conservatives-in-europe/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 20:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rajat Jain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-the-conservatives-in-europe/</guid>
        <description>Last week was a particularly brutal one for David Cameron and his policy on Europe. First the French president Nicholas Sarkozy told him to “shut up” over unhelpful criticisms over the Euro. To make matters worse, on his return, Mr Cameron faced an 81 member backbench rebellion over a proposed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Poles at the Polls
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-14-poles-at-the-polls/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 10:24:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Piotr Faba,Rajat Jain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-14-poles-at-the-polls/</guid>
        <description>A radical libertarian party could hold the key to power in Poland after Sunday, when the EU’s sixth largest economy and only country to not contract in 2009 held parliamentary elections. Unsurprisingly, the incumbent centrist PM came out on top; Donald Tusk’s Civic Platform won 39.2% – a slight …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Politics of Summer 2011
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-the-politics-of-summer-2011/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 20:14:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rajat Jain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-the-politics-of-summer-2011/</guid>
        <description>With Felix Politics on holiday for the summer, you’re probably worried that you’ll either have to read a proper political paper for the next three months (really very dull) or become completely ignorant of the world around you. Fear not! Below are the only important headlines that may, or may not, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Obama’s muddled foreign policy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-obamas-muddled-foreign-policy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 20:09:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rajat Jain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-obamas-muddled-foreign-policy/</guid>
        <description>Last week a UN resolution tabled by Lebanon, condemning Israel’s settlements as illegal, was vetoed by the United States. This came despite overwhelming support for the resolution from most of the international community, including the other fourteen Security Council members – even the United …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Arab world shakes, the West shifts nervously
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-the-arab-world-shakes-the-west-shifts-nervously/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 20:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rajat Jain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-the-arab-world-shakes-the-west-shifts-nervously/</guid>
        <description>The suicide of a young Tunisian salesman last month could well change the world’s political scene. In much the same way that Paris sneezed and Europe caught a cold, which lead to (admittedly slow) liberal reform in the nineteenth century, Mass political protest in Tunisia has triggered popular …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Year’s Resolutions
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-new-years-resolutions/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 20:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,Rajat Jain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-new-years-resolutions/</guid>
        <description>Silvio Berlusconi
Well 2010 certainly has been an interesting year for the Italian Prime Minister. Barely surviving several votes of no confidence throughout the year and having his coalition partner Gianfranco Fini and four other coalition government members step down has done a terrible number on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Peace in Korea
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-peace-in-korea/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 18:43:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rajat Jain,Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-peace-in-korea/</guid>
        <description>It is clear that North Korea is in a dire state in humanitarian and political terms. On the 60th anniversary of the start of the Korean War and 10th anniversary of opening diplomatic relations with the United Kingdom, from the outside it seems things have only gotten worse and this trend can only …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It could be worse; we could be in France
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-it-could-be-worse-we-could-be-in-france/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 19:19:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rajat Jain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-it-could-be-worse-we-could-be-in-france/</guid>
        <description>Britain’s first coalition government since the Second World War seems to be splitting at the seams as it unveils a budget to deal with the worst deficit caused by the worst recession in Britain since the Second World War. This has already caused a twenty four hour tube strike and backbench anger …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welfare for all?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-welfare-for-all/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 19:06:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rajat Jain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-welfare-for-all/</guid>
        <description>The middle classes throughout the developed world complain of faring worst from their governments’ budgets. They are, by definition, hard-working and economically productive. They face taxes as high as the wealthiest in their society, but find this reduces their ability to pay for relatively basic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>There’s a desperate need for extra money for universities
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-theres-a-desperate-need-for-extra-money-for-universities/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 19:21:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rajat Jain,Navid Nabijou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-theres-a-desperate-need-for-extra-money-for-universities/</guid>
        <description>University funding reform has been a long time coming; the principle of free education for all, long a mainstay of British political thought, had to be abandoned in 1998 following a review by Lord Dearing. Public funding had for many years failed to keep pace with increasing student numbers: between …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lib Dems in trouble over higher fees
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-lib-dems-in-trouble-over-higher-fees/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 19:20:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rajat Jain,Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-lib-dems-in-trouble-over-higher-fees/</guid>
        <description>The last few months have not been good for the Liberal Democrats. With poll ratings plummeting from 23 to 14% since joining the coalition, the reality of power for the first time in over a century is quickly turning into a nightmare. Low party morale and a new (but not, he stresses, New) Labour …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
