<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ed812/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ed812/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Birth, death, and the messiness in between
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-birth-death-and-the-messiness-in-between/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 09:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emiel de Lange,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-birth-death-and-the-messiness-in-between/</guid>
        <description>Where words leave off, music begins”, said the poet Heinrich Heine. Morgen und Abend, a new opera by Austrian composer Georg Friedrich Haas, attempts to go where words cannot and follows a man, Johannes, into existence and beyond into death. Although death (together with love) is one of those …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All That Fall: A Light Show Hiding Real Substance
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-16-all-that-fall-a-light-show-hiding-real-substance/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2015 18:55:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emiel de Lange,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-16-all-that-fall-a-light-show-hiding-real-substance/</guid>
        <description>We enter a dark room scattered with rocking chairs. The far wall is covered by an array of bright yellow lights, emanating heat and an irritating electrical buzz, while dimly lit bulbs hang from the ceiling. Taking our seats on the cushioned wood, I can see the looks of anticipation and curiosity on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pli selon pli: unravelling genius with the Ensemble Intercontemporain
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-8-pli-selon-pli-unravelling-genius-with-the-ensemble-intercontemporain/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 12:53:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emiel de Lange,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-8-pli-selon-pli-unravelling-genius-with-the-ensemble-intercontemporain/</guid>
        <description>The Barbican brought their ‘Boulez at 90’ celebrations to an end last week with a tribute from the composer’s own ensemble, the Ensemble Intercontemporain.
This was a rare chance for Londoners to hear cutting edge music from one of the world’s best contemporary music groups and a fitting tribute to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pli selon pli: Unravelling the Genius of the Contemporary with the Ensemble Intercontemporain
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-6-pli-selon-pli-unravelling-the-genius-of-the-contemporary-with-the-ensemble-intercontemporain/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 12:36:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emiel de Lange,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-6-pli-selon-pli-unravelling-the-genius-of-the-contemporary-with-the-ensemble-intercontemporain/</guid>
        <description>The Barbican brought their Boulez at 90 celebrations to an end last week with a tribute from the composer’s own ensemble, the Ensemble Intercontemporain. This was a rare chance for Londoners to hear cutting edge music from one of the world’s best contemporary music groups and a fitting tribute to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Boulez at 90: The Enfant Terrible of Modern Music
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-4-boulez-at-90-the-enfant-terrible-of-modern-music/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 16:22:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emiel de Lange,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-4-boulez-at-90-the-enfant-terrible-of-modern-music/</guid>
        <description>Pierre Boulez is _the _controversial figure at the forefront of musical development in the 20th Century. Though equally respected by his enemies as by his supporters, a certain stubbornness and radicalism has alienated many. For instance, in 1952 he declared in one fell swoop half of the musical …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Boulez at 90: The Enfant Terrible of Modern Music
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-4-5-boulez-at-90-the-enfant-terrible-of-modern-music/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2015 13:00:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emiel de Lange,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-4-5-boulez-at-90-the-enfant-terrible-of-modern-music/</guid>
        <description>Pierre Boulez is the controversial figure at the forefront of musical development in the 20th Century. Though equally respected by his enemies as by his supporters, a certain stubbornness and radicalism has alienated many. For instance, in 1952 he declared in one fell swoop half of the musical world …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Man and Superman: Comedy and Philosophy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-man-and-superman-comedy-and-philosophy/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 13:19:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emiel de Lange,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-man-and-superman-comedy-and-philosophy/</guid>
        <description>Man and Superman is at once both funny and serious. Billed as a “comedy and a philosophy”, this dual nature has posed problems in the past and at first Bernard Shaw staged these parts separately.
This season, the National Theatre presents the complete work, and, at almost four hours long it is quite …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why I&#39;m voting for Issie Barrett for Deputy President (Clubs and Societies)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-4-why-im-voting-for-issie-barrett-for-deputy-president-clubs-and-societies/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2015 13:58:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emiel de Lange,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-4-why-im-voting-for-issie-barrett-for-deputy-president-clubs-and-societies/</guid>
        <description>Clubs and societies needs someone who cares about them, and no one cares more than Issie. Clubs are where people make friends, try new things and do the things they love, and without them university life would be much poorer.
I spoke with Issie about her plans and hopes for Imperial clubs over lunch …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Mastersingers of Nuremburg – spectacular in every way
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-17-the-mastersingers-of-nuremburg-spectacular-in-every-way/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2015 16:34:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emiel de Lange,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-17-the-mastersingers-of-nuremburg-spectacular-in-every-way/</guid>
        <description>Hyperbole has never been my enemy, and I won’t shy from it now; Wagner’s The Mastersingers of Nuremberg is one of the pinnacles of Western art. But works of such scope and breadth of vision are notoriously difficult, and expensive, to perform. Opera houses must offer enlarged orchestras, vast crowds …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>MTSoc are The Producers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-19-mtsoc-are-the-producers/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2014 01:22:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emiel de Lange,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-19-mtsoc-are-the-producers/</guid>
        <description>This Tuesday, Imperial’s Musical Theatre society invited me to witness one of their final rehearsals – a full run through. And while it was bare bones up on the 10th floor of Physics, I still got to see all the singing, acting and dancing.
The last thing I would describe myself as is a fan of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Emiel’s Guide to Classical Music (Episode 8)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-emiels-guide-to-classical-music-episode-8/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 05:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emiel de Lange,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-emiels-guide-to-classical-music-episode-8/</guid>
        <description>Last week we discussed Josquin, who is often known as the ‘Beethoven of the 16th Century, and in particular his work Ave Maria. For many generations, Josquin was regarded by theorists and other thinkers as the composer who had perfected the art of music. As Martin Luther wrote; “He is the master of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Emiel’s Guide to Classical Music: Episode 7 - Josquin
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-emiels-guide-to-classical-music-episode-7-josquin/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 03:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emiel de Lange,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-emiels-guide-to-classical-music-episode-7-josquin/</guid>
        <description>Josquin des Prez, or Josquin for short, was an artist of mythical proportions. This was partly due to his massive talent, but also partly a result of the changing humanist culture. At the start of his career music was still grouped with geometry and arithmetic in the Quadrivium of taught subjects – …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Turandot: finished but flawed
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-turandot-finished-but-flawed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 03:18:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emiel de Lange,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-turandot-finished-but-flawed/</guid>
        <description>What: Turandot
Where: Royal Opera House, WC2
When: until 10th March
Price: Various
Puccini’s _Turandot _was “the end of the great tradition” of Italian opera. Ever popular, it is the grandest of them all, and yet it is deeply problematic. Set in a mythical China, at its simplest the tale concerns a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Corruption of a convent girl
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-corruption-of-a-convent-girl/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 09:49:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emiel de Lange,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-corruption-of-a-convent-girl/</guid>
        <description>What: Manon
Where: Royal Opera House, WC1
When: Until 6th February
Price: Various
Manon premiered in 1884, at the height of the Belle Époque. French imperialism was at its peak, and a spirit of optimism flowed on the streets of wealthy Paris. Twenty years earlier, Richard Wagner had brought his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>World class opera in our backyard
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-world-class-opera-in-our-backyard/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 04:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emiel de Lange,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-world-class-opera-in-our-backyard/</guid>
        <description>What: Ravel Double Bill – L’heure Espagnole &amp;amp; L’enfant et les Sortilèges Where: Royal College of Music, Britten Theatre, SW6 When: 6th and 7th Dec, 7.30pm
Price: £10, £20, £30, £40
Our prestigious neighbour, the Royal College of Music, is a fortress tucked away behind our own Sherfield building. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A true modern masterpiece
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-a-true-modern-masterpiece/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 22:07:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emiel de Lange,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-a-true-modern-masterpiece/</guid>
        <description>What: Satyagraha, with the English National Opera Where: London Coliseum, WC2 When: Until 8th Dec 2013 Price: various
Satyagraha has been lauded as a masterpiece of modern opera since its premiere in 1980. After witnessing it for myself, I can’t help but agree. This is not a conventional opera in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Emiel’s Guide to Classical Music: Episode 3
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-emiels-guide-to-classical-music-episode-3/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 18:10:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emiel de Lange,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-emiels-guide-to-classical-music-episode-3/</guid>
        <description> Ask someone to name a ‘Classical’ composer and they’ll reply with Bach, Mozart or Beethoven. The music we’ve discussed so far is, I’ll admit, a little bit ‘niche’; rarely performed in the concert hall, and probably the reserve of a special group of early music enthusiasts. Still, I’m going to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Magic Flute needs a fairy godmother
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-the-magic-flute-needs-a-fairy-godmother/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 02:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emiel de Lange,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-the-magic-flute-needs-a-fairy-godmother/</guid>
        <description>What: The Magic Flute with English National Opera Where: London Coliseum, WC2 When: Until 7 Dec 2013 Price: Various
In this fairy tale, Prince Tamino is sent to rescue his love Pamina, daughter of the Queen of the Night. When he finds and frees her, he discovers that her captor, Sarastro, is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Emiel’s Guide to Classical Music (Episode 2)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-emiels-guide-to-classical-music-episode-2/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 09:38:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emiel de Lange,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-emiels-guide-to-classical-music-episode-2/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the first real instalment of my guide to Classical Music! I hope to start introducing the great composers and some of the masterpieces which address the issues raised in my column last week, but I feel it’s necessary to describe the historical and theoretical context from which “classical …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Emiel’s Guide to Classical Music (Part I)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-emiels-guide-to-classical-music-part-i/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 00:40:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emiel de Lange,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-emiels-guide-to-classical-music-part-i/</guid>
        <description>The definition of Art is an issue that philosophers have struggled with for millennia. In the 19th Century two greats gave fundamentally opposing views. Arthur Schopenhauer, who thought the world around us a mere representation of reality, believed Art could reveal its true nature. He argued that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Die Fledermaus goes batty
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-18-die-fledermaus-goes-batty/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 21:59:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emiel de Lange,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-18-die-fledermaus-goes-batty/</guid>
        <description>What: Die Fledermaus with the English National Opera Where: London Coliseum When: Until 6th Nov 2013 Price: Various
Die Fledermaus, the Bat, is an operetta by the king of the Viennese waltz, Johann Strauss Jr. Operetta, the ancestor of today’s musicals, is an entirely different affair from opera. …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
