<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ec2212/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ec2212/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>We really need to talk about eating disorders
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-we-really-need-to-talk-about-eating-disorders/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 14:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily-Jane Cramphorn,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-we-really-need-to-talk-about-eating-disorders/</guid>
        <description>The past week on campus has been a busy one, what with the 2017 leadership elections, ‘show season’ at the union concert hall, and of course Varsity going on. But the past week has also seen activists across the nation trying to create change for people who are impacted by eating disorders. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Society has an eating disorder
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-society-has-an-eating-disorder/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 15:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily-Jane Cramphorn,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-society-has-an-eating-disorder/</guid>
        <description>Society has an eating disorder. Sweeping statement, I know, but take a second to look at the posters next time you get on the tube. Diets, cookbooks, meal replacement shakes, protein bars, detox teas and pretty much anything you can think of claiming to be the answer to your weight problems. Weight …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don&#39;t let the Monday blues get to you
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-dont-let-the-monday-blues-get-to-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:03:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily-Jane Cramphorn,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-dont-let-the-monday-blues-get-to-you/</guid>
        <description>Have you been feeling down this week? Allegedly there is an explanation for this – some claim it is the most depressing week of the year. More specifically, the Monday that just passed has been christened &amp;lsquo;Blue Monday&amp;rsquo; as a result of post-holiday reality kicking in and everyone generally …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Free the Nipple and me
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-28-free-the-nipple-and-me/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 14:53:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily-Jane Cramphorn,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-28-free-the-nipple-and-me/</guid>
        <description>You may have noticed that this week, the centrefold is a bit different. There are uncensored female nipples in it, and one pair belongs to me. Before you skip ahead (if you haven’t already done so) take a moment to read why this centrefold should not be viewed differently to nipple-free centrefolds …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Life after anorexia: IBS
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-life-after-anorexia-ibs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 12:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily-Jane Cramphorn,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-life-after-anorexia-ibs/</guid>
        <description>People often speak about the risks of anorexia and bulimia – how they can kill you, make your bones brittle and your hair fall out.
However, I want to talk about one very overlooked side effect, Irritable Bowel Syndrome (IBS). For many years I have starved and punished my body. I have abused …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reflecting on Mentality
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-reflecting-on-mentality/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 12:51:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily-Jane Cramphorn,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-reflecting-on-mentality/</guid>
        <description>After a successful campaign last academic year, Mentality has succeeded once again in capturing the interests of the staff and student body alike. On the 19th January 2016, Sir Anthony Seldon ‘headlined’ at Mentality’s most recent event, giving an honest and humbling talk about his personal …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
