<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rm1509/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rm1509/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>A bumper Bard evening
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-a-bumper-bard-evening/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 23:49:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Roxanne Middleton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-a-bumper-bard-evening/</guid>
        <description>Maybe you’ve had your fair share of proper Shakespeare, maybe you’ve already seen more than you want to, maybe you just like the idea of efficiency in getting through all of Shakespeare’s work in two hours. Well, you might just find this show appealing. A fun romp through famous plays and their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New generation South Africa
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-new-generation-south-africa/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 05:45:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Roxanne Middleton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-new-generation-south-africa/</guid>
        <description>The exhibition does not hold back, photos are large enough to step well away from, and with seventeen different photographers there is plenty there to see. As well as the familiar dignified portrait style are some real surprises. Amongst them Pieter Hugo’s astonishingly powerful picture of a man …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We Will Rock You
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-we-will-rock-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 19:11:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Roxanne Middleton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-we-will-rock-you/</guid>
        <description>When a cast is given the name of the musical they will perform 24 hours before curtain-up, no-one should expect anything particularly special. When that cast is from the glorious Musical Theatre Society, the tables are turned. This rendition of ‘We Will Rock You’ was absolutely phenomenal. With a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wreckage
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-wreckage/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 19:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Roxanne Middleton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-wreckage/</guid>
        <description>The grand opening of the exhibition in the Blyth Gallery at 6pm on Wednesday is open to everyone. There’ll be free wine, nibbles and a chance to meet the talented artists and talk to them about the works. The theme ‘Wreckage’ is explored through five large scale installations which have been put …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The clothes you’re not supposed to wear
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-the-clothes-youre-not-supposed-to-wear/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 19:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Roxanne Middleton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-the-clothes-youre-not-supposed-to-wear/</guid>
        <description>High fashion is not like anything you know or have seen in normal society. What is its link to the fashion worn by the ordinary clothes-wearing public? I have no idea. Images of beautiful women made bizarre by face paint and freakish garments as they strut down the catwalk (which may or may not be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Talent, Class of ‘10
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-imperial-talent-class-of-10/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2010 20:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Roxanne Middleton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-imperial-talent-class-of-10/</guid>
        <description>Do you all want to start by telling us a bit about what your plays are like?
Gilead: Let’s see, mine is a musical revue in the traditional sense of a revue, lots of catchy tunes with different words put to them, largely based on all the anecdotes I’ve picked up over my three years here. It sends up …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Interesting reflections in Hyde Park
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-8-interesting-reflections-in-hyde-park/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 07:02:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Roxanne Middleton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-8-interesting-reflections-in-hyde-park/</guid>
        <description>Hyde Park is being turned upside down by Anish Kapoor’s latest exibition. Four new sculptures have been put up in Kensington Gardens in Hyde Park for the next six months, with round-the-clock security guards to protect them against people and their grubby fingerprints. The exibition is being put on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Bluffer&#39;s Guide to being cultured
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-1-the-bluffers-guide-to-being-cultured/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 21:17:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Roxanne Middleton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-1-the-bluffers-guide-to-being-cultured/</guid>
        <description>1: Confidence
First things first, believe in yourself! I am at heart a populist. Discussions about obscure 18th century Abyssinian art movements can be left to know-it-all art students. but whether the art itself is interesting/beautiful/cool is free territory. You have the right to an opinion and …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
