<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ap1509/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ap1509/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Global cooling?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-global-cooling/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 20:04:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrew Purcell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-global-cooling/</guid>
        <description>The last week has seen a flurry of excitement over reports that solar activity may be set to decrease. Climate change deniers have sprung upon this news, with prominent Daily Telegraph blogger, James Delingpole, advocating that we increase greenhouse gas production, in order to mitigate any cooling …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Breathing life into spaceplane technology
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-breathing-life-into-spaceplane-technology/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 19:23:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrew Purcell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-breathing-life-into-spaceplane-technology/</guid>
        <description>The dream of spaceplanes has often been dismissed as fantasy, born out of bad 1950s science fiction films. According to most industry analysts, the rightful place of the spaceplane – along with food pills, floating cities and personal jetpacks – is consigned to the dustbin of history.
However, one …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Space Shuttle retires
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-the-space-shuttle-retires/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 19:42:24 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrew Purcell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-the-space-shuttle-retires/</guid>
        <description>After being delayed for over two weeks, on the 16th May the Space Shuttle Endeavour is set to blast off into space for the final time. Following this mission, NASA plans to send only one more shuttle into orbit. It will then retire its ageing shuttle fleet after a total of 135 spaceflights.
For …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Urban Ecology
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-18-urban-ecology/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 06:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrew Purcell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-18-urban-ecology/</guid>
        <description>Over half of the world’s 6.9 billion people now live in urban areas. So, perhaps it’s time for us to embrace the ecology of our urban areas, look at the species that thrive in these environments and take steps to protect them. At the same time, we must ensure that our urban environments do not …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Catch I, Science on the 11th March
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-catch-i-science-on-the-11th-march/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 20:55:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrew Purcell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-catch-i-science-on-the-11th-march/</guid>
        <description>J.B.S. Haldane famously remarked: &amp;ldquo;the universe is not only queerer than we suppose, but queerer than we can suppose&amp;rdquo;. As a geneticist and evolutionary biologist, Haldane believed that there are definite limits to human comprehension. He based this belief on the fact that our …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Optimism among the trouble in Tunisia
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-optimism-among-the-trouble-in-tunisia/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 20:37:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrew Purcell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-optimism-among-the-trouble-in-tunisia/</guid>
        <description>Until last week, Tunisia, normally considered one of the more politically stable North African states, had had only had two presidents since gaining independence from France in 1956. Now, following weeks of street protests and civil unrest, President Zine al-Abidine Ben Ali’s 23-year reign has come …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial’s Dr Dexter comes under fire for ‘degrading’ exhibition
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-imperials-dr-dexter-comes-under-fire-for-degrading-exhibition/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 19:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrew Purcell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-imperials-dr-dexter-comes-under-fire-for-degrading-exhibition/</guid>
        <description>A London art gallery’s display of a brain removed from the dead body of a multiple sclerosis sufferer has been attacked by Tory MP David Amess, who has branded the display as “disrespectful and unacceptable”.
Mr Amess, a Roman Catholic and former member of the health select committee, said “it’s one …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Defend our geeks
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-defend-our-geeks/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 19:33:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrew Purcell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-defend-our-geeks/</guid>
        <description>Is science vital? Imperial students most certainly think so.
Last Saturday over 2,000 scientists and supporters, with a large contingent from Imperial College, took to the streets outside Whitehall to protest against proposed cuts to the UK science research budget.
The event was the brainchild of Dr …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
