<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mc4509/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mc4509/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Review: Django Unchained
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-16-review-django-unchained/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2012 15:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-16-review-django-unchained/</guid>
        <description>Smashing two concepts together is a curious business - about as curious as the length of time that it takes to travel between Knightsbridge and South Kensington on the Piccadilly Line. But who else to turn to than Quentin Tarantino? With his latest feature film Django Unchained, he has delivered a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>£150 million partnership for Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-150-million-partnership-for-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 22:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-150-million-partnership-for-imperial/</guid>
        <description>A £150 million partnership aiming to support the development of the new Hammersmith-based Imperial West Technology Campus has been announced.
David Willetts, Minister for Universities and Science, revealed the £150 million partnership between Imperial and property company Voreda, alongside six other …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Constitution troubles at Council
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-15-constitution-troubles-at-council/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 07:32:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-15-constitution-troubles-at-council/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Union President Scott Heath found himself at loggerheads with Union Court (a committee designed to ensure that Union officers follow the rules of the Union) on Monday at the last session of Union Council of the academic year.
Following proposed changes to the Union Constitution …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Low turnout for General Meeting
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-8-low-turnout-for-general-meeting/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2012 08:35:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-8-low-turnout-for-general-meeting/</guid>
        <description>The Imperial College Union General Meeting was held on Wednesday 6 June, with several ideas proposed that could see the structure of the Union considerably change.
To make the meeting quorate (or for the attendees to have the ability to put proposed ideas into action) 200 eligible members were …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Blackboard Learn set for Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-8-blackboard-learn-set-for-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2012 08:32:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-8-blackboard-learn-set-for-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College’s virtual learning environment (VLE) is set to undergo an overhaul in time for next September, following a two year process to determine a successor for the College’s current VLE.
The new system, known as Blackboard Learn, was decided upon by a working group established in order to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial graduates jump at chance to help at London 2012
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-1-imperial-graduates-jump-at-chance-to-help-at-london-2012/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2012 12:11:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-1-imperial-graduates-jump-at-chance-to-help-at-london-2012/</guid>
        <description>As excitement mounts for this year’s sporting summer, and as career opportunities become ever more uncertain given the unsteady financial climate, a group of Imperial graduates have been given the best of both worlds, with the chance to work at the London 2012 Olympics this summer as part of a one …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>£73 million biomedical centre opened
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-1-73-million-biomedical-centre-opened/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2012 11:59:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-1-73-million-biomedical-centre-opened/</guid>
        <description>A new research facility built with the aim of channelling scientific discoveries into the prevention and treatment of diseases was opened on Monday 28 May on Hammersmith Campus.
The £73m six-floor, biomedical research focused Imperial Centre for Translational and Experimental Medicine (ICTEM) has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Sexism Survey
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-24-felix-sexism-survey/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 23:40:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie-Laure Hicks,Silvia Araguas Rodriguez,Philip Kent,Jonathan Kim,Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-24-felix-sexism-survey/</guid>
        <description>Over the past year, 10 articles and 231 comments have been written about sexism in science and at Imperial. Stephen Smith’s “Sexism at Imperial College” has been viewed over 7,500 times on the Felix website. Sexism is clearly an issue that concerns the Imperial community and 631 of you gave us your …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lecture podcasting to become reality
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-24-lecture-podcasting-to-become-reality/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 22:50:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-24-lecture-podcasting-to-become-reality/</guid>
        <description>Plans to record lectures are set to finally come to fruition next academic year. College is set to work with video capture platform Panopto in order to ensure that lectures are made more accessible to students.
The collaboration will result in live lecture streaming, the opportunity to view previous …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial falls in university ranking
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-24-imperial-falls-in-university-ranking/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 22:44:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-24-imperial-falls-in-university-ranking/</guid>
        <description>Imperial has dropped from 10th to 13th place in the Guardian University Guide 2013, the results of which were published on Monday 21 May. The guide, which ranks universities across the United Kingdom, saw institutions ranked across various areas, including results from the National Student Survey, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Now this is the story all about how Will Smith was at Ethos
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-now-this-is-the-story-all-about-how-will-smith-was-at-ethos/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 06:07:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-now-this-is-the-story-all-about-how-will-smith-was-at-ethos/</guid>
        <description>Hollywood big-hitter and modern day renaissance man Will Smith was to be found at Imperial’s very own Ethos Sports Centre on Princes Gardens last Wednesday morning.
Smith was visiting the centre as part of a promotional tour for the upcoming film Men in Black III, but managed to eschew the usual …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hall senior prospects in doubt
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-hall-senior-prospects-in-doubt/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 05:56:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-hall-senior-prospects-in-doubt/</guid>
        <description>Hall seniors at Wilson House have been left questioning the future of their traditionally guaranteed accommodation.
As reported last week, it emerged that Wilson House had been removed from Imperial’s accommodation website for prospective students ahead of a refurbishment next academic year, with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wilson House not listed on accommodation website
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-wilson-house-not-listed-on-accommodation-website/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 19:17:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-wilson-house-not-listed-on-accommodation-website/</guid>
        <description>Wilson House has been removed from Imperial College’s accommodation website for prospective students. In February, it was reported in Felix that the hall could potentially be closed for refurbishment for the 2012-2013 academic year.
A new hall of residence, named ‘Xenia’ has appeared on the website. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pub to remain on Level 0
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-pub-to-remain-on-level-0/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 19:10:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-pub-to-remain-on-level-0/</guid>
        <description>Following a meeting of the Management Board on 20 April, an agreement has been reached over the proposed development of the space currently occupied by the Holland Club on Level 0 of Sherfield.
The space will continue to provide a “pub facility”, which will be open to staff, postgraduate research …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union election results (finally) announced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-4-union-election-results-finally-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2012 01:26:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-4-union-election-results-finally-announced/</guid>
        <description>The results for this year’s Union ‘Big Elections’ were announced over a staggered period this year . The elections, which saw a record turnout of 41.09% of students, also saw a technical issue that and disagreements between candidates over campaigning that ultimately led to a delay of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial TEDx talks prove popular online
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-4-imperial-tedx-talks-prove-popular-online/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2012 00:52:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-4-imperial-tedx-talks-prove-popular-online/</guid>
        <description>Video footage of March’s TEDxImperialCollege event is now available to view on YouTube, with a talk by programmer John Graham-Cumming about Charles Babbage’s Analytical Machine enjoying over 18,000 views at the time of going to print.
TEDx is a program of local and self-organised events based upon …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Russell Group extends its reach to four more institutions
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-16-russell-group-extends-its-reach-to-four-more-institutions/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2012 01:54:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-16-russell-group-extends-its-reach-to-four-more-institutions/</guid>
        <description>The Russell Group has agreed to extend its membership to four more universities. Durham, Exeter, Queen Mary and York are the four institutions that will join the traditionally 20-strong association of public research universities, of which Imperial College London is a member.
The Russell Group, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>More Summer Ball plans outlined
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-16-more-summer-ball-plans-outlined/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2012 01:50:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-16-more-summer-ball-plans-outlined/</guid>
        <description>Tickets are now on sale for this year’s scaled-down Summer Ball, to be held on 23 June. Promising a “transformed South Kensington campus” and marking the return of a black tie formal dinner option, the Union has sought to firmly overview the financial risk of the event in order to avoid a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Election campaigning begins across campus
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-9-election-campaigning-begins-across-campus/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 01:11:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-9-election-campaigning-begins-across-campus/</guid>
        <description>Campaigning for this year’s Union Elections began in earnest on Monday, with candidates for the available positions given the opportunity to show students across Imperial their credentials.
Wednesday saw the second-ever ‘Meet the Candidates’ live televised hustings take place, broadcast by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sabbatical Interviews 2012: Deputy President (Education) – Jason Parmar
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-sabbatical-interviews-2012-deputy-president-education-jason-parmar/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 23:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-sabbatical-interviews-2012-deputy-president-education-jason-parmar/</guid>
        <description>What have you enjoyed most? I’ve enjoyed having an excellent insight into the higher education system. I get to meet representatives from other Russell Group Student Unions at the Aldwych Group where we talk about a whole host of topics. Seeing how other institutions deal with issues, and seeing how …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sabbatical Interviews 2012: Deputy President (Welfare) – Nicolas Massie
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-sabbatical-interviews-2012-deputy-president-welfare-nicolas-massie/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 23:23:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-sabbatical-interviews-2012-deputy-president-welfare-nicolas-massie/</guid>
        <description>What have you enjoyed most? That’s hard to say – it’s been brilliant, it’s been exciting, but most of all I’ve enjoyed seeing actual change for students. Imperial has never had any support for students who aren’t in halls and with a bit of effort I’ve managed to secure funding for them directly from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sabbatical Interviews 2012: Deputy President (Clubs &amp; Societies) – Monya Zard
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-sabbatical-interviews-2012-deputy-president-clubs-societies-monya-zard/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 23:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-sabbatical-interviews-2012-deputy-president-clubs-societies-monya-zard/</guid>
        <description>What have you enjoyed most? Freshers’ Fair! It was a lot of work and was very stressful, but it was definitely the most rewarding experience of the year so far; it was such a huge event and it’s something that you know you have to get right because it’s going to be the new students’ first experience …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sabbatical Interviews 2012: Deputy President (Finance &amp; Services) – Michael Foster
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-sabbatical-interviews-2012-deputy-president-finance-services-michael-foster/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 22:58:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-sabbatical-interviews-2012-deputy-president-finance-services-michael-foster/</guid>
        <description>What have you enjoyed most?
I think it’s working in the Union and being part of a team. It’s a very good atmosphere to work in and it really helps you do your role and also to see that you help other people do theirs as well – everyone’s got something to contribute and build on. Specifically within …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Black tie for Summer Ball
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-black-tie-for-summer-ball/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 22:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-black-tie-for-summer-ball/</guid>
        <description>In a paper brought to Imperial College Union Council last Monday (February 13) Deputy President (Finance &amp;amp; Services) Michael Foster outlined plans for this year’s Summer Ball, which will see the return of black-tie and a formal dinner.
The event, to be held one week later than usual on Saturday …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are 3D films worth it?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-are-3d-films-worth-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 23:11:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-are-3d-films-worth-it/</guid>
        <description>A long time ago, in a multiplex not so far away, Star Wars: Episode I – The Phantom Menace was released to a baying public, hungry for the most hyped film of the millennium. As parents accompanying their children fell asleep and grown adults cried out in horror at their collective childhood being …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Registration opens for TEDx
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-registration-opens-for-tedx/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 22:44:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-registration-opens-for-tedx/</guid>
        <description>Ticket prices for TEDxImperialCollege have been revealed as registration opens today. Tickets for students will be £10, while all others will pay £25. It has also emerged that Google is to be the main sponsor of the event.
The organisers have stressed that registration doesn’t guarantee a ticket. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Holland Club change on the cards
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-holland-club-change-on-the-cards/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 22:43:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-holland-club-change-on-the-cards/</guid>
        <description>Potential plans for a proposed renovation of the Holland Club have been provided as part of the area’s ongoing feasibility study this week. The Holland Club Committee has voiced its disapproval over what it considers to be a lack of communication from those in charge of the study, while Imperial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Holland Club Petition
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-holland-club-petition/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 00:37:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-holland-club-petition/</guid>
        <description>As the results of a feasibility study that will determine the future of the Holland Club still remain to be announced, an e-petition in support of its continuation has received nearly 400 signatories at the time of writing.
The petition letter, addressed to Imperial College, argues against any …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Clayponds in crisis
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-clayponds-in-crisis/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 21:57:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-clayponds-in-crisis/</guid>
        <description>Students have expressed their concern at the planned closure of postgraduate hall of residence Clayponds, with Imperial College Union President Scott Heath expressing his &amp;ldquo;disappointment&amp;rdquo; at an alleged lack of communication between the College and the Union with regards to the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial West masterplan unveiled
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-imperial-west-masterplan-unveiled/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 22:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-imperial-west-masterplan-unveiled/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London has submitted a planning application for the second phase of the development of a new postgraduate campus at Wood Lane, with the project aiming to include the construction of a 34-storey residential tower block.
Imperial purchased the Wood Lane site from the BBC in September …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Horizons initiative to challenge undergraduates
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-imperial-horizons-initiative-to-challenge-undergraduates/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 22:09:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-imperial-horizons-initiative-to-challenge-undergraduates/</guid>
        <description>Imperial has unveiled a new pilot scheme for undergraduates, which aims to challenge students to consider global issues through use of their scientific knowledge.
The new initiative, entitled Imperial Horizons, is being led by the materials physicist Professor Adrian Sutton.
The free programme …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Council Chairman calls on government to reconsider drug policy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-council-chairman-calls-on-government-to-reconsider-drug-policy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 22:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-council-chairman-calls-on-government-to-reconsider-drug-policy/</guid>
        <description>The Council Chairman of Imperial College, Baroness Eliza Manningham-Buller, has called on the government to reconsider its current drugs policy following the ongoing expense of the “War on Drugs”. Speaking at a meeting held by the All Party Parliamentary Group on Drug Policy Reform, the ex-Director …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pembridge Annexe to be demolished
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-pembridge-annexe-to-be-demolished/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 20:19:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-pembridge-annexe-to-be-demolished/</guid>
        <description>Plans to demolish a disused annexe from behindPembridge Gardens hall of residence in favour of a residential development have been clarified by the College Fund.
Pembridge Gardens, located in Notting Hill, has been operating at approximately 105 bedspaces since 2009, when it handed over its annexe …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why should you go into teaching?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-why-should-you-go-into-teaching/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 19:48:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,Matthew N Colvin,Navid Nabijou,Deepka Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-why-should-you-go-into-teaching/</guid>
        <description>Can you think of any reason why an Imperial student might want to become a teacher?” “They got a third class, maybe?” This response from a second year mathematician may well sum up the opinions of some Imperial students, and indeed a section of society’s wider opinion of the profession. We’ve all …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Club chairs lukewarm over bar nights
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-club-chairs-lukewarm-over-bar-nights/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 19:30:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-club-chairs-lukewarm-over-bar-nights/</guid>
        <description>Members of the Arts and Entertainments Board (AEB) voiced overwhelming discontent with the Union’s new rules on holding bar nights for clubs and societies.
Under new rules set out by Deputy President (Finance &amp;amp; Services) (DPFS) Michael Foster, clubs are no longer allowed to purchase kegs from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Interview: Eliza Manningham-Buller
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-interview-eliza-manningham-buller/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 21:24:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-interview-eliza-manningham-buller/</guid>
        <description>Late September – it’s the week before the beginning of a new academic year. As a new intake of students prepare to acclimatise to their new surroundings, a more experienced senior member of staff is also preparing for the hardships of the year ahead, as one should expect from someone in charge of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union Council kicks off year with Bar Night questions
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-union-council-kicks-off-year-with-bar-night-questions/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 20:22:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-union-council-kicks-off-year-with-bar-night-questions/</guid>
        <description>Monday 10 October saw the first Imperial College Union Council meeting of the academic year. Held in the Union Dining Hall and open to all students, the meeting saw this year’s sabbatical officers provide updates of their progress over the summer, presided over by this year’s Council Chair, David …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Silfest surpasses charity target
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-6-silfest-surpasses-charity-target/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 23:26:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-6-silfest-surpasses-charity-target/</guid>
        <description>Saturday 16 July saw Imperial’s Silwood Park campus in Berkshire play host to this year’s Silfest, with the annual independent music festival raising enough money to buy two cows.
Silfest, or the Silwood Festival was first held in 1999 and has since become an entirely student-run event. This year’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Summer Ball suffers £100,000 loss
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-7-15-summer-ball-suffers-100000-loss/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2011 16:49:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-7-15-summer-ball-suffers-100000-loss/</guid>
        <description>Management accounts from Imperial College Union show that this year’s Summer Ball made an estimated loss of £100,000.
The accounts, which cover the period from April to June 2011, show that the event made an overall loss of £122,123. Taking into consideration a donation of £20,000 from the College, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial announces increased bursaries
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-7-12-imperial-announces-increased-bursaries/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2011 15:14:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-7-12-imperial-announces-increased-bursaries/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London has today unveiled a new bursary package for UK students due to be affected by the planned rise in tuition fees.
The new package will provide a substantial increase of £2,500 towards the College’s maximum bursary, which currently stands at £3,500. This financial aid of up to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union supports journal subscriptions campaign
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-union-supports-journal-subscriptions-campaign/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 19:19:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-union-supports-journal-subscriptions-campaign/</guid>
        <description>The Union has publicly condemned the behavior of large academic journal publishing companies, claiming that their services are detrimental not only to Imperial, but to the Higher Education sector in general.
Currently, about 50% of Imperial College Library’s budget is spent on journals, which are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Council denies Deputy President (Finances &amp; Services) Honorary Life Membership
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-council-denies-deputy-president-finances-services-honorary-life-membership/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 18:54:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-council-denies-deputy-president-finances-services-honorary-life-membership/</guid>
        <description>The decision of Union Council on Monday to award Honorary Life Membership (HLM) of the Union to only five of six Sabbatical Officers, excluding Deputy President (Finance &amp;amp; Services) Ravi Pall, was overturned at a meeting of the Union Court on Wednesday.
The rejection of the Council’s decision …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial professors honoured in Queen&#39;s Birthday Honours List
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-imperial-professors-honoured-in-queens-birthday-honours-list/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 18:52:47 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-imperial-professors-honoured-in-queens-birthday-honours-list/</guid>
        <description>Two Imperial professors have been recognised on the Queen’s Birthday Honours List, which was published last Saturday.
Professor Nigel Brandon, Director of Imperial’s Energy Futures Lab, has been awarded an OBE alongside Professor Elisabeth Paice, Visiting Professor of the Professorial Department of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union awards honour students
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-union-awards-honour-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 18:49:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-union-awards-honour-students/</guid>
        <description>Winners of this year’s Union awards were announced on Monday at the final Union Council meeting of the academic year.
The awards recognise those working across the Union, from clubs and societies to representation, with a belief that ‘those who have gone over and above what is expected of them …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Professor Ian Owens to take up post at Natural History Museum
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-professor-ian-owens-to-take-up-post-at-natural-history-museum/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 21:01:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-professor-ian-owens-to-take-up-post-at-natural-history-museum/</guid>
        <description>Professor Ian Owens, the current head of the Department of Life Sciences, has been announced as the Natural History Museum’s new Director of Science.
In his new role, Professor Owens will be responsible for setting the strategic direction of its scientific activities and taking responsibility for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial joins £600 million medical research centre project
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-imperial-joins-600-million-medical-research-centre-project/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 18:09:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-imperial-joins-600-million-medical-research-centre-project/</guid>
        <description>Imperial and King’s College London are set to become involved in the construction and development of a London-based ‘world-leading’ medical research centre, the Francis Crick Institute.
Currently being built at Somers Town in North London, the institute will bring together researchers from its …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oxford University formally signals rise to £9,000 fees
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-oxford-university-formally-signals-rise-to-9000-fees/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 20:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-oxford-university-formally-signals-rise-to-9000-fees/</guid>
        <description>The University of Oxford has become the fourth institution in the country to officially announce a rise of tuition fees to the maximum figure of £9,000,
Following in the footsteps of Imperial, Cambridge and, most recently, Exeter, Oxford’s move to increase the fees for home and EU students has been …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pain in the career
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-pain-in-the-career/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 20:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-pain-in-the-career/</guid>
        <description>The world’s a pretty scary place at the moment, not least because of the abundance of Danny Dyer films being produced. In these uncertain times, it’s good to have a bit of security, so it’s no surprise that one of the hottest topics at the moment is one which turns even the most studious into …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A View From The Bridge
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-a-view-from-the-bridge/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 18:19:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-a-view-from-the-bridge/</guid>
        <description>Obsession, violence and romance are just some of the simmering tensions that provide a backdrop to DramSoc’s spring production, an adaptation of celebrated American playwright Arthur Miller’s A View From The Bridge.
Set in 1950s New York, the play tells the story of Eddie Carbone, his wife Beatrice …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kendall criticises teaching review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-kendall-criticises-teaching-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 19:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-kendall-criticises-teaching-review/</guid>
        <description>Further details about the ongoing Life Sciences undergraduate teaching review have been provided to students, with Union President Alex Kendall voicing concerns over the review’s relationship to the planned departmental restructure.
An e-mail was sent on Monday, 14th February, to students in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College pulls plug on Union server
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-college-pulls-plug-on-union-server/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 19:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-college-pulls-plug-on-union-server/</guid>
        <description>Senior Union figures were left at odds with College last week when the Union’s server was shut down by ICT security following a complaint made by a member of the public about an article posted on the Rugby Club’s website. The Union reacted angrily issuing a statement calling the shutdown “overblown …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pop star politicians
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-pop-star-politicians/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 19:54:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-pop-star-politicians/</guid>
        <description>Politicians want your vote, and they will do anything to get it. So it has been, so it will always be. But the difference today, in this age of growing individualism, television and internet and is that to sell you whatever you want, whoever you may be, their face needs to be seen. And what does …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College&#39;s Vagina Monologues
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-imperial-colleges-vagina-monologues/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 19:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-imperial-colleges-vagina-monologues/</guid>
        <description>Yikes, despite the title, I didn’t exactly realise that this was going to be exactly what it says on the tin. Eve Ensler’s all female and always controversial The Vagina Monologues saw an adaptation by DramSoc on three nights last week as part of SHAG Week events, and the taboo busting subject …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Falling out of love with tabloids
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-falling-out-of-love-with-tabloids/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 21:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-falling-out-of-love-with-tabloids/</guid>
        <description>The tabloids and I, we’ve had a chequered past to say the least. I grew up on a diet of the Daily Mail, yet it wasn’t until the merits of secondary education that I realised what I was fervently devouring wasn’t exactly all that wholesome. As I began to write more and more, something clicked. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union: Minimum English requirement should rise
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-union-minimum-english-requirement-should-rise/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 20:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-union-minimum-english-requirement-should-rise/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Union has revealed its response to the government’s student visa consultation with a mixed response to the suggested proposals.
As reported last week, the 31st of January saw the end of the consultation period for the review of the United Kingdom’s student immigration system. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cambridge punts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-cambridge-punts/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 20:21:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-cambridge-punts/</guid>
        <description>I was, as usual, fighting a losing battle.
“You see, Cambridge is far, far superior in simply every way, old chum,” said my old schoolmate, on the other, absurdly richer, side of the webcam.
“Consider, if you will, the countless events of vast social importance. Nightly, we dine in the presence of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Major flooding shuts Biochemistry
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-major-flooding-shuts-biochemistry/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 19:37:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-major-flooding-shuts-biochemistry/</guid>
        <description>The Biochemistry building has been hit with two serious floods this past week. A failure of a pipe connection to a rooftop water tank is believed to have caused the flood on Thursday morning while a suspected valve failure, or pump malfunction, caused a 6ft flood of water in the sub-basement during …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Twisted, but is it twisted enough?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-twisted-but-is-it-twisted-enough/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 19:34:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-twisted-but-is-it-twisted-enough/</guid>
        <description>Roald Dahl. Aside from traumatic experiences in chocolate factories and child eating giants, surely that kindly figure looking out from the back of his books was as child friendly as they get? Short answer: he wasn’t. There was another side that many are less aware of, his anthologies of short …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Life Sciences teaching review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-life-sciences-teaching-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 18:06:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-life-sciences-teaching-review/</guid>
        <description>The long-awaited review of teaching in the Department of Life Sciences has finally been opened to staff and student input. The review panel, led by Professors Murray Selkirk and Andy Purvis, aims to submit its recommendations to the Science Studies Committee in late April, after an initial period of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Does Imperial have a drinking problem?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-does-imperial-have-a-drinking-problem/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 21:11:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,Aemun Reza,Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-does-imperial-have-a-drinking-problem/</guid>
        <description>Following the controversial exposure of the drunken antics of Imperial medical students at the Reynolds Bar earlier this month, action has been taken to clamp down on the excessive drinking of “a minority of students”. However, as Felix found this week, many students have shrugged off concerns about …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Outdoor Club accident raises safety fears
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-outdoor-club-accident-raises-safety-fears/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 21:50:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-outdoor-club-accident-raises-safety-fears/</guid>
        <description>A club trip took a turn for the worse last November when a member of the Outdoor Club fell 100ft while climbing in the Lake District. The injured student was winter climbing on the slopes of Helvellyn, the third highest peak in England, with a small group of other Imperial students on the 27th of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College considers 8am start
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-college-considers-8am-start/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 21:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-college-considers-8am-start/</guid>
        <description>In a move sure to raise eyebrows among those who prefer an extra hour (or three) in bed, it has been revealed that a College committee is considering lengthening the academic day in order to ensure that Imperial is able to “accommodate the growing number of master’s courses and extracurricular …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial finally awakens
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-imperial-finally-awakens/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 21:45:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-imperial-finally-awakens/</guid>
        <description>When will Imperial march?’ was the question Felix asked last week. Government cuts to higher education and tuition fees of up to £9,000 had failed to bring out the inner revolutionary in the average Imperial student. What then would it take to inflame passions on campus? The answer arrived with a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The impact on modules and courses
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-the-impact-on-modules-and-courses/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 21:27:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-the-impact-on-modules-and-courses/</guid>
        <description>While the Department of Life Sciences maintain that their courses will retain the current ìdepth and breadthî despite the proposed changes, information has surfaced which claims that the number of staff involved in teaching is to be severely reduced, including those convening certain courses.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tuition fees: Bearable burden or crippling debt?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-tuition-fees-bearable-burden-or-crippling-debt/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 21:57:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Louis Constant,Olivia Ribeiro,Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-tuition-fees-bearable-burden-or-crippling-debt/</guid>
        <description>The latest higher education reforms have not been without significant resistance from many, with one of the key issues being the fear of significant debt following a proposed increase in tuition fees. Current graduates are no strangers to debt, with many owing several thousand pounds following their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Daniel Handler&#39;s The Basic Eight
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-daniel-handlers-the-basic-eight/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 20:18:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-daniel-handlers-the-basic-eight/</guid>
        <description>Probably best known under pseudonym Lemony Snicket, author of the popular &amp;ldquo;Series of Unfortunate Events&amp;rdquo; books, Handler&amp;rsquo;s debut novel delves into the lives of a group of close-knit friends at a San Francisco high school with razor sharp precision.
In a year where they should be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Further blow to Liberal Democrats’ credibility
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-further-blow-to-liberal-democrats-credibility/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 21:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-further-blow-to-liberal-democrats-credibility/</guid>
        <description>Student organizations have expressed outrage after it was recently revealed that a group of senior Liberal Democrat figures planned to surrender their policy on removing tuition fees in the case of a possible coalition government – two months before the general election.
In the document unveiled by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Activists plan Lib Dem HQ occupation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-activists-plan-lib-dem-hq-occupation/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 21:50:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-activists-plan-lib-dem-hq-occupation/</guid>
        <description>The dust has barely settled from the thousands of students who descended on London last week to demonstrate against the planned rise of tuition fees, but plans are already being set in motion across the country for further protests. Wednesday 24th November has been proposed by several anti-cuts …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Double trouble from Daniel Craig in Bond games spectacular
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-double-trouble-from-daniel-craig-in-bond-games-spectacular/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 20:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Gray,James Gollings,Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-double-trouble-from-daniel-craig-in-bond-games-spectacular/</guid>
        <description>007 Blood Stone
He’s blonde, bad and back. No, Boris Johnson hasn’t won a snap mayoral election, but instead Daniel Craig has stepped back into the shoes of James Bond for two (count ‘em) new videogame releases. 007 Blood Stone is an original adventure for the Bond series, not being based on any …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ACC Bar Night brings £1,000 profit
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-acc-bar-night-brings-1000-profit/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 22:10:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-acc-bar-night-brings-1000-profit/</guid>
        <description>The first Athletics Club Committee (ACC) Bar Night of the year took place on Wednesday 3rd November, raising over £1000 for various sporting clubs, with the success being hailed as the beginning of “a new age for the Union”.
A turnout of 600 people helped put the newly opened FiveSixEight bar to the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Uncertainty over PhD teaching income
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-uncertainty-over-phd-teaching-income/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 22:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-uncertainty-over-phd-teaching-income/</guid>
        <description>Senior figures in the Department of Electrical and Electronic Engineering have begun concerted efforts to ensure that postgraduate students understand the circumstances under which they are paid for teaching duties, introducing a potential new measure to reduce the current bursary and have students …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Prof Nutt: alcohol worse than heroin
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-prof-nutt-alcohol-worse-than-heroin/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 19:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-prof-nutt-alcohol-worse-than-heroin/</guid>
        <description>Imperial professor and former government adviser David Nutt has pitted himself against current drugs classification once again by claiming that alcohol is more harmful than various illegal substances in a newly released report.
The study, published in peer-reviewed medical journal The Lancet, was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Institute of Mathematical Sciences&#39; future uncertain
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-institute-of-mathematical-sciences-future-uncertain/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 20:06:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Navid Nabijou,Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-institute-of-mathematical-sciences-future-uncertain/</guid>
        <description>The Institute for Mathematical Sciences (IMS) has been restructured, and will be moved out of its home at 53 Prince’s Gardens into a uncertain future as the Faculty of Natural Sciences &amp;ldquo;rationalises&amp;rdquo; its resources. The previous model has been deemed unsustainable and a new model is being …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Another chronic Sonic failure
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-another-chronic-sonic-failure/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 19:35:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-another-chronic-sonic-failure/</guid>
        <description>Poor Sonic has been having a bit of a rough time recently. Despite Mario and Luigi continuing their Godfather-esque dominance over pretty much any market they lay their eyes upon, their spiky blue hedgehog nemesis has enjoyed some high-profile, big-budget releases. However with a menagerie of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Postgraduate Wood Lane campus approved
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-postgraduate-wood-lane-campus-approved/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 19:32:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-postgraduate-wood-lane-campus-approved/</guid>
        <description>Plans for Imperial College London’s development of a new postgraduate campus at Wood Lane have gained impetus following their approval by Hammersmith &amp;amp; Fulham Council.
The Council’s decision follows the sale of the BBC’s 7.7 acre Woodlands site, previously occupied by BBC Worldwide, in September …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial wins as science is spared major cuts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-imperial-wins-as-science-is-spared-major-cuts/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 19:30:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,Katherine Bettany,Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-imperial-wins-as-science-is-spared-major-cuts/</guid>
        <description>In the controversial Spending Review presented to Parliament on Wednesday, George Osborne revealed the details of the UK’s deepest spending cuts for decades, designed to reduce our budget deficit by £83 billion pounds before 2014&amp;frasl;15.
With Britain paying £120 million a day in debt interest …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Electrical Engineering postgrads demand pay for teaching
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-electrical-engineering-postgrads-demand-pay-for-teaching/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 19:16:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-electrical-engineering-postgrads-demand-pay-for-teaching/</guid>
        <description>The Department of Electrical and Electronic Engineering has been forced to clarify its position regarding the payment of its postgraduate students.
Confusion stemmed from some PhD students claiming that their acceptance letters for the doctoral training scheme did not make clear whether the listed 4 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can we solve a problem like teaching?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-7-can-we-solve-a-problem-like-teaching/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 22:13:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-7-can-we-solve-a-problem-like-teaching/</guid>
        <description>Professor Omar Matar, Director of Undergraduate Studies for Chemical Engineering notes that “members of staff have a finite amount of endurance and certainly the students are in the same sort of boat” in terms of the amount of work that requires feedback. Professor Julia Buckingham, Pro-Rector …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students give damning verdict on teaching standards
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-7-students-give-damning-verdict-on-teaching-standards/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 22:12:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-7-students-give-damning-verdict-on-teaching-standards/</guid>
        <description>The results of the latest National Student Survey have led Imperial College to announce a campaign to improve the assessment of students’ work, with the Rector Sir Keith O&amp;rsquo;Nions becoming personally involved in an attempt to lead a noted improvement across all College departments.
Launched in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Terror assault police officers to join Babar Ahmad in jail?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-7-terror-assault-police-officers-to-join-babar-ahmad-in-jail/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 22:03:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-7-terror-assault-police-officers-to-join-babar-ahmad-in-jail/</guid>
        <description>A group of police officers accused of attacking former employee of Imperial College and terrorist suspect Babar Ahmad appeared in court last month. Police Constables Mark Jones, 43, Roderick James-Bowen, 40, Nigel Cowley, 33, and Detective Constable John Donohue, 36, appeared at City of Westminster …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
