<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/srg109/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/srg109/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Healthy Procrastination
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-healthy-procrastination/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 21:42:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia Goldberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-healthy-procrastination/</guid>
        <description>Dare I say it, but this is the penultimate issue of Felix this term – which means only one thing: exam season is looming. Don’t worry, I’m not saying you need to start revising just yet, the “holidays” (AKA five weeks of cramming) are still a couple of weeks away. Just keep in mind that however hard …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Mini Food Survey
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-the-mini-food-survey/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 02:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia Goldberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-the-mini-food-survey/</guid>
        <description>In light of the Sex Survey, I thought: why not conduct my own Food Survey? It’s not exactly the most highly scientific of surveys (dodges open fire), but answered by Felix food writers and fellow food lovers, maybe the survey will give a new life into the food on campus – or not, in some cases. Most …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sophia Goldberg on the #1 New Year’s resolution
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-sophia-goldberg-on-the-1-new-years-resolution/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 23:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia Goldberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-sophia-goldberg-on-the-1-new-years-resolution/</guid>
        <description>Do you have the same recurring New Year’s resolutions? I’ve heard them all before: stop drinking so much, do a problem sheet, get organised, text/call mum more, text/call gran more, stop texting/calling people so much and see family/friends in person, and personally, stp speakin in txt. The most …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jamie Oliver - Eat your Heart Out
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-jamie-oliver-eat-your-heart-out/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 23:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia Goldberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-jamie-oliver-eat-your-heart-out/</guid>
        <description>My dad gave me Jamie Oliver’s 15 Minute Meals this year. Like the Hairy Dieters (AKA the Hairy Bikers), Jamie believes anyone can cook and eat great, healthy food. However, Jamie claims you can do it in 15 minutes. Given that you’re not superhuman it may take you a little longer – it took me about …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bring Cyprus to London
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-bring-cyprus-to-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 23:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia Goldberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-bring-cyprus-to-london/</guid>
        <description>Last Thursday we, the Food Editors, decided to paint the town red! We hit the “Cyrus Hospitality” event, organised by the Imperial College London Cypriot society.
Yiango invited us along and, being food lovers, it was a great excuse for Carol and I to try something new. Being students we obviously …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Patches of pumpkins
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-patches-of-pumpkins/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 02:54:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia Goldberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-patches-of-pumpkins/</guid>
        <description>For the perfect pumpkin you will need a pumpkin (surprise surprise), a large spoon, a pencil, a and tea light, one small and one large knife, plus lots of newspaper. If you plan on carving multiple pumpkins it’s best to do it outside. If you’re cutting them inside, be sure to cover the table …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Balans-ed meal
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-balans-ed-meal/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 13:14:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia Goldberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-balans-ed-meal/</guid>
        <description>The Balans menu is an eclectic mix of dishes from Thai to Italian and a wide variety of cocktails. It is a café style restaurant, which specialises in cocktails. If you can’t agree where to eat out, then this is a great place for you as there’s something for everyone on the menu.
In hindsight the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
