<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/skw10/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/skw10/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Spinning chairs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-29-spinning-chairs/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 15:30:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephanie Walton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-29-spinning-chairs/</guid>
        <description>Some people really can sing. And I don’t just mean in tune with a token crescendo or diminuendo. I mean with style and true feeling.
The Voice is a TV show which searches for these very people and assesses them on the quality of their voices alone. In the so called “Blind Auditions” the vocal …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bumper year for Physics’ Joanna Haigh
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-bumper-year-for-physics-joanna-haigh/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 18:11:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephanie Walton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-bumper-year-for-physics-joanna-haigh/</guid>
        <description>Climate physicist Professor Joanna Haigh is enjoying a glittering start to 2013. In recognition of her services to Physics she was appointed Commander of the British Empire (CBE) in the New Year Honours and earlier this month she was elected a Fellow of the Royal Society (FRS).
She is also the first …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial student wins national science communication competion
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-9-imperial-student-wins-national-science-communication-competion/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 12:01:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephanie Walton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-9-imperial-student-wins-national-science-communication-competion/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College’s Leon Vanstone has been crowned the UK’s FameLab champion 2013. In this annual hunt for the nation’s best science communicators, each contestant has exactly three minutes to impress a panel of three judges. They may explain any scientific concept but cannot use assisting slides or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Making a splash in Mexico
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-7-making-a-splash-in-mexico/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2013 19:37:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephanie Walton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-7-making-a-splash-in-mexico/</guid>
        <description>Mexico receives such bad press these days that it is hard to believe it has a safe and beautiful peninsula kicking out into the Caribbean Sea. There are white beaches, fascinating Mayan ruins and magnificent colonial cities. It seems that the only two drawbacks to this balmy “Yucatán” Peninsula are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Squash’s day out with the Pros
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-squashs-day-out-with-the-pros/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 23:19:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephanie Walton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-squashs-day-out-with-the-pros/</guid>
        <description>Rich people tend to lavish their money on fast cars, helicopters and yachts. Portable glass squash courts, though, are surely the ultimate display of status and wealth. The court can be assembled at the drop of a hat (well… within three weeks) at whatever location the owner fancies. Which means that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fear of flying: just common sense!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-fear-of-flying-just-common-sense/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 23:06:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephanie Walton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-fear-of-flying-just-common-sense/</guid>
        <description>Flying is terrifying: trust me, I’ve tried it. And don’t bother trying to contradict me, because how could sitting in a metal can 30,000 feet up in the air not be scary?
Don’t get me wrong though. I’m a Physicist and a firm believer in both Bernoulli’s Principle and Newton’s Second Law (indeed I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wallowing in the Wadden
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-wallowing-in-the-wadden/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 12:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephanie Walton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-wallowing-in-the-wadden/</guid>
        <description>I doubt many visitors to The Netherlands stray far beyond the amazing museums, canals and liberal attractions of Amsterdam. So it was perhaps unsurprising that I was met with quizzical looks when I announced that I was off to The Netherlands to go Wadlopen. Wadlopen, the art of walking on mudflats …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rubbish sports and the Olympics
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-rubbish-sports-and-the-olympics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 12:50:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephanie Walton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-rubbish-sports-and-the-olympics/</guid>
        <description>Forgive me, reader, if you’ve reached Olympic saturation point over the summer. No doubt I would have done so long ago, had I not spent a large part of those two weeks in a lecture theatre in The Netherlands. Utrecht train station, I excitedly discovered, had a large screen TV showing the Games. I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Organ donation: is it selfless or selfish?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-organ-donation-is-it-selfless-or-selfish/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 19:42:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephanie Walton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-organ-donation-is-it-selfless-or-selfish/</guid>
        <description>Don’t worry. I’m not going to intimidate you with statistics in order to convince you to give your organs away at death. Nor am I going to persuade you that you’ll be needing them in the afterlife. It is after all your body and it’s really none of my business what you do with it.
But I wonder if you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cha cha cha near the beach
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-cha-cha-cha-near-the-beach/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 19:19:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephanie Walton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-cha-cha-cha-near-the-beach/</guid>
        <description>I used to loathe dancing. I was one of those people who stands in the corner looking awkward, refusing to join the dance floor. However, in a moment of daring I tried Latin American dancing and not that long after I found myself travelling one Sunday morning to the south coast for my first …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Give Boris Bikes a chance
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-give-boris-bikes-a-chance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 06:29:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephanie Walton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-give-boris-bikes-a-chance/</guid>
        <description>I should be on Transport for London’s pay roll. Why? Because the times that I have helped people release bikes from Boris’ blue stands are innumerable. The people requiring assistance are mostly tourists, whom I often have little patience with. So what is it that makes their plight so important to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Accidents, emergencies, and Ajmer
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-accidents-emergencies-and-ajmer/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 19:09:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephanie Walton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-accidents-emergencies-and-ajmer/</guid>
        <description>How far is it to Ajmer?”, I asked, concerned.
Ajmer, although famous for its holy Muslim shrine to the great Sufi saint Moinuddin Chishti, was not originally on our itinerary. So how did we find ourselves seeking its Accident and Emergency department at 11pm on Easter Saturday?
Puskhar, a sacred …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
