<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ae1409/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ae1409/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Enjoy a night on King’s Road at the famous and glamorous JuJu
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-7-enjoy-a-night-on-kings-road-at-the-famous-and-glamorous-juju/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 18:57:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Krestas,Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-7-enjoy-a-night-on-kings-road-at-the-famous-and-glamorous-juju/</guid>
        <description>JuJu is an award winning bar located in the heart of glamorous Chelsea on King’s Road. It’s the ideal place for after work drinks or a pre-clubbing warm up. JuJu offers the finest cocktails in London, including the popular Pornstar Martini, mixed by undoubtedly brilliant bartenders. For the more …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Discover a new taste at pan-asian Umami
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-3-discover-a-new-taste-at-pan-asian-umami/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 16:08:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Krestas,Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-3-discover-a-new-taste-at-pan-asian-umami/</guid>
        <description>There’s no way you can stand another lunch at Queen’s Tower, or the Library Cafe, or even the JCR after your exams. It’s just unacceptable! If you feel that life at Imperial has become monotonic (and at the moment your mind thinks of functions) then you need a getaway. Today we’ll present you with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>POCA’s poppy atmospheres
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-pocas-poppy-atmospheres/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 21:12:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-pocas-poppy-atmospheres/</guid>
        <description>POCA is formed of Poca (vocals), George Karpasitis (guitars), David Horler (bass) and Jack Painting (drums). They have collaborated with Sophie Frankford (violin), Midori Jaeger (cello) and Elin Klingfors and Txako Jones (backing vocals).
Anastasia: How did you get the initial motivation to form …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Fairtrade Food Awards: The Results
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-imperial-fairtrade-food-awards-the-results/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 22:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Krestas,Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-imperial-fairtrade-food-awards-the-results/</guid>
        <description>First Place:Brigitte Jessica Janssen’s Gooey, Fibre And Mango infused Blackberry Muffins earned her the top prize: a £30 voucher for online shopping site ethicalsuperstore.com. Congratulations!
Ingredients 30g jumbo oats 2 eggs 185g self-raising flour 40g Fairtrade demara sugar 25g mix of pumpkin + …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Big Fat Real Greek!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-the-big-fat-real-greek/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 21:52:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Krestas,Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-the-big-fat-real-greek/</guid>
        <description>Many of you may feel a bit unwilling to visit a Greek restaurant because of Greece’s absurd and unjustifiable dealing of its politico-economic crisis. Besides, it is a fact, especially for those studying economics, that a country so small as Greece and with such a small and limited economy, can …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get creative in the kitchen after lectures
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-get-creative-in-the-kitchen-after-lectures/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 20:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-get-creative-in-the-kitchen-after-lectures/</guid>
        <description>You have finished lectures, you have just returned home and you are starving. The worst thing is that you’re sick of eating fast food, but you don’t have that much experience with cooking.
Relax, this article is dedicated to you! There are a lot of simple recipes, even for those of you who have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The secrets of a lobster
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-the-secrets-of-a-lobster/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 21:48:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-the-secrets-of-a-lobster/</guid>
        <description>The next time you see live lobsters at a restaurant market, don’t be afraid of them! You will see that they’re pretty easy to cook and enjoy.
Lobsters are very expensive though, and that is not only because they are very popular, but because it’s very difficult to find them. They live in holes and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Geography Cake
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-geography-cake/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 22:36:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-geography-cake/</guid>
        <description>Ingredients 3 eggs 3 glasses of self raising flour 3&amp;frasl;4 glass of sugar 3&amp;frasl;4 glass of oil 1 glass of milk 3 tsp of Baking Powder 1 tbsp of cognac 2 tbsp of Drinking Chocolate
Preheat the oven to 180°C/350°F. Beat the oil and the sugar together until smooth. Whisk the eggs and add them to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get your food life SORTED
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-get-your-food-life-sorted/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 21:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-get-your-food-life-sorted/</guid>
        <description>What is SORTED in one sentence? We’re a genuine bunch of mates who teamed up to run SORTED Food, an online cooking hub that aims to solve the food problems of our audience, and to prove that you can have a bit of fun in the kitchen; cooking doesn’t have to be so serious!
Why do you believe SORTED …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Food that loves you back
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-food-that-loves-you-back/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 21:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-food-that-loves-you-back/</guid>
        <description>Finally, there’s a place in London where vegetarians can completely be themselves. As soon as you enter tibits a warm welcome from the staff, accompanied with a high-class atmosphere and tempting smells coming from the buffet are enough to set up the scene of an exceptional breakfast, lunch or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wine Culture
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-wine-culture/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 21:43:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-wine-culture/</guid>
        <description> There is one familiar rule which simply says that “Red with meat, white with fish”. Is it correct though? In most cases, a red wine is more suitable for a meat-based dish, simply because the tannins (particular ingredients of red wine) bind the proteins of meat, resulting in a harmonic matching. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Interview: Mark Pitts-Tucker
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-interview-mark-pitts-tucker/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 20:43:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-interview-mark-pitts-tucker/</guid>
        <description>A: You are the cheese grader for Cathedral City. What does Cathedral City Cheese have different from other cheese brands?
M: All of the cheese used for Cathedral City is made at the award winning Davidstow Creamery on the north Cornish coast. The meadows are lush and the milk is creamy. All these …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Food Experiments
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-food-experiments/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 21:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-food-experiments/</guid>
        <description>Young science students from Sherborne Girls in Dorset have discovered what makes the perfect boiled egg and soldiers. In an “Eggsperiment” commissioned by the Royal Society of Chemistry, a team of 12 girls tested one of Britain’s favourite breakfasts and confirmed the optimum time for boiling an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The wisdom of nature
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-the-wisdom-of-nature/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 21:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-the-wisdom-of-nature/</guid>
        <description>The truth is that organic products have managed to attract a large number of people in the United Kingdom. In addition, the increase in the number of people buying organic goods is showing no signs of slowing down. The supporters of this ‘green lifestyle’ believe that it is not just a fashion trend …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ready, steady, chat
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-ready-steady-chat/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 21:33:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-ready-steady-chat/</guid>
        <description>He has hosted the longest running cookery series in the world and has worked as a chef in hotels and restaurants across London after training at Westminster Catering College.
He has worked in the kitchens of Verreys, The Strand Palace, The Dorchester and Browns amongst others, and set up his own …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Food Awards: The Results
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-28-imperial-food-awards-the-results/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 14:02:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anastasia Eleftheriou,Michael Krestas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-28-imperial-food-awards-the-results/</guid>
        <description>We would like to thank everyone who contributed to the first Imperial Food Awards and proved how important food is in our lives.
Surely, nothing could have happened without the support of our generous sponsors. Let us thank once again the Cypriot Society, Dishoom Bombay Café, Riverford Organic Farm, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Margaritas @ home: it’s cocktail time
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-14-margaritas-home-its-cocktail-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 00:04:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-14-margaritas-home-its-cocktail-time/</guid>
        <description>Margarita is the most common tequila-based cocktail and was most probably invented in Mexico, although there is no solid proof of its origin. We like it in its classic form or with strawberry, pineapple, peach, mango or papaya flavours.
You can enjoy your favourite margarita with a Mexican meal or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Food Awards
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-imperial-food-awards/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 23:52:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-imperial-food-awards/</guid>
        <description>It’s our pleasure to announce the first Imperial Food Awards competition! Organised and judged by the Food Editors of Felix, this is your chance to prove your talent and creativity in cooking. In short, you shouldn’t miss it. The reason? Loads of fantastic prizes will be awarded to the winner, who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dishoom, one of the best Bombay Cafés that London has to offer?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-dishoom-one-of-the-best-bombay-cafs-that-london-has-to-offer/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 23:27:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Krestas,Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-dishoom-one-of-the-best-bombay-cafs-that-london-has-to-offer/</guid>
        <description>One minute away from Leicester Square Station, Dishoom offers great Indian food at great prices in an extraordinary yet cosy atmosphere.
A: I literally can’t move at the moment. I’m full. You should have stopped me after the fifth dish! M: What could I have done? Everything was great! However, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chocolate Week announces a melt-in-your-mouth lineup
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-chocolate-week-announces-a-melt-in-your-mouth-lineup/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 13:02:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-chocolate-week-announces-a-melt-in-your-mouth-lineup/</guid>
        <description>I have good news for the chocolate-lovers; the biggest celebration of chocolate in the UK is on its way! A wonderful opportunity for the public to learn more about the chocolate market in the UK and have fun in a unique way.
The highlight of the week, is the Chocolate Unwrapped show where visitors …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>¡Sabor Sabor!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-sabor-sabor/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 10:18:47 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-sabor-sabor/</guid>
        <description>One roof, three party rooms, four teachers, five DJs and hundreds of guest make for one of London’s most interesting dance events. It takes place every first Friday of the month at Firefly Bars &amp;amp; Restaurants across London, and for those that prefer to have a warm-up before the event, dance …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ai Chihuahua!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-ai-chihuahua/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 21:18:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-ai-chihuahua/</guid>
        <description>Drinking, Dancing and Dining is the motto of this place - a place where you can drop in after a walk at Covent Garden market and have a tasty and relatively cheap Mexican meal. There are fantastically named cocktails, like “Orgasm please!” and “Blow work”, and tunes blasting from 11pm until 3am. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bada: make things happen!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-bada-make-things-happen/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 18:38:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-bada-make-things-happen/</guid>
        <description>While Android and iOS have become increasingly popular and must-have platforms, Samsung has an alternative to suggest: the Bada ecosystem. In June 2010, Bada-based Samsung Apps were launched in 118 countries, with over a hundred million downloads and more than 13,000 applications available by March …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>As Greek as it gets
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-as-greek-as-it-gets/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 19:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-as-greek-as-it-gets/</guid>
        <description>There are many students in Imperial that love Greek food and I am not talking solely about the Greeks! Traditional Greek cuisine is full of incredible smells and tastes: from the salty feta cheese; the tempting meat meze with the refreshing tzatziki; the thick pita bread and the skewers, the unique …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>International Night
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-19-international-night/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2011 15:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-19-international-night/</guid>
        <description>Last Friday, 11th of February at 7:00 p.m, the Great Hall of Sherfield Building was packed from Imperial College students, friends, parents and staff. The reason? One of the most entertaining and full of fun event that is organized annually by the Imperial College Overseas Societies Committee; the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Take two leeches and call me tomorrow
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-take-two-leeches-and-call-me-tomorrow/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 20:27:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-take-two-leeches-and-call-me-tomorrow/</guid>
        <description>Most of us believe that leeches belong to the category of the most disgusting and dangerous creatures of this world. They can, however be beneficial for people’s health.
Leeches – the word deriving from the old English word for physician, laece – are mainly used for treating abscesses, painful …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Building green cities from scratch
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-building-green-cities-from-scratch/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 20:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-building-green-cities-from-scratch/</guid>
        <description>Ecologists and environmental scientists are trying hard to raise public awareness about environmental problems. I believe that everyone understands that we live on a suffering planet which has various increasing needs and demands, which is why cities all over the world have set high targets to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hidden behind a computer screen: The psychological effects of distancing through the internet
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-hidden-behind-a-computer-screen-the-psychological-effects-of-distancing-through-the-internet/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 21:33:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-hidden-behind-a-computer-screen-the-psychological-effects-of-distancing-through-the-internet/</guid>
        <description>People find it easier to express their feelings hidden behind their computer screens. They can confess things to people that they would never talk about face to face, like suppressed feelings or personal thoughts. So how exactly did people communicate before the internet?
However, the distancing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Diaspora: social without the invasion
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-diaspora-social-without-the-invasion/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 20:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-diaspora-social-without-the-invasion/</guid>
        <description>Diaspora is an open source social network built by four students at NYU’s Courant Institute; Daniel Grippi, Maxwell Salzberg, Raphael Sofaer, and Ilya Zhitomirskiy.
They had been inspired by a talk about freedom and ownership online, by Eben Moglenn, and focussed by the fact that the large social …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hawking’s lesson for life
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-hawkings-lesson-for-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 18:47:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anastasia Eleftheriou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-hawkings-lesson-for-life/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday 20th October, a very rare public lecture was given by one of the most famous and respected physicists alive today, Stephen Hawking, at the Royal Albert Hall in South Kensington.
By the start of the lecture, the hall was fully packed with people of all ages. Professor Hawking was …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
