<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/klb09/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/klb09/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The Reluctant Fundamentalist
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-the-reluctant-fundamentalist/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 18:41:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-the-reluctant-fundamentalist/</guid>
        <description>Adapted from the novel of the same name, this Mira Nair film which opened at the Venice Film Festival last year tells the story of Changez (Ahmed), an American educated Pakistani, whose political and religious loyalty we are continuously asked to question.
The film takes place in two time-space …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FDR gets some
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-fdr-gets-some/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 01:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-fdr-gets-some/</guid>
        <description>It is sometime in June 1939, at Franklin D Roosevelt’s (Murray) private estate, upstate New York. Europe is on the brink of war, and King George V (West) and Queen Elizabeth (Coleman) are about to become the first British monarchs ever to visit America, in a bid to improve relations and convince …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Santa Claus won’t make you happy, but these films will...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-santa-claus-wont-make-you-happy-but-these-films-will/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 15:06:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-santa-claus-wont-make-you-happy-but-these-films-will/</guid>
        <description>1.) The Sound of Music
Julie Andrews plays a nun turned governess for a bunch of super cute Austrian children and their super hot father (Christopher Plummer – just me?) Set against the backdrop of WW2, this charming family oriented film always gets me in the mood for the holidays.
2.) Harry Potter …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Twilight sucks...and not in the good way
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-23-twilight-sucksand-not-in-the-good-way/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2012 00:38:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-23-twilight-sucksand-not-in-the-good-way/</guid>
        <description>The Twilight Saga comes to a much needed close with its final instalment. The main problem with this film is that Meyer’s final book barely contained enough content for one film, let alone two franchise-bleeding epics. Consequently, this film ended up being two hours in which essentially, nothing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Great films I hate (or why I shouldn’t be a Film Editor: The Sequel)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-great-films-i-hate-or-why-i-shouldnt-be-a-film-editor-the-sequel/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 21:42:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-great-films-i-hate-or-why-i-shouldnt-be-a-film-editor-the-sequel/</guid>
        <description> Following on from last week’s feature, &amp;lsquo;Shit films I love&amp;rsquo;, I decided to continue my public shaming. The following films have caused much contension in the Felix Office – one in particular is one of my co-Editor&amp;rsquo;s favourite films. But I&amp;rsquo;m sure everyone has been there – …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Shit films I love (or why I shouldn’t be a Film Editor...)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-shit-films-i-love-or-why-i-shouldnt-be-a-film-editor/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 13:50:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-shit-films-i-love-or-why-i-shouldnt-be-a-film-editor/</guid>
        <description> I was recently challenged to rate every film I have ever seen. Apart from being a shockingly huge task, it also threw up a massive problem. Because there are incredible films for every emotion. And of course there are some God-awful films too – less said about these the better. The problem I have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Taken 2 Review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-taken-2-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 13:33:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-taken-2-review/</guid>
        <description>Producer Luc Besson and director Olivier Megaton had a smash hit on their hands with 2008’s Taken, starring Liam Neeson as the ex-CIA guy whose daughter was kidnapped by traffickers in Europe. Needless to say, Liam went after the bad guys, found them and killed them. Sorted. It was such a success …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Argo F*** Yourself”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-argo-f-yourself/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 23:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-argo-f-yourself/</guid>
        <description>Based on true events, Affleck’s latest directorial is a darkly comic mixture of thriller and political satire.
When the US embassy in Tehran is stormed in November 1979 in retaliation for American interference in Iranian politics, six diplomats, nicknamed ‘the house-guests’ take shelter in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An interview with Medic President Suzie Rayner
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-an-interview-with-medic-president-suzie-rayner/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 21:23:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,Madhura Ghosh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-an-interview-with-medic-president-suzie-rayner/</guid>
        <description>Felix: How do you think the medical school has changed since this time last year (with respect to the Daily Mail article highlighting the binge-drinking culture of ICSM)? Suzie Rayner (SR): The changes made [after] the Daily Mail article last January have caused some necessary changes to bar …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Alcohol: why should you care?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-alcohol-why-should-you-care/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 21:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,Madhura Ghosh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-alcohol-why-should-you-care/</guid>
        <description> It’s that time of year again when we all start to make, and consequently break, all those well-meant resolutions we dreamt up over the Christmas break. But one resolution that couldn’t afford to be broken was that made by Imperial College School of Medicine (ICSM) this time last year: its …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why should you go into teaching?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-why-should-you-go-into-teaching/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 19:48:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,Matthew N Colvin,Navid Nabijou,Deepka Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-why-should-you-go-into-teaching/</guid>
        <description>Can you think of any reason why an Imperial student might want to become a teacher?” “They got a third class, maybe?” This response from a second year mathematician may well sum up the opinions of some Imperial students, and indeed a section of society’s wider opinion of the profession. We’ve all …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial NHS Trust deny reported plans to close St Mary&#39;s
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-9-10-imperial-nhs-trust-deny-reported-plans-to-close-st-marys/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 15:40:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-9-10-imperial-nhs-trust-deny-reported-plans-to-close-st-marys/</guid>
        <description>A heated exchange has broken out between Imperial College Healthcare NHS Trust and The Independent newspaper, amid fears that St Mary’s Hospital, based at Paddington, will be closed and sold for housing.
Reported in The Independent on Monday, managers at the Trust were said to have been considering …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Details of new bursary scheme emerge
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-details-of-new-bursary-scheme-emerge/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 19:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-details-of-new-bursary-scheme-emerge/</guid>
        <description>A College committee is working on proposals to increase Imperial’s bursary provision that could see more students receiving financial aid. The proposals from the Fees and Financial Aid Working Group would see students from families earning £60,000 receiving bursaries (up from the current £50,000), …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NUS President won’t seek re-election
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-nus-president-wont-seek-re-election/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 12:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-nus-president-wont-seek-re-election/</guid>
        <description>Last week Aaron Porter, president of the NUS, made the decision that he would not seek re-election at the national conference in April – effectively bringing his troubled yearlong presidency to an end.
Speaking in an interview with The Guardian, Porter highlighted the need for a “fresh outlook – …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Medic RAG week raises over £20,000
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-medic-rag-week-raises-over-20000/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 12:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-medic-rag-week-raises-over-20000/</guid>
        <description>Last week hundreds of Imperial’s medical students raised £23,000 for St Mary’s Hospital Paediatric Department in a series of events as part of their annual RAG week.
The biggest event of the week was the traditional ‘Circle Line’ pub crawl and charity collect, attended by over 500 medical students …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial to charge £9,000
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-imperial-to-charge-9000/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 18:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Madhura Ghosh,Katherine Bettany,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-imperial-to-charge-9000/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College has this week revealed that it plans to charge the maximum £9,000 tuition fee rate for 2012 entry. The move is an unsurprising one, with the universities of Cambridge and Oxford signalling earlier this month that higher fees would be necessary to fill a deficit created by government …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Angry students told to hop off ‘Hopper Bus’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-angry-students-told-to-hop-off-hopper-bus/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 19:19:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-angry-students-told-to-hop-off-hopper-bus/</guid>
        <description>Disgruntled students have this week found themselves unable to use the NHS Trust ‘Hopper Bus’ service, a shuttle service that runs between NHS Trust sites.
The service, piloted in April 2009, had until recently been a useful form of free transport for Imperial students, most notably medical …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The UK’s organ shortage kills 3 people every day...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-the-uks-organ-shortage-kills-3-people-every-day/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 18:41:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anna Perman,Katherine Bettany,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-the-uks-organ-shortage-kills-3-people-every-day/</guid>
        <description>Imagine. Something in your machinery has stopped working. Somewhere in your body, a vital organ, your kidneys, eyes, your heart, has malfunctioned. Your doctor says that the damage is irreversible and that you need a replacement.
For nearly 8,000 people in the UK currently waiting for an organ …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Singapore medical school receives $150 million boost
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-singapore-medical-school-receives-150-million-boost/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 21:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-singapore-medical-school-receives-150-million-boost/</guid>
        <description>Imperial’s new Singaporean medical school; a partnership between Imperial and the Nanyang Technological University, has this month received a gift of $150 million from the Lee Foundation.
The school, newly named the Lee Kong Chian School of Medicine after the Lee Foundation’s founder, philanthropist …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Medical school embarrassed by controversial Daily Mail article
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-medical-school-embarrassed-by-controversial-daily-mail-article/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 21:38:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-medical-school-embarrassed-by-controversial-daily-mail-article/</guid>
        <description>In an unpromising start to the New Year, the reputation of Imperial College School of Medicine was brought into disrepute by a scathing article published in the Daily Mail.
A no-holds-barred account of a recent Sports Night at the Reynolds bar – home to the medics – featured in the article, complete …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let’s be more open about mental illness
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-lets-be-more-open-about-mental-illness/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 21:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,Elizabeth Crouch,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-lets-be-more-open-about-mental-illness/</guid>
        <description>Two o’clock in the morning. I had got home from an amazing night out and was falling asleep when I heard people running in the corridor. It was a Friday night and we were Freshers, so I thought nothing of it; I turned over and pulled the duvet tighter around me.
Literally seconds later I was woken …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>No help for volunteers as Outreach takes budget cut
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-no-help-for-volunteers-as-outreach-takes-budget-cut/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 22:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,Yilin Wei,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-no-help-for-volunteers-as-outreach-takes-budget-cut/</guid>
        <description>The Imperial Volunteering Centre (IVC) is to be almost entirely scrapped due to funding difficulties caused by a cut by the Higher Education Funding Council for England (HEFCE) and also a large reduction in the Outreach department budget. Heather Jones, Deputy President (Clubs &amp;amp; Societies) and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial wins as science is spared major cuts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-imperial-wins-as-science-is-spared-major-cuts/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 19:30:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,Katherine Bettany,Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-imperial-wins-as-science-is-spared-major-cuts/</guid>
        <description>In the controversial Spending Review presented to Parliament on Wednesday, George Osborne revealed the details of the UK’s deepest spending cuts for decades, designed to reduce our budget deficit by £83 billion pounds before 2014&amp;frasl;15.
With Britain paying £120 million a day in debt interest …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
