<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jp1409/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jp1409/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Google to the power of Googol for fainboiz
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-21-google-to-the-power-of-googol-for-fainboiz/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2013 00:32:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jason Parmar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-21-google-to-the-power-of-googol-for-fainboiz/</guid>
        <description>Note: Some or all of this article may be parody&amp;hellip;
It’s been an incredible year for the world’s coolest company.
Consistently ranked as the best place to work for as long as I can remember, the last 12 months has seen some pretty ground-breaking steps forward for the Mountain View company: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Microsoft going hard?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-microsoft-going-hard/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 01:07:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jason Parmar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-microsoft-going-hard/</guid>
        <description> It’s not unfair to call Microsoft a reactive company, i.e. they follow trends and build on others innovations, it’s in their history.
Excel was an improved spreadsheet of existing VisiCalc, Word was an improved word processor of existing MicroPro and Internet Explorer was an improved web browser of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Illegal downloading, that&#39;s oldschool
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-30-illegal-downloading-thats-oldschool/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 11:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jason Parmar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-30-illegal-downloading-thats-oldschool/</guid>
        <description> Writing the previous article on Google Music’s introduction to the UK market reminded me of an interesting question that I’ve been asking myself for a while, “has the progress in the digital music market, which gives consumers a better deal, reduced the amount we illegal download?” I think that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Google music is finally here
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-30-google-music-is-finally-here/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 11:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jason Parmar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-30-google-music-is-finally-here/</guid>
        <description> I used to use browser based music services “Grooveshark” &amp;amp; “Hypem” in addition to downloading to fulfil my musical listening needs. However, I knew it wasn’t really sustainable, especially considering that Grooveshark is in a very long legal battle and is currently being sued by several labels, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Will W8 cause us grief?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-will-w8-cause-us-grief/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 02:25:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jason Parmar,Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-will-w8-cause-us-grief/</guid>
        <description>Some of us are not normal people (but then again, we are Imperial students). We live on the bleeding edge of technology where we thrive on using the latest and greatest of gadgets and software. We readily consume new technology and are willing to learn and adapt. In case of an interface paradigm …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Windows 8 - the difference between 8, RT &amp; Pro
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-windows-8-the-difference-between-8-rt-pro/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 02:24:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jason Parmar,Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-windows-8-the-difference-between-8-rt-pro/</guid>
        <description>Windows 8 came out today, and the media world is buzzing to see if this will make or break Microsoft’s future. In the past Microsoft consumers faced more choices of varieties of Windows than in a trip to Subway! Starter, Home Basic, Home Premium and, and, and, were often subject to intense …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get your Christmas tablet treat early with Felix Tech
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-get-your-christmas-tablet-treat-early-with-felix-tech/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 20:59:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,Jason Parmar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-get-your-christmas-tablet-treat-early-with-felix-tech/</guid>
        <description> Seasons come and go, but Christmas never changes and considering that it’s only 65 shopping days away, you might as well get started making your wish list (parents do need something to spend money on!). So to help you get an idea, here are 4 budget tablets that might tickle your fancy!
iPad Mini On …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Freshers Introduction to Tech
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-9-freshers-introduction-to-tech/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 10:21:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jason Parmar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-9-freshers-introduction-to-tech/</guid>
        <description> General Productivity
If you actually want to pass your degree, you best get yourself Microsoft Office: it’s the shit. If not, you can try Open Office, but, in this Tech Editor’s opinion, if you do venture down that path, make sure you get both! Like those before you, Open Office users are likely to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Add me on MySpace?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-add-me-on-myspace/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 11:53:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jason Parmar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-add-me-on-myspace/</guid>
        <description>After launching in 2003, MySpace was guilty of taking many of our social networking virginities by taking advantage of us being embarrassing teenagers while we posed, pouting in front of mirrors with a 1MP camera phone.
But then we grew up and most of us realised that editing our profile HTML to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>OMG new smartphones!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-omg-new-smartphones/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 11:44:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jason Parmar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-omg-new-smartphones/</guid>
        <description>Unless you’ve been trapped under a rock or on a ton of last minute holidays the last month before freshers’ week, you’ll be aware that a ton of great new smartphones been announced.
The Samsung Galaxy S3 (or GS3), Nokia Lumia 920, and Apple iPhone 5 are getting priority as my choice to represent the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nokiasoft: a match made in heaven
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-nokiasoft-a-match-made-in-heaven/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 19:55:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jason Parmar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-nokiasoft-a-match-made-in-heaven/</guid>
        <description>When Nokia announced their partnership with Windows Phone 7 instead of Android back in February I honestly thought that they’d made one of the biggest mistakes in the company’s history. How wrong I was.
Windows Phone 7
As much as I’d like to talk about the physical phone, the truth is, just like the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
