<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/le14/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/le14/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Solar cells absorb 20% more light with nanoscale coating</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-solar-cells-absorb-20-more-light-with-nanoscale-coating/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lara Bailey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-solar-cells-absorb-20-more-light-with-nanoscale-coating/</guid>
        <description>Researchers at the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) have developed a nanoscale coating for solar cells. These are made of thousands of glass beads of sulphur dioxide, each no larger than one-hundredth of the width of a human hair.
The coating creates an optical ‘whispering …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Solving our environmental problems without hindering reproductive rights</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-12-solving-our-environmental-problems-without-hindering-reproductive-rights/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lara Bailey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-12-solving-our-environmental-problems-without-hindering-reproductive-rights/</guid>
        <description>I read a Forbes article by Tim Worstall recently, where he suggests that women using the contraceptive pill should pay £1105 ($1500) in tax to due to its environmental impact. That’s right: a bank-breaking one thousand pounds per woman. Such a tax would significantly limit access to the pill – I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NHS Watchdog Reveals Crippling Mental Health Services</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-nhs-watchdog-reveals-crippling-mental-health-services/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lara Bailey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-nhs-watchdog-reveals-crippling-mental-health-services/</guid>
        <description>The government has been accused of ‘neglecting’ children’s mental health, following a report revealing some children were waiting up to 18 months for treatment.
The report, which was authored by the Care Quality Commission (CQC) – an independent regulator of health and social care services – showed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>75% of global honey contaminated with pesticides</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-75-of-global-honey-contaminated-with-pesticides/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lara Bailey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-75-of-global-honey-contaminated-with-pesticides/</guid>
        <description>According to a study published 6th of October, 75% of global honey samples were contaminated with several neonicotinoid pesticides.
Levels detected are below the threshold deemed dangerous for human consumption. The report, however, adds weight to a growing body of evidence suggesting that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pot and its potential
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-pot-and-its-potential/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lara Bailey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-pot-and-its-potential/</guid>
        <description>Everyone is familiar with the perceived positive and negative connotations of Marijuana. In 2016 alone, 51% of Americans smoked cannabis, and its global use is on the rise due to recent legalisation in several US states. However, despite its widespread use, surprisingly little has been confirmed in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Erecto-shock therapy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-erecto-shock-therapy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 12:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lara Bailey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-erecto-shock-therapy/</guid>
        <description>Transcranial magnetic stimulation (TMS) is a technique currently used in the treatment of migraines and depression. It involves stimulating the part of the brain that is linked to reward and pleasure. Patients undergoing treatment for depression may receive numerous sessions of TMS, but it is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The galaxy’s guide to hitchhiking
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-the-galaxys-guide-to-hitchhiking/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 13:40:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lara Bailey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-the-galaxys-guide-to-hitchhiking/</guid>
        <description>It has been known for a long time that galaxies move, and our Milky Way is no exception. The Milky Way and its 50 neighbours, together referred to as the ‘Local Group’, have been moving in a particular direction, and until now it was not known why. A team of researchers from South Africa, Germany, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Trump Presidency | a new era for America... a disaster for Earth?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-a-trump-presidency-a-new-era-for-america-a-disaster-for-earth/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 15:53:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lara Bailey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-a-trump-presidency-a-new-era-for-america-a-disaster-for-earth/</guid>
        <description>A man who described climate change as “created by the Chinese” and “fictional” is now the leader of the free world.
The World Meteorological Organisation, a UN body, recently released data showing that 2011 – 2015 have been the hottest years on record. Moreover, many extreme weather events that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ice sheet melting faster than predicted
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-ice-sheet-melting-faster-than-predicted/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 08:54:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lara Bailey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-ice-sheet-melting-faster-than-predicted/</guid>
        <description>Antarctica boasts the largest mass of ice on earth, a colossal 27 million km3, comprised of three vast ice sheets: the East, the West and the Antarctic Peninsula. With warming seas and climbing temperatures, scientists focused their attention on the West Antarctic Ice Sheet, due to its vulnerability …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
