<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Features on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/features/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Features on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/features/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Three years after my roommate’s death I’m ready to move on
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-three-years-after-my-roommates-death-im-ready-to-move-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:56:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonathan Masters,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-three-years-after-my-roommates-death-im-ready-to-move-on/</guid>
        <description>A few weeks ago I finally came to the end of my three year course at Imperial, and although it is a cliché, the time has simply flown by. As I handed in the final final final draft of my undergraduate dissertation into turnitin, I suddenly burst into tears. Now it could have been a combination of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial academics on Trump and climate
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-imperial-academics-on-trump-and-climate/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 14:48:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-imperial-academics-on-trump-and-climate/</guid>
        <description>Last week Trump declared to the world that he’d be pulling the US out of the Paris Agreement. Within hours, Elon Musk resigned from the President’s Board of Advisors, American states such as California went rogue and protested the move, vouching to uphold their commitment anyway, and world leaders …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The election and the NHS
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-the-election-and-the-nhs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 14:25:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Dan Faehndrich,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-the-election-and-the-nhs/</guid>
        <description>Since the surprise of 7th May 2015, the NHS has fallen into its darkest times since its inception. As a medical student, seeing my colleagues here and across the whole medical profession has, frankly, made becoming a doctor look the least appealing it’s looked since 14 year-old me decided it was the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Manifesto breakdowns
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-manifesto-breakdowns/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:59:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,Cale E Tilford,Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-manifesto-breakdowns/</guid>
        <description> This piece aims to break down the main party manifestos and summarise a few key policies. This is by no means a full and in-depth analysis of each party. Mainly because the manifestos are long and complex, and it’s exam season. [Insert tinfoil hat theory that the timing of the election coincides …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An idiot’s guide to the UK general election
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-an-idiots-guide-to-the-uk-general-election/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:57:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-an-idiots-guide-to-the-uk-general-election/</guid>
        <description>Ding ding ding, it’s election time again. No, you haven’t woken up from that nap in 2020, they’ve called an early election. Do you have no idea who you’re voting for? Well, you’re in luck my friend, because we’ve got a whole pull-out complete with manifesto breakdowns, and personal views on who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Afterhours sessions in the Central Library
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-afterhours-sessions-in-the-central-library/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:29:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-afterhours-sessions-in-the-central-library/</guid>
        <description>How does one end up in the Library past midnight? Maybe you had a paper to submit tomorrow. You thought you had everything under control. You were halfway there but you made the mistake of taking a break and committing to an episode of the Great British Bake Off. Six hours later you get a text from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In defence of being flaky
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-in-defence-of-being-flaky/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:25:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-in-defence-of-being-flaky/</guid>
        <description>Be honest, we all have that friend who’s a complete flake. You know, you make plans with them only to have them cancel at the last minute. Maybe this happens repeatedly. They’re really fucking annoying, right? Maybe you don’t even want to bother to reschedule. Maybe they’re so flaky that you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why do we stigmatise abortion?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-why-do-we-stigmatise-abortion/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 17:42:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-why-do-we-stigmatise-abortion/</guid>
        <description>I haven’t had an abortion. In fact, I only know two people who have and they personally told me of it. One was a girl I went to school with, who had an abortion aged 15, and lost a lot of friends who had never realised they were pro-life until that moment. The other is my mother, who speaks about it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My friend, a fresher, got pregnant
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-my-friend-a-fresher-got-pregnant/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 17:41:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-my-friend-a-fresher-got-pregnant/</guid>
        <description>This is a story about a friend (yes, it is actually about a friend). Just like any good story, it starts with a nice (by British standards anyway) spring day with my best friend telling me that she’s pregnant.
“So what?” you ask. “People get pregnant all the time!” While that may be true, she is not …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>eSports | Imperial vs UCL
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-esports-imperial-vs-ucl/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 17:29:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-esports-imperial-vs-ucl/</guid>
        <description>For most people, the 12th of March was just another Sunday. For a group of certain individuals, however, it was a chance for lasting and eternal glory. Well, more like temporary happiness for a few days, but hey, we all have to take what we can get.
This Sunday, an eSports tournament was held …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The National Wedding Show is decadent and depraved
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-the-national-wedding-show-is-decadent-and-depraved/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 17:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theo Farah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-the-national-wedding-show-is-decadent-and-depraved/</guid>
        <description>As I walked along Hammersmith Road to the convention centre, Kensington Olympia, a faltering bundle of nerves, I scanned my brain for excuses not to enter the palatial structure. Fortified by a cocktail of stimulants, I still felt lacking in brass for my foray behind enemy lines. Twenty-one and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let’s talk about Drugs #realtalk
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-lets-talk-about-drugs-realtalk/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 14:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,David Charchoglyan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-lets-talk-about-drugs-realtalk/</guid>
        <description>Do you know why some drugs are called ‘Drugs’ with a capital D? Or why your school was so eager to drill into you that some things are bad no-questions-asked-because-I-said-so during those insufferable PSHE lessons? Why some substances are kept completely out of our reach and have a seven year …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get brought LOW | Reading as relaxation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-get-brought-low-reading-as-relaxation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 13:43:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-get-brought-low-reading-as-relaxation/</guid>
        <description>&amp;ldquo;Life without art is not worth living”
I don’t often write reviews. I find it hard to judge someone’s work – partially because I never feel like I have the authority or knowledge to publicly share my personal criticism, and partially because I believe in making art for the sake of art, which …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Higher Education faces depression epidemic
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-higher-education-faces-depression-epidemic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 13:23:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-higher-education-faces-depression-epidemic/</guid>
        <description>Recent years show an alarming trend amongst students. Rising rates of mental illness show little sign of slowing. In the past ten years, suicide rates have almost doubled. In York, up to 50% of ambulance call-outs to the university were for self-harm or suicide attempts. This is a far from localised …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Academy Awards 2017 | Our predictions of who will win, and who should win
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-academy-awards-2017-our-predictions-of-who-will-win-and-who-should-win/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 14:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-academy-awards-2017-our-predictions-of-who-will-win-and-who-should-win/</guid>
        <description> Best Director It seems likely that Damien Chazelle will snatch this award for La La Land, but it would be a pyrrhic victory, given that his far-superior breakout feature Whiplash didn’t even earn him a nomination. Chazelle manages to mine the classic trope box of old-fashioned Hollywood musicals, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Love is the drug you can’t get enough of
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-love-is-the-drug-you-cant-get-enough-of/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-love-is-the-drug-you-cant-get-enough-of/</guid>
        <description> Let’s be real. Love is a drug. It inhibits our ability to think clearly, turns us into terrible people, and makes us do stupid things. Face it, it’s far more harmful than a few hours gurning at the weekend. But just like with drugs, there are different kinds of highs, and so now, in honour of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are we killing the planet in style | Sustainable Fashion
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-are-we-killing-the-planet-in-style-sustainable-fashion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:47:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Eloise Hunt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-are-we-killing-the-planet-in-style-sustainable-fashion/</guid>
        <description>At the thought of pollution, we imagine raw sewage pumped into rivers, open-caste mines and oil spills. We don’t often think of our fluffy unicorn slippers or plaid shirts. But the overall impact the fashion industry has on our planet is shocking. The production of clothing has been estimated to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s a queer gal to do/see/watch/listen to? Our guide to your gal-pal culture fix
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-whats-a-queer-gal-to-doseewatchlisten-to-our-guide-to-your-gal-pal-culture-fix/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 15:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-whats-a-queer-gal-to-doseewatchlisten-to-our-guide-to-your-gal-pal-culture-fix/</guid>
        <description> Film Appropriate Behaviour
Desiree Akhavan directs and stars in this comedy about an American-Iranian bisexual going through a breakup. It’ll make you feel worse about your recent breakup but then, strangely, better. It’s pretty funny and feels quite real. The protagonist also struggles with coming …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Should the T be dropped from LGBT?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-should-the-t-be-dropped-from-lgbt/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 14:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elizabeth Windo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-should-the-t-be-dropped-from-lgbt/</guid>
        <description>It’s easy to look from the outside at a pride parade and see a unified grouping of similarly minded people. But under this facade of togetherness, within the LGBT community lies a volatile mixture of groups that sometimes have radically different goals. An example of this is the recent push that has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Being non-binary at Imperial is not fun
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-being-non-binary-at-imperial-is-not-fun/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 14:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-being-non-binary-at-imperial-is-not-fun/</guid>
        <description>There is a misconception held by many queer secondary school students that universities are very progressive and tolerant places. The It gets better project is all but built on this idea promoted by society that it’s okay if times are tough now, because one day you will escape your small town. You …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Starving anxiety into submission | Anorexia
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-starving-anxiety-into-submission-anorexia/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 18:07:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-starving-anxiety-into-submission-anorexia/</guid>
        <description>I thought the only way I could dull my anxiety was starving it. If I was dizzy and needed to concentrate hard on staying upright, there was no space left to worry. Before long I’d reach a comfortable haze, unable to carry a thought for more than a few seconds. The emptiness inside my stomach made …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students take to the streets to protest Trump | Are the days of political apathy over?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-students-take-to-the-streets-to-protest-trump-are-the-days-of-political-apathy-over/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 15:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-students-take-to-the-streets-to-protest-trump-are-the-days-of-political-apathy-over/</guid>
        <description>Donald Trump has consistently been on the collective consciousness for a while. Though Trump’s presidency could globally affect climate change and human rights, to name only a few areas of concern, amongst some journalistic circles, there’s the additional concern that the international focus on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Protesting Trump | The Women’s March through the eyes of Imperial students
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-protesting-trump-the-womens-march-through-the-eyes-of-imperial-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 14:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-protesting-trump-the-womens-march-through-the-eyes-of-imperial-students/</guid>
        <description>    Indira Mallik   Ana Villanueva | felix reader I asked myself a question the first time I heard about the Women’s March: Is it necessary? The answer is yes. I joined tens of thousands of people because I needed to share a message too. It was not a complaint. We advocated tolerance and respect for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BEEP BEEP BEEP | Brexit update
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-beep-beep-beep-brexit-update/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 14:19:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-beep-beep-beep-brexit-update/</guid>
        <description>The sun keeps on rising, the world keeps on spinning and the Brexit debate rages on. Last week Theresa May made a speech at Lancaster House which outlined her twelve point plan for the UK’s negotiation plan as she looks to trigger Article 50 and leave the European Union for good.
The main headline …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Millennials are all that can save us in this post-truth world
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-the-millennials-are-all-that-can-save-us-in-this-post-truth-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 15:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Giacomo I Boscaini-Gilroy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-the-millennials-are-all-that-can-save-us-in-this-post-truth-world/</guid>
        <description>As a year, 2016 really pissed me off. I remember when 2008 ended. I remember people saying that it would be consigned to history as the year of the Great Recession. My call is that 2016 will be seen as the year of the fuck-up. The future looks uncertain and shaky. No one planned for political …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The university meme page revolution
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-the-university-meme-page-revolution/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 15:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,Paul Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-the-university-meme-page-revolution/</guid>
        <description>T his strange world of memes which we currently find ourselves in – one where a president can be catapulted to the White House with the help of online fascists and Pepe the Frog – is terrifying. There was an undercurrent of darkness in the memes that defined 2016: we celebrated Harambe’s death as if …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A seat at the (culture) roundtable
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-a-seat-at-the-culture-roundtable/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 15:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-a-seat-at-the-culture-roundtable/</guid>
        <description>During the American election cycle on his comedy show Last Week Tonight, John Oliver had a running gag – “look up,” he’d say “that faint glimmer in the distance? That’s rock bottom.” So it has seemed for most of 2016; in almost every sphere, particularly in politics, bad news has been followed by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your favourite films of 2016
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-your-favourite-films-of-2016/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 14:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-your-favourite-films-of-2016/</guid>
        <description> Alex Heib, Max Lewis-Clarke and Meryl Anil 1. Arrival Intelligent sci-fi films are rare, with ones involving aliens rarer still. Arrival uses these foreign beings to examine how language shapes our view of the world, how it can be the source of conflict but also how it can be the solution. This …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An idiot’s guide to 2016
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-an-idiots-guide-to-2016/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 14:28:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-an-idiots-guide-to-2016/</guid>
        <description> It’s been a rollercoaster ride. Except a rollercoaster ride where you threw up on yourself at the start. But, let’s take a trip down memory lane; there are a few nuggets of joy to be found amongst the pile of crap that was 2016. Promise.
January So it didn’t really get off to the best of starts did …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Idiot’s Guide To A Post Brexit World
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-7-4-an-idiots-guide-to-a-post-brexit-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 09:55:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-7-4-an-idiots-guide-to-a-post-brexit-world/</guid>
        <description>So, we’re out. What now, eh? What came to pass last Thursday and early Friday morning was, whichever way you cut it, historic. No full country, this deep in the EU, has left it before and now we’ve got to deal with the fallout for better or for worse.
Chaos was the undoubtedly the adjective of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The FELIX Sex Survey 2016
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-the-felix-sex-survey-2016/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 09:01:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-the-felix-sex-survey-2016/</guid>
        <description>Here it is, for the sixth year running, the infamous FELIX Sex Survey results. Thank you so much to everyone who trusted us with your deepest, darkest, and occasionally unrealistic and obviously made-up secrets (we deleted those responses from our data). Six hundred or so of you took the time to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We interview the DPFS candidates
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-15-we-interview-the-dpfs-candidates/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 13:23:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-15-we-interview-the-dpfs-candidates/</guid>
        <description>We asked the DPFS candidates why they didn&amp;rsquo;t run for the role in March, and this is what they told us.
Sampriti Gupta: I could not run in the Leadership Elections in March because I had my final exams during that time which were my first priority. Instead I was planning on running next year …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Next year our sabbs become the highest paid in the country
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-next-year-our-sabbs-become-the-highest-paid-in-the-country/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 08:23:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-next-year-our-sabbs-become-the-highest-paid-in-the-country/</guid>
        <description>Next year’s sabbs, who were elected in March and take up their roles officially this August, will, on paper, become the best-paid full-time sabbatical officers in the country. They’ll have jumped from fourteenth highest-paid sabbs to the highest, beating last year’s highest, LSE, who pay a modest …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How much does the Rector get paid?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-how-much-does-the-rector-get-paid/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 09:06:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-how-much-does-the-rector-get-paid/</guid>
        <description>The college’s Rector does a very important job. They go on Radio 4 for us, they sign open letters in newspapers, and if you’re lucky and they’re not having a round off, they shake your hand at graduation. The amount these members of staff get paid is always a point of contention.
This week, we took …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Imperial endowment fund – what are we investing in?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-the-imperial-endowment-fund-what-are-we-investing-in/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 08:43:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-the-imperial-endowment-fund-what-are-we-investing-in/</guid>
        <description>Imperial’s investment portfolio is a well-known part of the college’s assets. Much like a savings account, a board decides where we invest year on year, to make the most of our stacks of cash and earn us interest. This is done by most universities, and whereas Oxford and Cambridge’s endowments are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FELIX investigates study drugs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-felix-investigates-study-drugs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 09:02:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-felix-investigates-study-drugs/</guid>
        <description>Like all good things in life, this article starts with a disclaimer: FELIX is by no means advocating the use of these so-called study drugs. I don’t know about you, but shitting every hour doesn’t scream productive work mode to me, – each to their own. We’re just giving you some facts and student …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What makes a good GUM clinic?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-what-makes-a-good-gum-clinic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 09:01:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-what-makes-a-good-gum-clinic/</guid>
        <description>Apparently I engage in risky sexual behaviour. This means that like the good millennial I am, I have to periodically get tested to make sure that I&amp;rsquo;m free from the nasties that make sex a little less fun and a little more infectious (and not in a good way). Although there are many sexual …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to have sex in halls
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-how-to-have-sex-in-halls/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 09:00:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-how-to-have-sex-in-halls/</guid>
        <description>With exams finishing and the sun coming out, Imperial is a hive of frenzied sexual activity, as inhibitions are shed in anticipation of the long summer break. But if you live in a shared room in halls, it strongly limits the privacy available for the exciting sexual encounters that we’re all …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Virtual reality porn is a game-changer
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-virtual-reality-porn-is-a-game-changer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 08:58:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-virtual-reality-porn-is-a-game-changer/</guid>
        <description>When Palmer Luckey kickstarted the virtual reality revolution in 2012 I doubt he expected that one of primary uses of his new technology would be pornography. We’ve seen smartphones change the way we watched porn, and VR is set to do the same. While 3D porn itself is nothing new (it’s been around …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An idiot’s guide to the EU referendum
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-an-idiots-guide-to-the-eu-referendum/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 08:57:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-an-idiots-guide-to-the-eu-referendum/</guid>
        <description>Over the course of the last UK election period and for the bulk of 2016 so far, the media and news in general has been focussed on the UK’s membership within the European Union, but what’s actually going on?
Where did the EU come from?
In essence the European Union (EU) is a group of 28 countries …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I’m a slut and proud
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-im-a-slut-and-proud/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:45:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-im-a-slut-and-proud/</guid>
        <description>This article was published as part of FELIX&amp;rsquo;s Sex Survey launch. Do the survey here.
I’ve been called a slut more times than I can count, both as an insult and as a compliment. Whilst some people recoil from the notion of a sexually empowered female, many celebrate us girls who openly love …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Iconic sex toys that changed the world
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-iconic-sex-toys-that-changed-the-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:43:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-iconic-sex-toys-that-changed-the-world/</guid>
        <description> This article was published as part of FELIX&amp;rsquo;s Sex Survey launch. Do the survey here.
If there’s one thing that I’ve learnt over the course of my adult life, it’s how to get myself off, and I don’t think there’s any shame in admitting that. In recent years, more and more women have begun …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What’s your degree worth now?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-whats-your-degree-worth-now/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:34:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-whats-your-degree-worth-now/</guid>
        <description>We’re constantly being told that degrees aren’t as valuable as they used to be. And fair enough. Your mate from home’s 2:2 in film and media studies might not expect to be as valuable as your mum’s desmond in computing from the 80s, but an Imperial degree is an Imperial degree, right?
Perhaps not. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We’re having a Mayor-off
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-20-were-having-a-mayor-off/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 14:54:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-20-were-having-a-mayor-off/</guid>
        <description> Next Thursday, Londoners go to the polls to vote in their new Mayor of London. Twice-elected Conservative Boris Johnson has moved onto bigger and better things, and now Labour’s Sadiq Khan and the Conservative Zac Goldsmith are going head to head below in this: our comparison of the two …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Being a virgin isn’t a big deal anymore
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-being-a-virgin-isnt-a-big-deal-anymore/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 11:47:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-being-a-virgin-isnt-a-big-deal-anymore/</guid>
        <description>This article was published as part of FELIX&amp;rsquo;s Sex Survey launch. Do the survey here.
Out of all my friends I was set to be one of the first to lose it, and by it I mean my virginity.
I don’t really know why. I guess it’s just because I had a series of boyfriends, quite a few guy friends and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We need to talk about contraception
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-we-need-to-talk-about-contraception/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 11:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-we-need-to-talk-about-contraception/</guid>
        <description>This article was published as part of FELIX&amp;rsquo;s Sex Survey launch. Do the survey here.
In the UK, we’re lucky enough to have access to free contraception, regardless of who you are. The NHS provides 15 different methods, ranging from the provision of free condoms, to implanted devices, to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A letter to...the man who broke my heart
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-a-letter-tothe-man-who-broke-my-heart/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 11:42:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-a-letter-tothe-man-who-broke-my-heart/</guid>
        <description>This article was published as part of FELIX&amp;rsquo;s Sex Survey launch. Do the survey here.
I learnt so much from you.
You taught me how to love like I’ve never loved before. You taught me how to cry more than I’ve ever cried before. You taught me how to voice my opinions, to argue, to debate. You …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I had sex in the tunnels under Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-15-i-had-sex-in-the-tunnels-under-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 09:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-15-i-had-sex-in-the-tunnels-under-imperial/</guid>
        <description> Heads were banged, and knees were scraped
 This article was published as part of FELIX&amp;rsquo;s Sex Survey launch. Do the survey here.
It was a bright, sunny day in the summer of 2014. The renovation of the West Basement of Beit was well underway, and amidst the flurry of activity, I discovered some …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The women of Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-the-women-of-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 11:34:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-the-women-of-imperial/</guid>
        <description>The odds are good, but the goods are odd, or so goes the saying on the ‘talent’ at our beloved university. It’s an oft-referred trope of Imperial: on open days, we’re warned that there’s no shortage of dudes, and forced conversations during freshers’ week often resort to, “Wow, there are loads of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“I’d say I lost 90% of my friends circle when I said that I was going to transition”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-id-say-i-lost-90-of-my-friends-circle-when-i-said-that-i-was-going-to-transition/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 11:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ben Williams,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-id-say-i-lost-90-of-my-friends-circle-when-i-said-that-i-was-going-to-transition/</guid>
        <description>Iam ten minutes late by the time I get on the line to Anjeli Patel – not something I reckon would be taken lightly at Ernst &amp;amp; Young LLP, where she works as an associate in assurance within Wealth and Asset management.
Ms Patel was a guest speaker during Imperial’s LGBT+ week, and FELIX took the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Things you’re desperate to ask your Muslim lab partner
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-things-youre-desperate-to-ask-your-muslim-lab-partner/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 11:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-things-youre-desperate-to-ask-your-muslim-lab-partner/</guid>
        <description> Muslims are probably one of the easiest groups of people to identify from the way we dress, girls being more obvious than guys. As Muslims we find that there’s a lot of confusion about why we do certain things and people speculate because they’re too scared to ask in case we get offended. Contrary …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Could Imperial ever go on a rent strike?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-could-imperial-ever-go-on-a-rent-strike/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 11:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-could-imperial-ever-go-on-a-rent-strike/</guid>
        <description>We’ve had our fair share of housing disputes at Imperial.
If you think people don’t care, check out the ICTV’s ‘Imperial Questions Live’ debate on the subject of Weeks hall from last year. Think union council but with ironed shirts and better behaviour since it’s on YouTube for eternity and there …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An idiot’s guide to the US Election
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-an-idiots-guide-to-the-us-election/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 09:07:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-an-idiots-guide-to-the-us-election/</guid>
        <description>The United States Presidential election. The $6 billion race for the White House. The battle between Democrats and Republicans, Donkeys versus Elephants. Like an Olympics for politicians, it happens every four years and has the potential to shape world economics and policy until the next one.
But …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>12 Jar Jar Binks GIFs That Sum Up Your Life At Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-16-12-jar-jar-binks-gifs-that-sum-up-your-life-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 18:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,Felix Editor,Theresa Davey,Grace G Rahman,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-16-12-jar-jar-binks-gifs-that-sum-up-your-life-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description> 1. When You Arrive Sober At Your First ACC  2. When You Sit Your First Exam At Imperial    Tumblr   3. When You Can&amp;rsquo;t Decide Between Pieminister And The Salad Bar    Tumblr   4. When You Fall For Your Lab Partner    Tumblr   5. When It&amp;rsquo;s Five To Nine And You&amp;rsquo;re Desperate For The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Alumnus goes Galactic
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-alumnus-goes-galactic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 14:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Parikshat Singh,Benjamin Fernando,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-alumnus-goes-galactic/</guid>
        <description>Vice President of Virgin Galactic and Imperial alumnus, Jonathon Firth, is involved in developing the first commercial spaceflight company. He attended the 2015 SpaceLab conference last month, where he cornered him for an interview.
Felix: Would you mind telling us a little about your background, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In conversation with the author, documentary maker and popular philosopher, Alain de Botton
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-18-in-conversation-with-the-author-documentary-maker-and-popular-philosopher-alain-de-botton/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2015 20:53:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-18-in-conversation-with-the-author-documentary-maker-and-popular-philosopher-alain-de-botton/</guid>
        <description>There are not many people who can say they have set up an international school, written books that have been bestsellers in 30 countries, and given two TED talks. Fewer still can say they have re-hung an art museum and worked as Heathrow airport’s first ever writer-in-residence – but the author, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let’s talk about sex...ual health
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-4-lets-talk-about-sexual-health/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2015 23:39:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecily Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-4-lets-talk-about-sexual-health/</guid>
        <description>This year 65% of sexually active students admitted to having had unprotected sex in the past. 31% of you have apparently been well behaved, while the remaining 4% chose not to say whether they had done it or not.
Remember you can pick up condoms for free at a number of places on campus, including …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The transgender community at Imperial: those who are silently struggling
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-4-the-transgender-community-at-imperial-those-who-are-silently-struggling/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2015 23:37:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-4-the-transgender-community-at-imperial-those-who-are-silently-struggling/</guid>
        <description>The Felix Sex Survey found that 9 of the respondents do not identify with the gender they were assigned at birth. A third of those respondents said they were unhappy with their sex life, and a few commented about the issues they face as transgender individuals.
Some cited difficulty in finding …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Never Have I Ever”: The sexual adventures of Imperial students
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-4-never-have-i-ever-the-sexual-adventures-of-imperial-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2015 23:36:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-4-never-have-i-ever-the-sexual-adventures-of-imperial-students/</guid>
        <description>The perennially popular drinking game gets easier with the arrival of the sex survey. If you’re looking for an easy way to get people to drink, look no further than the old classics: fuck buddies, and one night stands.
53% of students have had a one night stand, with the males proving more likely to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Love and relationships at Imperial College London
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-4-love-and-relationships-at-imperial-college-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2015 23:33:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecily Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-4-love-and-relationships-at-imperial-college-london/</guid>
        <description>According to this year’s survey data, just 41% of Imperial students are single or “not seeing anyone” exclusively. A surprisingly high 46% of you are in an exclusive relationship at the moment, and 8% are seeing someone but “non-exclusively”.
4% are seeing multiple people (get you), while 1% did not …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>So how happy are Imperial students with their sex lives?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-4-so-how-happy-are-imperial-students-with-their-sex-lives/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2015 23:32:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecily Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-4-so-how-happy-are-imperial-students-with-their-sex-lives/</guid>
        <description>Overall, 62% of us are ‘happy’ or ‘very happy’ with our sex lives at Imperial. Only 21% reported that they were ‘unhappy’ or ‘very unhappy’ (sorry folks), while 15% didn’t feel one way or the other.
The remaining 2% did not wish to say how they felt – so it’s anyone’s guess why they’re filling out a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Universities and Student Unions employ peculiar methods to relieve exam stress
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-21-universities-and-student-unions-employ-peculiar-methods-to-relieve-exam-stress/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2015 20:38:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecily Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-21-universities-and-student-unions-employ-peculiar-methods-to-relieve-exam-stress/</guid>
        <description>Exam season is most definitely upon us, and this year more and more Universities and Student Unions are attempting to reduce students’ stress levels with a variety of bizarre initiatives ranging from Puppy Therapy to ball pits.
In an ever-growing trend, students are being encouraged to put down …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Do you want a firetruck with your beer?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-1-do-you-want-a-firetruck-with-your-beer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:34:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonathan Masters,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-1-do-you-want-a-firetruck-with-your-beer/</guid>
        <description>Craft beer has seen an exponential increase in popularity in the last four years, and with that increased demand have come entrepreneurs seeking to profit.
However, some of those capitalising on the trend were more likely to be found in the lab than down the bar only a few years ago. Imperial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What does it mean to have a mental health problem at Imperial?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-20-what-does-it-mean-to-have-a-mental-health-problem-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2015 14:58:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>George Butcher,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-20-what-does-it-mean-to-have-a-mental-health-problem-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>If you have 400 Facebook friends aged 16 to 24, the chances are that 14 of them have generalised anxiety disorder, 35 of them have self-harmed and 24 of them have attempted suicide. Over our life time, a quarter of us will suffer from a mental health problem.
Felix has investigated what it means to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Getting close to Cowley
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-getting-close-to-cowley/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 23:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xuan Chen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-getting-close-to-cowley/</guid>
        <description>Professor Steven Cowley is the CEO of the United Kingdom Atomic Energy Authority and a part-time professor in plasma physics here at Imperial College. But that’s not what catches the attention of an entire cohort of physics undergraduates every year – it’s his lectures, where his charisma and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Behold, the UK’s finest collegiate a cappella groups
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-30-behold-the-uks-finest-collegiate-a-cappella-groups/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 00:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xuan Chen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-30-behold-the-uks-finest-collegiate-a-cappella-groups/</guid>
        <description>Last weekend Imperial College played host to the vivacious, nerve-wracking, and outrageously outstanding International Championship of Collegiate A Cappella (ICCA) UK Semifinal competition: a massive undertaking attracting the best unaccompanied singing groups in the world.Nine of the UK’s best …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Exchange your unwanted clothes for new outfits at a fraction of the price
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-16-exchange-your-unwanted-clothes-for-new-outfits-at-a-fraction-of-the-price/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 15:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vivien Tang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-16-exchange-your-unwanted-clothes-for-new-outfits-at-a-fraction-of-the-price/</guid>
        <description>Do you want to take part in the first Clotho exchange on campus? Click attending on their facebook event now and don&amp;rsquo;t forget to bring your clothes to Sherfield lobby on Tuesday the 20th and Thursday the 22nd of January.
Our story began two months ago, when we founded our sustainable fashion …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s go hyper
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-lets-go-hyper/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 00:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xuan Chen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-lets-go-hyper/</guid>
        <description>The biannual gathering of dedicated Japanese markets and exhibitors took place two weekends ago, and managed an exhibition which was a verifiable smorgasbord of Japanese culture.
Exhibitions like these are a clarion call for like-minded small and medium business owners to come together in one place …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What would Wheeler do?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-what-would-wheeler-do/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 20:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bernadett Tildy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-what-would-wheeler-do/</guid>
        <description>Bernadett: Where are you from and do you think it affected your outlook of Imperial?
Tom: In a very positive way, yes! I am from Salcombe in south Devon. The international population at Imperial has always been very stimulating for me. I went from a very un-diverse community to meeting people at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The biggest Forum to discuss change
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-the-biggest-forum-to-discuss-change/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 20:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pippa Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-the-biggest-forum-to-discuss-change/</guid>
        <description>Climate change is a hotter topic than ever. The 2014 IPCC report, hot from the press, recommends that 80%of the world’s power should be from low-carbon sources by 2050. This will limit the warming of the atmosphere to 2°C, the agreed ‘tipping point’ for disastrous consequences.
UN Secretary General …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Educating the masses on Funding
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-educating-the-masses-on-funding/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 20:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrew Tranter,Alex Savell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-educating-the-masses-on-funding/</guid>
        <description>Higher Education Funding (HEF) is certainly not sexy. Like British Politics it has all the charisma of your average British politician. But it is important. It’s important because defining the future of how Universities receive funding is something that will affect thousands of young people who (for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The force behind Freshers’ Fair
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-the-force-behind-freshers-fair/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 23:51:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bernadett Tildy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-the-force-behind-freshers-fair/</guid>
        <description>B: What clubs and societies are you currently involved in or have you been a member of?
A: Last year I was in Muay Thai, Karate, Ju-Jitsu, Sinfonietta Orchestra and I used to be involved in the 2 clubs my friends were setting up: Comedy and North American society.
B: Did you always want to become a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“I’m a massive nerd, I like sci-fi and riding horses.”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-im-a-massive-nerd-i-like-sci-fi-and-riding-horses/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 23:47:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bernadett Tildy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-im-a-massive-nerd-i-like-sci-fi-and-riding-horses/</guid>
        <description>Bernadett: What’s your academic background?
Alex: I started at Imperial in 2006, doing Physics. I did the 4 year course, then I did my MRes in 2010&amp;frasl;11. And since then, I’ve been doing my PhD.
B: Where are you from, and how has it affected your outlook on Imperial?
A: I’m from Bath. Yeah, I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Prof. Sir John Pendry, the physicist famous for inventing the invisiblity cloak
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-prof-sir-john-pendry-the-physicist-famous-for-inventing-the-invisiblity-cloak/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 23:34:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Fernando,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-prof-sir-john-pendry-the-physicist-famous-for-inventing-the-invisiblity-cloak/</guid>
        <description>Professor Sir John Pendry, FRS, holds a Chair in Theoretical Solid State Physics here at Imperial. In 2014 he was awarded the $1M Kavli Prize by the Norwegian Academy of Science and Letters in recognition of his work in the field of nano-optics. This article is a summary of an interview for Felix …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pascal Loose, Deputy President (Education) is here to give students the satisfaction they deserve
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-pascal-loose-deputy-president-education-is-here-to-give-students-the-satisfaction-they-deserve/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 23:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bernadett Tildy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-pascal-loose-deputy-president-education-is-here-to-give-students-the-satisfaction-they-deserve/</guid>
        <description>Bernadett: Where are you from?
Pascal: I’m from Belgium, born in Brussells but my family is German.
B: Do you think that the Sabb team can accurately represent the international student population of Imperial?
P: The Sabb team is not as diverse as we hoped it to be, or as we could be, but in the end …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“I came from a generation that thought that misery and intellect were synonymous.&#34;
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-i-came-from-a-generation-that-thought-that-misery-and-intellect-were-synonymous/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 22:46:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Fernando,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-i-came-from-a-generation-that-thought-that-misery-and-intellect-were-synonymous/</guid>
        <description>BF: Why don’t you tell me a little bit about yourself, and why you want to be the next Dean?
TW: I grew up in North London on a council estate, and today turning up at the place that when I was young was the place to be to study science still shocks me. I do my research and my teaching, but how can …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Everyone loves a bit of D... PW
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-everyone-loves-a-bit-of-d-pw/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 22:42:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bernadett Tildy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-everyone-loves-a-bit-of-d-pw/</guid>
        <description>B: Where are you from, and how has it affected your outlook on Imperial?
C: I’m from Bristol. I suppose Bristol isn’t that diverse, so coming to London, specifically Imperial, has been a very enjoyable experience for me, meeting lots of different people from lots of different countries. It’s been …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Comic Convention you’d be crazy to miss but even crazier to attend
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-the-comic-convention-youd-be-crazy-to-miss-but-even-crazier-to-attend/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 19:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xuan Chen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-the-comic-convention-youd-be-crazy-to-miss-but-even-crazier-to-attend/</guid>
        <description>Why would someone with no knowledge of any anime, comic books, and video games attend an event aimed at bringing these people together? Curiosity, that’s why.
The MCM London Comic Convention starts much earlier than I anticipated; costumed attendees with bright hair and elaborate costumes board the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are you up to the Challenge?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-are-you-up-to-the-challenge/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 19:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pietro Aronica,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-are-you-up-to-the-challenge/</guid>
        <description>What is the capital of Kenya? Which is the largest moon of the Solar System? Who is the only person to have been awarded two unshared Nobel Prizes?
For many people, the answer to those questions is “who cares?”, or, if they’re feeling charitable, “just google it”. For a select few, however, being …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Scrabble World Championships 2014: Grudge Match Against an 8 year-old
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-scrabble-world-championships-2014-grudge-match-against-an-8-year-old/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 13:05:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-scrabble-world-championships-2014-grudge-match-against-an-8-year-old/</guid>
        <description>Away from the top of the leader board, one of the most notable players here at tournament is New Zealand’s Lewis Hawkins. What sets him out from the rest of the crowd is that, being aged 8, he’s at least a decade younger than anyone else here. Learning from my failures in adopting the direct …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Scrabble World Championships: Prince Goes To Prague
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-scrabble-world-championships-prince-goes-to-prague/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 13:02:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-scrabble-world-championships-prince-goes-to-prague/</guid>
        <description>Prince goes to Prague
On December 6th at around midday, at least 55 games were taking place at the SCRABBLE Champions’ Tournament in Prague. 110 players from across the globe had convened in Prague for a tilt at the title of SCRABBLE World Champion and a share of the €25,000 prize pot. Players from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pirates: A Review With Scientists
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-20-pirates-a-review-with-scientists/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2014 16:13:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-20-pirates-a-review-with-scientists/</guid>
        <description>Without making so bold a claim so as to say that we’ve never watched porn, it’s fair to say that neither of us are connoisseurs of the cinematographic genre. However, the 2005 feature-length Pirates, with its million-dollar budget, was the most expensive pornographic film ever made at the time, a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Up to Scratch at Shapes &amp; Blades?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-12-up-to-scratch-at-shapes-blades/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 17:56:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Harveen Hayer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-12-up-to-scratch-at-shapes-blades/</guid>
        <description>It couldn’t wait until after exams, my split ends were like the multiple-headed monster from Disney’s Hercules. Thus a trip to the hairdressers was to be the scenario of choice one Thursday evening after labs.
Usually I go home to get my haircut (courtesy of Bank of Mum) but a quick sift of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Energy Efficiency at Imperial – How Green Are We?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-12-energy-efficiency-at-imperial-how-green-are-we/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 17:54:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sebastian Gosden,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-12-energy-efficiency-at-imperial-how-green-are-we/</guid>
        <description>Imperial is a big organisation. Fifteen thousand students, six thousand members of staff, nine campus areas and a billion pound annual budget. By account of its sheer size, the College consumes a great deal of resources: energy, plastics, water, lavatory paper, and it all stacks up. Fortunately, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix goes to #SPANC for the weekend
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-felix-goes-to-spanc-for-the-weekend/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 02:03:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence de Lussy Kubisa,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-felix-goes-to-spanc-for-the-weekend/</guid>
        <description>Lugging the recommended 200 copies of Felix, I skilfully avoided Friday rush hour and made my way to King’s Cross to attend the Student Publication Association National Conference (#SPANC) being hosted at Nottingham Trent University. Due to an administrative oversight (idiocy) tickets were …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tell me friends, what is your Secret?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-tell-me-friends-what-is-your-secret/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 02:01:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-tell-me-friends-what-is-your-secret/</guid>
        <description>It’s often said that in the Internet Age there is no more anonymity but this is only half true. Yes, thanks to Facebook I’ll know that the girl from my old English class in Year 12 has just broken up with her boyfriend and is playing Taylor Swift on a tear-filled triumphant loop on Spotify but the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Helping friends with depression
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-helping-friends-with-depression/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 00:59:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marissa Lewis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-helping-friends-with-depression/</guid>
        <description>In the last Wellbeing section, I wrote about my experience with recovering from depression. Maybe it’s because I don’t make a habit of talking about my mental illness but I was genuinely surprised at the positive reception it received from friends, acquaintances and even complete strangers. As a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Felix Guide to Revision 2014 - Part 1
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-8-the-felix-guide-to-revision-2014-part-1/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 13:52:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-8-the-felix-guide-to-revision-2014-part-1/</guid>
        <description>Most of you will be revising (or trying to) over the Easter break, either panicking or comfortably smug and prepared, having started revision before the year started.
Either way, following on from our Fresher&amp;rsquo;s study advice article, we at Felix would like to add our “two cents” into the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Cancer Envy Campaign
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-28-the-cancer-envy-campaign/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2014 11:47:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Plummer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-28-the-cancer-envy-campaign/</guid>
        <description>Pancreatic cancer has the lowest survival rate out of the common cancers; only three percent make it past five years, with the majority only making it to 4-6 months after diagnosis. The campaign aimed to improve public awareness regarding this. Its tagline portrayed how those with pancreatic cancer …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Three is no longer a crowd
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-28-three-is-no-longer-a-crowd/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2014 11:44:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nadiah Fernandes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-28-three-is-no-longer-a-crowd/</guid>
        <description>We are even closer to seeing Britain become the first country in the world to allow a three person baby to be born through IVF, as draft rules were announced last week to regulate the process. This is in an attempt to help mothers with faulty mitochondria bear healthy children. Mitochondria are the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A call for doctors
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-28-a-call-for-doctors/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2014 11:42:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thomas Stroud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-28-a-call-for-doctors/</guid>
        <description>The number of doctors travelling abroad on ‘humanitarian’ missions in order to provide help for the millions of people suffering in less developed countries is nanoscopic. In fact, more doctors in the less developed countries such as Ghana, Sierra Leone and Syria are migrating to the UK because of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dirty Stethoscopes
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-28-dirty-stethoscopes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2014 10:42:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thomas Stroud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-28-dirty-stethoscopes/</guid>
        <description>A study published this month has displayed the possibility that a doctor’s stethoscope could be a major source of bacterial transmission in clinical practice. The study, published in an issue of Mayo Clinic Proceedings, exposed how stethoscopes contain a huge number of bacteria relative to a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Night of Sun, Sex and Slavery with Imperial Cinema
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-a-night-of-sun-sex-and-slavery-with-imperial-cinema/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 13:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ellen Mathieson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-a-night-of-sun-sex-and-slavery-with-imperial-cinema/</guid>
        <description>It’s amazing how things happen and time passes without you realising it. For some of you reading this, the upcoming Spring All-Nighter could very well be your last. This could be your final chance to sit in a crowded room and spend an evening, a night and part of a morning watching some of the best …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>International Night Successes
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-international-night-successes/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 13:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charmain T X Li,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-international-night-successes/</guid>
        <description>International Night (I-Night): Beyond Barriers 2014 organised by the Overseas Societies Committee (OSC) took place whho weeks ago in the Great Hall. Bringing together 10 different Imperial College student societies in a nail-biting competition, it involved colourful acts from Thai Society, Hellenic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Face to Face with Abdulla Sheikh
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-24-face-to-face-with-abdulla-sheikh/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 03:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-24-face-to-face-with-abdulla-sheikh/</guid>
        <description>Can you tell us a bit about your current business in the sustainability sector?
Yes I can! Our name is Whotter; our team consists of myself, Carlo, a PHD from Physics and Arthur a Masters student from Paris. We are trying to harness green energy from waste as never done before. It’s an innovative …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>House of Cards from the House of Lords
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-24-house-of-cards-from-the-house-of-lords/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 03:36:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Morton,Diana Lucaci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-24-house-of-cards-from-the-house-of-lords/</guid>
        <description>How has your life changed as a result of writing House of Cards?
It totally… I wrote it as an accident. I wrote it as a result of a bet. Actually, I didn’t even write it as a bet, I was challenged on a holiday to see if I could write a book and I was really bored and had nothing else to do on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Should the Role of Government Chief Scientific Advisor be Democratised?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-17-should-the-role-of-government-chief-scientific-advisor-be-democratised/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2014 17:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aamna Mohdin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-17-should-the-role-of-government-chief-scientific-advisor-be-democratised/</guid>
        <description>What would happen if the next UK Government Chief Scientific Adviser (GCSA) was elected through a public vote? That’s exactly what a group of us from the science communication masters are attempting to find out. The GCSA is the head of the Government Office for Science, and the personal adviser on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Obituary: Bob Crow
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-17-obituary-bob-crow/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2014 17:19:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Fernando,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-17-obituary-bob-crow/</guid>
        <description>London awoke to a shock on Tuesday morning with the news that Bob Crow, the leader of Rail, Maritime and Transport (RMT) union had died at the age of 52. During the RMT strikes last month that crippled London Crow sprang to national prominence as the situation pitted him against Boris Johnson, Mayor …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Recovering from depression
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-recovering-from-depression/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 04:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marissa Lewis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-recovering-from-depression/</guid>
        <description>There’s been a movement in the last couple of years to get people talking about their experiences with mental health, whether it’s on a national scale such as Mind’s Time to Talk campaign or Imperial’s own OpenMinds campaign. There’s also been a move to try and explain life with a mental illness to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Exploring the Student Consultation Framework
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-exploring-the-student-consultation-framework/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 04:39:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>David Goldsmith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-exploring-the-student-consultation-framework/</guid>
        <description>Dear Students, I am writing to ask for your feedback on something I am developing. Running for the position of Union President I promised, in my manifesto, to “Demand a new mechanism to ensure student consultation from the outset of College decision-making” and in doing so help prevent situations …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
