<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/apk06/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/apk06/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Ecology on a massive scale
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-25-ecology-on-a-massive-scale/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 23:52:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander P H Kendall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-25-ecology-on-a-massive-scale/</guid>
        <description>On the first day, as we drove to plot ‘D’, I thought it would be simple. I had worked in tropical rainforests before; they had been easy to walk in, an open understory with sparse seedlings caused by the intense shading of the canopy. This forest however, as I discovered after hours of tripping, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mystery over Masters fee rises
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-mystery-over-masters-fee-rises/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 21:35:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander P H Kendall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-mystery-over-masters-fee-rises/</guid>
        <description>Since the government cut funding for higher education and Undergraduate fees were forced up, much has been speculated about the corresponding rise in Postgraduate fees. Though technically the funding from the Government for Postgraduate fees was also cut, since it is lumped in with the total …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union letter clarifying future of Summer Ball
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-union-letter-clarifying-future-of-summer-ball/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 20:38:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander P H Kendall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-union-letter-clarifying-future-of-summer-ball/</guid>
        <description>Note: This letter is from the Union, the author has been selected as Alex Kendall simply for convenience.
The Summer Ball is, for many, an opportunity for a final party with friends before the summer holidays or even the job market for anyone finishing their degree and so, rightly, students want a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rifles, polar bears, and sub-zero temperatures
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-rifles-polar-bears-and-sub-zero-temperatures/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 20:24:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander P H Kendall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-rifles-polar-bears-and-sub-zero-temperatures/</guid>
        <description>&amp;ldquo;So of course you’re going to have to take rifles.”
“What?”
We had gone to see Lorraine Craig, Chair of Imperial’s Exploration Board, about our proposed expedition.
“Rifles. There will be polar bears on Svalbard; they outnumber people. I’ve had them poke their heads into my tent once or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Broken promises
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-broken-promises/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 19:27:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander P H Kendall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-broken-promises/</guid>
        <description>Last week’s Felix headline announced that I accused Professor Dallman, the Principle of Natural Sciences, of lying to the College Council. Those are not the exact words that I used (I said she lied to the Union President and misled College Council), but the implications are large and it is worth …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Review is right
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-the-review-is-right/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 18:53:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander P H Kendall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-the-review-is-right/</guid>
        <description>The Browne Review aims to advise the Government on changes to the system of Higher Education Funding. Although the headline proposal has been to allow universities to set their own fees, the proposals in the review would, if enacted, mean that anyone could go to university regardless of wealth. It …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
