<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/nk1515/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/nk1515/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>This week’s science picture
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-this-weeks-science-picture/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 09:24:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Natasha Khaleeq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-this-weeks-science-picture/</guid>
        <description>With Euro 2016 in full swing there is no better time to explore the science of football. Why are some players such as Cristiano Ronaldo naturally gifted whereas others need to work hard in nurturing their skill? Dr. Manning, at the University of Liverpool, published research that suggests football …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This week’s science picture
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-this-weeks-science-picture/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 08:27:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Natasha Khaleeq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-this-weeks-science-picture/</guid>
        <description>Coral bleaching has severely impacted the Great Barrier Reef over the past month. The corals, which are in constant competition with algae for light and nutrients, seem to be losing the battle, with many bleached coral skeletons completely engulfed in algae. Pictures and testimonials from Lizard …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This week’s science picture
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-this-weeks-science-picture/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 09:23:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Natasha Khaleeq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-this-weeks-science-picture/</guid>
        <description>Oceanic toxin levels have increased due to harmful algal blooms (HABs) which plague shellfish and in turn affect the humans that consume them. Recently NOAA and partners deployed an underwater robot that measures toxicity. The robot, known as the Environmental Sample Processor (ESP), was made at the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This week’s science picture
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-this-weeks-science-picture/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 08:57:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Natasha Khaleeq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-this-weeks-science-picture/</guid>
        <description>For 107 hours Portugal ran on renewable energy alone. From the 7th to the 11th May the country’s electricity consumption was completely covered by renewable sources. Data analysis of national energy network figures revealed this. The Portuguese desire for clean energy was encouraged by the EU’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This week’s science picture
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-this-weeks-science-picture/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 09:09:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Natasha Khaleeq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-this-weeks-science-picture/</guid>
        <description>Large shoals of fish attract a range of predators including multiple species of whale. A recent study though, found that although many species might be feasting on herring at the same time, whales tend to stick with their own kind when preying. By mapping different whale calls, research found …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This week’s science picture
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-this-weeks-science-picture/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 09:03:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Natasha Khaleeq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-this-weeks-science-picture/</guid>
        <description>Conservationists have launched a worldwide campaign asking the public to help combat illegal wildlife trade. Despite efforts to prevent the billion pound industry, it continues to grow. A recent increase in poaching threatening species has raised concerns about the long-term survival of iconic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This week’s science picture
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-this-weeks-science-picture/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 09:56:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Natasha Khaleeq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-this-weeks-science-picture/</guid>
        <description>Halley’s Comet, a ball of ice and rock left over from the creation of the Milky Way, only makes an appearance every 75 years, so sadly we have to wait until 2061 before we get another glimpse of it. However, we are in the midst of meteor shower. Earth is twirling though the tail of Halley’s Comet. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Women of Imperial: Professor Jo Haigh
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-women-of-imperial-professor-jo-haigh/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 11:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Natasha Khaleeq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-women-of-imperial-professor-jo-haigh/</guid>
        <description>Professor Joanna Haigh is one of Imperial’s leading scientists. In 2009, she became the first woman to become Head of the Physics Department. As she’s eager to say herself, “It’s a great department and a lot of fantastic science is going on here.”
Recently she’s become co-director of Imperial’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This week’s science picture
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-this-weeks-science-picture/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 11:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Natasha Khaleeq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-this-weeks-science-picture/</guid>
        <description>Claudia Schulz, a PhD student in the Department of Computing, has been awarded Imperial College’s Best Graduate Teaching Assistant Award. She hopes that “showing children what cool tech jobs are out there and having role models” is a great way to increase the number of female scientists. By becoming …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This week’s science picture
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-this-weeks-science-picture/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 11:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Natasha Khaleeq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-this-weeks-science-picture/</guid>
        <description>Unmanned micro air vehicles (MAVs) are being used for a range of applications, from surveying dangerous areas to delivering packages. So far however, long range and high manoeuvrability are mutually exclusive. A collaboration of Imperial with Southampton, is developing a MAV prototype with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This week’s science picture
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-this-weeks-science-picture/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 11:36:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Natasha Khaleeq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-this-weeks-science-picture/</guid>
        <description>Junior doctors are not going to accept the new contracts that Jeremy Hunt is trying to impose on them, so they’re planning three more strikes as well as launching a judicial review. The government condemned the announcement, arguing that the contract will improve services. However, Dr Johann …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This week’s science picture
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-this-weeks-science-picture/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 11:20:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Natasha Khaleeq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-this-weeks-science-picture/</guid>
        <description>Two black holes merged billions of light years away, causing a ripple in the fabric of spacetime big enough to be measured by scientists at the LIGO Collaboration. The results provide further support for Einstein’s theory of general relativity.
The 4km long interferometers at LIGO simultaneously …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This week’s science picture
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-this-weeks-science-picture/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 11:33:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Natasha Khaleeq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-this-weeks-science-picture/</guid>
        <description>Guerilla Science held their V-Day event last Monday at The Book Club. The night titled ‘An Evening of Lust, Sex and Brains’ aimed at demonstrating how senses and brains react when people meet that special someone. Guests were to undertake several challenges based on scientific findings, all while …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This week’s science picture
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-this-weeks-science-picture/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 12:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Natasha Khaleeq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-this-weeks-science-picture/</guid>
        <description>From space, Earth is a sensational sight often hard to grasp because seeing where all of human history has occurred, can be quite emotional and very impactful. As time goes by, visible signs of climate change start to appear. Those on land may notice air pollution, deforestation, or even rises in …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
