<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/njk12/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/njk12/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Malaria mozzies can’t resist smelly feet
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-malaria-mozzies-cant-resist-smelly-feet/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 22:05:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nicholas Kennedy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-malaria-mozzies-cant-resist-smelly-feet/</guid>
        <description>Compared to uninfected mosquitoes malaria parasite-containing mosquitoes are approximately three times more attracted to the smell of humans, a study shows.
The researchers from the London School of Hygiene &amp;amp; Tropical Medicine infected malaria mosquitoes with the deadly parasite that causes …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Shakespeare’s sonnets encoded in DNA
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-shakespeares-sonnets-encoded-in-dna/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 23:35:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nicholas Kennedy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-shakespeares-sonnets-encoded-in-dna/</guid>
        <description>Forget parchment in calf skin binding. Forget mock pine filing cabinets jammed with A4. Forget CDs, DVDs, MP3s – in fact, forget all digital, data-storing acronyms.
A team of scientists has stored all 154 of Shakespeare&amp;rsquo;s sonnets in DNA – the Bard of Avon quickly turns in his grave – along …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ugandan pygmy tribe display flexible footwork skills
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-ugandan-pygmy-tribe-display-flexible-footwork-skills/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 00:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nicholas Kennedy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-ugandan-pygmy-tribe-display-flexible-footwork-skills/</guid>
        <description>Scientists from Dartmouth College, Hanover, recently focused on the ankle-flexibility of pygmy populations in Uganda. They filmed the honey-gathering behaviourof pygmies to measure the flexibility of their ankle joints.
The findings, reported in The Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Brief History of Pigs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-a-brief-history-of-pigs/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 23:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nicholas Kennedy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-a-brief-history-of-pigs/</guid>
        <description>Ninety-seven million years ago pigs and humans were one of the same. Well, sort of. There wasn’t exactly a four-trottered, bristly-nosed Homo-something snuffling through the Cretaceous. But we did share a common ancestor, a small generic mammal prototype, whatever that might be.
Actually it probably …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>MS drug trial shows potential
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-ms-drug-trial-shows-potential/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 21:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nicholas Kennedy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-ms-drug-trial-shows-potential/</guid>
        <description>A new drug is the most effectivetreatment for multiple sclerosis (MS), say researchers at the University of Cambridge.
The scientists treated MS patients with alemtuzumab, a monoclonal antibody normally used to fight leukaemia. Alemtuzumab proved more effective than a first-choice drug, interferon …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Deadly snake venom better pain-killer than morphine
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-deadly-snake-venom-better-pain-killer-than-morphine/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 20:46:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nicholas Kennedy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-deadly-snake-venom-better-pain-killer-than-morphine/</guid>
        <description>Few of us associate the black mamba, one of the world’s most venomous snakes, with pain relief. But findings recently published in Nature show that black mamba venom may be a more effective pain-killer than morphine.
The black mamba, Dendroaspis polylepis, is feared throughout southern and eastern …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
