<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/as1911/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/as1911/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Tokyo No-Go: When acting goes wrong
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-tokyo-no-go-when-acting-goes-wrong/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 13:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Arianna M Sorba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-tokyo-no-go-when-acting-goes-wrong/</guid>
        <description>I’m pretty obsessed with Japanese culture. I’m also an ardent feminist, and I’m constantly moaning to anyone who’ll listen about the lack of interesting female characters in modern literature. So I was more than ready to love Harajuku Girls, a new play about three women growing up in modern day …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>1,500 masterpieces looted by the Nazis found in Munich
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-1500-masterpieces-looted-by-the-nazis-found-in-munich/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 09:44:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Arianna M Sorba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-1500-masterpieces-looted-by-the-nazis-found-in-munich/</guid>
        <description>Around one billion euros worth of art has been discovered in the home of an 80 year old man in Munich. The collection, including pieces by Matisse, Picasso, Renoir and others, represents one of the largest recoveries of looted art in recent history, and includes many pieces previously unknown to art …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Six Ideas for Trafalgar Square’s Fourth Plinth
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-six-ideas-for-trafalgar-squares-fourth-plinth/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 01:49:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Arianna M Sorba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-six-ideas-for-trafalgar-squares-fourth-plinth/</guid>
        <description> Really Good – David Shrigley A 10m tall elongated thumbs-up sign, cast in bronze. What’s not to like? Really Good is a brilliantly sarcastic idea from David Shrigley, a Glaswegian artist known for his deliberately naive deadpan humour. Apparently Shrigley hopes that the sculpture, if made, will …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>5 Posters for your bedroom wall
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-5-posters-for-your-bedroom-wall/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 14:23:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Arianna M Sorba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-5-posters-for-your-bedroom-wall/</guid>
        <description> 1. Chinese Girl Now one of the most popular art prints of all time, the original Chinese Girl recently sold for almost £1 million in a London auction. It was painted in 1950 by Russian artist Vladimir Tretchikoff after he spotted the model forthe painting in a laundrette.
The quirky contrast …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Getting to the points of Lichtenstein
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-getting-to-the-points-of-lichtenstein/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 23:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Arianna M Sorba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-getting-to-the-points-of-lichtenstein/</guid>
        <description>“Whaam!” is probably one of the most reproduced pieces of art on the planet. That bold comic style, that distinctive script, the perfect coloured dots&amp;hellip; The piece is so distinctively Lichtenstein that it has perhaps come to define him as an artist. However as this retrospective shows, Roy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Royal Institution may sell its Mayfair Home
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-royal-institution-may-sell-its-mayfair-home/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2013 01:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Arianna M Sorba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-royal-institution-may-sell-its-mayfair-home/</guid>
        <description>The Royal Institution in Mayfair has been a centre for scientific research and communication for over two centuries. Previously the workplace of such scientific greats as Michael Faraday and George Porter, the Ri now focuses on outreach, running courses, book clubs, school events, and the famous …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Creepy and Curious at the Hunterian Museum
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-creepy-and-curious-at-the-hunterian-museum/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 01:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Arianna M Sorba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-creepy-and-curious-at-the-hunterian-museum/</guid>
        <description>At a loss for what to do this weekend? Unusually interested in the science of life? Then why not take a trip to the Hunterian Museum? Hidden away inside the Royal College of Surgeons in Holborn, it is the ultimate destination to explore all the gory details of animal biology, and satisfy any morbid …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Super-massive black hole baffles scientists
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-super-massive-black-hole-baffles-scientists/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 01:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Arianna M Sorba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-super-massive-black-hole-baffles-scientists/</guid>
        <description>Astronomers analysing data from the Hobby-Eberly Telescope in Texas have spotted an enormous black hole — but in a relatively miniscule galaxy.
Most galaxies, such as our own Milky Way, are thought to have a super-massive black hole at their centre. Current theories suggest that the two grow in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The naked truth about the late works
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-the-naked-truth-about-the-late-works/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 22:48:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Arianna M Sorba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-the-naked-truth-about-the-late-works/</guid>
        <description>“One of Britain’s most influential artists”, “the father of pop art”, “one of the most innovative and audacious printmakers ofthe age”. These phrases have all been used to describe the late Richard Hamilton, creator of such famous collages as Just what is it that makes today’s homes so modern, so …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>North Star is shrinking
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-north-star-is-shrinking/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 22:29:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Arianna M Sorba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-north-star-is-shrinking/</guid>
        <description>According to new analysis of more than 160 years worth of data, the North Star may be wasting away, shedding an amount of gas equivalent to up to the mass of the Earth each year.
The North Star, also known as Polaris, has been used by navigators for centuries, as its alignment with the Earth’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oddities of Physics
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-oddities-of-physics/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 19:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Arianna M Sorba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-oddities-of-physics/</guid>
        <description>The SAF main lecture theatre was full to bursting last Wednesday evening, as Simon Foster and his troupe of postgraduate students put on an exciting and informative show on ‘The Oddities of Physics’. Guests were welcomed into the building with a display by the Imperial College Juggling Society, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ancient popcorn found in Peru
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-ancient-popcorn-found-in-peru/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 22:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Arianna M Sorba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-ancient-popcorn-found-in-peru/</guid>
        <description>They may not have had any decent bowls to eat it from, but new research suggests that, as long ago as around 4600 BC, ancient Peruvians were eating popcorn. A research group led by Tom Dillehay from Vanderbilt University, and Duccio Bonavia, from Peru’s Academia Nacional de la Histori, have found …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Enter the Zarina
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-enter-the-zarina/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 22:19:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Arianna M Sorba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-enter-the-zarina/</guid>
        <description>To coincide with the world premiere of her latest film installation ‘Yellow Patch’, the Whitechapel Gallery in East London is currently showing the first major retrospective of the artwork of Zarina Bhimji. Born in Uganda to Indian parents, Bhimji left for Britain in the early 1970s to escape the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
