<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/emily_freeman/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/emily_freeman/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Rock Throughout the Ages</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-rock-throughout-ages/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Freeman,Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-rock-throughout-ages/</guid>
        <description>The roots of rock as a genre are buried deep in the other sounds of the 50s: blues, jazz, R&amp;amp;B and country, amalgamated together to form its own unique genre, known as rock and roll. This began in the deep south of the states, where the first electric guitars began to make a heavy impact on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Starcrawler Comfortably Blows Minds at Camden Show</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-starcrawler-comfortably-blows-minds-at-camden-show/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Freeman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-starcrawler-comfortably-blows-minds-at-camden-show/</guid>
        <description>3 stars
Ah, Underworld. So many incomplete memories of too many nights out. So many vivid memories of strange men standing just a bit too close when you’re just trying to have a night out with friends. Despite my current opinion of Underworld, it will always hold a special place in my …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Old Blue Last Hit by Furious Punk Noise</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-old-blue-last-hit-furious-punk-noise/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Freeman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-old-blue-last-hit-furious-punk-noise/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
I hiked up to Shoreditch last week to catch one of my favourite bands at the moment, Girls in Synthesis, as they played one of the ‘Fifty Fest’ shows to promote the new music on the bill for Brighton’s The Great Escape Festival.
Before GiS came The Cool Greenhouse, who offered up low-key …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Thank you for the warm welcome back” - My Chemical Romance and Rage Against the Machine announce reunions!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-MCR-and-RatM-announce-reunions/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Freeman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-MCR-and-RatM-announce-reunions/</guid>
        <description>It’s been a hefty week in music news, after the shock announcement of a reunion from emo-legends My Chemical Romance shortly followed by a similar post from the rap-metallers Rage Against the Machine.
MCR fans were overwhelmed on Halloween after MCR socials posted about ‘Return’, their first show in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>50 Years Young – Led Zeppelin II Celebrates Half a Century of Blowing People’s Minds</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-50-years-young-led-zeppelin-2-celebrates-half-century-blowing-peoples-minds/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Freeman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-50-years-young-led-zeppelin-2-celebrates-half-century-blowing-peoples-minds/</guid>
        <description>Led Zeppelin II was formed out of incessant pressure from their record label Atlantic Records, who wanted to ride on the hype of Led Zeppelin’s first album, Led Zeppelin, released 7 months beforehand in March 1969. The important consequence of this meant that recording occurred throughout the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>JOHN is Out Here (on the Fringes)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-JOHN-is-out-here-on-fringes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Freeman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-JOHN-is-out-here-on-fringes/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
JOHN, often known as JOHN (TIMESTWO) as both members of the duo are called John, have a brand spanking new album out. And as unimaginative as their band name is, this album is far from the same. Based out of Crystal Palace, South London, JOHN rode into the current post-punk wave along with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sleep: The Snoozefest in Kentish Town</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-sleep-snoozefest-kentish-town/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Freeman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-sleep-snoozefest-kentish-town/</guid>
        <description>1.5 stars
Last Friday night: a dreary evening, where all I wanted as we headed off to Kentish Town was for my heart, body and soul to be warmed by heavy rock. Luckily, we were heading to the lovely O2 Forum Kentish Town, a theatre-turned-venue which tonight was hosting the 90s stoner rock legends …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The anomalous King Gizzard and the Lizard Wizard </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-anomalous-king-gizzard-and-lizard-wizard/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Freeman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-anomalous-king-gizzard-and-lizard-wizard/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
As the chuggy riff of ‘Self-Immolate’ broke out over Alexandra Palace last Saturday, someone threw an entire pint down me. Not the best start to one of the best gigs I’ve been to in a long time, but certainly a memorable one. This night was definitely memorable for the band playing as well: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>King Gizz are exactly as you’d expect: fucking great</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-king-gizz-are-exactly-as-you-d-expect-fucking-great/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Freeman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-king-gizz-are-exactly-as-you-d-expect-fucking-great/</guid>
        <description>The queue looped around two corners as fans waited eagerly to pass beneath the dome of the O2 Academy Brixton. Spanning the readergraph above them hailed the cause: Australian psych-rockers King Gizzard and the Lizard Wizard. Performing their only London show in the support of the immense five …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Queens of the Stone Age flex their muscles</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-queens-of-the-stone-age-flex-their-muscles/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Freeman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-queens-of-the-stone-age-flex-their-muscles/</guid>
        <description>These people want you to be calm, but I don’t want you to be calm – I want you to take your fucking trousers off” lead singer Josh Homme’s Californian drawl crooned to the 20,000 strong crowd at the O2 Arena last Tuesday. Queens of the Stone Age, the legendary heavy rock band, embarked on the UK leg …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
