<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/pd111/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/pd111/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Reseachers produce an even greener solar cell
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-reseachers-produce-an-even-greener-solar-cell/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 02:07:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavitar Devgon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-reseachers-produce-an-even-greener-solar-cell/</guid>
        <description>A new solar cell is being pioneered by researchers at the Northwestern University, USA. Rather than using lead perovskite as the conductor to harvest light, the research team developed cells which utilise tin. The research paper was published in the Nature Photonics journal earlier this week.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New catalyst removes excess atmospheric carbon
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-new-catalyst-removes-excess-atmospheric-carbon/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 05:14:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavitar Devgon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-new-catalyst-removes-excess-atmospheric-carbon/</guid>
        <description>Researchers from the University of Delaware have developed a new catalyst that may reduce the surplus carbon dioxide in the atmosphere. The proposed nano-porous silver catalyst encourages the conversion of carbon dioxide into carbon monoxide. While initially this may not sound like a victory, it is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Untouchable photons
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-untouchable-photons/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 16:01:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavitar Devgon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-untouchable-photons/</guid>
        <description>Photons can often be difficult to measure because as soon as they are, they are gone. Most measurement methods require direct absorption, or are in some other way destructive to the nature of the particle. This means that you have little time to glean all of the information before it disappears, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Collisions unbound: what is the future for CERN?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-collisions-unbound-what-is-the-future-for-cern/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 02:20:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavitar Devgon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-collisions-unbound-what-is-the-future-for-cern/</guid>
        <description>Currently, experiments at CERN have halted, giving time for maintenance work and a renovation of its equipment to take place. It is set to continue its experiments in 2015, where the energy intensity of its collisions will be increase from 4 trillion electron-volts to 6.5. The excitement caused by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Antibody treatment for cancer
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-antibody-treatment-for-cancer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 09:38:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavitar Devgon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-antibody-treatment-for-cancer/</guid>
        <description>There is plenty of on-going research in the field of battling cancer, whether chemically, physically or biologically. A research group from southern California is developing a new strategy on improving the transport of medicine within the patients’ body, by creating antibodies which only activate in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>7th rock from another sun
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-7th-rock-from-another-sun/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 09:38:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavitar Devgon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-7th-rock-from-another-sun/</guid>
        <description>Discovering exoplanets nearly 20 years ago allowed physicists to change their view of the universe. We had always known that our Sun was not the only star in the wide universe, but then came confirmation that there are star systems like ours too, with planets of all sizes orbiting one, two or three …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Electricity and Bubbles
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-electricity-and-bubbles/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 20:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavitar Devgon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-electricity-and-bubbles/</guid>
        <description>Blowing bubbles from soapy water has been a favourite past time for all of us. Struggling as we try to catch them before the breeze takes them higher and higher provided us with hours of delight. We never gave a thought to the physics behind it, because, well, that would ruin the fun.
Bubbles …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Heatwave at the corona
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-heatwave-at-the-corona/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 23:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavitar Devgon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-heatwave-at-the-corona/</guid>
        <description>The enormous fusion furnace at the centre of our solar system has been continually belting out light and heat for the past 4.6 billion years since its formation. From the distance the Earth lies from the sun, the solar rays are strong enough to warm the atmosphere to around 20-30°C. The sun’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your atomic number’s up
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-your-atomic-numbers-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 00:21:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavitar Devgon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-your-atomic-numbers-up/</guid>
        <description>Whether it was using sand, sundials or swinging pendulums, humans have strived to create more efficient time keeping devices. The past century saw a large jump with the introduction of the atomic clock. Current models operate by measuring the microwave energy signature of electrons dropping between …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Building a virtual brain
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-building-a-virtual-brain/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 01:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavitar Devgon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-building-a-virtual-brain/</guid>
        <description>Intelligence has been a hot topic in robotics for decades – ever since we started creating computers and machines, we have wanted to imbue them with a similar level of learning and intelligence to our own. So we turned to the most intelligent machine we had – our brains. Researchers in this field …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Has Kyoto Really Been Successful?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-has-kyoto-really-been-successful/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 23:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavitar Devgon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-has-kyoto-really-been-successful/</guid>
        <description>It has been nearly 15 years since the governments gathered in a stuffy assembly hall on a December evening and decided to enact the Kyoto Protocol. It legally came into effect in 2005 and during this Green Week, we have decided to see if it has really made any difference.
According to the official …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Featured Fiction: Revenge!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-featured-fiction-revenge/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 21:22:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavitar Devgon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-featured-fiction-revenge/</guid>
        <description>A lonely tree stood solitary on a darkening hill. Its branches were bare and no birds would roost in its empty canopy. The bark towards its trunk was peeling off and patchy in many places giving a diseased appearance. Gnarled roots grew twisted in the parched earth, meaning that the whole tree …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reporting on the latest from Raincatcher Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-reporting-on-the-latest-from-raincatcher-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 21:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavitar Devgon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-reporting-on-the-latest-from-raincatcher-imperial/</guid>
        <description>In the latest fundraising endeavour, open to both Raincatcher members and members of the public, each person will carry 10 litres of water approximately 10 miles from Tower Bridge to Imperial College. The Water Carry Walk is taking place this Saturday (10 March) so it’s not too late to join in, but …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Black holes: cosmic creators
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-black-holes-cosmic-creators/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 20:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavitar Devgon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-black-holes-cosmic-creators/</guid>
        <description>In the 1930s, soon after Einstein came up with his equations on general relativity, Karl Schwarzchild developed a solution that predicted what became known as a black hole. Essentially a mass compressed into such a small volume that its gravitational pull is literally irresistible; not even light is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The technology behind Raincatcher
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-the-technology-behind-raincatcher/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 23:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavitar Devgon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-the-technology-behind-raincatcher/</guid>
        <description>By now, I’m sure you’ve heard a lot about Raincatcher’s aims. But how much of the technology behind our systems do you know about?
In order to support our aim of providing clean, sustainable supplies of water to people who currently cannot access it, Raincatcher sends a team to Tanzania every year …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Have you heard about Raincatcher Imperial?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-have-you-heard-about-raincatcher-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 21:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavitar Devgon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-have-you-heard-about-raincatcher-imperial/</guid>
        <description>We all take for granted that when we switch on the tap, clean, drinkable water will pour out. Sadly, for millions of people around the globe, this is not the case.
The Problem
In many countries, state-funded municipal supplies are expensive, leaving the poorest billion people in the world with no …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Have you seen my time cloak?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-have-you-seen-my-time-cloak/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 22:12:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavitar Devgon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-have-you-seen-my-time-cloak/</guid>
        <description>Yes, you read right: time cloak. But what is this mysterious device? Well, it works to conceal an event in time. This is not just science fiction; experiments and investigations have been carried out to show that such a cloak might actually be a possibility.
Now before you get too many wild ideas, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A pearl in the ocean
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-a-pearl-in-the-ocean/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 22:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavitar Devgon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-a-pearl-in-the-ocean/</guid>
        <description>A couple of weeks ago, the British Sikh Doctors Organisation and Imperial Sikh Society worked together to put on an outstanding meet and greet event with Sikhs from all around London, a few charities and talks on a variety of topics, culminating in the screening of the new-to-the-UK movie: Ocean of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Particles from thin air
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-particles-from-thin-air/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 20:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavitar Devgon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-particles-from-thin-air/</guid>
        <description>40 years ago, physicists Hendrik Casimir and Dirk Polder, proposed that empty space wasn’t really empty. This may seem counterintuitive, but the answer lies in quantum mechanics. Quantum mechanics tells us is that a vacuum cannot have zero energy. It is actually a sea of virtual particles, usually …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Natural born killers?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-natural-born-killers/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 20:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavitar Devgon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-natural-born-killers/</guid>
        <description>We can all name famous psychopaths, be they the fictional Hannibal Lecter or real life Jack the Ripper. They can cause fear or uneasiness in even the most hardy of us. But what really makes a serial killer? Why are psychopaths so different from ‘us’?
The Horizon episode, Are you Good or Evil, …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
