<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/dominic_ede/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/dominic_ede/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Knives Out (2019)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-knives-out/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dominic Ede,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-knives-out/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
It’s not often that a film starts getting almost unanimous praise from critics, so when this murder mystery from Rian Johnson started to garner attention from almost every direction, it left me wondering: what makes this film so good?
It centres around the family of Harlan Thrombey, a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Most Important Films of the Decade</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-most-important-films-of-decade/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charlotte Arrand,Zuzanna Janusz,Dominic Ede,Jasmin Daley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-most-important-films-of-decade/</guid>
        <description>Now that this decade is coming to a close, for the last paper of the year we thought we’d do a roundup of what we think are the most important films of the 2010’s, featuring one from each film writer. These films don’t necessarily line up with the ones we have loved the most, however, they are what …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Third Man (1949): A Look at the Film Turning 70</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-the-third-man-1949-look-at-film-turning-70/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dominic Ede,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-the-third-man-1949-look-at-film-turning-70/</guid>
        <description>Looking back at this aged and distant film allows you to visualise the significant amount of time that has passed since Felix was established in 1949, and also gives some relevant perspective in the advances cinema has made. Written by Graham Greene, the film centres around Holly Martins (Joseph …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>La Chinoise (1967)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-la-chinoise-1967/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dominic Ede,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-la-chinoise-1967/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
As an afterthought to this review, earlier this year I read an Ali Smith book called ‘Public Library and Other Stories’. While (slightly) irrelevant to the book, the cover featured a shot of two people reading on a balcony with strong red, white, and blue colours dominating the frame. On the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your Father’s Murderer: A Letter to Zachary</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-your-fathers-murderer-a-letter-to-zachary/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dominic Ede,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-your-fathers-murderer-a-letter-to-zachary/</guid>
        <description>Sometimes it’s nice to just have a good cry at a movie, cathartic even; so with a quick Google for some of the saddest films ever made, followed by a little scrolling on Reddit, I came across this recommendation from Ubertraquer with the bold words “without a doubt the most tragic and heart …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Marriage Story: BFI Film Festival</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-marriage-story-BFI-film-festival/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dominic Ede,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-marriage-story-BFI-film-festival/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
What I love about Marriage Story. It’s a great film, moving. The writing is provoking and rexal. It’s a film that’s honest, really honest. It makes you cry. It makes you laugh. It’s very clear about what it wants to portray. It is excellent.
If this introduction seems a little strange to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Meet the Film Editors</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-meet-film-editors/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dominic Ede,Charlotte Arrand,Matthew Leontsinis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-meet-film-editors/</guid>
        <description> Dominic Ede:
With first term already swiftly underway, I’m sure many of you will be unsure what to do with all this free time you have. To ease your concern we’ve created our lists of top 5 films with a little bit of something for everyone.
First, cutting our favourite films down to a list of five …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Farewell</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-the-farewell/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dominic Ede,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-the-farewell/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
You’d be forgiven for not having heard the name Lulu Wang before Sundance 2019, but after making a big splash this year with The Farewell, her name should be at the top of directors we can be sure to expect more of in the future.
Based on Wang’s own experience, The Farewell follows Billi …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
