<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/cb403/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/cb403/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Dinner
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-dinner/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:47:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-dinner/</guid>
        <description>Bond is back. The girls, the music, the martinis, the awfully brilliant one-line quips (“Where the hell have you been, Bond?”… dramatic pause … “Enjoying death”). And the cars. Nothing beats an Aston Martin DB5. Aston Martin has done so much to be cool, to be sexy, so why did it insist on producing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Boisdale of Belgravia
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-boisdale-of-belgravia/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 21:23:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-boisdale-of-belgravia/</guid>
        <description>I hadn’t been to the Belgravia branch of Boisdale for around three years. You see, the last time I went I had the worst date of my life. Not one to judge someone for their job title, I took an Exotic Credit Trader at Barclays Capital to dinner for what should have been a stonking night out. But it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>La Famiglia
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-la-famiglia/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 13:20:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-la-famiglia/</guid>
        <description>It doesn’t seem quite right to say there’s a dodgy part on the King’s Road. But there is, just beyond the trendy Bluebird brasserie, where the pavement gets a bit dirtier, the shops a bit more Londis. It is here that one stumbles upon La Famiglia restaurant. A place that proves eating out is just as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Higgs boson? Probably Heston again
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-higgs-boson-probably-heston-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 22:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-higgs-boson-probably-heston-again/</guid>
        <description>Heston Blumenthal can be a bit pretentious. Take his recipe for green bean salad:
 Build a zero-gravity space capsule and fill with water. Bring water to boil.  Chop ends off beans using Navy SEALS LASER tracking system. Insert vacuum-packed green beans into the capsule. Cook for 265.3π seconds, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Old Man and the Movie
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-the-old-man-and-the-movie/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 20:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-the-old-man-and-the-movie/</guid>
        <description>It was Tuesday and I found myself having a beer in Brinkley’s, the louche Chelsea eatery and favourite Hugh Grant haunt, and I was surrounded by middle-aged desperate housewives. They were botoxed and dyed blonde and high-heeled. It was then that I became engulfed in a peculiar Hemingwayesque …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Student occupations return in force
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-student-occupations-return-in-force/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 22:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-student-occupations-return-in-force/</guid>
        <description>Students and staff affiliated with Members of Cambridge Defend Education have been staging a sit-in protest in a university lecture theatre at University of Cambridge since Wednesday 23 November.
Protestors took over the lecture theatre as Universities Minister David Willetts was about to give a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Calm down dear, it&#39;s only an opinion!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-calm-down-dear-its-only-an-opinion/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 22:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-calm-down-dear-its-only-an-opinion/</guid>
        <description>Silvio Berlusconi has proved himself a great salesman and a poor statesman. Sounds good, doesn’t it? Has a certain panache. The only thing is, I didn’t come up with it. The succinct, elegant sentence was written by Beppe Severgnini, the reputable Italian political commentator, in a recent Financial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NHS Trust rejects improper financial behaviour allegations
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-nhs-trust-rejects-improper-financial-behaviour-allegations/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 21:09:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-nhs-trust-rejects-improper-financial-behaviour-allegations/</guid>
        <description>The Imperial College Healthcare NHS Trust has rejected allegations of impropriety from The Sunday Times and Private Eye concerning its commissioning of management training courses from Coalescence Consulting, which is owned by the Trust’s interim chief executive Mark Davies and his wife Karen …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Make a meal of it
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-9-30-make-a-meal-of-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2011 12:21:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-9-30-make-a-meal-of-it/</guid>
        <description>So, I’m sitting in the Union, and the Felix Editor comes up and says, “Hi, would you like to go and review Giraffe?” And I say yes, especially as the restaurant is paying. But now, all I can think is, “Oh shit.” You see, I’m stuck. I just don’t know how to write a proper food review – I mean, where …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The éclair that grates relativity
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-the-clair-that-grates-relativity/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 20:18:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-the-clair-that-grates-relativity/</guid>
        <description>Last week, whilst consuming a coffee and éclair, I had a debate with a friend about string theory, gravity, and whether everything is made of particles or waves. It was then that a rather charming French friend stopped for a brief chat. And, sure enough, we concluded that French women are definitely …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Ferrari FF: phwoar wheel drive
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-27-the-ferrari-ff-phwoar-wheel-drive/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 15:30:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-27-the-ferrari-ff-phwoar-wheel-drive/</guid>
        <description>Forgive me. I understand that the overuse of compliments can appear naïve at the best of times, and deceitful at the worst. My gut tells me that it’s a terrible, terrible mistake to not be able to spot the flaw in something, that I’m being tricked. I cringe at my credulousness. But, you see, the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dear Alan Sugar
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-dear-alan-sugar/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 04:29:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-dear-alan-sugar/</guid>
        <description>Dear Alan, Lord, Sir, Del Boy,
Generally, I am stuck for jokes. I write a piece about modern art, say, only to end up forcefully comparing Damien Hirst’s latest oeuvre to a pickled turd. Artful journalism it is not. But then, once a year, The Apprentice shows up and the jokes write themselves. So, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fusion comes to London
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-fusion-comes-to-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 18:23:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-fusion-comes-to-london/</guid>
        <description>What kind of city do we live in? The London social calendar is full of awfully pretentious events charging ludicrous amounts of dosh for a very ordinary experience whilst managing to be incredibly vile and unwelcoming about it at the same time. Events where the lighting has that weird, trendy glow …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lunching in Knightsbridge: Daphne’s
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-21-lunching-in-knightsbridge-daphnes/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2011 11:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-21-lunching-in-knightsbridge-daphnes/</guid>
        <description>Spring fever is fast approaching. And as Mark Twain puts it, “when you’ve got it, you want - oh, you don’t quite know what it is you do want, but it just fairly makes your heart ache, you want it so!” Except, Mark, you know perfectly well what you want. You want to enjoy ice-cold beers in the park, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Savouring the Tuscan hills
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-savouring-the-tuscan-hills/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 19:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-savouring-the-tuscan-hills/</guid>
        <description>Quite often, when planning my next holiday, I get all too carried away with the prospect of exciting adventures and wonderful discoveries. I’ve plodded along on a camel in the Sahara, watched an interesting game of ping-pong in Bangkok, and even catapulted myself out of a plane somewhere in Texas. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Orleans Jazz
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-new-orleans-jazz/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 21:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-new-orleans-jazz/</guid>
        <description>New Orleans music is an addiction. Its diversity portrays every emotional state and as the legendary jazz musician Ellis Marsalis puts it, &amp;ldquo;at a time when individualism is becoming an endangered species, the sounds of the Bayou represent a celebration of the individual&amp;rdquo;. Put simply, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fancy food stylings en français
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-fancy-food-stylings-en-franais/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 21:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-fancy-food-stylings-en-franais/</guid>
        <description>Samuel Furse
As avid readers of the Comment section will know, I recently finished my PhD. I had not thought much about what came after, as there was a peculiar type of feeling that it might never end, for a while. It did, and in so happening I wanted to celebrate. The agèd Ps (they do not yet know …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gallery art should be special
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-gallery-art-should-be-special/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 19:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-gallery-art-should-be-special/</guid>
        <description>You may recall Miroslaw Balka’s “Box of Darkness” that was displayed at the Tate Modern back in 2009. For the uninitiated, it was effectively a very big box that was very dark, and you could walk around inside it, and, err, well that was about it really. Except it wasn’t really very dark as there …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Does watching TV ruin your life?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-does-watching-tv-ruin-your-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 20:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-does-watching-tv-ruin-your-life/</guid>
        <description>Charles Betts
I find going out on a Saturday night in London an odd thing. I’ve usually had a rough week, I’m tired, fed-up with humanity, feeling miserable and in a pretty foul mood. I feel the onset of a cold thanks to a vitamin D deficiency that the city’s winter brings. I would quite like to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The hazards of eating out
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-the-hazards-of-eating-out/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 20:21:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-the-hazards-of-eating-out/</guid>
        <description>The SCR food, with its leather-tough beef, dry chicken, and liquefied peas – is there anything more depressing? Well, yes – genocide, estate agents, malaria, sexual rape, facebook rape, yawn rape, and Robert Peston. The SCR is, after all, just a university canteen in a country mocked globally for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Positive signs for graduates
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-positive-signs-for-graduates/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 18:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-positive-signs-for-graduates/</guid>
        <description>A poll by the Association of Graduate Recruiters (AGR) of 222 recruiters in the UK reveals an 8.9% annual increase in graduate jobs, with a forecast of a further 3.8% increase for this year.
The survey indicates that salaries are likely to remain static. The average salary is predicted to stay at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Should we worry about climate change?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-should-we-worry-about-climate-change/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 21:22:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-should-we-worry-about-climate-change/</guid>
        <description> Charles Betts
The end of the world always seems to be approaching. The Millennium Bug was supposed to turn every computer on the planet mental, activating every nuclear bomb and killing us all on verse two of Auld Lang Syne. The UK chief medical officer told us in 2005 that bird flu would wipe out …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Hawaiian antidepressant
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-the-hawaiian-antidepressant/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 19:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-the-hawaiian-antidepressant/</guid>
        <description>There are an awful lot of grumpy people in London at the moment. They’re fed up with the daily commute on overcrowded trains, the fellow passengers sneezing all over them, and the realisation that they just don’t have the will power to keep any New Year resolutions. But actually their crabbiness …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Weakness plagues British politics, but not Top Gear
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-12-weakness-plagues-british-politics-but-not-top-gear/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2010 14:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-12-weakness-plagues-british-politics-but-not-top-gear/</guid>
        <description>Britain’s political leaders are having a rough December. As three wise men steadily travel from the East to a barn in Bethlehem with gifts of gold, myrrh, and frankincense, it seems that we at home have been left to cope with three vain stooges that can only offer broken pledges, little …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Explosion risk rumoured to be cause of spray-fabric lab closure
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-explosion-risk-rumoured-to-be-cause-of-spray-fabric-lab-closure/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 22:04:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-explosion-risk-rumoured-to-be-cause-of-spray-fabric-lab-closure/</guid>
        <description>An explosion risk is rumoured to be the cause of Prof Paul Luckham’s Chemical Engineering laboratory closure in October. The laboratory was being used to test an innovative “spray-on-clothing” developed in conjunction with Dr Manel Torres. Scientists think the fabric, created through careful use of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the Future for BP?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-whats-the-future-for-bp/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 21:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-whats-the-future-for-bp/</guid>
        <description>Why is BP a good choice for graduates?
Emma: We are interested in having a long term relationship with Imperial graduates as many of them have a desire to use their degree, and given Imperial’s focus on high quality engineering and science it is an extremely good match for us as an organisation. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Some like it Haute
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-some-like-it-haute/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 21:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-some-like-it-haute/</guid>
        <description>Italy may be home to the greatest number of UNESCO World Heritage Sites in the world, however, as of last week the French can boast pipping the Italians to arguably the most questionable of awards ever granted by the United Nations’ cultural organisation. The French multi-course gastronomic meal has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Three lambs on the shirt
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-three-lambs-on-the-shirt/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2010 21:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-three-lambs-on-the-shirt/</guid>
        <description>Barack Obama has something in common with the England Football team. For good or bad, he made politics interesting again during the 2008 Presidential campaign. Yet since he has been in power, his approval ratings have started to drop as people realise with just how unreachable their levels of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pedal to the Vettel
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-pedal-to-the-vettel/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 21:04:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-pedal-to-the-vettel/</guid>
        <description>Nine months is a long time in Formula 1. In March the motoring clique feverishly anticipated the return of the seven-times world champion Michael Schumacher. Arguably the best driver in the history of the sport was making an epic comeback, driving the car that was originally intended for the then …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Forza Berlusconi! At least he’s living La Dolce Vita
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-forza-berlusconi-at-least-hes-living-la-dolce-vita/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 21:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-forza-berlusconi-at-least-hes-living-la-dolce-vita/</guid>
        <description>Silvio Berlusconi is, in his own words, “the best political leader in Europe and the world.” To most foreign commentators, however, he is at best a carefree, flamboyant playboy who likes to throw sexy parties at his Sardinian Villa. He makes Hugh Hefner seem an amateur, and Bill Clinton a choir boy. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Were the French right to strike?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-were-the-french-right-to-strike/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 19:09:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-were-the-french-right-to-strike/</guid>
        <description>Samuel Furse
Yawn yawn, the French are on strike again, and I and others are left wondering what the point is. This time at least, it appears to be some sort of principle, though whether this raises them above the level of London Underground tube drivers striking is questionable. The majority of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>&#34;We should be working towards the American system of higher education&#34;
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-we-should-be-working-towards-the-american-system-of-higher-education/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 19:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-we-should-be-working-towards-the-american-system-of-higher-education/</guid>
        <description>In September, during a speech at Queen Mary University, Vince Cable said “there is no justification for taxpayers’ money to be used to support research that is neither theoretically outstanding nor commercially useful.” What is your stance?
My concern is that with so much of scientific research it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is Wayne Rooney Worth it?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-is-wayne-rooney-worth-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 19:44:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-is-wayne-rooney-worth-it/</guid>
        <description>Isn’t it about time that everyone gave Wayne Rooney a break? Let’s get things straight from the off. I am not going to try to defend some of Rooney’s actions over the past few months: some of his off-field behaviour is quite simply indefensible.
As for his form, just go easy on Shrek. The age old …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let’s talk about coffee - what else?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-lets-talk-about-coffee-what-else/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 19:38:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-lets-talk-about-coffee-what-else/</guid>
        <description>Dark, very intense, balanced, unique, mysterious, delicate and smooth with a strong character, body and deep sensual aftertaste. Or at least that’s how the ladies in the Nescafé Nespresso adverts put it (much to the disdain of George Clooney). Indeed, not much compares with the pleasures of an early …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jamie’s US mission comes to a close
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-jamies-us-mission-comes-to-a-close/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 19:30:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-jamies-us-mission-comes-to-a-close/</guid>
        <description>Channel 4 aired the finale of Jamie Oliver’s American Food Revolution on Monday night, a six episode TV series that documents the Naked Chef’s attempts to reform the eating habits of Huntington, West Virginia. The city has recently been identified as the US’s unhealthiest by the Centers for Disease …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pipe fault causes extensive damage to Aero building
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-pipe-fault-causes-extensive-damage-to-aero-building/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 19:04:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-pipe-fault-causes-extensive-damage-to-aero-building/</guid>
        <description>A water leak in an Aeronautical Engineering lab has caused extensive material damage within the department.
A PhD student is rumoured to have incorrectly attached a water pipe to a laser cooling supply system on Friday 8th October, however this is unconfirmed. The leaking supply was left running …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Freshers make do with marquee as bar and club remain closed
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-7-freshers-make-do-with-marquee-as-bar-and-club-remain-closed/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 21:59:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-7-freshers-make-do-with-marquee-as-bar-and-club-remain-closed/</guid>
        <description>The opening of the new Imperial College Union venues FiveSixEight (can’t they count?) and Metric has been delayed by 3 weeks and 1 month respectively. Disappointed students will have to wait until the 18th of October to experience the new bar FiveSixEight and the 29th of October for the new club …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
