<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sjw209/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sjw209/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>A Dishonorable Mention
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-a-dishonorable-mention/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 11:38:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-a-dishonorable-mention/</guid>
        <description>Put simply, Dishonored is what you get if you ask the company who created Skyrim to go away and make Bioshock. It’s got the immersive atmosphere of the former but with the vibrant, larger-than-life visual style of the latter – and it’s a great combination. The art director (who was a big player in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Social media never achieves anything
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-1-social-media-never-achieves-anything/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2012 12:52:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-1-social-media-never-achieves-anything/</guid>
        <description>I’ve got a problem. A problem with you. And your friends. The whole lot of you, in fact, and the way in which you all spread your ideas using social media. Basically, over the past couple of years social media has quickly evolved from a novel way of keeping in touch into a way for people to share …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The future of gaming...?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-the-future-of-gaming/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 21:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Cook,Omar Hafeez-Bore,Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-the-future-of-gaming/</guid>
        <description>Interested in how gaming got to where it is today? See our companion article here!
Michael Cook
It’s hard to look at where we came from and try to assess where we might be in even a few years time. How impossible something like OnLive might have seemed before the Internet was even a possibility …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gaming through the ages: ‘When this baby reaches 88 miles per hour...’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-gaming-through-the-ages-when-this-baby-reaches-88-miles-per-hour/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 20:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Omar Hafeez-Bore,Michael Cook,Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-gaming-through-the-ages-when-this-baby-reaches-88-miles-per-hour/</guid>
        <description>Interested in what our writers think of the future of gaming? See the companion article here!
Felix Issue 500 (1978) - Michael Cook
It’s June 1978, and Felix is celebrating its 500th issue being printed. Meanwhile, on the other side of the world, Japanese arcades are playing host to a videogame that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Snapshots of the future
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-snapshots-of-the-future/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 18:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Worthington,Abhimanyu Chugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-snapshots-of-the-future/</guid>
        <description>Douglas Heaven sees programmable cells, not silicon chips
There’s a lot of speculation about where the future of computing lies. Quantum computers and qubits promise to open up computational problems that are unfeasable using bits alone; nanotech materials such as graphene look set to change the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Living up to election promises
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-living-up-to-election-promises/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 20:54:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-living-up-to-election-promises/</guid>
        <description>&amp;ldquo;I want it to be the year where your Union makes a Guinness World Record attempt.” “Vote for me for better quality lecture notes.”
Sorry, what? Can you say that again, please? I think my brain might be haemorrhaging. I was expecting to hear some realistic, sensible proposals coming out of your …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>GaME 2011: Marc Hull from Frontier Developments
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-27-game-2011-marc-hull-from-frontier-developments/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 13:39:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-27-game-2011-marc-hull-from-frontier-developments/</guid>
        <description>So what did you study at Imperial?
I did Computing, graduating in 2006. I then started doing a PhD and then got lured away by the games industry after 1 year of that – I never completed it. I joined Frontier in 2007 and I’ve been working there ever since, so yeah, that’s about three and a half years …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>GaME 2011: James Fairbairn from Media Molecule
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-27-game-2011-james-fairbairn-from-media-molecule/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 13:36:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-27-game-2011-james-fairbairn-from-media-molecule/</guid>
        <description>What did you study at Imperial?
I did the BSc in Physics from ‘97 to 2000, although even then I was fiddling with computers a lot more than I was paying attention to my physics course, unfortunately.
So you finished your BSc and then what happened?
So then what happened was I ended up getting a job …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Service stoppage since Sony server security scandal
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-service-stoppage-since-sony-server-security-scandal/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 15:00:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-service-stoppage-since-sony-server-security-scandal/</guid>
        <description>It’s been a frustrating fortnight for Playstation 3 owners everywhere. PlayStation Network, the service used to play online on the PS3, was closed almost two weeks ago leaving gamers without access to any online content or multiplayer games. It was revealed that the service was closed not for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>28 games to help you avoid revision
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-22-28-games-to-help-you-avoid-revision/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2011 16:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-22-28-games-to-help-you-avoid-revision/</guid>
        <description>Nanaca Crash
The first thing you should know about this game is that it’s Japanese, which therefore means it’s been liberally sprinkled with craziness. In this anime-style game you control a girl on a bike whose main objective is to crash into a man, sending him flying, and then to keep him in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PlayStation Suite to bring big titles to Android phones
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-playstation-suite-to-bring-big-titles-to-android-phones/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 20:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-playstation-suite-to-bring-big-titles-to-android-phones/</guid>
        <description>The “Next Generation Portable” a.k.a. the PSP2, was announced two weeks ago at Sony’s ‘Playstation Meeting 2011’. The world stared, the world gaped and the world was awed. Quite right too: few had been expecting such an impressive device. (Thankfully it won’t be long before the device itself slams …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>EA&#39;s Creatively challenged
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-4-eas-creatively-challenged/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 16:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-4-eas-creatively-challenged/</guid>
        <description>When _Create _was first announced, it was a dream come true. Electronic Arts, creators of The Sims series, were making a new kind of creation-simulation game. No mention of houses or families – yes, they were finally making The Sims without the Sims! At last, players could build a house (or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wossy reveals Nintendo 3DS details
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-wossy-reveals-nintendo-3ds-details/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 20:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-wossy-reveals-nintendo-3ds-details/</guid>
        <description>Although Nintendo let their big bosses have the honour of announcing the Nintendo 3DS, the successor to their current range of handheld consoles, the task apparently fell to Jonathan Ross to host the latest press conference on the upcoming device.
With disgusting beard and sharp quips in evidence, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>HTML5: The next level for web games
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-html5-the-next-level-for-web-games/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 20:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-html5-the-next-level-for-web-games/</guid>
        <description>Gaming is no longer all about consoles. Web games have gone from being the domain of bespectacled nerds to the salvation of the chronically bored masses. As game authors set the bar increasingly higher and tax our browsers to the limit, a new contender enters the eternal web format wars. To make a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ilomilo: Cute but still smart
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-ilomilo-cute-but-still-smart/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 19:54:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-ilomilo-cute-but-still-smart/</guid>
        <description>Despite sounding like the name of the trendiest new cocktail to hit London bars, or perhaps the location of the latest hit tourist spot in the Balkans, _ilomilo _is in fact the latest arcade game from Swedish game house SouthEnd Interactive. Ilo and Milo are the protagonists: little egg-shaped blobs …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Yet another gripping game from the WWE
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-15-yet-another-gripping-game-from-the-wwe/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 18:24:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-15-yet-another-gripping-game-from-the-wwe/</guid>
        <description>The last time I played a wrestling game was in 1998 on the original PlayStation 1. WWF Warzone was the first 3D wrestling game ever, and although I had no particular interest in wrestling it was a title I came back to every so often. So, twelve years on, how much have things changed?
On the surface, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Another chronic Sonic failure
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-another-chronic-sonic-failure/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 19:35:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-another-chronic-sonic-failure/</guid>
        <description>Poor Sonic has been having a bit of a rough time recently. Despite Mario and Luigi continuing their Godfather-esque dominance over pretty much any market they lay their eyes upon, their spiky blue hedgehog nemesis has enjoyed some high-profile, big-budget releases. However with a menagerie of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sequels aplenty at Eurogamer Expo
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-10-sequels-aplenty-at-eurogamer-expo/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 15:53:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-10-sequels-aplenty-at-eurogamer-expo/</guid>
        <description>Fallout: New Vegas
For the first of our ‘sequels to recently released games’ theme, Fallout: New Vegas was on show this year at Eurogamer just weeks before it comes out in the shops. Although not a direct sequel to last year’s smash hit Fallout 3, as the game takes place in an entirely new location …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Just arrived and already bored? Time to get online!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-1-just-arrived-and-already-bored-time-to-get-online/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 23:06:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-1-just-arrived-and-already-bored-time-to-get-online/</guid>
        <description>You’ve arrived at your new university and you’re already stressed out. You’ve got to cope with Welcome Week events, meeting new people and the challenge of moving into your new halls, and what you really need is a quick game of Modern Halo Call Of Warfare 2 Strike Deluxe to take the edge off! But, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>3D&#39;s Back Baby! You Ready?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-6-16-3ds-back-baby-you-ready/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2010 18:30:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-6-16-3ds-back-baby-you-ready/</guid>
        <description>The age of the red-and-blue grainy cliché is over! Cast aside your cheap cardboard spectacles and make way for a new era of unparalleled 3D realism accompanied by spectacular picture quality. However, instead of overpriced cinema screenings the revolution is going to happen right in your front room, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Touchscreen Patent Wars
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-3-16-the-touchscreen-patent-wars/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 15:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-3-16-the-touchscreen-patent-wars/</guid>
        <description>On March 2nd, Apple Inc. filed a suit against mobile phone manufacturer HTC in which they claimed ten of their patents relating to mobile devices had been infringed. The case covers nearly every Android-based phone that HTC manufactures, including the new Google-endorsed Nexus One and the T-Mobile …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your Digital Footprint
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-3-4-your-digital-footprint/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 12:33:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-3-4-your-digital-footprint/</guid>
        <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a common misconception that when you&amp;rsquo;re on the Internet, you&amp;rsquo;re anonymous. Surfing along, happily not giving away any personal data; it&amp;rsquo;s hard to imagine how you could be recognisable amongst the vast sea of people browsing online. In fact, your computer gives away a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chip-and-PIN yourself into a world of hurt
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-18-chip-and-pin-yourself-into-a-world-of-hurt/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2010 14:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-18-chip-and-pin-yourself-into-a-world-of-hurt/</guid>
        <description>The days of securely paying with plastic are over. It&amp;rsquo;s high time we all went back to paying with paper money, or perhaps even doubloons. They&amp;rsquo;re both probably safer than the current electronic system we have in the UK, the infamous &amp;lsquo;Chip-and-PIN&amp;rsquo;. Last week, eminent security …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Google&#39;s done with China&#39;s censorship
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-22-googles-done-with-chinas-censorship/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 19:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-22-googles-done-with-chinas-censorship/</guid>
        <description>Google and China have never really been the best of friends, and now finally it&amp;rsquo;s all over. Following security breaches of Google servers by hackers thought to originate from China, last week Google announced that it would be removing censorship from all of its Chinese services. Although the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
