<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sarahamilton14/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sarahamilton14/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Trump can&#39;t ruin the environment by himself (even if he is trying)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-trump-cant-ruin-the-environment-by-himself-even-if-he-is-trying/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 14:56:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sara Hamilton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-trump-cant-ruin-the-environment-by-himself-even-if-he-is-trying/</guid>
        <description>There’s a lot one can say against Donald Trump, but thus far he has stuck to his word (or tried to a least). After doing his best to rid the US of ‘bad hombres’, last Thursday he proceeded to attack another of his enemies – the environment – by announcing the withdrawal of the US from the Paris …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New discoveries in space
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-new-discoveries-in-space/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 15:12:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sara Hamilton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-new-discoveries-in-space/</guid>
        <description>Are current politics getting you down? Worried that the world is heading in the wrong direction? Worry not –habitable, pristine, Trumpless, planets are coming soon to galaxies near you (perhaps). Indeed, a newly-discovered solar system just 39 light years from Earth contains planets that are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>China charges ahead environmentally
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-china-charges-ahead-environmentally/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 14:04:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sara Hamilton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-china-charges-ahead-environmentally/</guid>
        <description>I can’t speak for everyone, but when I think of China in relation to the environment, an image of coal and smog-full Beijing, with millions of citizens running around in protective anti-pollution masks, springs to mind. Henry Wang, in his talk Energy and Environment Growth Strategies hosted by the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Does Trump’s presidency signal the start of a ‘post-truth’ era in science?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-does-trumps-presidency-signal-the-start-of-a-post-truth-era-in-science/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 16:36:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sara Hamilton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-does-trumps-presidency-signal-the-start-of-a-post-truth-era-in-science/</guid>
        <description>You know something is seriously wrong in the scientific community when you hear “post-truth” and science put together. Indeed, this term, coined international word of 2016 by Oxford dictionary has recently been appearing in headlines worldwide as a new way of thinking about science in this new world …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial, Trump and other things that piss Sara off
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-imperial-trump-and-other-things-that-piss-sara-off/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sara Hamilton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-imperial-trump-and-other-things-that-piss-sara-off/</guid>
        <description>One of my 2017 felix-related resolutions was to diversify my activist feelings away from the environment. Not that I’m bored about talking about it – not at all. Every week there seems to be some lab somewhere making breakthroughs on green energies, new legislation about restricting urban transport, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Making waves in physics | 2016
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-making-waves-in-physics-2016/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 14:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sara Hamilton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-making-waves-in-physics-2016/</guid>
        <description>This week Physics World has announced the winner of its yearly Breakthrough of the year: the Ligo Scientific Collaboration, involving more than 80 institutions worldwide, for “its revolutionary, first-ever direct observations of gravitational waves”. This is the first ever direct evidence of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Life-saving engineering
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-life-saving-engineering/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 14:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sara Hamilton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-life-saving-engineering/</guid>
        <description>Mention science and saving lives and we often think of scrubs, scalpels and open-heart surgery. Joanne Beale from Engineers Without Borders, in her talk ‘Massive Small Change in Mozambique’ opens our eyes to the fact that doctors are not the only ones saving lives directly – engineers are doing it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The fate of American Science
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-the-fate-of-american-science/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 15:54:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sara Hamilton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-the-fate-of-american-science/</guid>
        <description>The 9th of November saw tears, despair and a whole lot of memes as the results of the 2016 presidential election rolled in. As I woke up to BBC alerts of Trump’s win on my phone, I found myself reliving that fateful Friday morning in June – closing my eyes, telling myself it was all a dream and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why vegetables are saving the planet
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-why-vegetables-are-saving-the-planet/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 16:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Sara Hamilton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-why-vegetables-are-saving-the-planet/</guid>
        <description>I can already feel the eye-rolls. The “Oh, this vegan hippy nonsense again” eye-roll, so before I lose you all, let me promise that I’m not going to preach about animals’ feelings or inform you how tasty avocado is. What I am going to tell you about is a VegFest-induced realization of how easy it is …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
