<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/tbc09/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/tbc09/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Avian attraction
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-avian-attraction/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 18:34:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thea Cunningham,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-avian-attraction/</guid>
        <description>When it comes to choosing a mate, female sparrows have shown they’re anything but bird-brained. According to new research, the feathered females don’t simply pick the most physically attractive, but instead assess the quality of their potential suitor’s inner values.
It all comes down to a cluster …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Residents of Rome flee earthquake predicted in 1915...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-residents-of-rome-flee-earthquake-predicted-in-1915/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 16:35:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thea Cunningham,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-residents-of-rome-flee-earthquake-predicted-in-1915/</guid>
        <description>Urban myth or not, rumours of a possible earthquake predicted over 90 years ago sparked mass panic in Rome this week, with residents vacating the Eternal City for fear of a large tremor. The prediction was made in 1915 by Italian-born seismologist Raffaele Bendandi, who forecast Rome would be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Scientific foundations of Tōhoku quake
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-scientific-foundations-of-thoku-quake/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 20:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thea Cunningham,Charles Harvey,Kelly Oakes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-scientific-foundations-of-thoku-quake/</guid>
        <description>Like all large earthquakes, the Japanese quake occurred in what is known as a subduction zone. In these zones – which are common in the Pacific – large slabs of solid rock called tectonic plates move towards each other. When they collide, the less dense plate will ride over the denser plate, which …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Clone Wars
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-the-clone-wars/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 21:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thea Cunningham,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-the-clone-wars/</guid>
        <description>The film industry isn’t shy of a human cloning plot or two (Alien Resurrection, Multiplicity, The Island, anyone?) and last month was no exception with the UK release of Never Let Me Go, based on the 2005 novel by British author Kazuo Ishiguro. The film centers around three youths – Kathy, Tommy and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Seahorse race to equine finish line
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-seahorse-race-to-equine-finish-line/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 20:33:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thea Cunningham,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-seahorse-race-to-equine-finish-line/</guid>
        <description>How did the seahorse get its shape? According to a new study published in Nature Communications, the tiny critters’ horse-like bodies evolved to help them capture prey large distances away from their beady eyes.
Seahorses, so-called because their bent head, curved neck and long snout resemble our …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Orbit shift led to ancient methane increase
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-orbit-shift-led-to-ancient-methane-increase/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 20:21:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thea Cunningham,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-orbit-shift-led-to-ancient-methane-increase/</guid>
        <description>An investigation into the mysterious rise of methane levels in the atmosphere over the past 5,000 years has suggested its causes are natural, not anthropogenic.
Joy Singarayer at the University of Bristol and colleagues found the Earth’s rotation, and not agriculture, is likely to be to blame for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Backing the future of Parkinson&#39;s research
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-backing-the-future-of-parkinsons-research/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 19:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thea Cunningham,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-backing-the-future-of-parkinsons-research/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College is set to become a research centre in a major new study into Parkinson’s disease, led by Hollywood star Michael J Fox.
The research, co-ordinated and part-funded by the Michael J Fox Foundation for Parkinson’s Research, will recruit patients in the earliest stages of the disease in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sir Francis Dalton: crime fighter
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-sir-francis-dalton-crime-fighter/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 20:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thea Cunningham,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-sir-francis-dalton-crime-fighter/</guid>
        <description>For those of you familiar with TV crime series like C.S.I and Dexter, you’ll know that fingerprinting plays a large part in catching the wanted. But you might not be aware that if it weren’t for a man named Francis Galton, using fingerprints to catch criminals wouldn’t be possible. In fact, the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sweet thoughts curb hunger pangs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-sweet-thoughts-curb-hunger-pangs/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 20:08:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thea Cunningham,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-sweet-thoughts-curb-hunger-pangs/</guid>
        <description>Want to shed your Christmas bulge but can’t resist the Quality Streets? Then imagine eating them, for it could help you in the long run. A study published in Science over the festive period has shown how imagining eating a certain food can reduce your consumption of that food.
The team at Carnegie …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
