<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ync111/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ync111/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>London calling - summer in the captial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-9-london-calling-summer-in-the-captial/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2015 15:52:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-9-london-calling-summer-in-the-captial/</guid>
        <description>Not all of us have the time to jet off to a different location and spend the summer holidays hopping from one destination to another, but that doesn’t mean that you can’t have fun in good old London either. In fact, London is one of the most visited cities of all times and there’s probably a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Travel made easy - the world of apps
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-9-travel-made-easy-the-world-of-apps/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2015 15:10:47 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-9-travel-made-easy-the-world-of-apps/</guid>
        <description>It’s no secret that the internet has revolutionized the world: there are a whole host of information and applications available now that wasn’t there a few decades ago. People can now do everything on their phone that no one could even dream of before – in fact, I still remember putting my phone …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Packing tips for budget airline
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-9-packing-tips-for-budget-airline/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2015 15:03:47 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-9-packing-tips-for-budget-airline/</guid>
        <description>Travelling on budget airline isn’t easy – you got the luggage restriction, liquid restriction and only airline magazines for entertainment. However, with their unbeatable prices you can only grit your teeth and adhere to the increasingly intricate rules of hand luggage restriction to save the extra …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Losing yourself in Venice: to boat, or not to boat
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-25-losing-yourself-in-venice-to-boat-or-not-to-boat/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2015 12:59:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-25-losing-yourself-in-venice-to-boat-or-not-to-boat/</guid>
        <description>Perhaps one of the most frequently asked question for travelers in Venice is whether they should take the water buses or not.
And the answer to these questions, as always, is that it depends. On what exactly, you might ask? Here’s a list of factors for you to consider:
1) Are you able to walk for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Around the World in 19 Festivals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-17-around-the-world-in-19-festivals/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2015 18:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-17-around-the-world-in-19-festivals/</guid>
        <description>Travel is the only thing you can buy that would make you richer – there’s no denying that visiting a place in person brings history to live in a way that words never can.
What better way to get to know a place and its culture than to take part in a festival? With over 6,500 spoken languages, 194 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Working Holiday - the substainable and immersive way to travel
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-17-working-holiday-the-substainable-and-immersive-way-to-travel/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2015 14:45:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-17-working-holiday-the-substainable-and-immersive-way-to-travel/</guid>
        <description>I had been fascinated by the concept of working holiday for a while now and even more so when an old friend of mine embarked on her own journey to Australia with her boyfriend, updating us on her 6-months adventure through social media. It seems to be a popular alternative for many young people …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Discover new places through your friends
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-17-discover-new-places-through-your-friends/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2015 14:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-17-discover-new-places-through-your-friends/</guid>
        <description>Or have you ever found an amazing place tucked away in a city that you think you know everything about and wanted to share it to the world?
Whether the answers to both questions are correct, then Kites is the app for you. It allow users to view and write short recommendations anywhere in the world. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is buying travel deals on Groupon safe?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-is-buying-travel-deals-on-groupon-safe/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 14:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-is-buying-travel-deals-on-groupon-safe/</guid>
        <description>With Groupon becoming more and more universally well known, one can purchase virtually anything, from clothes to household appliances to restaurant deals, at a discounted price. However, a lot of people hesitate in the face of travel deals.
For those of you less familiar with the concept, Groupon is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Top 5 places to visit when in Brussels
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-top-5-places-to-visit-when-in-brussels/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 14:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-top-5-places-to-visit-when-in-brussels/</guid>
        <description>Only a two hour train ride away is the dazzling city of Brussels, full of gastronomical and architectural treasures. The capital of Belgium is known to be small, but the three days I spent there wasn’t enough to visit everywhere I wanted to – though if you go all out on the transport, you might be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oh Christmas lights, so Christmas-y
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-oh-christmas-lights-so-christmas-y/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 19:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-oh-christmas-lights-so-christmas-y/</guid>
        <description>It is getting to everyone’s favourite time of the year again, and the capital has already decked out for the season.
From white fairy lights to giant reindeer, there’s no end to what London can dream up with.
Here’s some of my favourite.
Oxford Street
There’s nothing like the glittering Christmas …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s the most, wonderful time, of the year...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-its-the-most-wonderful-time-of-the-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 19:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-its-the-most-wonderful-time-of-the-year/</guid>
        <description>Every Christmas holiday, people are often tempted to go abroad, whether to visit famous Christmas markets or enjoy the festive vibes of the country.
However, there is just as much to do on this island, especially in the capital where we are. I have scoured through the internet for the most …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fashion Rules: regal fashion at Kensington Palace
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-fashion-rules-regal-fashion-at-kensington-palace/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 21:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-fashion-rules-regal-fashion-at-kensington-palace/</guid>
        <description>Almost every girl has dreamt of being a princess at some point in her life. Being able to live in a fairy-tale castle, enjoy the privileges and most of all, the dresses and beautiful outfits that come with it. Look at Cinderella; she got a dress from her fairy god mother and the next thing you know, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The highlights of Berlin
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-the-highlights-of-berlin/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 20:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-the-highlights-of-berlin/</guid>
        <description>It has been almost thirty years since the fall of the Berlin Wall when the capital of Germany finally became whole again. Left with gaping wounds on their landscape, the city has been reborn in an extraordinary way in the last three decades whilst embracing its cultural heritage.
On one hand you …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
