<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jr2514/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jr2514/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>An Interview with Mayor of London candidate George Galloway
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-7-5-an-interview-with-mayor-of-london-candidate-george-galloway/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 10:02:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-7-5-an-interview-with-mayor-of-london-candidate-george-galloway/</guid>
        <description>Born in Dundee, Galloway became involved in politics from a very young age and is now campaigning as RESPECT Party candidate for Mayor of London. Known as a political maverick and divisive figure in British politics, Galloway has been lauded for his lively rhetoric and impassioned debating style. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In conversation with the author, documentary maker and popular philosopher, Alain de Botton
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-18-in-conversation-with-the-author-documentary-maker-and-popular-philosopher-alain-de-botton/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2015 20:53:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-18-in-conversation-with-the-author-documentary-maker-and-popular-philosopher-alain-de-botton/</guid>
        <description>There are not many people who can say they have set up an international school, written books that have been bestsellers in 30 countries, and given two TED talks. Fewer still can say they have re-hung an art museum and worked as Heathrow airport’s first ever writer-in-residence – but the author, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The leadership races to watch over the Summer
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-18-the-leadership-races-to-watch-over-the-summer/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2015 19:44:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-18-the-leadership-races-to-watch-over-the-summer/</guid>
        <description>Four candidates will be on the ballot paper when Labour Party members get to vote on Ed Miliband’s successor in September. Nominations closed on Wednesday and Shadow Secretary of State for Health Andy Burnham is the bookies’ favourite. Burnham received 68 nominations from MPs (the minimum to be on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Talking to physicist Brandon Brown, author of ‘Max Planck: Driven by Vision, Broken by War’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-17-talking-to-physicist-brandon-brown-author-of-max-planck-driven-by-vision-broken-by-war/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2015 22:44:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-17-talking-to-physicist-brandon-brown-author-of-max-planck-driven-by-vision-broken-by-war/</guid>
        <description>Brandon Brown has spent his career teaching Physics. Starting off as physics graduate from Rice University, Brandon got his PhD from Oregon State University and later attained a certificate in Science Communication at the University of Califronia, Santa Cruz. Now a professor at the University of San …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Do we need electoral reform?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-30-do-we-need-electoral-reform/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2015 09:43:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-30-do-we-need-electoral-reform/</guid>
        <description>The election is finally over. It was a tightly contested campaign but in the end, the Tories carried the day. The final tally put the Conservatives on a slim majority, and sent Labour back to the opposition benches for another five years. The country has moved further to the right, which ironically …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Our future: as told by Her Majesty
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-our-future-as-told-by-her-majesty/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 00:26:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-our-future-as-told-by-her-majesty/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday the 27th May, 20 days after the general election, the Queen outlined the proposed legislation of the new government.
The speech included promises that her government would guarantee an EU refrendum by the end of 2017, after a sort period of negotiation with other European nations and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ireland votes “Yes&#34; to legalising same-sex marriage
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-23-ireland-votes-yes-to-legalising-same-sex-marriage/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2015 18:08:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-23-ireland-votes-yes-to-legalising-same-sex-marriage/</guid>
        <description>Ireland has made history as the first country in the world to legalise same-sex marriage by popular vote.
Over 3.2 million people were asked whether they wanted to amend Ireland’s constitution to allow gay and lesbian couples to marry, in a referendum asking the electorate to vote “Yes” or “No” to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mad Max: Fury Road Review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-19-mad-max-fury-road-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2015 21:22:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-19-mad-max-fury-road-review/</guid>
        <description>In the distant future, water wars have destroyed society, law and order has broken down and human civilisation has fallen. “Mad” Max Rockatansky, played by Tom Hardy, is a lone survivor in the arid desert wastelands of Australia. Captured by the &amp;lsquo;War Boys’ - led by King Immortan Joe (Hugh …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Anti-austerity” riots break out in Whitehall and beyond
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-anti-austerity-riots-break-out-in-whitehall-and-beyond/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 12:38:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-anti-austerity-riots-break-out-in-whitehall-and-beyond/</guid>
        <description>Hundreds of anti-austerity protesters took part in impromptu protests across the UK on Saturday, with a London rally starting outside the Conservative Party headquarters.
Protestors threw traffic cones, smoke bombs and other objects at the police in central London, angry that the Conservatives won …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An interview with Andy Slaughter MP
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-an-interview-with-andy-slaughter-mp/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 12:15:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-an-interview-with-andy-slaughter-mp/</guid>
        <description>The Labour politician Andy Slaughter was elected as Member of Parliament for Hammersmith in 2010, and was re-elected last week with 50% of the vote. Previously the MP for Ealing, Acton and Shepherd’s Bush from 2005 to 2010, Slaughter has been the Shadow Justice Minister since 2010, serving on the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>15 arrested in anti-austerity protest in London
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-12-15-arrested-in-anti-austerity-protest-in-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 15:59:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-12-15-arrested-in-anti-austerity-protest-in-london/</guid>
        <description>Protestors threw traffic cones, smoke bombs and other objects at the police in central London, angry that the Conservatives won the general election.
Thousands gathered in the impromptu protests, where Officers in riot gear clashed with a &amp;ldquo;minority&amp;rdquo; of protesters who were demonstrating …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cameron’s reshuffled cabinet: the big hitters in government
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-12-camerons-reshuffled-cabinet-the-big-hitters-in-government/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 09:06:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-12-camerons-reshuffled-cabinet-the-big-hitters-in-government/</guid>
        <description>There’s not much change at the top in Cameron’s cabinet reshuffle, but in the ‘bottom’ half there are far more young and fresh faces, including more women.
This punchy, more camera friendly cabinet is designed to show the changing face of the conservative government, and full of people who may prove …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nigel Farage remains UKIP leader after the party rejects his resignation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-11-nigel-farage-remains-ukip-leader-after-the-party-rejects-his-resignation/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2015 17:50:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-11-nigel-farage-remains-ukip-leader-after-the-party-rejects-his-resignation/</guid>
        <description>Love him or hate him, you’ll be seeing even more of Nigel Farage in the near future.
On 8th May Nigel Farage offered his resignation to the United Kingdom Independence Party’s National Executive Committee (UKIP’s ruling board), which was rejected on 11th May. Many believe this bizarre scenario, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>General Election 2015: the winners and losers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-8-general-election-2015-the-winners-and-losers/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 17:58:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-8-general-election-2015-the-winners-and-losers/</guid>
        <description>We have a surprise Conservative 12-seat majority, as the Tories swept across England, while Scotland saw a landslide victory for the SNP, Wales remained majority Labour and Northern Ireland&amp;rsquo;s DUP defended their share of the seats. The Liberal Democrats suffered a catastrophic election result …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The big Debate between the biggest names in politics
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-1-the-big-debate-between-the-biggest-names-in-politics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:30:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-1-the-big-debate-between-the-biggest-names-in-politics/</guid>
        <description>The first and only televised election debate for this year’s general election took place earlier this month, featuring seven party leaders from across the United Kingdom. The two-hour debate was structured around four key questions on the following topics: tackling the deficit, the future of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Just how do you decide who to vote for?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-1-just-how-do-you-decide-who-to-vote-for/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:28:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-1-just-how-do-you-decide-who-to-vote-for/</guid>
        <description>The novelist and essayist George Orwell once said that political language is “designed to make lies sound truthful and murder respectable, and to give an appearance of solidity to pure wind.” He wrote that over half a century ago, but it is just as relevant today as it was then. Perhaps even more …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Election 2015: Labour versus Conservative policies
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-4-21-election-2015-labour-versus-conservative-policies/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 13:49:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-4-21-election-2015-labour-versus-conservative-policies/</guid>
        <description>Regardless of the precise results of this May’s general election, only two men are in with a chance of leading the country over the next parliament: the incumbent Prime Minister David Cameron or the Leader of the Opposition Ed Miliband. In the last five years we have seen a surge in support for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Alternates, wipe the blood off my drums”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-4-15-alternates-wipe-the-blood-off-my-drums/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2015 22:43:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-4-15-alternates-wipe-the-blood-off-my-drums/</guid>
        <description>Written and shot by the young American director Damien Chazelle, Whiplash is an ambitious piece of storytelling that chronicles the development and suffering of a young musician with dreams of becoming one of the greatest drummers of his generation. The film follows Shaffer Conservatory of Music …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hillary Clinton: &#39;I’m running for president&#39;
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-4-12-hillary-clinton-im-running-for-president/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2015 22:32:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-4-12-hillary-clinton-im-running-for-president/</guid>
        <description>Hillary Clinton has officially announced her candidacy for the US Democratic presidential nomination in 2016, confirming years of speculation that she would run a second time after losing the nomination in 2008 to Barack Obama. The former First Lady of the United States, U.S. Senator and United …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Scottish National Party: what you need to know
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-29-the-scottish-national-party-what-you-need-to-know/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2015 23:06:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-29-the-scottish-national-party-what-you-need-to-know/</guid>
        <description>You’ve probably heard by now that the upcoming General Election is the most unpredictable and arguably one of the most important in recent UK political history. Minor parties are winning a large number of votes, diminishing the chances of an outright single-party majority in the process.
It is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>House: A Post-Mortem
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-house-a-post-mortem/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 12:09:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-house-a-post-mortem/</guid>
        <description>If you have never watched House, I envy you. It is one of the most nuanced and intelligent shows ever created, and there are 177 episodes for you to enjoy for the first time. In the eight years that House ran (2004-2012) it was distributed to over 60 countries and at one point had the highest …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oh oil, is there nothing you can’t do?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-13-oh-oil-is-there-nothing-you-cant-do/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 01:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-13-oh-oil-is-there-nothing-you-cant-do/</guid>
        <description>In the last two decades the Middle East has experienced Sunni and Shia suppression, the toppling of dictators, Western intervention, Western withdrawal and the spread of fundamentalist terrorism.
The problems in the region are vast, systemic and complicated. And while I don’t pretend for a second to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Boko Haram leader pledges allegiance to Islamic State
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-13-boko-haram-leader-pledges-allegiance-to-islamic-state/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 01:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-13-boko-haram-leader-pledges-allegiance-to-islamic-state/</guid>
        <description> A video of Abubakar Shekau, the leader of the militant extremist group Boko Haram, has emerged in which he swears allegiance to Islamic State (IS).
The message said: “We announce our allegiance to the Caliph of the Muslims and will hear and obey in times of difficulty and prosperity, in hardship …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How do you like your tea?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-how-do-you-like-your-tea/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 19:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-how-do-you-like-your-tea/</guid>
        <description>A fresh cup of English Breakfast tea is truly something to behold. It is the liquid of the Gods and the chosen tipple of this great nation. Make no mistake; to sip a piping hot mug of English breakfast tea after a parched stretch is to know true pleasure. In the last few years I have picked up a few …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why don’t more young people vote?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-6-why-dont-more-young-people-vote/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 16:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-6-why-dont-more-young-people-vote/</guid>
        <description>With just 61 days to go until polling stations open across the United Kingdom, party election campaigns are well under way. In 2010, voter turnout was at 65%. The over-65’s demographic had an overall turnout of 76%. Amongst 18-24 year olds, however, turnout was only 44% and recent polls indicate …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Two Lawyers. One Degree. And some great television.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-3-two-lawyers-one-degree-and-some-great-television/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 14:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-3-two-lawyers-one-degree-and-some-great-television/</guid>
        <description>Now in its fourth series, _Suits _is an American legal drama that premiered in June of 2011. Created by Aaron Korsh, the first episode is one of the best pilots in recent television history.
Here’s the set up: Mike Ross (Parick J. Adams) is a bright college dropout with a photographic memory but no …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An interview with Robin McGhee
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-3-an-interview-with-robin-mcghee/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 14:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-3-an-interview-with-robin-mcghee/</guid>
        <description>At 23 years old, Robin McGhee has already been involved with the Liberal Democrats for over a decade. While reading History at Oxford University, Robin affirmed his interest in politics and stood for a local council seat. Since graduating, he has been involved in television, journalism, research, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>House of Cards series 3 review: worth the wait, worth your weekend
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-3-house-of-cards-series-3-review-worth-the-wait-worth-your-weekend/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 12:34:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-3-house-of-cards-series-3-review-worth-the-wait-worth-your-weekend/</guid>
        <description>This review contains one big spoiler!
After a year of waiting, the much anticipated third series of House of Cards has finally reared its head. The 13-episode season was uploaded to Netflix at 8am last Friday, and no doubt millions of people decided to binge on the web television series over the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tory MP for Kensington will step down at election
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-24-tory-mp-for-kensington-will-step-down-at-election/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2015 16:42:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-24-tory-mp-for-kensington-will-step-down-at-election/</guid>
        <description>Sir Malcolm Rifkind has resigned as Chairman of the Intelligence and Security Committee, a parliamentary committee, and will step down as Kensington’s MP at the end of this parliament. This comes after criticism over “cash-for-access” claims directed at the senior politician (as well as Labour MP …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kensington MP suspended from Tory Party
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-23-kensington-mp-suspended-from-tory-party/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 15:43:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-23-kensington-mp-suspended-from-tory-party/</guid>
        <description>The party whip and MP Sir Malcolm Rifkind has been suspended from the Conservative party in parliament after becoming embroiled in ‘cash for access’ allegations.
In an investigation conducted for an episode of Channel 4’s documentary series Dispatches, journalists met with Rifkind, pretending to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The evolution of Arctic Monkeys
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-20-the-evolution-of-arctic-monkeys/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 17:42:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-20-the-evolution-of-arctic-monkeys/</guid>
        <description>Born and bred in Sheffield, Arctic Monkeys are an English rock band that formed in 2002. Most commonly associated with The Libertines and The Strokes, Arctic Monkeys consist of front man Alex Turner (lead vocals, rhythm guitar, lead guitar), Jamie Cook (lead guitar, rhythm guitar), Nick O’Malley …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don’t drink and drive – but if you do, call me
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-20-dont-drink-and-drive-but-if-you-do-call-me/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 17:10:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-20-dont-drink-and-drive-but-if-you-do-call-me/</guid>
        <description>Uttered by criminal lawyer and opportunist Saul Goodman (Bob Odenkirk) in the final season of Breaking Bad, the words “Don’t drink and drive – but if you do, call me” give you an idea of the unscrupulous and charismatic character he was throughout the now-classic series. But Saul wasn’t always like …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2015 General Election: it’s complicated
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-19-2015-general-election-its-complicated/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2015 23:58:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-19-2015-general-election-its-complicated/</guid>
        <description>The upcoming UK general election is set to be the most unpredictable vote in living memory. Labour and the Conservatives are practically neck and neck with only 75 days to go and the odds of a hung parliament have never been shorter. Britain appears to be entering an era of six-party politics, where …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Best Show Not On Television
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-the-best-show-not-on-television/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 14:51:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-the-best-show-not-on-television/</guid>
        <description>Based on the novels by Michael Dobbs and the British political drama by Andrew Davies, House of Cards is a Netflix original series that follows U.S. Congressman and Majority Whip Francis Underwood, played by Kevin Spacey, who after being denied the position he was promised of Foreign Secretary in a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brooklyn Nine-Nine: For Your Consideration
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-brooklyn-nine-nine-for-your-consideration/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 18:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-brooklyn-nine-nine-for-your-consideration/</guid>
        <description>Sitcoms are notoriously hard to get right; and cop genre comedies especially so. TV history is full of huge success stories and miserable failures. For every triumphant series there are four or five flops, many of which never even make it to the pilot stage. But despite the significant challenges …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Charlie Hebdo just isn’t funny enough
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-charlie-hebdo-just-isnt-funny-enough/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 01:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-charlie-hebdo-just-isnt-funny-enough/</guid>
        <description>Let’s face it, 2014 was not a great year. Tragedies ranging from epidemics to political tension to aviation mysteries to religious extremism defined those twelve depressing months. Even the supposed sporting highlights were overshadowed by allegations of greed and corruption. At best, it was a …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
