<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/andy_djaba/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/andy_djaba/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Strawberries &amp; Creem Festival 2019</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-07-31-strawberries-creem-festival-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-07-31-strawberries-creem-festival-2019/</guid>
        <description>Felix was in attendance as Strawberries &amp;amp; Creem, the up-and-coming independent festival, made its return, bringing its signature line-up of house and R&amp;amp;B, and Noughties throwbacks. Despite a severely muddy site due to heavy rainfall over the days leading up to the festival, revellers’ …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union to launch h-bar evening food service</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-union-to-launch-h-bar-evening-food-service/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-union-to-launch-h-bar-evening-food-service/</guid>
        <description>Imperial students will soon be able to enjoy evening bar food at h-bar again, following the Union’s announcement that it will be launching a new menu at h-bar on Wednesday 26th June.
This comes in response to student discontent at College’s decision to cut the evening bar food offering at h-bar in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial hosts Prime Minister Theresa May</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-imperial-hosts-prime-minister-theresa-may/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-imperial-hosts-prime-minister-theresa-may/</guid>
        <description>Prime Minister Theresa May paid a visit to Imperial College London on Wednesday 12th June. Senior Teaching Fellow Dr. Colin Hale played host as the Prime Minister toured the department’s Carbon Capture Pilot Plant.
The Prime Minister, who was accompanied by Energy and Clean Growth Minister Claire …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Five reasons to visit Strawberries &amp; Creem Festival</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-five-reasons-to-visit-strawberries-creem-festival/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-five-reasons-to-visit-strawberries-creem-festival/</guid>
        <description>Strawberries &amp;amp; Creem, the up-and-coming independent festival returns to Cambridge’s Haggis Farm on Saturday 15th June with its signature line-up of house, hip-hop and R&amp;amp;B, and Noughties throwbacks. Speaking to Felix, Cambridge University graduate Chris Jammer - the festival co-founder (who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Location, location, location</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-location-location-location/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-location-location-location/</guid>
        <description>The other week, when they had the big marquee on the lawn [for Postgraduate Graduation], one of my colleagues was up here quite late and two or three international students were up here. My colleague said, ‘there’s nobody here, everyone’s gone home’, and they said, ‘I just want to take a photograph …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial and The Times host event tackling air pollution</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-imperial-and-the-times-host-event-tackling-air-pollution/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-imperial-and-the-times-host-event-tackling-air-pollution/</guid>
        <description>Monday evening saw Imperial and The Times collaborate to host the latest joint event in their year-long partnership.
The event, titled &amp;ldquo;How can we fix London&amp;rsquo;s air pollution problem&amp;rdquo; and consisting of a presentation and panel discussion, explored the media&amp;rsquo;s role in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is the Summer Ball &#34;unsustainable&#34;?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-is-the-summer-ball-unsustainable/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-is-the-summer-ball-unsustainable/</guid>
        <description>Preparations for Imperial College Union&amp;rsquo;s annual Summer Ball, which is set to be held on Saturday 22nd June, recently hit a snag as many of the involved student societies threatened to pull out over changes to this year&amp;rsquo;s event.
Dance Imperial, A Capella and Big Band societies were …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Business School exam blunder</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-business-school-exam-blunder/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-business-school-exam-blunder/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Business School students were left reeling when it was revealed to them that they would have to resit an exam due to an error.
The students, who originally sat the Corporate Finance exam in Spring, noticed a &amp;ldquo;huge mess up&amp;rdquo;. Speaking to Felix, an MSc Climate Change, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College Union holds 7th annual Student Academic Choice Awards</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-imperial-college-union-holds-7th-annual-student-academic-choice-awards/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-imperial-college-union-holds-7th-annual-student-academic-choice-awards/</guid>
        <description>Monday evening saw Metric transformed to host the 2019 Student Academic Choice Awards (SACAs).
The award ceremony, which was first launched in 2012 to provide students the opportunity to recognise, reward and celebrate excellence amongst College staff, received over 1500 nominations. In February, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Everything you need to know about The Great Exhibition Road Festival 2019</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-everything-you-need-to-know-about-the-great-exhibition-road-festival-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-everything-you-need-to-know-about-the-great-exhibition-road-festival-2019/</guid>
        <description>This year, staff and students at Imperial College will see big changes to the annual Imperial Festival. With the 200-year anniversary of the births of Queen Victoria and Prince Albert fast approaching, this year the festival will be a collaborative effort for the first time. 19 other cultural …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial community pens open letter calling for confirmed support for the trans community</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-imperial-community-pens-open-letter-calling-for-confirmed-support-for-the-trans-community/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-imperial-community-pens-open-letter-calling-for-confirmed-support-for-the-trans-community/</guid>
        <description>Members of the Imperial community have come together to write a letter calling for Imperial College&amp;rsquo;s Senior Management to confirm its full support of the transgender community and condemn transphobia. This comes after it came to light that Imperial&amp;rsquo;s Vice Provost (Education), Professor …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Becoming: An Intimate Conversation with Michelle Obama</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-becoming-an-intimate-conversation-with-michelle-obama/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-becoming-an-intimate-conversation-with-michelle-obama/</guid>
        <description>Michelle Obama brought the European leg of her book tour for her memoir, Becoming, to London on 14th April in emphatic fashion. Stepping out at London’s O2 arena to Alicia Keys’ ‘Girl on Fire’, the former US First Lady was met with rapturous applause and a standing ovation from a 15,000-stong …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Exclusive: Professor Simone Buitendijk on the future of education at Imperial</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-felix-exclusive-professor-simone-buitendijk-on-the-future-of-education-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-felix-exclusive-professor-simone-buitendijk-on-the-future-of-education-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been two years since Imperial began the overhaul of its curriculum through the Learning and Teaching Strategy and, with the launch of increased digital learning - online degrees, a studio space and the use of Vitual Reality in courses such as Chemical Engineering and Medicine - it&amp;rsquo;s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>HP #WomeninTech Roundtable</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-hp-womenintech-roundtable/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-hp-womenintech-roundtable/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday 10th April, Felix attended a roundtable discussion on the perceived barriers of women in the UK to joining the tech industry.
The event was jointly hosted by HP and The Fawcett Society, the UK’s leading organisation campaigning for equality between women and men, and drew upon an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial calls Access and Participation Plan discussion</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-imperial-calls-access-and-participation-plan-discussion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-imperial-calls-access-and-participation-plan-discussion/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College and the Union jointly held an open forum discussion on its plans to improve access for students from widening participation (WP) backgrounds.
The meeting took place from 12:00 - 13:00 in Meeting Room 3 in the Union Building and was attended by many of the Liberation Officers, as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College Science Showcase</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-imperial-college-science-showcase/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-imperial-college-science-showcase/</guid>
        <description>Pint of Science is a science festival that aims to communicate contemporary scientific developments to the public in an interesting, engaging and approachable way by bringing scientists to the pub and other accessible places. A driving factor in the success of Pint of Science is its ability to draw …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In Memoriam: Muhammad Hafiz Bin Zainal</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-30-in-memoriam-muhammad-hafiz-bin-zainal/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-30-in-memoriam-muhammad-hafiz-bin-zainal/</guid>
        <description>It is with deep regret that Felix shares the sad news that Muhammad Hafiz Bin Zainal (known as Hafiz), who joined the Department of Chemistry as an undergraduate student in 2015, has died. During his time at Imperial, Hafiz was very much involved in student societies and the wider Imperial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Winners of 2019 Leadership Elections announced at Results Party</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-16-winners-of-2019-leadership-elections-announced-at-results-party/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-16-winners-of-2019-leadership-elections-announced-at-results-party/</guid>
        <description>The 2019 Leadership Elections drew to a close at last night’s Results Party in Metric.
Next year’s Officer Trustees will be Abhijay Sood, Tom Fernandez Debets, Fifi Henry, Shervin Sabeghi and Ashley Brooks - in the positions of Union President, Deputy President (Clubs &amp;amp; Societies), Deputy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial celebrates women&#39;s entrepreneurship at WE Innovate final</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-imperial-celebrates-women-s-entrepreneurship-at-we-innovate-final/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-imperial-celebrates-women-s-entrepreneurship-at-we-innovate-final/</guid>
        <description>Thursday 7th March saw five entrepreneurs compete for a share of a £30,000 prize fund in the final of Imperial Enterprise Lab&amp;rsquo;s WE Innovate women&amp;rsquo;s entrepreneurship programme.
The evening began with brief addresses from Liz Choonara, Head of Programmes &amp;amp; Community at the Imperial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Psychodrama Review</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-psychodrama-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,Simran Kukran,Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-psychodrama-review/</guid>
        <description>1. Psycho
What a way to kick off the album. A truly building track, Dave and the instrumentation become one as the listener is guided through the three main psyches that Dave will expand on throughout the album. Not only does he switch up his flow, content and delivery with each transition, but he …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>SCI{L}ENCE</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-sci-l-ence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-sci-l-ence/</guid>
        <description>Sci{l}ence is a weekly podcast for women in STEM. It gives women a platform to talk about what it is really like working in typically male-dominated fields. All the guests are highly accomplished and inspiring women in STEM, deliberately kept anonymous with disguised voices. This allows them to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix&#39;s Annual Sabb Review</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-felix-s-annual-sabb-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-felix-s-annual-sabb-review/</guid>
        <description>This week, in keeping with tradition, Felix is reviewing the sabbatical officers! Having begun their tenure in August 2018, it is now time to review their performance as we reach the sixth month of their occupancy of Beit quad. For those of you not in the know, the Sabbs are the elected …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>National Student Pride 2019: More Pride, Less Prejudice </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-national-student-pride-2019-more-pride-less-prejudice/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-national-student-pride-2019-more-pride-less-prejudice/</guid>
        <description>As LGBT History Month draws to a close, National Student Pride (NSP), the UK’s largest LGBT+ careers fair, holds its annual conference at the University of Westminster.
NSP brings a vibrant mix of graduate careers fairs, conferences, debates, cinema screenings, parties, exhibitions, and workshops to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>h-bar hit by College cuts</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-h-bar-hit-by-college-cuts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-h-bar-hit-by-college-cuts/</guid>
        <description>Staff and postgraduate students have been left disgruntled following the announcement that the popular h-bar will be ceasing its evening bar food service.
The decision, which was taken by College, means that, from Friday 1st March, food will no longer be available in h-bar after 7pm. This change is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial hospitals face £650m repair bill</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-imperial-hospitals-face-650m-repair-bill/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-imperial-hospitals-face-650m-repair-bill/</guid>
        <description>Three west London hospitals run by the Imperial College Healthcare NHS Trust are the most urgently in need of repair in the country. Charing Cross (which is the hospital with the highest urgent repair bill of £312m) in Hammersmith, St. Mary’s in Paddington and Hammersmith Hospital are facing total …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial to launch arts fellowship</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-imperial-to-launch-arts-fellowship/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-imperial-to-launch-arts-fellowship/</guid>
        <description>Staff and students at Imperial College London will be offered the opportunity to have their artistic and creative talents nurtured through a new arts fellowship starting in October 2019.
The Blyth Art Fellowship, a new initiative run through Imperial’s Blyth Music and Arts Centre, will provide …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NeighbourHOOD Grammys 2019</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-neighbourhood-grammys-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,Lé Osikomaiya,Jamell Samuels,Jamil Wallace-Williams,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-neighbourhood-grammys-2019/</guid>
        <description>Album of the Year | Daytona, Pusha T
“It was written like Nas but it came from Quentin”
Nominations | ASTROWORLD, Travis Scott | Invasion of Privacy, Cardi B | Black Panther, Various Artists | FM!, Vince Staples | Victory Lap, Nipsey Hussle | Book of Ryan, Royce da 5’9’’
ASTROWORLD marked Travis’ …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sir Michael Barber visits Imperial</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-sir-michael-barber-visits-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-sir-michael-barber-visits-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Sir Michael Barber. the Head of the Office for Students (OfS), visited Imperial College London on the morning of Wednesday 13th February.
The OfS Head was accompanied by Imperial President, Professor Alice Gast, and the Provost, Professor Ian Walmsley, as the visit began at the Carbon Capture Pilot …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union to scrap breakfast offering following huge losses</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-union-to-scrap-breakfast-offering-following-huge-losses/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-union-to-scrap-breakfast-offering-following-huge-losses/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Union announced its decision to cancel its breakfast offering following substantial financial losses.
From Monday 18th February, Union Breakfast will cease to be served and the opening hours in FiveSixEight will revert to 12pm. The decision was taken a week ago, with the breakfast …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Positive changes to Leadership Elections 2019 as nominations open</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-positive-changes-to-leadership-elections-2019-as-nominations-open/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-positive-changes-to-leadership-elections-2019-as-nominations-open/</guid>
        <description>Nominations for The Leadership Elections 2019 opened on Monday 4th February with hundreds of opportunities for students to lead Imperial at the highest level, and a slew of positive changes aimed at improving the experience for both candidates and voters.
This is the biggest democratic exercise at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students to be refunded following Sport Imperial screw-up</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-students-to-be-refunded-following-sport-imperial-screw-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-students-to-be-refunded-following-sport-imperial-screw-up/</guid>
        <description>Imperial students who paid for gym membership prior to the 1st September 2018 change in pricing structure have been offered a refund due to an error on Sport Imperial’s part.
Sport Imperial acknowledged and apologised for the mistake in an email sent out on 5th October inviting all students who were …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial welcomes Deputy Editor of The Times</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-imperial-welcomes-deputy-editor-of-the-times/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-imperial-welcomes-deputy-editor-of-the-times/</guid>
        <description>Imperial played host to Emma Tucker, the Deputy Editor of The Times on Monday 28th January. After viewing a Data Observatory showcase in the Data Science Institute, Emma sat down with Felix for a brief interview:
Felix: How do you think fake news has affected your job or the job of being a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial celebrates inaugural Liberation &amp; Community Week</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-imperial-celebrates-inaugural-liberation-community-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-imperial-celebrates-inaugural-liberation-community-week/</guid>
        <description>Monday 21st January saw the launch of Imperial College Union’s first Liberation &amp;amp; Community Week, with a panel discussion hosted by the Deputy President (Welfare), Becky Neil.
The launch event, which was titled, “Inclusivity Starts Here” and took place in the Union Concert Hall, featured a panel …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New development in ongoing bursary saga</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-new-development-in-ongoing-bursary-saga/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-new-development-in-ongoing-bursary-saga/</guid>
        <description>Tuesday’s Union Council saw the announcement of £250k funding secured for “unfairly underfunded” 2015 bursary cohort students.
This represents the latest update in an ongoing saga following the Union’s request for reimbursement for undergraduate students from the “squeezed middle” £35,000 - £60,000 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Heroic Hamzah helps deliver baby at tube station</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-heroic-hamzah-helps-deliver-baby-at-tube-station/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-heroic-hamzah-helps-deliver-baby-at-tube-station/</guid>
        <description>First year medical student, Hamzah Selim, has delivered his first baby - at a tube station.
Hamzah, who graduated from Imperial in 2018 with a BSc in Biomedical Science and now studies at University College London, was on his way home following an anatomy lecture on the afternoon of Tuesday 15th …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Business School made my life hell!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-the-business-school-made-my-life-hell/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-the-business-school-made-my-life-hell/</guid>
        <description>An ex-Imperial student has reached out to Felix to share the experience she had last year with the Business School; an experience which she describes as “tantamount to discrimination against people with mental health problems and those who are gender non-conforming.”
Amy Freelander, who works full …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Andy’s Top Ten Most Anticipated Albums of 2019</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-andy-s-top-ten-most-anticipated-albums-of-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-andy-s-top-ten-most-anticipated-albums-of-2019/</guid>
        <description>Ordinarily I would kick off the year writing about my top ten most anticipated hip-hop albums. However, as I’ve mentioned before, I was left quite underwhelmed by hip-hop in 2019 and I’m struggling to come up with ten hip-hop albums I’m really looking forward to this year. As a result, I’m expanding …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Andy’s Top Ten Hip-Hop Albums of 2018</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-andy-s-top-ten-hip-hop-albums-of-2018/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-andy-s-top-ten-hip-hop-albums-of-2018/</guid>
        <description>I don’t actually think 2018 has been a very good year for hip-hop. There were very few ambitious projects dropped this year and not enough artists took risks with their music. J. Cole’s KOD is a prime example. Although a very good album, with it being featureless again, it felt like he produced much …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ethos gym expanding!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-ethos-gym-expanding/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-ethos-gym-expanding/</guid>
        <description>Ethos gym is to be expanded in the new year, following months of collaboration between the Deputy President (Clubs &amp;amp; Societies) [DPCS], Sport Imperial and the College.
This change comes following complaints of the gym being too small and overcrowded in feedback taken over the last two years. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s a Sabb, Sabb Situation</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-it-s-a-sabb-sabb-situation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-it-s-a-sabb-sabb-situation/</guid>
        <description>Felix: For the people that don&amp;rsquo;t know, can each of you explain what your role is.
James: I’m DPCS. My role is two-fold in looking after our 370-odd clubs and societies, their creation, their day-to-day running and, when things go wrong, basically helping them out of a pickle and supporting …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London university students help blood cancer charity, Anthony Nolan, celebrate 20 years of lifesaving</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-london-university-students-help-blood-cancer-charity-anthony-nolan-celebrate-20-years-of-lifesaving/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-london-university-students-help-blood-cancer-charity-anthony-nolan-celebrate-20-years-of-lifesaving/</guid>
        <description>Blood cancer charity, Anthony Nolan, celebrates 20 years of its student volunteer network, &amp;ldquo;Marrow&amp;rdquo;.
Imperial is amongst ten London universities with a Marrow society and, over the last 20 years, Imperial Marrow has joined other Marrow socieities in holding over 400 events to raise …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>White City Woes</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-white-city-woes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-white-city-woes/</guid>
        <description>Autumn 2018 saw the opening of the Molecular Sciences Research Hub (MSRH), which represents a new research home for the Department of Chemistry on Imperial’s new White City campus. With the first term in White City drawing to a close, Felix reached out to various staff and students across all levels …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial students sound the alarm on fossil fuel investments</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-imperial-students-sound-the-alarm-on-fossil-fuel-investments/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-imperial-students-sound-the-alarm-on-fossil-fuel-investments/</guid>
        <description>Divest Imperial, an Imperial College Union-affiliated environmental campaign group, held an on-campus protest demanding Imperial divests from fossil fuels.
The protest, which took place on Tuesday 20th November, was part of the National Day of Action for Divestment. Targeting universities across the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In conversation with Professor Stephen Curry</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-in-conversation-with-professor-stephen-curry/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-in-conversation-with-professor-stephen-curry/</guid>
        <description>With the recent publication of Imperial&amp;rsquo;s Equality, Diversity and Inclusion (EDI) Strategy and Imperial&amp;rsquo;s launch of the Race Equality Charter survey, Felix sat down with Professor Stephen Curry, for an exclusive interview.
Felix: I wanted to get your take on the strategy for Equality …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial launches partnership with The Times and The Sunday Times</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-imperial-launches-partnership-with-the-times-and-the-sunday-times/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-imperial-launches-partnership-with-the-times-and-the-sunday-times/</guid>
        <description>Imperial has announced an exciting new collaboration with Times Newspapers Ltd to “advance their shared interests in the future of science and culture” and including a year-long programme of joint events and activity led by the student community at Imperial.
The media partnership, which will see all …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In memoriam: Imperial mourns passing of former Provost, Professor James Stirling FRS</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-in-memoriam-imperial-mourns-passing-of-former-provost-professor-james-stirling-frs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-in-memoriam-imperial-mourns-passing-of-former-provost-professor-james-stirling-frs/</guid>
        <description>Professor James Stirling, who served as Imperial&amp;rsquo;s Provost from August 2013 to August 2018, passed away on Friday 9th November, surrounded by his family and loved ones.
Professor Stirling was a distinguished physicist, whose work resulted in more than 300 research papers. In his role as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial launches Race Equality Charter Survey</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-imperial-launches-race-equality-charter-survey/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-imperial-launches-race-equality-charter-survey/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London is in the process of producing an action plan to apply for the Race Equality Charter (REC) award and, to launch this process, staff and students are being invited to complete a 10-minute confidential survey. This, in conjunction with the publication of the College&amp;rsquo;s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Samm Henshaw takes us to church</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-samm-henshaw-takes-us-to-church/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-samm-henshaw-takes-us-to-church/</guid>
        <description>I recently had the pleasure of being in attendance as Samm Henshaw treated fans to a phenomenal one-off show.
Samm Henshaw rose to popularity following the success of his two-part Sound Experiment EP projects, the most recent of which was released in 2016. Samm has since largely been on the road, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The State of the Union</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-the-state-of-the-union/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-the-state-of-the-union/</guid>
        <description>A few weeks ago, I wrote a News article about a concerning image that emerged showing Jarlath O’Hara, the Managing Director of Imperial College London, pictured beside a man dressed in blackface. I was first made aware of the image on 27th September If I’m honest, my initial reaction to the picture …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Unrest Over New Union Staff Food &amp; Drink Policy</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-unrest-over-new-union-staff-food-drink-policy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-unrest-over-new-union-staff-food-drink-policy/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Union&amp;rsquo;s new &amp;ldquo;Staff Food &amp;amp; Drink Policy&amp;rdquo; has come under heavy criticism by multiple members of Union bar staff.
Staff were made aware of the new policy, which was drawn up by Julia Mattingley, the Head of Commercial Services, on Monday 29th October. The new …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Provost in Town</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-new-provost-in-town/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-new-provost-in-town/</guid>
        <description>Professor Ian Walmsley FRS, who started his new role as Provost of Imperial College London on 1st September, sat down with Felix for an exclusive interview. The Imperial alumnus and world-renowned expert in ultrafast and quantum optics, who joined the College from his role as Pro-Vice-Chancellor …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union Clamps down on Lockpicking Workshop</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-union-clamps-down-on-lockpicking-workshop/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-union-clamps-down-on-lockpicking-workshop/</guid>
        <description>On Monday 22nd October, Imperial College Union cancelled Imperial Left Forum&amp;rsquo;s Lockpicking Workshop amidst various concerns regarding the potential numbers that the event had attracted.
The event, which had initially been scheduled to take place on Tuesday 23rd October in Blackett 630, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial&#39;s Dodgy Dealings</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-imperial-s-dodgy-dealings/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-imperial-s-dodgy-dealings/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London has been revealed to be the largest UK beneficiary of donations from the controversial and much-maligned Sackler Trust, receiving £2.5m last year.
The Sackler family has come under recent scrutiny amidst the US opioid addiction and overdose crisis. Last year, the family …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ede &amp; Ravenscroft accused of “anti-competitive” business practices</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-19-ede-ravenscroft-accused-of-anti-competitive-business-practices/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-19-ede-ravenscroft-accused-of-anti-competitive-business-practices/</guid>
        <description>Ede &amp;amp; Ravenscroft, the company which provides graduation gowns for Imperial’s (and other universities’) annual graduation ceremonies, has been accused of driving the cost of gown rental up through “anti-competitive” business practices.
In the week that saw more than 2500 undergraduate students …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College London takes part in the first Green GB Week</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-imperial-college-london-takes-part-in-the-first-green-gb-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-imperial-college-london-takes-part-in-the-first-green-gb-week/</guid>
        <description>This past week saw Imperial play an active role in the first Green GB Week.
Green GB Week is a week of events and activity bringing together businesses, schools, colleges, universities, community groups, and charities to explore how clean growth will change our futures and others can contribute to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Joe Biden, the former U.S. Vice-President, visits Imperial</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-joe-biden-the-former-u-s-vice-president-visits-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-joe-biden-the-former-u-s-vice-president-visits-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Joe Biden, the US Vice President during Barack Obama’s administration, paid Imperial a visit on 9th October to deliver the inaugural lecture of the Imperial Cancer Research UK (CRUK) Centre. Vice President Biden spoke of the “urgency of now” as cancer research realises a radical, highly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Compromising image of Imperial College Union Managing Director emerges</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-12-compromising-image-of-imperial-college-union-managing-director-emerges/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-12-compromising-image-of-imperial-college-union-managing-director-emerges/</guid>
        <description>A compromising image involving the Managing Director of Imperial College Union has emerged, Felix reports.
The photograph shows Jarlath O&amp;rsquo;Hara, the Managing Director of Imperial College Union, standing beside a man at what appears to be a party. The man can be seen posing while dressed in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College Men&#39;s Rugby Club loses appeal</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-15-imperial-college-men-s-rugby-club-loses-appeal/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-15-imperial-college-men-s-rugby-club-loses-appeal/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday 3rd October, it was revealed that Imperial&amp;rsquo;s Men&amp;rsquo;s Rugby Club (ICURFC) had lost its appeal against the sanctions following its February &amp;ldquo;Fiesta Dash&amp;rdquo; event. The sanctions, which included all four ACC Rugby teams being banned from competing in their first three …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students call on big business to get its act together to build a more equal society </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-students-call-on-big-business-to-get-its-act-together-to-build-a-more-equal-society/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-students-call-on-big-business-to-get-its-act-together-to-build-a-more-equal-society/</guid>
        <description>Students across the UK are mobilising to urge their potential future employers to do more to ensure that they play their part in reducing inequality and building a fairer world. They are calling on the leaders of the FTSE 350 (combining the FTSE 100 and FTSE 250) to learn from, support and buy from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College celebrates Black History Month</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-imperial-college-celebrates-black-history-month/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-imperial-college-celebrates-black-history-month/</guid>
        <description>October marks the start of Black History Month and Imperial College London will launch a College-wide campaign in celebration.
From 8th October, a digital exhibition showcasing the profiles and achievements of black staff, students and alumni of Imperial will take over screens across Imperial’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First year medical students to be given insight into mental health support </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-first-year-medical-students-to-be-given-insight-into-mental-health-support/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-first-year-medical-students-to-be-given-insight-into-mental-health-support/</guid>
        <description>With World Mental Health Day on 10th October, first year medical students at Imperial College London will be given the opportunity to learn more about mental health support through a new medical simulation.
The simulation, designed by third year Imperial medical students Amna Ahmed, Joshua Walton …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>COMPETITION: Win a tote bag designed by bespoke artist, Bambi, at Freshers&#39; Fair!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-competition-win-a-tote-bag-designed-by-bespoke-artist-bambi-at-freshers-fair/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-competition-win-a-tote-bag-designed-by-bespoke-artist-bambi-at-freshers-fair/</guid>
        <description>London based eco-fashion campaign #LoveNotLandfill has enlisted the support of anonymous street artist Bambi to redesign clothes banks and encourage recycling of unwanted clothes.
The #LoveNotLandfill campaign, co-funded by the EU and London Waste And Recycling Board (LWARB), aims to educate young …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Graduates top University earnings table</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-imperial-graduates-top-university-earnings-table/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-imperial-graduates-top-university-earnings-table/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London graduates have beaten Oxbridge to earn the highest salaries in their first year after graduation, according to research by the job website, Adzuna.
The average Imperial graduate earns £37, 931 in their first year after graduation, which is over £5000 more than the £32,374 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The most important meal of the day!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-the-most-important-meal-of-the-day/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-the-most-important-meal-of-the-day/</guid>
        <description>On 24th September, Imperial College Union announced it would now be serving breakfast in FiveSixEight, ahead of the new academic year.
A year on from the widely unpopular decision to scrap breakfast in the Senior Common Room (SCR), students and staff alike can now enjoy a delicious breakfast in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>James Medler&#39;s Magic Money Tree</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-09-20-james-medler-s-magic-money-tree/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-09-20-james-medler-s-magic-money-tree/</guid>
        <description>The Deputy President (Clubs &amp;amp; Societies) and the Harlington Grants Fund Committee call for proposals from clubs and societies for a £500,000 grant.
The deadline for applications is Monday 8th October 2018. However, clubs and societies must get in contact with James Medler, the Deputy President …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sport Imperial announce increases to Ethos prices</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-07-19-sport-imperial-announce-increases-to-ethos-prices/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 16:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-07-19-sport-imperial-announce-increases-to-ethos-prices/</guid>
        <description>Sport Imperial announced the introduction of an annual membership fee that will be coming into effect from 1st September.
For students, access to the gym and pool at Ethos will cost £30 a year from 1st September to 31st August. Staff Club Imperial memberships will also increase by £1.50 a month. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial 600 takes Pride at annual parade</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-07-19-imperial-600-takes-pride-at-annual-parade/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-07-19-imperial-600-takes-pride-at-annual-parade/</guid>
        <description>Staff and postgraduate students at Imperial College London participated in the annual Pride in London parade. 29 people made up the Imperial cohort, whose entry was co-ordinated by Imperial 600, the College’s LGBTQ+ network for staff and postgraduate students. The Imperial cohort was joined by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The revision soundtrack you wish you had this year</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-the-revision-soundtrack-you-wish-you-had-this-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Henry Eshbaugh,Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-the-revision-soundtrack-you-wish-you-had-this-year/</guid>
        <description>Right in time for the end of exam season, the usual suspects rec some LPs that you should’ve been listening to all along. Sucks you don’t have a time machine, or you could’ve had that many more hours of pleasant revision coasting emotionally on the bangin’ tunes we tell you to like. Well, there’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>There’s Too Many Man, Too Many Many Man!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-there-s-too-many-man-too-many-many-man/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-there-s-too-many-man-too-many-many-man/</guid>
        <description>This week, Isaac Freeling and I hosted Ella and Tayla from the “Too Many Man Show” on our podcast, “2 Gs in a Pod”, (shameless plug!) to have an open and frank discussion about misogyny in hip-hop. It’s something I’ve wanted to write about for a while and, following our discussion, I felt inspired …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>DAMN. Kung Fu Kenny!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-damn-kung-fu-kenny/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-damn-kung-fu-kenny/</guid>
        <description>I feel like I’ve spent the last five months as Felix Music Editor almost exclusively writing about Kendrick Lamar. Nonetheless, please indulge me one more time… I’ll try to keep it brief. Kendrick Lamar completed the UK leg of his DAMN. world tour last week, performing six nights and shutting down …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>3rd Annual NeighbourHOOD Grammys</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-3rd-annual-neighbourhood-grammys/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,Isaac Freeling,Lé Osikomaiya,Jamell Samuels,Jamil Wallace-Williams,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-3rd-annual-neighbourhood-grammys/</guid>
        <description>The Grammys went ahead and got it wrong again but fear not, the NeighbourHood Grammys Committee are back at it again for a third year! Music Editor Andy Djaba is joined by Isaac Freeling, Lé Osikomaiya, Jamell Samuels, and Jamil Wallace-Williams to restore balance to the streets and ensure that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Andy’s most anticipated hip-hop albums of 2018</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-andy-s-most-anticipated-hip-hop-albums-of-2018/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-andy-s-most-anticipated-hip-hop-albums-of-2018/</guid>
        <description>Last year might have only just finished, but resident hip-hop afficionado and Music Editor Andy Djaba is back. Following on from his top albums of 2017, he lets us know what he&amp;rsquo;s looking out for in the year ahead.
 10 Drake
 Drake ended ‘Do NotDisturb’, the final track of More Life, his 2017 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Andy’s Top Ten Hip-Hop Albums of 2017</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-andy-s-top-ten-hip-hop-albums-of-2017/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-andy-s-top-ten-hip-hop-albums-of-2017/</guid>
        <description>10 FUTURE Future
In February, Future quietly went about making history by dropping two albums, FUTURE and HNDRXX, in the space of seven days. In doing so, he became the first artist in music history to have two different albums debut at number one in consecutive weeks. On HNDRXX, we were met with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You can’t Trump the ALL-AMERIKKKAN BADA$$ </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-you-can-t-trump-the-all-amerikkkan-bada/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-you-can-t-trump-the-all-amerikkkan-bada/</guid>
        <description>For obvious reasons, Donald Trump’s presidency and the current hostile political climate in the US has provoked a knee-jerk response of protest and defiance from hip-hop culture. A plethora of rappers have recently adopted a more political approach through their music and 22-year-old Brooklyn rapper …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Future Hndrxx Tour: an enjoyable, if not all that memorable, performance</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-future-hndrxx-tour-an-enjoyable-if-not-all-that-memorable-performance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-future-hndrxx-tour-an-enjoyable-if-not-all-that-memorable-performance/</guid>
        <description>In February, Atlanta rapper Future surprised fans by releasing his eponymous fifth studio album with little advance warning. FUTURE is a seventeen-track trap offering that went straight to number one in its first week. However, although Future’s fans were satisfied, Future was not. A mere seven days …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>J. Cole’s 4 Your Eyez Only tour</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-j-cole-s-4-your-eyez-only-tour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-j-cole-s-4-your-eyez-only-tour/</guid>
        <description>J. Cole’s 4 Your Eyez Only tour touched down in London town early this week, with the Dreamville front man selling out two nights at the O2 Arena. Cole was supported by his labelmates Ari Lennox, EARTHGANG (whose recent Rags-EP is worth a listen and whose Robots EP drops on Friday), and J.I.D. (who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Deep Dive into DAMN.</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-deep-dive-into-damn/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-deep-dive-into-damn/</guid>
        <description>Since dropping back-to-back classics with 2012’s good kid, m.A.A.d city (GKMC) and 2015’s To Pimp a Butterfly (TPAB), Kendrick Lamar has been relatively quiet – I would go as far as to say that we’ve had to put up with polished mediocrity in his absence. He did surprise fans with Untitled Unmastered …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>More Life by Drake
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-more-life-by-drake/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 16:24:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-more-life-by-drake/</guid>
        <description>After countless delays (something which is seemingly becoming an unfortunate feature of all Drake releases these days), More Life was finally released on 18th March. My excitement was palpable to say the least. In my opinion, Drake’s work often falls victim to his own procrastination and hype, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gang Signs and Prayer
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-gang-signs-and-prayer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 15:24:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-gang-signs-and-prayer/</guid>
        <description>Over recent years, the UK grime and urban scene has had a renaissance and one man has been at the forefront of this wave – the WickedSkengMan live in the flesh, Stormzy (Michael Omari Jr.) In addition to his raw musical talent, Stormzy’s omnipresence on social media: uploading daily Snapchat …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NeighbourHOOD Grammys 2016
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-neighbourhood-grammys-2016/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 14:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-neighbourhood-grammys-2016/</guid>
        <description> Album of the year The Life of Pablo, Kanye West [aka Yeezus] “We on an Ultralight Beam… This is a God dream… This is everything.”
Despite the unprecedented commercial success of Views, the committee came to the decision that Drizzy simply has to come harder than he did on this album to be deserving …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Drake: The Boy Meets World Tour
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-drake-the-boy-meets-world-tour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 15:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-drake-the-boy-meets-world-tour/</guid>
        <description>Desiigner’s Panda played in the O2 arena as I sat high up waiting for Drake to take to the stage, so high up that I genuinely had a nosebleed during the show. I couldn’t help but overhear the comments of the girls sitting beside me. “I’m so glad they made a song about my favourite animal”, one said …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Most anticipated hip-hop albums of 2017
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-most-anticipated-hip-hop-albums-of-2017/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 16:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-most-anticipated-hip-hop-albums-of-2017/</guid>
        <description> 10. Lil Wayne | Tha Carter V Cast your mind back to June 2008. Lil Wayne and Birdman were still best mates and Wayne had just dropped his critically acclaimed sixth studio album, including four top 20 singles, and went on to be Wayne’s most successful to date, selling 3.6 million copies and winning …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>4 Your Eyez Only J Cole review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-4-your-eyez-only-j-cole-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 14:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-4-your-eyez-only-j-cole-review/</guid>
        <description>JCole’s last album release, 2014 Forest Hills Drive, received critical acclaim and was met with exceptional commercial success, making it the first LP in 25 years to sell over a million copies without a guest appearance. On November 27th 2015, J. Cole and Kendrick Lamar raised fans’ hopes of finally …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Andy’s Top 10 hip-hop albums of 2016
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-andys-top-10-hip-hop-albums-of-2016/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 14:57:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-andys-top-10-hip-hop-albums-of-2016/</guid>
        <description> 10. Kendrick Lamar | “Untitled Unmastered” In March Kendrick surprised fans with a compilation of unused demos recorded during the making of 2015’s To Pimp a Butterfly, his 3rd studio album. Kendrick previewed three of the tracks on late night talk shows throughout 2015 and during his performance …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
