<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/nms15/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/nms15/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Science &amp; the City
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-science-the-city/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 09:11:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Naomi Stewart,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-science-the-city/</guid>
        <description>The year has come to an end. We’ve jammed and transformed our brains, learning some things better than others. We’ve prepared ourselves with the tools we need for the next chapter in our lives. As we all go our own ways this summer (unless you’re stuck here on campus toiling away while everyone …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Public healthcare cuts cause otherwise preventable deaths
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-public-healthcare-cuts-cause-otherwise-preventable-deaths/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 09:11:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Naomi Stewart,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-public-healthcare-cuts-cause-otherwise-preventable-deaths/</guid>
        <description>We all witnessed the devastating effects of the 2008 economic crisis, as ordinary people lost their jobs and homes, and saw their hard-earned savings and financial security evaporate. Now a team of researchers are warning that the financial collapse may have also led to the preventable deaths of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science &amp; the City
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-science-the-city/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 08:28:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Naomi Stewart,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-science-the-city/</guid>
        <description>There are some of us puttering around campus that remember a time before smartphones and constantly available internet. Even before sharing just the one computer in the corner of the living room with your entire family, waiting painstakingly for the whirling ring of the AOL dialup to finish, only to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science &amp; the City
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-science-the-city/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 09:18:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Naomi Stewart,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-science-the-city/</guid>
        <description>Very few of us are here at Imperial because we’re interested in the inner machinations of the political beast. But as argued lately in Felix, science and scientists need to wake up and start caring about science and policy. Besides being a way to sell ourselves better and increase funding from one …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cosmic dust hints at alternate history
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-cosmic-dust-hints-at-alternate-history/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 08:52:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Naomi Stewart,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-cosmic-dust-hints-at-alternate-history/</guid>
        <description>At the end a of white-washed hallway on the second floor of the RSM building, Dr Matthew Genge has been unlocking the mysteries of the universe through his research on micrometeorites – otherwise known as cosmic dust. Last week however, Genge published a paper in Nature which opened some doors to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science &amp; the City
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-science-the-city/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 09:06:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Naomi Stewart,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-science-the-city/</guid>
        <description>Questions on ethics arise in all fields of science, from vaccinations to military weapons. But given the mutability of morality and ethical stances across cultures, individuals, and time, it’s difficult to pinpoint where the lines of what is moral should be drawn. What of the devastating effects of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science &amp; the City
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-science-the-city/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 09:04:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Naomi Stewart,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-science-the-city/</guid>
        <description>We’re caught in an odd crux of perspectives on justifications for science and technology. There’s the age-old idea of fundamental research having inherent, non-monetary value as a social service - sort of like a library, providing building blocks of knowledge we can all draw from. Increasingly, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science &amp; the City
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-science-the-city/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 09:53:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Naomi Stewart,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-science-the-city/</guid>
        <description>Humans have always looked up at the sky in awe and fascination. For thousands of years we’ve searched for light and guidance in its movements, while hanging our fables and myths on the celestial bodies like regal robes. And little wonder – almost all of the elements in our bodies are made from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science &amp; the City
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-science-the-city/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 11:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Naomi Stewart,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-science-the-city/</guid>
        <description>In modern times, the peer-reviewed publication is seen as the basic benchmark for science. Of course, science must be publicly accessible and able to be duplicated. And with increased metrics and funding in the sciences dependent on performance measured by frequency and recognition of publications, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science &amp; the City
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-science-the-city/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 11:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Naomi Stewart,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-science-the-city/</guid>
        <description>In our occidental institutions of learning, the hallways hear the daily echoes of our scientific history being taught in classrooms. “We stand on the shoulders of giants” was a 12th century quote, though more commonly attributed to Sir Isaac Newton. It’s an acknowledgment of our predecessors, the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science &amp; the City
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-science-the-city/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 11:38:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Naomi Stewart,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-science-the-city/</guid>
        <description>Despite huge changes since the 19th century, there is still an uneven playing field for women in STEM (science, technology, engineering, and maths).
Recently the Academy of Sciences in South Africa found that globally, women make up less than 12% of the membership of the influential bodies of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science &amp; the City
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-science-the-city/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 11:35:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Naomi Stewart,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-science-the-city/</guid>
        <description>Across the spectrum of living organisms we have species that are adaptable and flexible, known as generalists, and those who occupy unique niches and exploit them maximally, known as specialists. Raccoons are generalists – they’ll eat anything, anytime, anywhere. On the other hand, koala bears are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science &amp; the City
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-science-the-city/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 11:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Naomi Stewart,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-science-the-city/</guid>
        <description>She walks among us and with us. Rattling in our pockets beside loose change, beaming through the air, whipping us through the underground in the much-beloved, spacious Tube, and sending Londoners south to Ibiza or Tangiers. Science is everywhere in our world. But it’s more than just a pragmatic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Zika virus spurs global health emergency
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-zika-virus-spurs-global-health-emergency/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 12:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Naomi Stewart,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-zika-virus-spurs-global-health-emergency/</guid>
        <description>In 1947, researchers uncovered a unique virus in macaque monkeys in the Zika Forest in Uganda, transmittable through the bite of infected Aedes mosquitoes, the same ones responsible for yellow fever and dengue.
Almost 20 years later, the namesake Zika virus was discovered in a human in Nigeria. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Star powered science
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-star-powered-science/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 14:37:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Naomi Stewart,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-star-powered-science/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College’s very own André Arroja Neves has won the New Horizons in Mathematics Award at the Breakthrough Prizes, which was held at the NASA Ames Research Centre in Silicon Valley on November 9th. The professor in the Department of Pure Mathematics won the prize, along with Codá Marques, for …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
