<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/yll08/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/yll08/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>European playground exposed</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-european-playground-exposed/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 19:58:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dylan Lowe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-european-playground-exposed/</guid>
        <description>The lowdown: Once the playground of Romans and feudal lords alike, modern Europe is now flocked by visitors pursuing the delights it has to offer. The diversity of cultures, languages, history, cuisine and so on are reasons us Brits should roam our continental neighbours.
Culture: To say the least, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Regal charms of New Zealand
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-regal-charms-of-new-zealand/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 21:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dylan Lowe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-regal-charms-of-new-zealand/</guid>
        <description>The lowdown: Two million tourists tread the two islands of New Zealand every year – for a very good reason. Its natural beauty is second to none; its reputation as an adrenaline junkie’s wettest of dreams well deserved.
Culture: Easy-going, liberal – the Kiwis presenting a big culture gap is as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Popping your travel cherry</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-popping-your-travel-cherry/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 19:43:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dylan Lowe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-popping-your-travel-cherry/</guid>
        <description>Jetting off around the world can be a little, well, daunting. That’s why the Felix Travel team have gotten together for The Daily Felix to help you plan that life-changing trip. Over the coming days we’ll be giving you the low-down on some of the more popular travel destinations, but for starters …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stick to the plan
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-stick-to-the-plan/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 20:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dylan Lowe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-stick-to-the-plan/</guid>
        <description>Like a good respectable self-reformist, you decreed upon yourself the commandments that are your resolutions for 2011. One of which includes the desire to ‘travel more’. With a destination picked and dates decided but yet to arrive, you perch on your seat counting the milli-seconds before you take …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Small world, huh?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-small-world-huh/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 20:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dylan Lowe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-small-world-huh/</guid>
        <description>Nestled on the stool, the silhouette was none other than what obstructed me as I wrestled, pints in both grasps, my way to the booth where my friends were seated. I bellowed a ’scuse-me – my voice drowned out amid patrons of the busy Queenstown bar – and attracted his attention. Hysteria, on both …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stingy travelling git
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-stingy-travelling-git/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 20:47:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dylan Lowe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-stingy-travelling-git/</guid>
        <description>Irony simply cannot be expressed in a better way: I was attempting to explain the concept of budget travelling to a PR guy representing Dubai Tourism.
In the previous week I was strolling through the aisles of stands at the World Travel Market, a prominent travel expo which annually lures …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It scared me shitless
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-it-scared-me-shitless/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 19:39:47 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dylan Lowe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-it-scared-me-shitless/</guid>
        <description>A couple of things you can never forget about a bungy jump: the expression of your co-conspirators’ faces, and the fateful countdown that mount to your eventual plunge.
Conspirators because you and your fellow jumpers are cheating on death, defying gravity and your natural instincts.
As for the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>One tasty-looking trek
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-one-tasty-looking-trek/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 18:49:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dylan Lowe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-one-tasty-looking-trek/</guid>
        <description>New Zealand. For a land-of-the-long-white-cloud the size of United Kingdom, which secludes itself in the south-eastern corner of the world map, and houses a population of sheep outnumbering that of humans by 15:1, it boasts an uncanny amount of eccentrics and their heroic – yet insane – antics. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tourism held hostage?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-tourism-held-hostage/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 19:56:47 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dylan Lowe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-tourism-held-hostage/</guid>
        <description>Despite being seven hundred miles away from the scene of the hostage situation, I felt trapped.
The city of Hong Kong reached a state of media gridlock as every TV channel turned their immediate attention to a dozen of its residents, encased in a tour bus in the possession of a hostile …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
