<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/steve_allain/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/steve_allain/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with Conservation: how we can all help</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-connect-with-conservation-how-we-can-all-help/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-connect-with-conservation-how-we-can-all-help/</guid>
        <description>Over the past few months, I have been updating you all with a number of conservation stories, both optimistic, and less so. Now, to wrap things up, I thought it would be a good idea to give you all a few ideas on how you can make a few small changes to your daily routine to help save the planet. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with Conservation: cat-astrophe</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-connect-with-conservation-cat-astrophe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-connect-with-conservation-cat-astrophe/</guid>
        <description>One of the more surprising invasive species, now found across the world thanks to mankind, is the domestic cat! Whether these moggies are pets left to roam free, or have established themselves as feral population, both cause unimaginable damage to various species around the globe. Domestic cats have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with Conservation: insect apocalypse</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-connect-with-conservation-insect-apocalypse/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-connect-with-conservation-insect-apocalypse/</guid>
        <description>Remember back to the days of your childhood when you would go on long drives to see family, or to visit the coast on a warm bank holiday. Like me, you may have been observant enough to recognise that car windscreens are devilishly good at catching insects. Fortunately, this was picked up by the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with Conservation: Malta bird massacre</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-connect-with-conservation-malta-bird-massacre/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-connect-with-conservation-malta-bird-massacre/</guid>
        <description>If there is one group of birds you have probably noticed declining in the British countryside over the past few years, it is the songbirds. Songbirds are a large group of birds, which, as their name suggests, like to sing, filling the landscapes they inhabit with the beautiful sound of bird songs. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with Conservation – Information Conservation Technology</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-connect-with-conservation-information-conservation-technology/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-connect-with-conservation-information-conservation-technology/</guid>
        <description>It is becoming increasingly clear that technology is advancing at such a rate that tasks that once took conservationists weeks or months have been cut down to a number of days. This includes the use of equipment such as camera traps, drones, and custom-built prototypes that are project specific. If, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with conservation: Snake Fungal Disease</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-connect-with-conservation-snake-fungal-disease/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-connect-with-conservation-snake-fungal-disease/</guid>
        <description>In recent years, we have seen a spike in the number of fungal diseases infecting wildlife, causing population declines. This includes the chytrid fungus in amphibians and white-nose syndrome in bats. Recently, a new fungus has been discovered in the US, which so far seems to exclusively infect …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with conservation – the scandal of Sudan</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-connect-with-conservation-the-scandal-of-sudan/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-connect-with-conservation-the-scandal-of-sudan/</guid>
        <description>Some of you may have recently read that the last male northern white rhinoceros, called Sudan, was put down due to age-related ailments. The northern white rhinoceros is a a now functionally-extinct subspecies of the white rhinoceros, with only two females remaining. This day was imminent – with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flagship species – putting the con in conservation</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-flagship-species-putting-the-con-in-conservation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-flagship-species-putting-the-con-in-conservation/</guid>
        <description>For those unaware of what a flagship species is: it is a species selected by a conservation organisation, such as the World Wide Fund (WWF), to act as an icon or symbol for a defined issue or environmental problem. This being said, you are all probably thinking of one of the best-known flagship …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with Conservation – LEGO goes green</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-connect-with-conservation-lego-goes-green/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-connect-with-conservation-lego-goes-green/</guid>
        <description>It may be a surprise – for those who remember treading on rogue LEGO pieces in the dark – to hear the company is going green by producing plant-based plastics! Known as LEGO Botanical Elements, they will start to enter playsets later on this year, with the first pieces to be replaced including …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with conservation – A lonely frog</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-connect-with-conservation-a-lonely-frog/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-connect-with-conservation-a-lonely-frog/</guid>
        <description>Just in times for Valentine’s Day, a Sehuencas water frog named Romeo had an online dating profile setup to search for love. This sort of thing isn’t usually newsworthy, except for the fact Romeo has been dubbed ‘the world’s loneliest frog’. He is the only known individual of his species, and the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with conservation – orangutan genocide</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-05-connect-with-conservation-orangutan-genocide/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-05-connect-with-conservation-orangutan-genocide/</guid>
        <description>In the summer of 2015, I was lucky enough to visit Borneo; here I was able to observe orangutans in the wild, amongst other spectacular wildlife. This was a very humbling experience and one that I will never forget! Recently a portion of the news really caught my attention – for the wrong reasons, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with conservation – photographing extinction</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-23-connect-with-conservation-photographing-extinction/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-23-connect-with-conservation-photographing-extinction/</guid>
        <description>Looking forward to the future of species conservation, the depressing and sobering truth is that some species may not be around for future generations to enjoy. The only evidence of their existence will be media, and written reports or books documenting their ecology and distribution. How will …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with conservation – Imperilled Pangolins</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-connect-with-conservation-imperilled-pangolins/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-connect-with-conservation-imperilled-pangolins/</guid>
        <description>The group of the most trafficked animal is one that you may not have even heard of, the pangolin. There are eight extant species of pangolin found across the Old World in Africa and south-east Asia; they relatively unassuming animals, they are also known as scaly anteaters due to the fact that they …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with conservation – Detection dogs</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-connect-with-conservation-detection-dogs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-connect-with-conservation-detection-dogs/</guid>
        <description>Most people are aware of the amazing ability dogs have to sniff out targeted items or substances they have been trained for. Although more commonly known as ‘sniffer dogs,’ the correct term for such trained canines is detection dogs. They are frequently used at airports and other international …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with conservation – Visiting Venom</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-connect-with-conservation-visiting-venom/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-connect-with-conservation-visiting-venom/</guid>
        <description>Snakes, spiders and scorpions are probably some of the animals that come to mind when you think of the word venom. There is a wide range of other venomous animals too – including the platypus, jellyfish, and, surprisingly, two species of frogs! To be clear, venom is a toxin that requires a delivery …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with conservation – successes in 2017</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-connect-with-conservation-successes-in-2017/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-connect-with-conservation-successes-in-2017/</guid>
        <description>2017 was a peculiar year for us all, with world politics turned on its head, as well as the United States of America pulling out of the Paris Climate Agreement. None of this seemed to phase the passionate and dedicated conservationists working around the clock to ensure that their species of choice …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with Conservation – de-extinction dilemma</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-connect-with-conservation-de-extinction-dilemma/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-connect-with-conservation-de-extinction-dilemma/</guid>
        <description>You may be aware that there are currently growing efforts to clone long-extinct animals such as mammoths, which would be sure to put a smile on John Hammond’s face. There is a growing consensus in the scientific community that we should use similar technology to resurrect recently extinct animals. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with conservation: oceanic ghostbusters</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-connect-with-conservation-oceanic-ghostbusters/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-connect-with-conservation-oceanic-ghostbusters/</guid>
        <description>I am sure that many of you have been moved by the recent sequences in Blue Planet II highlighting the devastating effects that plastic is having in our oceans. Although the production team removed all the plastic they came across, this pales in comparison to the amount that actually ends up in our …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
