<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sam_welton/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sam_welton/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The brilliant mess of the Birmingham pantomime</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-18-the-brilliant-mess-of-the-birmingham-pantomime/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sam Welton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-18-the-brilliant-mess-of-the-birmingham-pantomime/</guid>
        <description>Pantomimes follow a simple formula. Jokes, colourful costumes and a pervasive camp atmosphere combine to form family entertainment. As had been family tradition for over ten years, this Christmas I experienced the Birmingham pantomime. Now, experienced really is the word as in that time it has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse, yet another Sony  Spider-Man reboot, but it’s actually good?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-spider-man-into-the-spider-verse-yet-another-sony-spider-man-reboot-but-it-s-actually-good/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sam Welton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-spider-man-into-the-spider-verse-yet-another-sony-spider-man-reboot-but-it-s-actually-good/</guid>
        <description>Sony pictures is very hit-or-miss when it comes to super hero films. Sam Ramey’s Spider-Man trilogy can probably be credited with kick-starting the modern superhero boom, in which Spider-Man 2 is still widely considered an exemplar. However, it’s been a bumpy ride. Fantastic 4 has had three films …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fallout 76: How Bethesda alienated their fans and destroyed their reputation with a single game</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-fallout-76-how-bethesda-alienated-their-fans-and-destroyed-their-reputation-with-a-single-game/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sam Welton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-fallout-76-how-bethesda-alienated-their-fans-and-destroyed-their-reputation-with-a-single-game/</guid>
        <description>Fallout 76 could have just been another shoddy game sent out to die, but due to a continuous string of baffling decisions and mistakes it has managed to tarnish Bethesda’s reputation, possibly irreversibly. For those unaware of just how badly Bethesda has screwed the pooch, let me take you through …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Amateur dramatics is a powerful thing</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-amateur-dramatics-is-a-powerful-thing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sam Welton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-amateur-dramatics-is-a-powerful-thing/</guid>
        <description>At the weekend I went home to see my family, and while there saw a show from the local youth drama club. My sister was in it; she’ll be going to university next year, making this her last performance. The show was great fun, not exactly Shakespeare but the cast were having a good time and that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fallout 76- I want to love you</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-fallout-76-i-want-to-love-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,Sam Welton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-fallout-76-i-want-to-love-you/</guid>
        <description>Let me lay down my biases up front. I do love fallout; I’ve clocked an irresponsible number of hours in 4 and New Vegas over the last few years. I gel with the art direction, I like the setting and I love a good open world. I, however, also ardently defended Fallout 76 when it was announced. I saw …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Microtransactions: the covert gambling ring of the gaming community</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-microtransactions-the-covert-gambling-ring-of-the-gaming-community/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anthony Onwuli,Sam Welton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-microtransactions-the-covert-gambling-ring-of-the-gaming-community/</guid>
        <description>The gambling accusation refers to loot boxes, effectively Pokémon booster packs for in-game cosmetics and perks. Much like card packs, most of the contents are common trash, but there is always potential of finding something rare and flashy that you can show off. Fundamentally, both card packs and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Johnny English’s Third Strike</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-johnny-english-s-third-strike/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sam Welton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-johnny-english-s-third-strike/</guid>
        <description>Johnny English Strikes Again is an unfortunate movie. It feels like it ran out of something; maybe it was time, maybe it was interest, but it was probably money. What could have been another classic Rowan Atkinson vehicle has ended up a hollow and corporate mess, and yet the occasional scene had the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Venom: The Worst Kind of Bad Film</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-venom-the-worst-kind-of-bad-film/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sam Welton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-venom-the-worst-kind-of-bad-film/</guid>
        <description>Venom is a bloated mess. The spectre of studio compromise looms over it in a big way. It has some glaring flaws but I can’t entirely hate it, since there were elements and sequences I found really engaging.
It’s the worst kind of bad film: passion and talent are on display and at some point this …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
