<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/phc11/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/phc11/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Big Headlines &amp; Little Englanders
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-big-headlines-little-englanders/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 22:11:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Padraic Calpin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-big-headlines-little-englanders/</guid>
        <description>Though everyone seems to be resigned to the Coalition trundling along to 2015, there’s still a bite to British (though perhaps more specifically English) politics. It’s been a tumultuous month, with waves of Tory rebellion unsettling David Cameron and the guffawing face of Farage barely off the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial trailing in equal access to education
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-imperial-trailing-in-equal-access-to-education/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 23:44:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Padraic Calpin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-imperial-trailing-in-equal-access-to-education/</guid>
        <description>At the core of student opposition to the College’s decision to close Garden Hall and open a new residence in North Acton is a concern for Imperial’s less well off students. Campus Services seems to have demonstrated an utter disregard for the possibility that poorer students may be forced out off …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS Album of the Week 12
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-ams-album-of-the-week-12/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 13:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Padraic Calpin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-ams-album-of-the-week-12/</guid>
        <description>Whenever I have an article to write I find the first sentences and phrases always come to me when I’m walking on my own. My rough draft for this review emerged the same way; I was ready to talk less about the album, which was okay, and more about the promise of My Bloody Valentine recording once …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Egypt: Two years on, new protests
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-egypt-two-years-on-new-protests/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 23:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Padraic Calpin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-egypt-two-years-on-new-protests/</guid>
        <description>January 25th 2013 wasthe second anniversary of the Egyptian protests that led to the fall of the autocratic regime of Hosni Mubarak. Tahrir Square was once again filled with protesters, their anger now directed at the current elected President Mohamed Morsi, and the police who are accused of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Le Misérable
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-le-misrable/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 00:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Padraic Calpin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-le-misrable/</guid>
        <description>“GéGé” is the affectionate nickname of famous French actor Gérard Depardieu; but lately he hasn’t been the recipient of much affection. Instead, Depardieu has found himself at the centre of a debate that has taken place in countless nations since the financial crisis began; how great should the tax …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Politics Précis
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-politics-prcis/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 22:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Padraic Calpin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-politics-prcis/</guid>
        <description>Italian Elections Heat Up
On the 9th of December Mario Monti, Italy’s “technocrat” leader, stepped down amid a boycott by Berlusconi’s Freedom People party over budget decisions. Appointed after Berlusconi lost his parliamentary majority and resigned amongst personal scandals, Monti’s government was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>DIIV in The Garage
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-diiv-in-the-garage/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 03:42:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Padraic Calpin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-diiv-in-the-garage/</guid>
        <description>Zachary Cole Smith is the guitarist for lo-fi surf rock outfit Beach Fossils, whose band-members are currently off pursuing their own side-projects. For Smith, his efforts have coalesced into DIIV (said ‘Dive’), with the debut album Oshin coming out earlier this year.
From these names, you get no …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UK&#39;s Green Success
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-uks-green-success/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 23:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Padraic Calpin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-uks-green-success/</guid>
        <description>The UK’s current stance on Green policy is mixed at best: despite Coalition pledges to be the ‘Greenest Government Ever’, Cameron and Clegg have come under repeated fire, whether over the planned ‘Dash for Gas’, or the Tory energy minister insisting on challenging the coalition policy on onshore …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>King Krule: Live
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-king-krule-live/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 23:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),Padraic Calpin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-king-krule-live/</guid>
        <description>King Krule, a lonely rider of the current music scene, the only one that is really talking about being in pain (his own words), is the alias of an 18-year old South Londoner, Archie Marshall, accompanied on stage by a bassist, drummer, saxophonist and guitarist. Archie first caught people’s eye last …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kaleidoscopes of Canada
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-kaleidoscopes-of-canada/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:28:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Padraic Calpin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-kaleidoscopes-of-canada/</guid>
        <description>IDM (which, unfortunately, is short for intelligent dance music) is an incredibly interesting genre. Also dubbed “Armchair Techno” , it’s a loosely defined term for experimental electronic music. The sounds lumped under this label can vary wildly, from the hauntingly nostalgic to tracks with beats …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Abortion debate resurfaces
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-abortion-debate-resurfaces/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 21:14:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Padraic Calpin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-abortion-debate-resurfaces/</guid>
        <description>One of the central features of David Cameron’s reinvention of the Conservative party going in to the 2010 election was the pull to the centre; dressed in the vocabulary of the Big Society and Green Conservatism, they sought to shed the old-fashioned, right-wing image. ‘Backbench’ MPs may have been …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Freshers fooled by large number of fake Facebook groups
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-freshers-fooled-by-large-number-of-fake-facebook-groups/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 16:04:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Padraic Calpin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-freshers-fooled-by-large-number-of-fake-facebook-groups/</guid>
        <description>For new students joining Imperial College each year, the various Facebook groups for halls, subjects, and for the entire year of Freshers as a whole are an invaluable resource, both for specific questions and getting to know your future class/house/roommates (delete as appropriate). Unfortunately, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Back Boris? Not bloody likely!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-back-boris-not-bloody-likely/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 22:24:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Padraic Calpin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-back-boris-not-bloody-likely/</guid>
        <description>This May, Londoners will again be called upon to elect a mayor, and if the polls are anything to go by the race between incumbent Boris Johnson and returning rival Ken Livingstone is too close to call. The thing is, I have real difficulty understanding how that can be so. Cynics remark that British …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Occupy Protests are succeeding. Just look at this paper
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-the-occupy-protests-are-succeeding-just-look-at-this-paper/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 21:27:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Padraic Calpin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-the-occupy-protests-are-succeeding-just-look-at-this-paper/</guid>
        <description>The Occupy movement, inspired by protest in Spain, made famous in New York and now a global phenomenon, is succeeding. On the face of it, this might seems to be an audacious claim. Indeed, some of you will be reading this and audibly scoffing; “They have no clear goals; what are they succeeding at?” …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
