<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mff113/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mff113/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The Editors’ picks of the past year...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-the-editors-picks-of-the-past-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 09:29:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-the-editors-picks-of-the-past-year/</guid>
        <description> Picks for summer The Serpentine Pavilion
The Serpentine Gallery’s Pavilion, a mere stone’s throw from the South Ken campus, is perhaps one the best places to amp up the culture factor on a sunny summer’s day. It’s free, it’s outside (bang in the middle of Hyde Park), and it houses a caf. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The EU contribution to the Arts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-the-eu-contribution-to-the-arts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 09:01:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-the-eu-contribution-to-the-arts/</guid>
        <description>According to the Leave campaign, it is to the tune of £350m a week that the patriarchal dictators in the EU extort our poor impoverished island. As the great cultural icons Boris and Nigel might like to believe, if it were not for the bloodsucking greed of the EU, each and every British family up …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Suicide
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-the-suicide/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 10:16:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-the-suicide/</guid>
        <description>The National’s latest modernisation of an old classic, The Suicide has all the potential of a biting satirical comedy with little of the finesse or foundation to really pull it off. While the laughs are frequent and at times provocative, the play struggles to maintain its momentum and leaves little …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kieran Hodgson doping his way to the top
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-12-kieran-hodgson-doping-his-way-to-the-top/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2015 11:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-12-kieran-hodgson-doping-his-way-to-the-top/</guid>
        <description>In 2003 a young, frail lad from West Yorkshire had only one idol, the great Lance Armstrong. Inspired by the serene, omnipotent cyclist come lying bastard, Kieran Hodgson is taking the world by storm with his completely honest, unadulterated, dope-free journey. Fun and easy-going, Hodgson’s set is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All hail the Frieze?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-all-hail-the-frieze/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 11:43:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-all-hail-the-frieze/</guid>
        <description>The dirty side of the art world isn’t always obvious, but Frieze London is making every effort to scream it in your face. The fair ranges from the dull to the exceptional – as you would expect from any art fair – but the commercial machine seems to bleed through everything. Located in a giant …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The hilarious world of Ahir Shah
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-the-hilarious-world-of-ahir-shah/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 11:38:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-the-hilarious-world-of-ahir-shah/</guid>
        <description>The sharpest, most politically charged comedy I have ever seen – period. Of course what I’ve seen is somewhat limited, but that changes little; Ahir Shah is exceptional. There are many great comedians who make you laugh, and some who make you cry, but few can make you think and feel like Shah. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Surreal Counterargument to Capitalist Society
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-1-a-surreal-counterargument-to-capitalist-society/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 10:13:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-1-a-surreal-counterargument-to-capitalist-society/</guid>
        <description>Using animation, live music, physical theatre, and stand-up comic timing, Golem is less your standard play and more a cabaret spectacle. Despite a slightly weaker plot than hoped, Golem’s message about corporate greed and human idleness is poignantly addressed by its technical achievements. With …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lost in the Wild
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-4-24-lost-in-the-wild/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2015 13:57:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-4-24-lost-in-the-wild/</guid>
        <description>If only third time lucky always worked out. With another long-winded, lacklustre display from the Orange Tree, I am starting to lose patience with Paul Miller’s tenure at this fantastic theatre.
A rare early work by the Nobel Prize winning Doris Lessing, _Each his own Wilderness _is branded a play …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Play Mas fails to live up to its promise
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-play-mas-fails-to-live-up-to-its-promise/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 13:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-play-mas-fails-to-live-up-to-its-promise/</guid>
        <description>The joy of carnival is infectious. Dressing up, getting drunk and parading around town to the sound of steel drums: what could be better? Every culture has a different spin on carnival, but few know how to do it better than the Trinidadians’ annual Play Mas.
Written in 1974 by the Trinidadian …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Utterly Overpowered By Arthur Miller
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-22-utterly-overpowered-by-arthur-miller/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 17:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-22-utterly-overpowered-by-arthur-miller/</guid>
        <description>I have a confession to make. In my ignorance, I know practically nothing about Arthur Miller. Arguably one of the greatest playwrights of the twentieth century, at least a superficial understanding of Miller’s work should probably be expected from me, but not even that can I offer. Clueless, but …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Interview: Jon Haynes in Conversation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-22-interview-jon-haynes-in-conversation/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 17:35:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-22-interview-jon-haynes-in-conversation/</guid>
        <description>The afternoon I meet Jon Haynes on Bond Street, I really should have better things to be doing. With a lab report due in 24 hours and a rehearsal to plan for later in the day, this interview couldn’t come at a much worse time. But this opportunity is too good to miss. With numerous awards and an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London’s Best Small Theatres - Part 1
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-17-londons-best-small-theatres-part-1/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2015 16:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-17-londons-best-small-theatres-part-1/</guid>
        <description> ## The Finborough Theatre ## If every small theatre were like the Finborough I’d probably never have any complaints. Punching well above its weight, the Finborough has long been regarded as one of the absolute best fringe venues in London for a number of years. A small theatre which uniquely hosts …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London’s best small theatres - Part II
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-17-londons-best-small-theatres-part-ii/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2015 16:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-17-londons-best-small-theatres-part-ii/</guid>
        <description> ## Battersea Arts Centre There’s something wrong with the Battersea Arts Centre. Although the management would have you believe its decrepit shell is from a beautiful Grade II listed former town hall, its insides leave a lot to be desired. However, what it lacks in a permanent purpose built modern …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Little Light – a family affair
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-17-little-light-a-family-affair/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2015 16:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-17-little-light-a-family-affair/</guid>
        <description>There’s something very familiar about watching siblings argue. Whether you’re brother or sister, older or younger, at some point in your relationship a certain degree of sibling rivalry seems inevitable. So, for a change, it was rather refreshing to see Little Light open on what felt like a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bonkers, But Not Brilliant - Bat Boy: The Musical
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-7-bonkers-but-not-brilliant-bat-boy-the-musical/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2015 19:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-7-bonkers-but-not-brilliant-bat-boy-the-musical/</guid>
        <description>I am not a fan of musicals. There, I’ve said it. When you grow up spending every waking moment with ‘theatrical types’ who sit around reciting ballads from Les Miserables, musicals can make you hate them. Listening to song after whiny song which all fail to add any story to the show, and with music …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Eradication: The Extreme of Experimental
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-7-eradication-the-extreme-of-experimental/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2015 19:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-7-eradication-the-extreme-of-experimental/</guid>
        <description>In the eerie Council Chamber of Battersea Arts Centre, a partition has been raised between the two halves of the room. With half the audience on one side and half on the other, two different plays are on show. In what feels like a set botched together from bits and pieces, the audience wait to find …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Unseen — The Hidden Wealths that Lie in the Depths of the Courtauld
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-31-unseen-the-hidden-wealths-that-lie-in-the-depths-of-the-courtauld/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2015 19:19:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-31-unseen-the-hidden-wealths-that-lie-in-the-depths-of-the-courtauld/</guid>
        <description>This January sees the opening of the Gilbert &amp;amp; Ildiko Butlerdrawings gallery at the Courtauld. The wonderful purpose built gallery, designed by 2013 Stirling prize winners Witherford Watson Mann Architects, finally gives the public a chance to see one of the most celebrated collections of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bonkers, But Not Brilliant - Bat Boy: The Musical
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-31-bonkers-but-not-brilliant-bat-boy-the-musical/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2015 19:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-31-bonkers-but-not-brilliant-bat-boy-the-musical/</guid>
        <description>I am not a fan of musicals. There, I’ve said it. When you grow up spending every waking moment with ‘theatrical types’ who sit around reciting ballads from Les Miserables, musicals can make you hate them. Listening to song after whiny song which all fail to add any story to the show, and with music …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>One Woman’s Triumph of Theatre
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-31-one-womans-triumph-of-theatre/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2015 18:42:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-31-one-womans-triumph-of-theatre/</guid>
        <description>Smart, sexy and absurd. One woman shows do not get any better than this. For an hour of complete hilarity, Violet Fox recounts her struggles to be an ever more extraordinary artist for her exceptionally ordinary audience.
Written and performed by the unbelievably talented Sonia Jalaly, The Story of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Interview with a vampire
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-interview-with-a-vampire/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 18:50:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-interview-with-a-vampire/</guid>
        <description>Tucked just off Cable Street, a short walk from the hustle and bustle of Aldgate, Wilton’s Music Hall is one of the hidden treasures of London’s East End. Positively steeped in history and tradition, it is one of the capital’s oldest music halls, and one of the very few surviving ones that retains …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Office Politics - A Car Crash of a Play
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-21-office-politics-a-car-crash-of-a-play/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2015 20:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-21-office-politics-a-car-crash-of-a-play/</guid>
        <description>Two days before I went to see Office Politics, I was hit by a car cycling home. Unfortunately… it would not be the only time I came close to death that week.
In my time writing for Felix I’ve seen shows which were great, and some which were mediocre, but nothing has come close to the complete …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pig Girl - A Murder Most Foul
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-21-pig-girl-a-murder-most-foul/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2015 20:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-21-pig-girl-a-murder-most-foul/</guid>
        <description>“People don’t disappear into thin air. Not in this country. Not in Canada.”
Pig Girl is a gruesome story we’ve heard all too often. Although a work of fiction, the play is inspired by the disappearance and murders of predominantly indigenous women over a number of years in Canada. Plagued by poor …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Romance and Ruins at the Royal Academy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-18-romance-and-ruins-at-the-royal-academy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 15:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-18-romance-and-ruins-at-the-royal-academy/</guid>
        <description>Anselm Kiefer is not an artist to approach in half measures. When I read that, in 1992, he turned his 35 acre studio in Barjac, France, into a giant Gesamtkunstwerk comprised of storerooms, installations, paintings, underground chambers, corridors, striking glass structures and huge lead sculptures, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>King Charles III – Princely Propaganda or Royalist Treat?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-king-charles-iii-princely-propaganda-or-royalist-treat/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 21:44:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-king-charles-iii-princely-propaganda-or-royalist-treat/</guid>
        <description>Royally entertaining…”, “stimulating comedy”, “a victoriously vulgar piece of light entertainment.” Not so fast!
That’s what the popular, royalist press of this country has been saying about this year’s must-see show,_ King Charles III_ at the Wyndham Theatre.
Of course, for a huge proportion of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>No Such Sweetness
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-no-such-sweetness/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 02:14:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-no-such-sweetness/</guid>
        <description>In January of this year, the UK Government pledged to accept 500 refugees from the Civil War in Syria. _Oh My Sweet Land _tackles the other 2.3 million refugees who don’t have that “privilege”. A collaboration between Amir Nizar Zuabi and Corinne Jaber resulted in this play, inspired by their trip …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Modern Family
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-7-modern-family/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 12:48:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-7-modern-family/</guid>
        <description>Only Lovers Left Alive
Director: Jim Jarmusch
Writer: Jim Jarmusch
Starring: Tom Hiddleston, Tilda Swinton, Mia Wasikowska, John Hurt, Anton Yelchin, Jeffrey Wright
Runtime: 122 minutes
Certification: 15
“It’s the zombies I’m sick of, and their fear of their own fucking imaginations.”
The result of …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
