<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/im1413/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/im1413/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Troy: Myth and Reality</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-troy-myth-reality/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-troy-myth-reality/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
Legend has it that the goddess of discord threw a golden apple into a crowd, bearing the inscription ‘for the most beautiful’. It was claimed by three goddesses, Athena, Hera and Aphrodite, and Zeus asked The Trojan prince Paris to make the final judgement. He chose Aphrodite, who promised …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your Union is Standing Firm</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-let-me-be-your-star-mtsoc-revue-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-let-me-be-your-star-mtsoc-revue-review/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
Sometimes all it takes to fall in love with a musical is that one special song or moment. MTSoc’s medley of musical classics hopes to scratch that itch with over fifteen musicals represented! With more than 45 performers taking part in the show in small groups, the audience was transported …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Love, Me and Compost: A Double Bill of Love and Trash</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-love-me-compost-double-bill-love-trash/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-love-me-compost-double-bill-love-trash/</guid>
        <description>Love, Me: 3.5 stars
Compost: 4 stars
Teaming up for a double-billed show, our very own MTSoc and Dramsoc have put together an original musical titled Love, Me, and an original play titled Compost, the latter of which was recently performed at the Edinburgh Fringe Festival over the summer.
Love, Me …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>When They See Us: Ava DuVernay’s ‘Central Park Five’ mini-series asks us to bear witness to painful truths</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-when-they-see-us-ava-duvernay-s-central-park-five-mini-series-asks-us-to-bear-witness-to-painful-truths/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-when-they-see-us-ava-duvernay-s-central-park-five-mini-series-asks-us-to-bear-witness-to-painful-truths/</guid>
        <description>At the outset of When They See Us, we meet a group of young Harlem boys. Kevin Richardson (Asante Blackk), the youngest, is a musical talent encouraged by his older sister to put Spring Break to good use - he could be as good as Miles Davis one day. Korey Wise (Jharrel Jerome) is sixteen and in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Vita &amp; Virginia Review</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-vita-virginia-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-vita-virginia-review/</guid>
        <description>Sometimes called the longest love-letter in history, Virginia Woolf wrote Orlando, the fictional biography of a gender-bending, time travelling Elizabethan nobleman, as a tribute to her friend, and sometimes-lover, Vita Sackville-West. Based to a great extent on the letters that the two acclaimed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Avalanche: A Love Story</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-avalanche-a-love-story/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-avalanche-a-love-story/</guid>
        <description>Hope springs eternal; that is both a blessing and curse for Julie Leigh’s protagonist, the Woman (Maxine Peake), in Avalanche: A Love Story. We meet Peake’s nameless character at a psychic’s gathering, which is really something of a supernaturally tinged group therapy session. Everyone there is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sex, Drugs, and Murder on the Heath</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-sex-drugs-and-murder-on-the-heath/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-sex-drugs-and-murder-on-the-heath/</guid>
        <description>We meet Anthony (Ciarán Owens), a man just shy of thirty-three (as he fond of telling us) at his arrival at a chemsex party. He is a seasoned pro, bantering with Ian Hallard’s accountant who is in charge of metering out the GBL doses mixed in with apple juice or lucozade. Just when he is about to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ferrante Reviewed</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-ferrante-reviewed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-ferrante-reviewed/</guid>
        <description>There are some books that you want to devour as fast as possible, sleep becomes secondary to being carried along the twists and turns of a novel’s relentless plots. Other books are to be savoured, each sentence in its perfect composition wondered over. Very rarely, a book is both. The Neapolitan …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Matthew Bourne’s Swan Lake retains its wild heart</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-matthew-bourne-s-swan-lake-retains-its-wild-heart/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-matthew-bourne-s-swan-lake-retains-its-wild-heart/</guid>
        <description>From the superstars of the Bolshoi to Billy Elliot raising money for a bus ticket to London, the history of the male ballet dancer is a checkered one- as filled with triumph and acclaim as derision and neglect. Few modern stagings have carved their place in the history of the male ballet star, or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gang signs and a Prayer</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-gang-signs-and-a-prayer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-gang-signs-and-a-prayer/</guid>
        <description>In their tracksuit hoodies and their Adidas creps, their mesh crop tops and skinny black jeans, their baseball caps and performative, cocksure swagger, the teenagers of Erica Whyman’s Verona would not look out place in a Stormzy video. In the new RSC production of Romeo and Juliet, Shakespeare’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Tale of Two Halves: Measure for Measure at the Donmar </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-a-tale-of-two-halves-measure-for-measure-at-the-donmar/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-a-tale-of-two-halves-measure-for-measure-at-the-donmar/</guid>
        <description>Truth is truth, and power is power. In her new staging of Measure for Measure at the Donmar, in which Hayley Atwell and Jack Lowden alternate their roles, director Josie Rourke sets to out to show that some things are universal.
During an evening’s performance, the stage – which is dominated by a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The new Royal Academy places students at its heart</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-the-new-royal-academy-places-students-at-its-heart/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-the-new-royal-academy-places-students-at-its-heart/</guid>
        <description>The Royal Academy is inextricably linked to summer in the capital by virtue of its most well known event: the Summer Exhibition. Each year works by amateur artists, those still looking for their big break, are exhibited alongside the work of the established Academicians: artists elected to the Royal …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>American Dream: Dirty Computer is the truth Janelle Monáe no longer wants to hide</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-american-dream-dirty-computer-is-the-truth-janelle-mon-e-no-longer-wants-to-hide/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-american-dream-dirty-computer-is-the-truth-janelle-mon-e-no-longer-wants-to-hide/</guid>
        <description>Janelle Monáe began her career by adopting an android alter-ego, Cindy Mayweather. In singing about oppression, forbidden love, and the struggle to be free in Cindy’s guise, she joined the tradition of artists like Ann Leckie, who see stories about Artificial Intelligence to be more than science …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Inheritance: the new Angels in America? </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-the-inheritance-the-new-angels-in-america/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-the-inheritance-the-new-angels-in-america/</guid>
        <description>E .M. Forster’s 1910 novel Howard’s End is a tale of Dickensian proportions about the dangers of materialism, and the importance of the responsibilities we owe each other. In it, the altruistic Schlegel siblings clash with the wealthy Wilcoxes: properties are bequeathed in secret; orphans become …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In the eye of the beholder: the male gaze in visual art</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder-the-male-gaze-in-visual-art/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder-the-male-gaze-in-visual-art/</guid>
        <description>The term ‘male gaze’ was coined by Laura Mulvey in 1999 in the context of cinema, in an essay in which she described the role of women in film as “to be simultaneously looked at and displayed”: the result of a heteronormative, patriarchal society in which women are expected to take a passive role. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Black, lesbian, mother, warrior, poet’</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22--black-lesbian-mother-warrior-poet/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22--black-lesbian-mother-warrior-poet/</guid>
        <description>Speaking at a conference on modern language in 1977, in a speech that would later be published as The Transformation of Silence into Language and Action, the poet-activist Audre Lorde reckoned with her mortality.
A few weeks prior, she said, she’d undergone a mastectomy to remove a tumour that in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Portraits of the Obamas unveiled in Washington</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-portraits-of-the-obamas-unveiled-in-washington/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-portraits-of-the-obamas-unveiled-in-washington/</guid>
        <description>On Monday, portraits of the former American President Barack Obama, and the former First Lady Michelle Obama were unveiled at the National Portrait Gallery in Washington DC. They were painted by Kehinde Wiley and Amy Sherald, who were selected by the Obamas after interviews at the White House; they …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The essential rainbow reading list</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-the-essential-rainbow-reading-list/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-the-essential-rainbow-reading-list/</guid>
        <description>A lengthy reading list, I think, is a quintessential part of the coming out story of every bookish queer person. From tentative forays into Sarah Waters’s debauched Victoriana to focused study of Virginia Woolf’s fabulously winding sentences, we use books to try and find ourselves, to build a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix recommends Valentine&#39;s reads… or the books to help you to forget about romance</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-felix-recommends-valentine-s-reads-or-the-books-to-help-you-to-forget-about-romance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,Alice Peberdy,Indira Mallik,Pavan Inguva,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-felix-recommends-valentine-s-reads-or-the-books-to-help-you-to-forget-about-romance/</guid>
        <description> Written on the Body by Jeanette Winterson
 The first question is, who is the narrator? She or he is never named, and their gender never revealed. &amp;ldquo;Why is the measure of love loss?&amp;rdquo; asks the opening sentence, and throughout the book we are taken through the narrator’s clandestine …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Amazing grace: John thrills at the National Theatre</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-amazing-grace-john-thrills-at-the-national-theatre/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-amazing-grace-john-thrills-at-the-national-theatre/</guid>
        <description>We are introduced to Pulitzer-winning playwright Annie Baker’s new play, John, by Mertis. Playing the aging proprietor of an Gettysburg bed &amp;amp; breakfast, Marylouise Burke, whose sense of comedic timing is impeccable, draws back the red velvet stage curtains with slow arthritic movements. In a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Try a Little Tenderness: The Brothers Size at the Young Vic</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-try-a-little-tenderness-the-brothers-size-at-the-young-vic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-try-a-little-tenderness-the-brothers-size-at-the-young-vic/</guid>
        <description>Plays and movies don’t often get written about young, working class, black men; in the rare instances that they are the focus, the light in which they are shown can be less than flattering. Portrayals are often one-dimensional, heavy on aggression and toxic masculinity. In this landscape of facile …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Salieri versus God : Amadeus at the National Theatre</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-salieri-versus-god-amadeus-at-the-national-theatre/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-salieri-versus-god-amadeus-at-the-national-theatre/</guid>
        <description>Why do good things happen to terrible people? Who among us has not balked at the happiness and success of someone we consider to be objectively odious, absolutely awful? In the late Peter Shaffer’s classic 1979 play, the virtuoso composer Mozart’s very name – ‘Amadeus’, “beloved by God” – is an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A winter of wonderful content: the art to watch out for this term </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-a-winter-of-wonderful-content-the-art-to-watch-out-for-this-term/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-a-winter-of-wonderful-content-the-art-to-watch-out-for-this-term/</guid>
        <description>Christmas trees are being thrown out, commuters are once again heading grim-faced into the bowels of the Underground, and many of you will be revising for exams, or settling back into another term of lectures – there’s no doubt about it, 2018 has officially begun.
Over in Victoria, Hamilton is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Never the same love twice</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-never-the-same-love-twice/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-never-the-same-love-twice/</guid>
        <description>We ask a lot of short stories — they need to make the reader, or, if on the stage, the audience, feel the same peaks and troughs of emotion as a lengthier work; they need to speak to us with the same profundity, take us on the same journey with far fewer resources at their disposal. Like the best …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2017 in review: the Arts editors take you through the best exhibitions and shows in London this year</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-2017-in-review-the-arts-editors-take-you-through-the-best-exhibitions-and-shows-in-london-this-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,Adam Gellatly,Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-2017-in-review-the-arts-editors-take-you-through-the-best-exhibitions-and-shows-in-london-this-year/</guid>
        <description>It’s a strange feeling, when you feel like you know an artist, that you have a reasonable understanding of his work, to then discover him afresh. But exactly what I experienced at Tate Britain in February, when the gallery put on the largest ever arrangement of Hockney’s work.
David Hockney, The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Clash of Cultures: Phoenix Editors special</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-clash-of-cultures-phoenix-editors-special/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,Adam Gellatly,Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-clash-of-cultures-phoenix-editors-special/</guid>
        <description>Phoenix, Felix ’s sister arts publication, returns this week with a teaser 8-page pullout. Arts Editors Indira Malik and Adam Gellatly and Felix Editor-in-Chief Fred Fyles talk to Phoenix Editors Liliane Laborde-Edozien, Catherine Webb, and Joy Aston about their plans for the magazine and their love …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lubaina Himid crowned winner of the Turner Prize</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-lubaina-himid-crowned-winner-of-the-turner-prize/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-lubaina-himid-crowned-winner-of-the-turner-prize/</guid>
        <description>The Turner Prize, which celebrates developments in contemporary British art, was awarded to Lubaina Himid on Tuesday night. Himid, 63, is the oldest recipient of the prestigious award, as well as the first woman of colour to be given the honour. Widely expected to win for her work that focuses on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An indescribable pause: The Impressionists’ love letter to London</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-an-indescribable-pause-the-impressionists-love-letter-to-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-an-indescribable-pause-the-impressionists-love-letter-to-london/</guid>
        <description>With the news fixed on the movement of refugees in Europe, the Tate has turned to an earlier period in the continent’s history when war and political instability caused a surge of migration into London. Brexit in their crosshairs, the curators preface the new exhibition on Impressionists with the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Home Is the Place…</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-home-is-the-place/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-home-is-the-place/</guid>
        <description>If weeks had themes, the theme of last week would’ve been empowerment. On Wednesday I ventured down into Imperial’s Enterprise Labs as part of the WE Innovate scheme and met dozens of inspiring, amazingly ambitious women just at the beginning of their careers desperate to make a difference in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Looking for love in the lonely city</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-looking-for-love-in-the-lonely-city/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-looking-for-love-in-the-lonely-city/</guid>
        <description>Olivia Laing in her exceptional book, The Lonely City, remarks, “So much of the pain of loneliness is about concealment. But&amp;hellip;what’s so shameful about wanting?”. Loneliness, and the barriers we set up even as we try to forge new connections are at the centre of David Eldridge’s new play. In …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sondheim’s classic Follies revived in London</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-sondheim-s-classic-follies-revived-in-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-sondheim-s-classic-follies-revived-in-london/</guid>
        <description>In Follies, the shine has rubbed off from the Weisman Theatre. The musical sees a group of retired chorus girls who once performed there gather to bid farewell to their old haunt before it is demolished. It is a love letter to the New York of old, the glamour of Broadway and the pain of reaching …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bold, vibrant, poignant: the unrealised genius of Jean-Michel Basquiat</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-bold-vibrant-poignant-the-unrealised-genius-of-jean-michel-basquiat/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-bold-vibrant-poignant-the-unrealised-genius-of-jean-michel-basquiat/</guid>
        <description>Hailed as a ‘radiant child’, Jean-Michel Basquiat erupted onto the 1980s New York art scene in as a teenager. He was just 18 when he began to scrawl poetic graffiti on the streets of New York with one of his school friends Al Diaz as SAMO© – a contraction of ‘same old, same old shit’. When the duo …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mad about the boy: Jane Eyre returns to the NT</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-mad-about-the-boy-jane-eyre-returns-to-the-nt/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-mad-about-the-boy-jane-eyre-returns-to-the-nt/</guid>
        <description>Jane Eyre opens with a scream – it’s one of the moments I think most after I leave the theatre. It is at once all the things I find difficult about the performance, and what seems essential to the spirit of the original novel which is itself a howl for women’s independence and self-determination. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Arts editors completely destroy box office incomes!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-arts-editors-completely-destroy-box-office-incomes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,Adam Gellatly,Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-arts-editors-completely-destroy-box-office-incomes/</guid>
        <description>National Theatre: Entry Pass
The NT offers an Entry Pass to those aged 16 - 25. After registering and providing proof of age, you’ll be entitled to a whole range of NT delights including access to exclusive workshops and events, and discounts in the NT bookshops, cafes, backstage tours and prop …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get to know your friendly neighbourhood Arts team!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-get-to-know-your-friendly-neighbourhood-arts-team/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,Adam Gellatly,Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-get-to-know-your-friendly-neighbourhood-arts-team/</guid>
        <description>INDIRA
Painting, making up stories, and endlessly ambitious crafts projects have been part of my life since early childhood. My writing in particular however never really found a focus until I came to Imperial. Maybe it was watching too much Gilmore Girls during my formative years, but the one thing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where’s the culture at?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-where-s-the-culture-at/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,Adam Gellatly,Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-where-s-the-culture-at/</guid>
        <description>GREEN PARK
Royal Academy: Best known for its annual extravaganza - the Summer Exhibition - the RA hosts a whole range of exhibitions. Upcoming shows not to be missed are Jasper Johns; ‘Something Re-sembling Truth’, and Dali/Duchamp, an exhibition that will explore how their outlook on art and life …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cat on a Hot Tin Roof | Jack O&#39;Connell shines in the Tennessee Williams classic
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-2-cat-on-a-hot-tin-roof-jack-oconnell-shines-in-the-tennessee-williams-classic/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 12:37:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-2-cat-on-a-hot-tin-roof-jack-oconnell-shines-in-the-tennessee-williams-classic/</guid>
        <description>In arguably what is Tennessee William’s most famous play, yearning and desperation boil over in the oppressive heat of the Mississippi delta. Brick Politt, the indulged youngest son, a onetime all-star athlete sinks into alcoholism to appease his gnawing guilt. His wife Maggie is driven to the edge …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Swet Shop Boys | Rap heroes of our time
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-swet-shop-boys-rap-heroes-of-our-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 17:01:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-swet-shop-boys-rap-heroes-of-our-time/</guid>
        <description>On the first of June, midway through his set, Riz Ahmed signalled for the sold-out crowd at Scala to quiet down. Leaning in close, unaccompanied by music, he rapped his 2011 single Sour Times; “Please allow me to vouch for mine…/ losing my religion to tomorrow’s headlines”. It had been exactly a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Soul of a Nation | A searing portrait of the Civil Rights Era
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-23-soul-of-a-nation-a-searing-portrait-of-the-civil-rights-era/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 12:13:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-23-soul-of-a-nation-a-searing-portrait-of-the-civil-rights-era/</guid>
        <description>“Is there a black aesthetic, and if there is, what form does it take?” is the question that concerns the artists assembled for Soul of a Nation. For some, like the Spiral collective, the answer lay in monochrome paintings with a strong political message. In Norman Lewis’ America the Beautiful, a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Swet Shop Boys | Rap heroes for our time
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-15-swet-shop-boys-rap-heroes-for-our-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 17:13:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-15-swet-shop-boys-rap-heroes-for-our-time/</guid>
        <description>On the first of June, midway through his set, Riz Ahmed signalled for the sold-out crowd at Scala to quieten down. Leaning in close, unaccompanied by music, he rapped his 2011 single Sour Times; “Please allow me to vouch for mine…/ losing my religion to tomorrow’s headlines”. It had been exactly a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Queer British Art (1861-1967) | Ostracised, criminalised, but never conquered
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-15-queer-british-art-1861-1967-ostracised-criminalised-but-never-conquered/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 15:59:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-15-queer-british-art-1861-1967-ostracised-criminalised-but-never-conquered/</guid>
        <description>Little rainbows have been popping up everywhere lately - on Facebook, in Skittles adverts, soon they’ll arriving on London’s streets. In fact, the rainbow flag has been flying over Tate Britain for some months now. The gallery will be kicking off the London Pride celebrations next Saturday with a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Summer Exhibition at the Royal Academy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-15-the-summer-exhibition-at-the-royal-academy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 15:17:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-15-the-summer-exhibition-at-the-royal-academy/</guid>
        <description>There aren’t many galleries in which you might expect to see a multimillion pound creation by a Turner prize winning artist exhibited on equal footing with an oil by Joe Bloggs from Surrey, but that is exactly what the Royal Academy’s Summer Exhibition offers. Each year, tens of thousands of works …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Life of Galileo | Stars, Revolution, and Rock and Roll
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-life-of-galileo-stars-revolution-and-rock-and-roll/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:17:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-life-of-galileo-stars-revolution-and-rock-and-roll/</guid>
        <description>Director Joe Wright has pulled out all the stops for the Young Vic’s new staging of Bertolt Brecht’s Life of Galileo. Under a huge makeshift planetarium dome actors in modern dress hurtle around the circular stage. Brendan Cowell as the titular man never seems to stop, at one moment stabbing apples …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Twelfth Night at the Globe | Emma Rice remixes Shakespeare with disco anthems and glittery fun
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-31-twelfth-night-at-the-globe-emma-rice-remixes-shakespeare-with-disco-anthems-and-glittery-fun/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 23:02:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-31-twelfth-night-at-the-globe-emma-rice-remixes-shakespeare-with-disco-anthems-and-glittery-fun/</guid>
        <description>When last season, Emma Rice was appointed artistic director, the Globe seemed to set a new course. Her tenure would mean the company would no longer be focused simply on conservation of Shakespeare but on mutation and adaptation of the classic texts for a modern audience. Yet, this, only her second …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Life of Galileo | Space and rock and roll
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-25-life-of-galileo-space-and-rock-and-roll/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 12:42:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-25-life-of-galileo-space-and-rock-and-roll/</guid>
        <description>Director Joe Wright has pulled out all the stops for the Young Vic’s new staging of Bertolt Brecht’s Life of Galileo. Under a huge makeshift planetarium dome actors in modern dress hurtle around the circular stage. Brendan Cowell as the titular man never seems to stop, at one moment stabbing apples …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Angels in America
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-angels-in-america/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 17:10:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-angels-in-america/</guid>
        <description>A gay fantasia on national themes” is the label Tony Kushner gave his play Angels in America, which is being staged at the National theatre for the first time since the 90s; and what a fantasia it is. Grounded in 1980s New York, the action sprawls across reality and delusion, from Salt Lake City to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Angels in America at the NT
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-10-angels-in-america-at-the-nt/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 18:57:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-10-angels-in-america-at-the-nt/</guid>
        <description>“A gay fantasia on national themes” is the label Tony Kushner gave his playAngels in America, which is being staged at the National Theatre for the first time since the 90s, and what a fantasia it is. Grounded in 1980s New York, the action sprawls across reality and delusion, from Salt Lake City to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Michelangelo &amp; Sebastiano | A Tale of two Masters
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-4-8-michelangelo-sebastiano-a-tale-of-two-masters/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2017 22:52:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-4-8-michelangelo-sebastiano-a-tale-of-two-masters/</guid>
        <description>The National Gallery’s blockbuster show on Michelangelo Buonarroti and his lesser known contemporary and friend, Sebastiano del Piombo attempts to bring the extraordinary beauty of Italy’s great piazzas and churches to London. Jaw-dropping works, from quickfire sketches on the back of boards to huge …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Terrains of the Body is a bold but beguiling show
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-terrains-of-the-body-is-a-bold-but-beguiling-show/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 17:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-terrains-of-the-body-is-a-bold-but-beguiling-show/</guid>
        <description>Hellen van Meene’s works combine this unsteady storyline with a heady mix of sensual textures and colours. Her works are celebrations of surface, with Vermeer-light like dappling across her subjects, bringing an incredible sense of tactility. Janaina Tschape’s work shares this obsession with tone, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Protest or stop complaining
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-protest-or-stop-complaining/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 16:22:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-protest-or-stop-complaining/</guid>
        <description>As part of the Women’s March millions of people took to the streets across the world on Saturday; it was a galore of pink home-knitted “pussy hats” and witty signs, but did it mean anything? Will it lead to change?
In a liberal democracy, political dissent by citizens can take the form of writing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A series of final problems | Sherlock
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-a-series-of-final-problems-sherlock/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-a-series-of-final-problems-sherlock/</guid>
        <description>In 2010 when Sherlock was first introduced to the world as Arthur Conan Doyle’s great detective being brought into the 21st century, co-creator Steven Moffat explained his motivations in making the series to Premium Hollywood thus: “This wasn’t a case of, ‘Let’s grab that off the shelf and update …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This term in Arts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-this-term-in-arts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-this-term-in-arts/</guid>
        <description> It’s safe to say that 2016 wasn’t kind to the world of culture. In a year of blow after blow to the pantheon of iconic cultural stars, the passing of two more bright lights – Carrie Fisher and her mother Debbie Reynolds – left the arts world reeling once more. 2017 brings with it a new hope that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AA Gill is away
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-aa-gill-is-away/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 15:55:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-aa-gill-is-away/</guid>
        <description>The journalist AA Gill, The Sunday Times food (and occasionally TV) critic, died last week, only three weeks after writing about his cancer diagnosis in his weekly column.
He broke the news with the kind sumptuousness of words he used in his criticisms; writing “there is barely a morsel of offal …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A seat at the (culture) roundtable
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-a-seat-at-the-culture-roundtable/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 15:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-a-seat-at-the-culture-roundtable/</guid>
        <description>During the American election cycle on his comedy show Last Week Tonight, John Oliver had a running gag – “look up,” he’d say “that faint glimmer in the distance? That’s rock bottom.” So it has seemed for most of 2016; in almost every sphere, particularly in politics, bad news has been followed by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Julius Caesar | A bold retelling of Shakespeare
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-julius-caesar-a-bold-retelling-of-shakespeare/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 15:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-julius-caesar-a-bold-retelling-of-shakespeare/</guid>
        <description>Just before the start of the performance, as we, the soon-to-be-audience, stand packed like sardines into the small lobby of the King’s Cross Theatre, the sirens go off. The chatter falls silent in the face of the piercing wail, followed by an uniformed prison officer pushing through the crowd – …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Artist in focus | Zaha Hadid, 1950–2016
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-artist-in-focus-zaha-hadid-19502016/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 15:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-artist-in-focus-zaha-hadid-19502016/</guid>
        <description>Picture a piece of contemporary architecture. You’re probably thinking of the work of Frank Gehry – his works are considered by many in the world of architecture to be defining buildings of the 20th and 21st century. Gehry buildings, the Guggenheim in Bilbao being one, are fiercely modernist; great …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Duke | Innovative political theatre
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-the-duke-innovative-political-theatre/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 16:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-the-duke-innovative-political-theatre/</guid>
        <description>Shôn Dale-Jones’ The Duke is about what we are willing to pay for the things we treasure. What is the value of a collectible piece of porcelain, of a script you’ve been working on for ten years, of a seat on a boat that is as likely to plunge you into the sea as to deliver you to safety? In the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Arts Interviews | Edie Edmundson
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-arts-interviews-edie-edmundson/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 15:59:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ezra Kitson,Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-arts-interviews-edie-edmundson/</guid>
        <description>The Little Matchgirl is a show populated by people and puppets, of which the eponymous character, masterfully operated by Edie Edmundson, is one. Our writer, Ezra Kitson, was fortunate enough to speak with her after the performance.
Edmundson was drawn to puppetry by a National Theatre production of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Pirelli #nofilter 2017 calendar
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-the-pirelli-nofilter-2017-calendar/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 12:42:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-the-pirelli-nofilter-2017-calendar/</guid>
        <description>Last year, I wrote about Pirelli turning over a new leaf; its 2016 edition had come on the heels of Playboy announcing that it would no longer feature nudity. What a winter of discontent, I said, for the meninists, won’t someone please think of all those poor men fighting for a world where old white …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Helen Marten wins the Turner Prize
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-helen-marten-wins-the-turner-prize/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 12:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-helen-marten-wins-the-turner-prize/</guid>
        <description>How to describe Turner Prize 2016 winner Helen Marten’s work? &amp;ldquo;Baffling&amp;rdquo; claim some critics, &amp;ldquo;Poetic&amp;rdquo;, others – Michael Gove, former Education Secretary went so far as to tweet &amp;ldquo;#Turnerprize2016 - congratulations to Helen Martin but #honestly is this = to Turner, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Return to Stars Hollow | Gilmore Girls
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-a-return-to-stars-hollow-gilmore-girls/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 15:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-a-return-to-stars-hollow-gilmore-girls/</guid>
        <description>Reviving beloved TV shows can be a tricky business. Shows that are missed tend to build up a mythology around them; with time and absence, every fault and inconsistency is forgiven. To bring them back, however, is to burst the rose tinted bubble of fond nostalgia and push them into the harsh lens of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Nutcracker | London&#39;s Christmas countdown has begun
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-the-nutcracker-londons-christmas-countdown-has-begun/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 15:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-the-nutcracker-londons-christmas-countdown-has-begun/</guid>
        <description>The Royal Opera House’s The Nutcracker, like the switching on of the lights on Oxford Street, or the Selfridge’s window display, marks London’s countdown to Christmas. The Christmas themed ballet is a tradition that has roots in Imperial Russia. The ballet, which was commissioned by the director of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Breaking the walls of the &#39;pre-invented world&#39;
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-breaking-the-walls-of-the-pre-invented-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 14:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-breaking-the-walls-of-the-pre-invented-world/</guid>
        <description>In an interview with The Paris Review Joan Didion describes the act of writing as &amp;ldquo;hostile&amp;rdquo;, explaining further: &amp;ldquo;you’re trying to make somebody see something the way you see it&amp;hellip;wrench around someone else’s mind&amp;rdquo;. The same can be said of any form of art. Truly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Deconstructing the myth of &#39;prancing princes&#39;
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-deconstructing-the-myth-of-prancing-princes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 15:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-deconstructing-the-myth-of-prancing-princes/</guid>
        <description>In 1976, tongue firmly in cheek, social scientists Deborah David, and Robert Brannon, outlined the four tenets of American masculinity; “no sissy stuff”, “be a big wheel”, “be a sturdy oak”, and “give em hell”. The terms might be joking; the principles behind them are not; emotional constipation, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The ‘nasty women’ of Broad City
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-1-the-nasty-women-of-broad-city/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-1-the-nasty-women-of-broad-city/</guid>
        <description>It was during the last US Presidential Debate that Donald Trump muttered ‘what a nasty woman’ Hillary Clinton was, the latest of Donald Trump’s transgressions. Minutes after the debate had finished, Twitter was ablaze with women reclaiming the insult. Elizabeth Warren made ‘nasty women’ the centre …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Editors’ picks of the past year...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-the-editors-picks-of-the-past-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 09:29:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-the-editors-picks-of-the-past-year/</guid>
        <description> Picks for summer The Serpentine Pavilion
The Serpentine Gallery’s Pavilion, a mere stone’s throw from the South Ken campus, is perhaps one the best places to amp up the culture factor on a sunny summer’s day. It’s free, it’s outside (bang in the middle of Hyde Park), and it houses a caf. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Royal Academy Summer Exhibition
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-royal-academy-summer-exhibition/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 09:26:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-royal-academy-summer-exhibition/</guid>
        <description>The Summer Exhibition at the Royal Academy is a bit like Glastonbury of the arts world, if the people who went were 97% white with a mean age of sixty. Along with fixtures like Wimbledon, it heralds in the summer, bringing together established artists from all the different disciplines: printmaking, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is David Hockney all he&#39;s cracked up to be?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-is-david-hockney-all-hes-cracked-up-to-be/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 08:34:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-is-david-hockney-all-hes-cracked-up-to-be/</guid>
        <description>Soon, London art galleries will be in the throes of a David Hockney takeover. Starting from July, the Royal Academy will showcase ‘82 portraits and one still life’, and beginning in February next year, the Tate will host a comprehensive retrospective spanning decades of the artist’s work. It should …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>When Beyoncé Gives You Lemons
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-when-beyonc-gives-you-lemons/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:36:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-when-beyonc-gives-you-lemons/</guid>
        <description>Lemonade, Beyoncé’s sixth studio album dropped on Saturday, with nothing but a seconds-long cryptic YouTube video to promote it. The ‘visual album’, directed by seven directors including Kahlil Joseph (Kendrick Lamar’s ‘m.A.A.d’), and Melina Matsoukas (‘Pretty Hurts’, ‘Formation’) is something …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The boys wanna be her
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-the-boys-wanna-be-her/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 12:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-the-boys-wanna-be-her/</guid>
        <description>Judith Leyster
Leyster, born in 1606 was the only woman to be appointed one of the Dutch Masters. It’s easy to see why, ‘Self-Portrait’ (pictured left) brilliantly shows what a virtuoso and throughly modern painter she was. The composition is a break from the rigidity and formality of portraiture of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Against a sea of troubles – theatre in the Jungle
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-against-a-sea-of-troubles-theatre-in-the-jungle/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 11:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-against-a-sea-of-troubles-theatre-in-the-jungle/</guid>
        <description>The question of whether the arts are a luxury or a necessity has become one of the issues surrounding the ‘Jungle’ refugee camp just outside Calais.
Over 6000 displaced people from some of the most violent places in the world have gathered in the camp, a collection of makeshift shelters, home to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Beyoncé wins the Super Bowl, again
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-beyonc-wins-the-super-bowl-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 11:53:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-beyonc-wins-the-super-bowl-again/</guid>
        <description>Beyoncé has never been one to shy away from making a statement; the surprise release of her self-titled album in 2013 proved that. The release of ‘Formation’ 24 hours before upstaging Coldplay at their headline gig at the Super Bowl could be a new high. Not only the manner of its release, but the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FELIX reacts to virtual reality
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-felix-reacts-to-virtual-reality/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 12:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Indira Mallik,Cale E Tilford,Lef Apostolakis,Saad Ahmed,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-felix-reacts-to-virtual-reality/</guid>
        <description>The year of virtual reality is finally upon us. This week, the FELIX team tried Gear VR, Samsung’s mobile virtual reality headset.
It’s not as powerful as competitors like Oculus Rift or the HTC Vive, but it’s a decent introduction to VR for the unacquainted.
Lef Apostolakis, Science Editor
I tried …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A vibrant tour of 20th century blossoms
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-a-vibrant-tour-of-20th-century-blossoms/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 12:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-a-vibrant-tour-of-20th-century-blossoms/</guid>
        <description>To walk into Painting the Modern Garden: Monet to Matisse at The Royal Academy is to plunge into a world of exuberant greenery, of sun-dappled paths, manicured lawns, a land where it is always spring, and Paris is always in bloom.
“Perhaps I owe it to flowers” Monet once said, “that I became a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The ancient art of being illustrated
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-the-ancient-art-of-being-illustrated/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 09:39:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-the-ancient-art-of-being-illustrated/</guid>
        <description>Skin as a blank canvas is not a new idea; Ötzi the Iceman, frozen sometime between 3239 and 3105 BCE had a tattoo. Inking or marking skin unites cultures and continents across the ages.
Until recently in the West, tattoos have been seen as a mark of belonging to a counterculture. They are so …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stand up stars raise money for refugees
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-stand-up-stars-raise-money-for-refugees/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 09:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-stand-up-stars-raise-money-for-refugees/</guid>
        <description>Last Wednesday, a constellation of comedy stars performed at the Eventim Apollo’s one off Stand Up in Action benefit to raise money for Action-Aid and the UN Refugee Agency (UNHCR), the charities providing aid in response to the global refugee crisis.
The night included routines by Jo Brand (Getting …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Slash and Burn: The Future of British Arts under the Tories
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-slash-and-burn-the-future-of-british-arts-under-the-tories/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 12:59:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-slash-and-burn-the-future-of-british-arts-under-the-tories/</guid>
        <description>Last Friday, Britain woke up to an entirely changed political landscape. Instead of days of coalition talks, or discussing the constitutional ins and outs of a minority government, we were faced with a Conservative majority. Within the space of hours, the commentators went from discussing the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Grand Master of Impressionism
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-the-grand-master-of-impressionism/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 13:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-the-grand-master-of-impressionism/</guid>
        <description>It’s not often that exhibitions are staged in celebration of art collectors. Perhaps it feels more like honouring the monetary value of the work than its impact, but Inventing Impressionism at the National Gallery shows how focussing on the collector can sometimes be a stroke of genius. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sargent – A Bridge To The Modern
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-22-sargent-a-bridge-to-the-modern/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 17:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-22-sargent-a-bridge-to-the-modern/</guid>
        <description>John Singer Sargent is not often included amongst the great painters of the late 19th century. It’s an exclusive club. Monet, Renoir, Picasso, Degas, Rodin, Cézanne, van Gogh, and Klimt amongst others dominate the public perceptions of art in the 1880s-1910s, and with good reason. Some of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Male, Pale, &amp; Stale?’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-31-male-pale-stale/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2015 18:37:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-31-male-pale-stale/</guid>
        <description>Last week, the unlikeliest of arguments took place. The participants: the somewhat passé singer James Blunt and Labour’s new culture secretary Chris Bryant. The topic: diversity (or lack thereof) in the British arts sector. Bryant sparked the row when, in his first interview since becoming shadow …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>At the Frontiers of Art, Performance, and Protest
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-18-at-the-frontiers-of-art-performance-and-protest/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 16:20:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-18-at-the-frontiers-of-art-performance-and-protest/</guid>
        <description>In recent years, the idea of revolution and protests has barely left the public consciousness, or our TV screens. From the Arab Spring across Syria, Libya and Egypt to the recent protests in Ferguson and New York against police brutality, protest has spread to all corners of the world.
The_ …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Transforming Modern Perceptions of Medieval Art
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-18-transforming-modern-perceptions-of-medieval-art/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 16:12:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-18-transforming-modern-perceptions-of-medieval-art/</guid>
        <description>Earlier this month, the author Saladin Ahmed wrote on Twitter “the fantasy vision of a medieval Europe devoid of people of colour isn’t realism. It’s a different word that starts with ‘r’ and ends with ‘ism’.”
 The fantasy vision of a medieval Europe devoid of people of colour isn&amp;rsquo;t realism. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Revealing the Reality of Campus Rape
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-revealing-the-reality-of-campus-rape/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 19:53:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-revealing-the-reality-of-campus-rape/</guid>
        <description>Something of a small revolution is taking place at Columbia University. Each day, Emma Sulkowicz, a 21 year old 3rd year student can be seen carrying her 23 kg mattress around campus. It’s not that she’s found a drastic solution to tiredness at lectures; but rather a powerful performance art piece. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Paralysed man walks after stem cell therapy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-paralysed-man-walks-after-stem-cell-therapy/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 21:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-paralysed-man-walks-after-stem-cell-therapy/</guid>
        <description>Last week, it was reported that Darek Fidyka, a man from Poland, had begun to walk. He had been paralyzed from the chest down since 2010 after a knife attack. His recovery was hailed as ‘more impressive than man walking on the moon’ by Geoffrey Raisman, whose research at UCL almost 30 years ago made …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is all art propaganda?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-is-all-art-propaganda/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 04:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-is-all-art-propaganda/</guid>
        <description>Art should comfort the disturbed and disturb the comfortable. It’s an instantly quotable adage from Banksy, but what does it actually mean? Can a line be drawn between outright political propaganda and the canvases hanging in every hip gallery in London? Or is all art propaganda, as the title of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Arts Emergency!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-arts-emergency/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 03:47:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-arts-emergency/</guid>
        <description>Present education policy seems to be driven by the political notion that culture should be seen as a ‘luxury’ and a ‘commodity’, and purely in terms of economic utility. In April 2013, arts secretary Maria Miller spoke on the subject of British arts, saying that the argument for continued arts …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Inside the home of architect Norman Swann
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-inside-the-home-of-architect-norman-swann/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 09:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-inside-the-home-of-architect-norman-swann/</guid>
        <description>The Scandinavian duo Elmgreen and Dragset’s Tomorrow exhibition is quite unlike anything else you would likely come across in the rest of the V&amp;amp;A. Everything is arranged to be touched, to be rummaged through. It places the viewer in the role of voyeur, passing uninvited through the house of …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
