<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/pa07/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/pa07/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial taught me how to be a better DJ
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-imperial-taught-me-how-to-be-a-better-dj/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 08:55:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pietro Aronica,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-imperial-taught-me-how-to-be-a-better-dj/</guid>
        <description>This will be my final article for FELIX, as, after nearly nine years, my time has come to leave Imperial. This newspaper has been an important part of my experience here, back from the very first copy I acquired in freshers’ week and kept because it had the instructions on how to operate washing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The EU is not perfect, but is the better option
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-the-eu-is-not-perfect-but-is-the-better-option/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 08:48:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pietro Aronica,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-the-eu-is-not-perfect-but-is-the-better-option/</guid>
        <description>I have written many times for FELIX with trollish tones and hyperbole, but this time, there is no exaggeration in what I say: I can think of no worse political catastrophe in our time than the UK leaving the European Union, perhaps only rivalled by a Trump presidency.
The upcoming referendum is of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You have bad taste if you like ales
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-you-have-bad-taste-if-you-like-ales/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:31:47 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pietro Aronica,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-you-have-bad-taste-if-you-like-ales/</guid>
        <description>Every day I wake up I thank the gods I’m not English. I thank them because I was not born in a country where a family of layabouts is put on the throne and worshipped for no goddamned reason. I thank them because I have much more international football to remember fondly. I thank the gods because my …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I want to say thank you to the bad people
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-i-want-to-say-thank-you-to-the-bad-people/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 01:29:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pietro Aronica,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-i-want-to-say-thank-you-to-the-bad-people/</guid>
        <description>This goes out to all the bad people. This is for the terrorists and the murderers; for those who are violent and bigoted, or ignorant and entitled; for the unscrupulous businessmen and the hypocritical prigs; for the unrepentant criminals and the self-righteous moralisers. To you, I wanna say thank …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are you up to the Challenge?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-are-you-up-to-the-challenge/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 19:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pietro Aronica,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-are-you-up-to-the-challenge/</guid>
        <description>What is the capital of Kenya? Which is the largest moon of the Solar System? Who is the only person to have been awarded two unshared Nobel Prizes?
For many people, the answer to those questions is “who cares?”, or, if they’re feeling charitable, “just google it”. For a select few, however, being …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Falsity of Hope
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-the-falsity-of-hope/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 13:14:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pietro Aronica,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-the-falsity-of-hope/</guid>
        <description>Don’t hope. Never hope.
Hope is a last resort, an admission of defeat. You hope when there is nothing left to do, nothing you can do: you can’t act, repair, work, correct or strive anymore, so you wish that things could go your way. All you’re left with is your powerlessness and the hope that cosmic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oh, what’s wrong with the world today?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-oh-whats-wrong-with-the-world-today/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 13:22:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pietro Aronica,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-oh-whats-wrong-with-the-world-today/</guid>
        <description>It used to be that the world was an absolutely awful place. People were starving left and right in all those countries to the South, the hole in the ozone layer was going to kill us all, there was no more oil left, grubby foreigners were going to steal all of our jobs, and the latest Star Wars movie …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On adaptations and dragons
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-on-adaptations-and-dragons/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 09:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pietro Aronica,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-on-adaptations-and-dragons/</guid>
        <description>As you are all undoubtedly aware, the Peter-Jackson-directed Tolkien-related orc-genociding movie trilogy for this decade is The Hobbit, which was for many cause of puzzlement and bewilderment, as the novel it is based upon is much shorter than The Lord of the Rings, and hence does not seem to be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Silvio Berlusconi: Down and Out
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-silvio-berlusconi-down-and-out/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 04:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pietro Aronica,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-silvio-berlusconi-down-and-out/</guid>
        <description>On the 27th of November 2013 at 17:43 Silvio Berlusconi was expelled from the Senate of the Italian Republic; he no longer represents anyone but himself. He cannot abuse his parliamentary seat anymore to avoid his legal troubles. He cannot run for office and may even be tried for his various crimes. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Tale of the Demonstrator
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-5-the-tale-of-the-demonstrator/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 16:44:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pietro Aronica,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-5-the-tale-of-the-demonstrator/</guid>
        <description>The demonstrator, working late at night, still has a stack of papers to correct for the following day. Though the bed beckons to him, he relentlessly keeps going, as students require his slightly-above-minimum wage insights and comments: without his feedback, they would have literally no other way …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In Defence of Memes
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-in-defence-of-memes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 01:49:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pietro Aronica,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-in-defence-of-memes/</guid>
        <description>Memes, meant in the sense of those internet jokes very fond of cats and stylised shouting faces, are often misunderstood.They are seen as part of a nerdy, self-referential culture keen on meta-humour and pushed beyond the limits of common human discourse by its anonymity, and while all of this is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>United States or Europe
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-united-states-or-europe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2013 01:46:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pietro Aronica,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-united-states-or-europe/</guid>
        <description>One of the most baffling things I’ve come across constantly when talking to British people is their use of the word “European” to mean “Beyond The Channel”, as if sharing strong political, historical, geographical, economic and cultural ties weren’t enough to make the UK part of the continent. Rule …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Steam sales pseudo-soliloquy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-steam-sales-pseudo-soliloquy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 00:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pietro Aronica,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-steam-sales-pseudo-soliloquy/</guid>
        <description>If you are a student at Imperial College, then there is a reasonable chance that you play video games, possibly on a PC. If you do, then you’ll most likely be familiar with Steam, but if not, let me sum it up for you: it’s like a vacuum cleaner for money. Specifically, my money, and the money of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>With the University Challenge team coasting into the next round, the team for next year is chosen
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-17-with-the-university-challenge-team-coasting-into-the-next-round-the-team-for-next-year-is-chosen/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 23:51:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pietro Aronica,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-17-with-the-university-challenge-team-coasting-into-the-next-round-the-team-for-next-year-is-chosen/</guid>
        <description>While this season’s University Challenge is still underway, with Imperial College’s team still in the running, the selections have already been made for next year.
The tryouts were organised by Imperial College Quiz Society, mostly composed of keen quizzers and former UC contestants, and was open to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The right to be wrong
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-the-right-to-be-wrong/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 22:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pietro Aronica,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-the-right-to-be-wrong/</guid>
        <description>Have you been wrong today? Have you failed at basic logic at least once since breakfast? Have you propagated a myth or notion that despite its spuriousness has persisted through laziness and avoidance of fact-checking? Have you done your duty as a human being and exercised your right as a citizen? …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Italy’s new Illuminati
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-italys-new-illuminati/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 22:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pietro Aronica,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-italys-new-illuminati/</guid>
        <description>By now, you might’ve heard the news about the Italian scientists that were found guilty of failing to warn the populace of the earthquake that devastated the region of Abruzzo three years ago. The Grandi Rischi (Great Risks) is a commission of experts on calamities whose purpose is to monitor the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Monarchy is outdated
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-7-monarchy-is-outdated/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 19:46:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pietro Aronica,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-7-monarchy-is-outdated/</guid>
        <description>If you’ve been in the country for the past month or so, you undoubtedly will have heard about the Queen’s Jubilee and the great festivities that accompanied it. National holiday, extended weekend, parades and lots of flag-waving to celebrate the monarch’s sixty year reign. One thing that I was taken …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The dark side of democracy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-the-dark-side-of-democracy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 22:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pietro Aronica,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-the-dark-side-of-democracy/</guid>
        <description>The reign of the tyrant is over. In Italy, people celebrated in the streets as Berlusconi resigned; across Europe, markets sighed in relief and hoped that his successor would be able to unscrew the pooch that he so thoroughly enjoyed screwing. The ‘it has to get worse before it can get better’ part …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Embrace your mediocrity
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-11-embrace-your-mediocrity/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2011 17:29:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pietro Aronica,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-11-embrace-your-mediocrity/</guid>
        <description>Greatness is overrated. Being awesome, epic, or whichever other adjective you want to use to describe superiority, is not worth it. It’s too much effort, spurred by exaggerated accounts of others who will fail to recognize your achievements. We’ve spent our entire lives being indoctrinated to aim …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
