<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ma1307/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ma1307/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Research Ethics at the Bottom of the Ice Bucket
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-research-ethics-at-the-bottom-of-the-ice-bucket/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 18:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-research-ethics-at-the-bottom-of-the-ice-bucket/</guid>
        <description>Remember those summer weeks when your entire Facebook feed was filled with people pouring cold water over themselves and making some form of disgruntled exclamations about the fact? Everyone from Victoria Beckham to my own mother took part in the ALS Ice Bucket Challenge, and good on them too.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Some postgraduates critical of h-bar
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-some-postgraduates-critical-of-h-bar/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 03:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-some-postgraduates-critical-of-h-bar/</guid>
        <description>The new-look postgraduate bar is set to open this Friday, with pictures released by the Union and College previewing what it will look like and explaining the services provided by the new space. With its combination of wood tables and green leather upholstery, the new look bar was described by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New postgraduate ħ opens
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-new-postgraduate-opens/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 03:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-new-postgraduate-opens/</guid>
        <description>A new postgraduate student and staff drinking and social venue on the South Kensington campus is set to open this Friday. In keeping with the Union’s trend of naming its drinking establishments with incredibly nerdy puns, the new space will be called ħ (pronounced h-bar), named after the reduced …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Herman Hesse’s Siddhartha
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-4-30-herman-hesses-siddhartha/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 14:59:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-4-30-herman-hesses-siddhartha/</guid>
        <description>Coming in at 114 pages long, Siddhartha is by far the easiest book to read by a Nobel Prize winning author. The guy I borrowed my copy off managed to read the whole thing in a particularly slow flight back from Jordan. I had only vaguely heard of either the book or the author before having the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A new kid on the block
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-a-new-kid-on-the-block/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2013 01:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-a-new-kid-on-the-block/</guid>
        <description>This week The Tab Imperial launched, a new online news source that focuses on news and life of being student at Imperial and around London.
The Tab will be updating hopefully daily, and we are aiming to be your one stop shop for news and views online after you’ve finished ranting on sexism comment …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Masterpiece of the Mundane
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-masterpiece-of-the-mundane/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 20:30:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-masterpiece-of-the-mundane/</guid>
        <description>Much has been said derisively of the German sense of humour, but my favourite book review of all time, translated for me by a friend, was of Jonathan Franzen’s 2010 work and appeared in a the German newspaper Süddeutsche Zeitung. The closing passage of it read, simply: “It’d probably be unbearably …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Sex Survey 2012
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-felix-sex-survey-2012/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 22:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Allinson,Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-felix-sex-survey-2012/</guid>
        <description>The number of respondents we had to the sex survey this year has been almost overwhelming. 1063 of you replied, and only about 20 of them as far as we could tell were blatant trolls (thank you guys btw for making us laugh).
Over the course of these next seven pages, we’ll delve into the details of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Big Brother is watching you
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-big-brother-is-watching-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 21:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-big-brother-is-watching-you/</guid>
        <description>Last term I went to Paris to meet up with a friend who is doing a year abroad. Being a man of modest means I took the overnight coach, arriving at the coach station at 5am. My friend was arriving by the first train from Clermont Ferrand at about 8am, which meant I got to spend two and a half hours …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Staff and students rally around Holland Club Campaign
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-staff-and-students-rally-around-holland-club-campaign/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 21:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-staff-and-students-rally-around-holland-club-campaign/</guid>
        <description>The future of Imperial College’s staff bar, the Holland Club, is in serious doubt this week as it emerged that college catering are potentially planning on converting the space into a new food outlet.
The news sparked widespread controversy online amongst both Imperial’s staff and postgraduate …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Fairytale Shredding
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-a-fairytale-shredding/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 20:26:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-a-fairytale-shredding/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College’s very own Musical Theatre Society consistently puts on hilarity filled shows that mix wild humour, a flair for the outrageous and an almost tangible passion for performance. The first term revue of late has progressively developed into something more elaborate. While still based …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The History of Legalisation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-the-history-of-legalisation/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 22:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-the-history-of-legalisation/</guid>
        <description>Originally made illegal in this country in 1928 as part of a international drive to rid the world of opium and other such nasties, the legal status of weed in the Britain depends on where it is classified under the 1971 Misuse of Drugs Act. Up until the early part of the last decade, that was Class …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Man’s Shoe Haven
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-a-mans-shoe-haven/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 10:24:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-a-mans-shoe-haven/</guid>
        <description>I rather like shoes, which is a problem because buying shoes is usually the low point of any shopping trip, especially for men. I guess we buy fewer shoes and don’t spend as much money on them, and thus as inferior customers get massively inferior treatment in shoe shops.
Your average ‘Office’ will …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The End of a Media Empire
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-8-5-the-end-of-a-media-empire/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 13:29:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gilead Amit,Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-8-5-the-end-of-a-media-empire/</guid>
        <description>Events of the past few weeks have shone a new light on how our media has been operated as a monopoly, with one arguably great but unquestionably evil man at its apex. With the disintegration of his empire, the question now facing all of us is how can the media change its ways of operating and still …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Quantum Uncertainty, Does God play dice?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-quantum-uncertainty-does-god-play-dice/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 20:01:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-quantum-uncertainty-does-god-play-dice/</guid>
        <description>The most recent Friends of Imperial event was a lecture by theoretical physicist Antony Valentini given to a packed SAF lecture theatre. The topic, Quantum Uncertainty, was a popular one: the fact that the half the audience had iPads and the other half had walking sticks —and one rather cool …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Glee: It’s time to start believing
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-glee-its-time-to-start-believing/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 20:08:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-glee-its-time-to-start-believing/</guid>
        <description>Although difficult to explain in purely logical terms, especially when one takes into account the stratospheric amount of money produced by this show, its world tour, album sales and branded lunchbox tie-ins, I think that Glee is underrated. Undoubtedly if you haven’t already stopped reading this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chaotic Cards &amp; Dynamic Dice
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-11-chaotic-cards-dynamic-dice/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 09:18:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-11-chaotic-cards-dynamic-dice/</guid>
        <description>The audience, of what was effectively a maths lecture, was a mixed crowd. Organised by Friends of Imperial – an organisation that encourages alumni and the public to get involved in the work of the College – the lecture drew people from a range of ages and walks of life, but all with an interest in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Does watching TV ruin your life?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-does-watching-tv-ruin-your-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 20:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-does-watching-tv-ruin-your-life/</guid>
        <description>Charles Betts
I find going out on a Saturday night in London an odd thing. I’ve usually had a rough week, I’m tired, fed-up with humanity, feeling miserable and in a pretty foul mood. I feel the onset of a cold thanks to a vitamin D deficiency that the city’s winter brings. I would quite like to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New HBO channel on Sky
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-new-hbo-channel-on-sky/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 20:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucia Podhorska,Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-new-hbo-channel-on-sky/</guid>
        <description>The Wire
When a series is chosen by Barack Obama as his favourite TV show, you know it’s going to be cool. Stand up comedian David O’Doherty made the joke that he knows people who love The Wire so much they can’t even describe it in words. “So what do you think of The Wire?” He asks, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Holy Fuck... What? That’s their name!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-holy-fuck-what-thats-their-name/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 20:26:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-holy-fuck-what-thats-their-name/</guid>
        <description>Holy Fuck are a chaotic band. Every song they play seemingly warrants an additional instrument, and every new musical nuance is brought about by haggard old equipment on the verge of falling apart. One moment in the set sees a band member amplifying film being wrenched off a reel to add to the epic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Drums play the Forum
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-the-drums-play-the-forum/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 20:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-the-drums-play-the-forum/</guid>
        <description>The Drums took to the stage in a euphoric daze to the sound of electronic ambience that echoed the electro-pop roots of founder members Jonathan Pierce (vocals) and Jacob Graham (guitar). The four–piece were complete with Tom Haslow on guitar and Connor Hanwick providing the drums.
First up was Best …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Books for intellectual City type sellouts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-books-for-intellectual-city-type-sellouts/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 19:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-books-for-intellectual-city-type-sellouts/</guid>
        <description>The only function of economic forecasting is to make astrology look respectable” said Ezra Solomon. For more funny lines from ivory tower economists, the fantastic ‘Freakonomics’ and ‘Superfreakonomics’ books by Steven Levitt and Stephen Dubner (both £5.30 from Amazon, £7,99 for kindle) show the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A way to reverse ageing? Yes please!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-a-way-to-reverse-ageing-yes-please/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 21:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-a-way-to-reverse-ageing-yes-please/</guid>
        <description>Ah yes, Nature: everyone’s favourite science journal. We slag it off as populist bullshit but secretly dream of the day our paper will be published in its glossy, simplistic covers. What garbage have they thrown at us this week? Oh hurrah, we’re going to be able to reverse the aging process. And no …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Comedy from the team who made milk funny
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-comedy-from-the-team-who-made-milk-funny/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 20:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-comedy-from-the-team-who-made-milk-funny/</guid>
        <description>Having just watched A Town Called Panic, I am employing every ounce of self-control and the limited reserve of dignity in my body and mind to prevent myself from writing this review in full caps-lock. Words alone cannot describe how much I enjoyed this film. Guttural noises would hardly do it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICU Cinema&#39;s Glory
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-icu-cinemas-glory/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-icu-cinemas-glory/</guid>
        <description>As reported in the last issue of Felix, ICU Cinema re-launched this week with a showing of Inception. The event was a runaway success, completely selling out within 10 minutes. A combination of brilliant choice of film, perfect timing at the quiet end of the beginning of term and incredibly friendly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix’s DVD Guide to October 31st</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-felixs-dvd-guide-to-october-31st/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 19:44:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Oliver Calderbank,Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-felixs-dvd-guide-to-october-31st/</guid>
        <description>Halloween parties are like sex: either a dark, lusty and twisted extravaganza enhanced by elaborate costumes; or an over-hyped and disappointing charade we do once a year because we feel socially compelled to. Helping you make yours the former, here is our guide of some new and re-released Horror …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Between a rock and a hard place – the battle for the Chilean Miner story rights
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-between-a-rock-and-a-hard-place-the-battle-for-the-chilean-miner-story-rights/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 19:16:47 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-between-a-rock-and-a-hard-place-the-battle-for-the-chilean-miner-story-rights/</guid>
        <description>The live feed of the Chilean miners’ rescue on the 13th October 2010 had it all: drama, suspense, and plenty of filler from the reporters on scene who were trying to occupy the long pauses between anything actually happening in San José de Copiapó. In this, a frequent theme was what would happen to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Critically acclaimed films that are actually terrible
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-1-critically-acclaimed-films-that-are-actually-terrible/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 22:56:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-1-critically-acclaimed-films-that-are-actually-terrible/</guid>
        <description>We all know the importance of conversation while making friends in your first week, especially the pit-falls of trying to not to sound lame. However, in spite of your best efforts to be cool, some pretentious knobber will always have something smart to say in response to your movie opinions, usually …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
