<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>We&#39;ve moved to a new location: felixonlinesummer.uk</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2020-04-05-new-website/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2020-04-05-new-website/</guid>
        <description>Head to felixonlinesummer.uk for our Summer 2020 coverage!
</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>After the Collapse of Man Comes… Jellyfish?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-after-collapse-man-jellyfish/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Amanda Hertzberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-after-collapse-man-jellyfish/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
How art interacts with and depicts the changing climate is pivotal to how we think about climate change. This is the underlying idea of Eco-visionaries running right now at the Royal Academy of Arts. Very much a multimedia exhibition, it features works from DeepMind, AntFarm and Olafur …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cyrano de Bergerac: Love Letters to Language</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-cyrano-bergerac-love-letters-language/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-cyrano-bergerac-love-letters-language/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
I had no idea of what kind of show to expect, Swayed to attend by media buzz and the prospect Of seeing James McAvoy - live on stage! A welcome break from his golden age Of threequels and reboots, Green screens and CGI substitutes, Blockbuster, record-buster, So-called cinematic filibuster. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Midsummer in Midwinter</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-midsummer-in-winter/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-midsummer-in-winter/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
For those unfamiliar with the plot, A Midsummer Night’s Dream is a classic Shakespearean comedy. In this adaptation by the National Youth Theatre (NYT), several changes to the plot and setting have been made. The most obvious setting change was that instead of the traditional Athens of, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Christmas Carol</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-a-christmas-carol/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laura Casas,Aya Hayakawa,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-a-christmas-carol/</guid>
        <description>3 stars
This ‘musical play’ is an original adaptation of a well-known and loved novella, thanks to the fresh use of music and direction. The use of carol-singing and handbell performances to break up the well-known narrative play a role in creating a Christmassy and joyful environment on stage, but …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why do we Pick and Choose when to Support People?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-20-why-pick-choose-support-people/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Damilola Toriola,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-20-why-pick-choose-support-people/</guid>
        <description>Recently there has been a lot of turmoil amongst social media users based on artists cancelling their concerts or wanting to abandon music all together because it damages their mental health. These artists have been receiving so much backlash simply because they want to put themselves first. Why do …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wolf of Wall Street - An Attempt at High-octane Fun Burns out Quickly</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-wolf-wall-street/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-wolf-wall-street/</guid>
        <description>2 stars
The Wolf of Wall Street is the latest immersive offering from director Alexander Wright, based on the 2013 film about unscrupulous stockbroker Jordan Belfort. The premise is that we - the audience - are all new employees at Belfort&amp;rsquo;s cash-swindling firm Stratton Oakmont. Right from the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2019 in Review: The Best Films I’ve Seen this Year</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-2019-in-review-best-films-this-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Zuzanna Janusz,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-2019-in-review-best-films-this-year/</guid>
        <description>It was not a difficult task to name my favourite films I watched this year – the ones listed below were truly memorable and entertaining. So here is my selection, a bit eclectic I would say, and since there is no way to rank these gems, I present them in alphabetical order – enjoy.
BROKEN FLOWERS …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>7 Must-See Destinations for Under £70</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-seven-must-see-destinations-under-70/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-seven-must-see-destinations-under-70/</guid>
        <description>Above: Copenhagen, Denmark
Student life is hard enough as it is, but travelling on a tight budget is a whole other struggle. Finding the perfect getaway only for your bank balance to shatter all your dreams is top two most heart-breaking feelings, and hint – it’s not number two. That’s why for our …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>70 Years of STEM Nobel Prizes &amp; Fields Medals</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-70-years-STEM-nobel-prizes-fields-medals/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Julia Dabrowska,Christine Parry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-70-years-STEM-nobel-prizes-fields-medals/</guid>
        <description>Below are 70 years worth of noteworthy awards in maths and science - but first, in recognition of our affiliated Imperial scientists, here’s a summary of our awardees &amp;amp; what they achieved:
1956: Cyril Norman Hinshelwood; Chemistry; for his research into the mechanism of chemical reactions
1958: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Brief History of Jazz </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-brief-history-jazz/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-brief-history-jazz/</guid>
        <description>By the time this newspaper came into existence, jazz was already old – or at least middle aged. Louis Armstrong had defined improvisation, swing had already been and gone, replaced by frantic bebop, cool jazz and eventually fusion. Genres like rock and soul had begun to rear their heads, offshoots …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Decade of UK Politics</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-decade-of-uk-politics/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-decade-of-uk-politics/</guid>
        <description>As the clock ticked midnight on 1st January 2010, the nation celebrated the completion of an entire decade into the new millennium. At the time, 10 Downing Street was occupied by Gordon Brown, the Prime Minister who took the country through the global financial crash of 2008. Brown had been part of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Amelie: A Warm Hug in this Cruel World</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-amelie-warm-hug-in-cruel-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-amelie-warm-hug-in-cruel-world/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
Adapted from the five-time Oscar nominated French language movie of the same name, Amelie tells the story of a girl with a wild imagination who takes pleasure in performing “small, but extraordinary acts of kindness” with the goal of bringing joy to those around her. What must she do to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Amnioverse: A Perfect Album Listening Experience</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-amnioverse-a-perfect-album-listening-experience/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-amnioverse-a-perfect-album-listening-experience/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
I don’t think I’d be offending anyone by saying that most listeners of electronic music focus more on singles than albums. When you listen to Hybrid Minds or Bicep you normally wouldn’t play the whole album start to finish. However, there are electronic albums that actively work against …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are we Headed for a New DotCom Bubble?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-are-we-headed-for-new-dotcom-bubble/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marios Papadopoulos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-are-we-headed-for-new-dotcom-bubble/</guid>
        <description>Above: Fig 1. Looking at around the year 1999, the NASDAQ leaped from below 3000 to the peak of 5048.62. It has taken 15 years for the NASDAQ to recover to that high. Will history repeat itself?
The entry of the new millennium was accompanied by a major stock market crash caused by a bubble known as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best of the Decade: Editor’s Choice (Jia Qi Tan)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-best-of-the-decade-editors-choice-jia/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-best-of-the-decade-editors-choice-jia/</guid>
        <description>Choosing and ranking the best TV shows of the decade might have been the most daunting task especially in the era of “Peak TV” where every provider churns out quality pieces at an unprecedented rate. But I’ve managed to narrow the list down to ten. I’m sure I have missed many gems, and this list is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best of the Decade: Editor’s Choice (Ozbil Ege Dumenci)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-best-of-decade-editors-choice-ozbil/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-best-of-decade-editors-choice-ozbil/</guid>
        <description>Let me start this by saying this is by no means an exhaustive list. I’m sure there’s shows that I haven’t got around to seeing yet that are just as great or even better than the stuff on this list. So, before you get all angry at me for not including Breaking Bad or Westworld on the list, it’s only …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Binge of the Week: The Crown (Season 3)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-binge-of-week-the-crown-season-3/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-binge-of-week-the-crown-season-3/</guid>
        <description>Season 3: 4.5 stars
Upon the initial release of the first season back in 2016, it was made very clear that the audience should not get too attached to the cast, as they would only be playing the Royal Family for the first two seasons. However, Claire Foy, Matt Smith and Vanessa Kirby, who played …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Editors’ Top Picks of the Decade</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-editors-top-picks-of-decade/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-editors-top-picks-of-decade/</guid>
        <description>When Breath Becomes Air by Paul Kalanithi
Image Above
Poetic, poignant, and profound, Paul Kalanithi’s memoir as a neurosurgeon diagnosed with Stage IV metastatic lung cancer is unbelievably powerful in Kalanithi’s quest to answer the difficult question of what makes a life worth living. It’s a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ethical Investment Paper Passed by College Council</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-ethical-investment-paper-passed-college-council/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-ethical-investment-paper-passed-college-council/</guid>
        <description>The paper, written by the Union President, Deputy President (Finance and Services), and Ethics and Environment Officer, was originally submitted on the 22nd of November and was passed with minor amendments from the President’s Board.
It establishes a ‘working group’ that is mandated to investigate …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FKA Twigs - Live</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-FKA-twigs-live/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-FKA-twigs-live/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
FKA twigs’ gig didn’t start until 9:30, by which point a large portion of the audience frustrated, having waited for over 2 hours. The curtains raised bit by bit, riling the crowd further. “This show had better be good” muttered someone behind me, thankfully, it was.
Twigs’ vocals were …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix 2019 General Election Poll: Results</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-felix-general-election-poll-results-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-felix-general-election-poll-results-2019/</guid>
        <description></description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Interviews: Anne Barrett, College Archivist</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-felix-interviews-anne-barrett-college-archivist/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-felix-interviews-anne-barrett-college-archivist/</guid>
        <description>Felix: Most students probably aren’t really aware that the college has archives – do you interact with students a lot?
Some of them are – particularly the constituent college unions – and I do host evenings with different groups. When I had the City and Guilds Union members in, they were looking at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Festive Favourites</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-festive-favourites/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charlotte Arrand,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-festive-favourites/</guid>
        <description>Since it is the season, I thought I would make a list of my go-to Christmas films for the December period. They aren’t going to be ground breaking - I’m sure you will have watched them before - nor will they be films I consider impressive, however they give me that warm festive feeling and get me …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Halo Reach on PC: A Perfect Port, but a Flawed Game</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-halo-reach-pc-perfect-port-flawed-game/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-halo-reach-pc-perfect-port-flawed-game/</guid>
        <description>Let me make one thing clear: I am absolutely biased. Halo Reach was a significant part of my teenagedom; I spent a frankly unhealthy amount of hours sprinting around the wide landscapes and vast alien structures of the original game. It defined my social life – I’d host huge all-night LAN parties …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hip Hop: The Genre Of The Decade</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-hiphop-genre-of-decade/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-hiphop-genre-of-decade/</guid>
        <description>Undeniably, hip hop dominated this decade, having established itself as one of the most diverse yet hereditary forced in modern culutre. I asked Hip Hop Soc members to pick their top 20 albums of the decade. This pretty banging consensus list is the result:
20. Barter 6 - Young Thug (2015)
19. 4:44 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Computers Took our Music Away</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-how-computers-took-our-music-away/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-how-computers-took-our-music-away/</guid>
        <description>Putting the history of a whole genre of music to paper is a mammoth task, especially for a genre as fluid and diverse as electronic music, so please forgive any oversight I may have made in trying to accomplish it. It is a story of technical innovation, experimentation, and of people coming …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hunger - The Battle Between the Self and the City</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-hunger-battle-between-self-and-city/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Byron Gamble,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-hunger-battle-between-self-and-city/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
Simply titled “Hunger”, director Fay Lomas delves into the psychological turmoil as this primal instinct comes face-to-face with ambition. What sacrifices are we willing to make for our dreams? Although the production is based on the 1890 novel written by modernist Knut Hamsun, it displays …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICBC Reflect on Mental Health and Spreading Awareness in the Rowing Community</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-icbc-reflect-mental-health-spreading-awareness-rowing-community/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-icbc-reflect-mental-health-spreading-awareness-rowing-community/</guid>
        <description>Mental health in sport is very often overlooked. Athletes are often perceived to be thick-skinned, resilient, and independent; looks can be deceiving. The thoughts, feelings, and emotions that navigate in that space between their ears are no different from that of any other person.
We are equally …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICHC Ladies 2s Reach the Top of their League</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-ichc-ladies-2s-reach-top-of-league/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chloe Jeremy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-ichc-ladies-2s-reach-top-of-league/</guid>
        <description>It has been a term of change for the ICHC L2s. The previous few seasons saw a lot of defeat, with moments of greatness and unbeatable team spirit, but just not many actual goals. Something had to change, and so October brought the hotly debated creation of the L3s, led by the blindingly optimistic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICHC: An Ode to Monday Night Training</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-ichc-ode-monday-night-training/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chloe Jeremy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-ichc-ode-monday-night-training/</guid>
        <description>It is 4:40 pm and I haven’t got as much work done as I’d hoped today. Why? A Marble Olympics YouTube hole, mental and emotional fatigue… TikTok? It doesn’t really matter. I log out of my hard-earned library computer and begin to pack up. Another student has noticed me stir and now hovers near my …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College Men’s Rugby take on Movember and Mental Health</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-imperial-college-mens-rugby-take-movember-mental-health/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Draper-Barr,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-imperial-college-mens-rugby-take-movember-mental-health/</guid>
        <description>This November, you may have been wondering why a male housemate had grown a moustache that looked more like a cappuccino stain than facial hair or why those loud blokes in ties in the union bar on a Wednesday were somehow looking more handsome than usual. It was because across Imperial and the UK, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Octopush battle it out in Oxford</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-imperial-octopush-battle-out-oxford/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Slater,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-imperial-octopush-battle-out-oxford/</guid>
        <description>On Saturday 30th November, the Octopush team (also known as Underwater Hockey or UWH) played their first competition of the year at the University of Oxford.
For the few people reading this who don’t already know, Octopush is a game created in 1954 by scuba divers to help them let off some steam …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In the Wake of Tragedy</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-wake-of-tragedy-icbc-members-alumni-sail-ocean-raise-mental-health-awareness/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bazil Saiq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-wake-of-tragedy-icbc-members-alumni-sail-ocean-raise-mental-health-awareness/</guid>
        <description>This article continues from a predecessor, &amp;ldquo;ICBC reflect on mental health and spreading awareness in the rowing community&amp;rdquo;.
A separate campaign, Race4René, in memory of René, was set up in 2018 with some of René’s closest friends and family, aiming to sail across the Atlantic with the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is It Art if Everybody Hates It?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-art-everyone-hates-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laura Casas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-art-everyone-hates-it/</guid>
        <description>Van Gogh, while alive (1853-1890), only sold one painting. Though we all agree that The Starry Night (1889) and Sunflowers (1888) are artworks, people of the time detested or at least ignored these canvases. Thus, was it not art then and it is now? Was it always art?
In contrast, other masterpieces …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It is Not Corbyn that we Should be Blaming but Labour Centrists</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-not-corbyn-blame-labour-centrists/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-not-corbyn-blame-labour-centrists/</guid>
        <description>The Red Wall
The so-called ‘Red Wall’ includes many of the old Labour strongholds like Great Gimsby, Workington, that is famously being challenged by the Tories, and Don Valley. Many of these seats have non-local MPs who have been given a safe seat as a reward. Don Valley in Yorkshire, for example, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Knives Out (2019)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-knives-out/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dominic Ede,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-knives-out/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
It’s not often that a film starts getting almost unanimous praise from critics, so when this murder mystery from Rian Johnson started to garner attention from almost every direction, it left me wondering: what makes this film so good?
It centres around the family of Harlan Thrombey, a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Liberation and Community at Imperial is an Issue for Today</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-liberation-community-imperial-issue-today/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shervin Sabeghi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-liberation-community-imperial-issue-today/</guid>
        <description>Above: Only men were allowed to drink in the Union Bar fifty years ago
The rights and freedoms for minority groups around the world are never handed on a platter – they are hard fought through liberation movements. From international women’s suffrage in the late 19th century, the American Civil …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mind the Gap: Movies to Look Out for this Break</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-mind-gap-movies-look-out-for-break/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jasmin Daley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-mind-gap-movies-look-out-for-break/</guid>
        <description>It’s cold, you’re bored, and your friends from home are looking for something to do. Look no further than our list of new releases to keep you entertained while we’re away.
BLACK CHRISTMAS: 12th December
A loose remake of the 1974 fan favourite Christmas movie. As the nights grow colder and darker, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Most Important Films of the Decade</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-most-important-films-of-decade/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charlotte Arrand,Zuzanna Janusz,Dominic Ede,Jasmin Daley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-most-important-films-of-decade/</guid>
        <description>Now that this decade is coming to a close, for the last paper of the year we thought we’d do a roundup of what we think are the most important films of the 2010’s, featuring one from each film writer. These films don’t necessarily line up with the ones we have loved the most, however, they are what …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pop Hits Take the West End: &amp; Juliet</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-pop-hits-take-west-end-juliet/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-pop-hits-take-west-end-juliet/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
Romeo and Juliet, is probably one of history’s most famous love stories which (spoiler alert) tragically ends in death. This modern retelling considers what could have happened if Juliet (Miriam-Teak Lee) was given a life beyond Romeo. She travels to Paris with an entourage consisting of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rock Throughout the Ages</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-rock-throughout-ages/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Freeman,Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-rock-throughout-ages/</guid>
        <description>The roots of rock as a genre are buried deep in the other sounds of the 50s: blues, jazz, R&amp;amp;B and country, amalgamated together to form its own unique genre, known as rock and roll. This began in the deep south of the states, where the first electric guitars began to make a heavy impact on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Seven Decades of Discovery</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-seven-decades-of-discovery/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Julia Dabrowska,Christine Parry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-seven-decades-of-discovery/</guid>
        <description>1949
Felix is launched, spawned from the University’s arts and culture magazine, Phoenix, after a need for news amongst the student community.
1950s
After WWII, the scientific community realised the full potential of its possibility and power, and feels an increased need to understand the social …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sir Geoffrey Wilkinson: Imperial’s Honoured Chemist and Recipient of the 1973 Nobel Prize in Chemistry</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-sir-geoffrey-wilkinson-imperials-honoured-chemist-recipient-1973-nobel-chemistry/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Arianne New,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-sir-geoffrey-wilkinson-imperials-honoured-chemist-recipient-1973-nobel-chemistry/</guid>
        <description>Any student who has been to the Chemistry Café would have seen the portrait of Sir Geoffrey Wilkinson at least once. Lying at the back of the café, with more pictures dotted throughout the building, and even his research paper framed right outside, he surely must be of importance. While most of us …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Space: The Final Frontier</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-space-final-frontier/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-space-final-frontier/</guid>
        <description>The College has, in recent years, struggled with the amount of space available on the South Kensington campus, and is separately making decisions like the sale of St. Mary’s and the construction of White City – but projects are still ongoing to optimise the space available. One such project is the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sports Editor’s Experience of the Relationship Between Sport and Mental Health</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-sports-editors-experience-of-relationship-sport-mental-health/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imraj Singh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-sports-editors-experience-of-relationship-sport-mental-health/</guid>
        <description>For Felix’s 70th Anniversary we’ve asked sports clubs for content on mental health in sport. I am happy to see that Imperial athletes, alongside their sport AND studies, run a range of campaigns spreading mental health awareness. Additionally, some teams have taken steps to promote welfare by having …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sun, Sex and Suspicous Parents: 1920s Edition</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-sun-sex-suspicious-parents-1920s-edition/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-sun-sex-suspicious-parents-1920s-edition/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
In a few weeks’ time we will be in a new decade, the 2020s. If it’s anything like the 1920s, it should be a blast! The Boy Friend gives a little glimpse into what life back then was like.. for young, pretty socialites at a finishing school on the French Riviera that is!
If you fit this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Surrealist Superstars</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-surrealist-superstars/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-surrealist-superstars/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
Brussels’s Place Royale is a mecca of art, like a small, art-oriented brother to the museums surrounding our beautiful campus. The Royal Museums that flank it comprise some of the finest works of the European canon, from the Flemish masters to the modern genius of Magritte. The latter’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tech Headlines: 9th December 2019</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-tech-headlines-9th-december-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sudarshan Sreeram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-tech-headlines-9th-december-2019/</guid>
        <description>Qualcomm XR2 - 5G Ready AR Glasses
At a special event in Maui, Hawaii, Qualcomm announced its new AR platform - XR2 5G, which succeeds the company’s older XR1 platform that still powers a number of VR and AR experiences. According to Qualcomm, the XR2 is the world’s first 5G-supported extended …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tepid Reviews for Dear Evan Hansen?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-tepid-reviews-dear-evan-hansen/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-tepid-reviews-dear-evan-hansen/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
It was rather surprising to me that the majority of the professional reviews for Dear Evan Hansen, the Broadway juggernaut that just made its way to the West End stage, have been rather tepid. Unlike its Broadway counterpart, which was showered with endless praise and a plethora of five …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Arrival: Two Brothers Reunited</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-the-arrival-two-brothers-reunited/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-the-arrival-two-brothers-reunited/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
Samad (Irfan Shamji) and Tom (Scott Karim) have lived very different lives. Different upbringings, different parents, different friends, different schools. Social, geographic and cultural barriers have divided them for over thirty years. But they have one thing in common, they are brothers, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Do’s and Don’t of a Student Christmas Dinner: How to Keep the Festive Mood on a Student Budget</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-dos-donts-christmas-dinner-keep-festive-mood-student-budget/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,Zahra Abiola,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-dos-donts-christmas-dinner-keep-festive-mood-student-budget/</guid>
        <description>THE BIRD
A whole roast turkey is the usual fare for a Christmas dinner but unless you are ready to buy way ahead, have an inordinate amount of oven space, and you don’t mind the lengthy brining and cooking process, I would steer clear. A poorly cooked turkey is way worse than no turkey at all. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The End of a Decade: Italy</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-end-of-decade-italy/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Luca Rameli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-end-of-decade-italy/</guid>
        <description>The past decade has witnessed a proper political earthquake in Italian politics: what once was is no more. The political framework that has been in place since the nineties has fallen – the abrupt political changes that have occurred are similar to the previous largescale reshaping of the political …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The End of a Decade: Spain</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-end-of-decade-spain/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-end-of-decade-spain/</guid>
        <description>The last decade has been a period of historical changes in Spain that have transformed its political culture and society forever. This historical phase is parallel to the European economic crisis and its aftermath, which were particularly intense in Southern European countries like Spain. Arguably, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Game Awards: Nominees, Discussion and Editor’s Top Picks of the Year. Time to get Hyped!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-game-awards-nominees-discussion-editors-top-picks-of-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freddie Ugo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-game-awards-nominees-discussion-editors-top-picks-of-year/</guid>
        <description>Shitty weather, extreme fatigue and incessantly annoying Christmas music. There are many signs that the end of the year is upon us, but one that is much cheerier – and a great topic of discussion – is The Game Awards. Effectively the Oscars of video games, The Game Awards celebrates the best games …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Greatest Play in the History of the World</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-greatest-play-in-history-of-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Deniz Ak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-greatest-play-in-history-of-world/</guid>
        <description>3 stars
A man wakes in the middle of the night to discover that the world has stopped. It was exactly 04:40. The title, intriguing and vague, leaves you wondering what the greatest play in the history of the world could possibly be.
The Greatest Play in the History of the World written by Ian …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Illusion of Accessible Theatre: How Far Have we Come and How Far do we Have Left to Go?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-illusion-accessible-theatre/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-illusion-accessible-theatre/</guid>
        <description>Ever since my stint as a Felix arts editor began, I’ve been preaching the importance of making theatre more accessible. For the most part, the baby-boomer leaning demographics at the theatre astonish me. I strongly believe this medium of arts can be a formative part of a young person’s development. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Marvelous Mrs. Maisel (Seasons 1 and 2)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-the-marvelous-mrs-maisel-seasons-1-and-2/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-the-marvelous-mrs-maisel-seasons-1-and-2/</guid>
        <description>Season 1: 5 stars
Season 2: 5 stars
Amazon Prime Video’s The Marvelous Mrs. Maisel is a period comedy-drama set in 1958 Manhattan, New York. It follows the self-discovery journey of Mrs. Miriam “Midge” Maisel, a housewife-turned-stand-up-comedian. It’s created by Amy Sherman-Palladino who is best …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Most Influential Games of the Decade: Felix Games Breaks it Down</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-most-influentiual-games-decade-felix-games-breaks-it-down/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freddie Ugo,Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-most-influentiual-games-decade-felix-games-breaks-it-down/</guid>
        <description>Redefining Open World Adventures: The Legend of Zelda Breath of the Wild
Despite being one of a long list of amazing Zelda games, Breath of the Wild is set apart by its unique method of story-telling and its risky gameplay choices that definitely payed off. Breath of the Wild is unlike other Zelda …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Ongoing Direction of the Union</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-ongoing-direction-of-union/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-ongoing-direction-of-union/</guid>
        <description>It has been confirmed that Jon Tucker, the Business School’s Faculty Operating Officer, will be providing interim support to the Union following the departure of the Managing Director.
The decision was made after a discussion with College by Jill Finney, the Chair of the Union’s Board of Trustees, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Rise and Fall of Jo Swinson’s Liberal Democrats</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-rise-and-fall-of-jo-swinsons-liberal-democrats/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lloyd T James,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-rise-and-fall-of-jo-swinsons-liberal-democrats/</guid>
        <description>Six months ago, British politics seemed poised for upheaval. The Liberal Democrats, standing on an unambiguously pro-remain platform, secured a higher vote share than both Labour and the Conservatives in the EU elections. The overall victory however, had gone to the equally unambiguous Brexit Party. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Third Man (1949): A Look at the Film Turning 70</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-the-third-man-1949-look-at-film-turning-70/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dominic Ede,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-the-third-man-1949-look-at-film-turning-70/</guid>
        <description>Looking back at this aged and distant film allows you to visualise the significant amount of time that has passed since Felix was established in 1949, and also gives some relevant perspective in the advances cinema has made. Written by Graham Greene, the film centres around Holly Martins (Joseph …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Wind of Heaven: From Bethlehem to Blestin</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-wind-of-heaven-bethlehem-to-blestin/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Swift Roberts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-wind-of-heaven-bethlehem-to-blestin/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
The greatest objection to God has always been emotional. While it is true that the debate over divine non-presence is clothed in the mild-breathed language of logicism and rationality, what stirs in us feeling enough to slacken faith and scorn perdition is the atrociousness of evil and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tragedy of the Commons: A Drama That Our Planet Is Not Enjoying</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-tragedy-commons-drama-planet-not-enjoying/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xiuchen Xu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-tragedy-commons-drama-planet-not-enjoying/</guid>
        <description>You may have heard of the term tragedy of the commons before, or you may have even studied about it. It is an important economic concept and is extremely relevant to many of the prevailing environmental issues. The problem stems from deep within human nature and is at the heart of corruption and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Troy: Myth and Reality</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-troy-myth-reality/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-troy-myth-reality/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
Legend has it that the goddess of discord threw a golden apple into a crowd, bearing the inscription ‘for the most beautiful’. It was claimed by three goddesses, Athena, Hera and Aphrodite, and Zeus asked The Trojan prince Paris to make the final judgement. He chose Aphrodite, who promised …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union Council Votes 36:1 to Reject Increase in Halls Rent Price</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-union-council-votes-reject-increase-halls-rent/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-union-council-votes-reject-increase-halls-rent/</guid>
        <description>The Union and College are currently in negotiations over the price of rent in first-year accommodation, which College is proposing to increase by 12.2% overall in order to match a break-even model as calculated by Campus Services. On Tuesday, December 3rd, the Union President and Deputy President …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>War Horse: A Year Later</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-war-horse-a-year-later/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-war-horse-a-year-later/</guid>
        <description>Last year, I was lucky enough to watch War Horse at the National Theatre, its return to the original National Theatre venue a celebration of the centenary of Armistice Day.I loved it so much the first time that I grabbed a different friend the next evening and ended up queueing for return tickets to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>World AIDS Day</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-world-aids-day/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freya Hepworth-Lloyd,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-world-aids-day/</guid>
        <description>It is estimated that over 100,000 people in the UK are living with HIV. An estimated 7,500 of those are undiagnosed. The life expectancy for people diagnosed early (15-59) is the same as the general population. However nearly half of HIV diagnoses are late.
HIV is transmitted through particular body …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your Union is Standing Firm</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-dramsoc-macbeth-scores-macb/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-dramsoc-macbeth-scores-macb/</guid>
        <description>2 stars
I don’t remember much about Macbeth, having only studied it briefly in my early secondary school days. While I may have forgotten the plot and the characters’ names, I could never forget the feeling of empowerment I experienced after learning of my king-slayer potential wrought from the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your Union is Standing Firm</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-let-me-be-your-star-mtsoc-revue-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-let-me-be-your-star-mtsoc-revue-review/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
Sometimes all it takes to fall in love with a musical is that one special song or moment. MTSoc’s medley of musical classics hopes to scratch that itch with over fifteen musicals represented! With more than 45 performers taking part in the show in small groups, the audience was transported …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your Union is Standing Firm</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-your-union-standing-firm/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-your-union-standing-firm/</guid>
        <description>There’s no doubt that this has been a tricky term for the Union. Our most senior member of staff is stepping down, the kitchens are closed, and student officers, in particular the deputy presidents, have had to work overtime to compensate for understaffing in the office.
Despite this, the Union is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“If you dare to struggle, you dare to win...”</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-dare-to-struggle-dare-to-win/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-dare-to-struggle-dare-to-win/</guid>
        <description>Before dawn on December 4th, 1969, Fred Hampton was murdered in his bed. He was killed in a police raid with the assent of local law enforcement, the state government’s prosecutor’s office, and the FBI. He was 21 years old.
Hampton was a member of the Black Panther Party. Established in 1966, the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Graduate CEO of Spyras Named UK’s Most Promising Entrepreneur </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-imperial-graduate-ceo-spyras-named-uk-most-promising-entrepreneur/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Powell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-imperial-graduate-ceo-spyras-named-uk-most-promising-entrepreneur/</guid>
        <description>J: How did the initial idea for Spyras come to you?
G: The initial aim was to get a good grade in my masters to go on to a job in finance or consulting! The technology had been concepted in the Guder Research group and it just needed someone to take it to the next step and commercialise it. My …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title></title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/issues/felix_1737/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/issues/felix_1737/</guid>
        <description></description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>1/3 analogue, 1/3 digital, 1/3 nature: Dominik Eulberg</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-third-analogue-third-digital-third-nature-dominik-eulberg/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-third-analogue-third-digital-third-nature-dominik-eulberg/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
Dominik Eulberg, the 41-year-old recluse birdwatcher, who happens to also make some of the best German techno, says that he feels drawn to the animalistic aspects of the genre. The sweating, the entranced dancing, the rapture when the crescendo lifts your feet off the ground. He brought all …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Guide to Video Game Collecting in 2019</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-guide-video-game-collecting-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freddie Ugo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-guide-video-game-collecting-2019/</guid>
        <description>As an avid fan of all things gaming, I love to look over at my wall and see stacks of games lining the shelves. From the Atari 2600 to the Nintendo Switch, I love them all; unfortunately, I have a student budget which does not come close to fuelling my need for games. Over the years, though, I have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Augmented Reality and Intelligence Automation</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-augmented-reality-intelligence-automation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sudarshan Sreeram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-augmented-reality-intelligence-automation/</guid>
        <description>Everyone’s heard of artificial intelligence, more commonly known as AI, but have you heard of intelligence augmentation, or IA? No, it’s not an illegal substance that alters your thinking capabilities to make you highly intelligent; though, it does come close!
IA is closely linked with AI, but it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Binge of the Week: Russian Doll</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-binge-of-week-russian-doll/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-binge-of-week-russian-doll/</guid>
        <description>Season 1: 5 stars
Netflix’s dramedy Russian Doll follows Nadia Vulvokov (played by Natasha Lyonne), a software developer who finds herself stuck in a time loop where she repeatedly dies and mysteriously relives her 36th birthday party. Nadia has to fix the “bug” in the code that is her life in order …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>CONSUME! CONSUME! CONSUME! CONSUME! CONSUME! Then Die</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-consume-then-die/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-consume-then-die/</guid>
        <description>It’s the most wonderful time of the year… for the big fat cats to cash in on your appetite for greed and low self-esteem. Christmas is around the corner, and the capitalist gods have sent their finest to wring out every ounce of self-respect we have: Black Friday. Since its beginnings in mid-20th …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Plans to Increase Halls Rent Again; Union to Negotiate Prices</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-college-plans-increase-halls-rent-union-negotiate-prices/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-college-plans-increase-halls-rent-union-negotiate-prices/</guid>
        <description>The price of rent in College-owned halls is set to increase again this year, with the student union acting in a consultation role with students.
The College’s total necessary revenue from halls rent is increasing by 12.2% in just one year in order to match a break-even model, in which revenue …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Digimon Story: Cyber Sleuth</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-digimon-story-cyber-sleuth/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-digimon-story-cyber-sleuth/</guid>
        <description>Now I don’t know about you, but Digimon was the bread and butter of my childhood, with its classic animation style and collection of surprisingly dark moments. I’m still traumatised by their equivalent of Sean Bean, Leomon, who seemingly could not go an episode without falling.
So you can imagine …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Exploitation of Animals in Wildlife Tourism </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-exploitation-animals-wildlife-tourism/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maya Prashad,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-exploitation-animals-wildlife-tourism/</guid>
        <description>Ecotourism has gained traction in recent years, focusing on socially responsible travel to destinations where flora, fauna, and cultural heritage are the main attractions. Wildlife-encounter tourism is not a new phenomenon, but thanks to social media it has steadily gained popularity. Who amongst us …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>General Election 2019: What are the environmental policies and promises of the parties?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-general-election-2019-what-are-environmental-policies-promises-of-parties/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xiuchen Xu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-general-election-2019-what-are-environmental-policies-promises-of-parties/</guid>
        <description>There is a short &amp;lsquo;glossary&amp;rsquo; near the end of the article to explain certain bits of jargon!
The public concern towards environmental issues are at a peak, and this is reflected in the manifestos of political parties, which have a heavier focus on environmental policies than those of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Heartache for Hertfordshire</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-29-11-heartache-hertfordshire/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Toby Daniels,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-29-11-heartache-hertfordshire/</guid>
        <description>With the squeals and whimpers of the Canterbury ‘players’ still fresh on our minds, we headed back to fortress Harlington to kick off our cup run. Today’s victims were familiar faces, they’d received a gentle 26-7 spanking a mere 5 weeks ago, an experience they were clearly unsatisfied with. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hong Kong: Home No More</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-hong-kong-home-no-more/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-hong-kong-home-no-more/</guid>
        <description>Hong Kong. An asphalt jungle lit by neon lights. The brutal trek up the Tiger’s Head and down towards the beaches of Discovery Bay. A mere cog in the global economy machinery. For me it was all that and more. But somehow six thousand miles away from the city I called home, I’ve now come to realise I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How is Brexit Going to Affect My Next Holiday?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-how-brexit-affect-holiday/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-how-brexit-affect-holiday/</guid>
        <description>I know what you’re thinking - another day, another Brexit article. But if you’re anything like us and have the travel bug, then you’re going to want to read this one. With Brexit being delayed once again to January at the soonest, there’s no better time to grab a bargain and finally book flights to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hyde Park Winter Wonderland Comedy Club</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-hyde-park-winter-wonderland-comedy-club/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Manfredi Castelli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-hyde-park-winter-wonderland-comedy-club/</guid>
        <description>2 stars
Between November and December of every year, Winter Wonderland opens its doors to Londoners and tourists alike as one of the most visited attractions. It has the perfect atmosphere for just going around the Christmas markets and enjoying the rides (of course while drinking mulled wine) but …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICXCAC Success at the Brighton 10k</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-ICXCAC-success-at-Brighton-10k/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Minty Hampden-Martin,Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-ICXCAC-success-at-Brighton-10k/</guid>
        <description>On Sunday 17th November, a rowdy group of 56 of Imperial’s finest specimens woke up in the wee hours to catch their 6:36 train from London Bridge. While most would cringe at the idea of such an early wakke-up on their rest day, the ICXCAC runners all rose to the challenge and (nearly all) made it on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Triathlon triumph at BUCS Duathlon</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-imperial-triathlon-triumph-bucs-duathlon/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>David Ho,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-imperial-triathlon-triumph-bucs-duathlon/</guid>
        <description>Sunday 24th November was one of those days where the world seemed to be set against the Imperial College triathlon team as they prepared for their first British Universities championships: in duathlon, a multisport event comprised of a run, followed by a cycle, then another run to finish.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Managing Director of the Union Steps Down</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-managing-director-union-steps-down/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-managing-director-union-steps-down/</guid>
        <description>The Managing Director of the Union, Jarlath O’Hara, announced on 18th November that he will be stepping down from his role at the end of December. The announcement was made via an email sent internally to ICU staff, and marks the end of Jarlath’s four-year tenure in the role.
In the email, the only …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Finance vs. Old Finance</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-new-finance-vs-old-finance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marios Papadopoulos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-new-finance-vs-old-finance/</guid>
        <description>Non-traditional banks, such as Revolut and Starling, among many others, have disrupted the banking industry. Banking had traditionally been a difficult sector for startups due to the regulations that dictated the establishment and operation of a bank. Following the 2008 financial crisis, regulatory …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oil Currencies: The Fight for Global Dominance</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-oil-currencies-fight-global-dominance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nehaal Pillai,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-oil-currencies-fight-global-dominance/</guid>
        <description>The United States of America has had a significant presence in the Middle East, a region so far away from it. Why? The reason is the preservation of the Petrodollar system, the currency in which most oil is traded. The demise of this system would bring about a colossal powershift from West to East: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Private Equity vs. Venture Capital:  A Closer Look</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-private-equity-vs-venture-capital-a-closer-look/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavan Singh Gill,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-private-equity-vs-venture-capital-a-closer-look/</guid>
        <description>Private equity and venture capital both refer to investments by individuals or firms/institutions in companies. However, the scale of the investment and the stage of companies they invest in differ.
Private equity
You can think of it as equity that is held privately, either by wealthy individuals or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Recipe: Pasta Aglio e Olio</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-pasta-aglio-e-olio-recipe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Haider Nazerali,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-pasta-aglio-e-olio-recipe/</guid>
        <description>I first saw this amazing quick pasta dish being made in the Netflix film ‘Chef’ (100% great to watch when you’re procrastinating your next lab report or essay) and it looked delicious. Thanks to social media sites stalking my life, it didn’t take long for a recipe to appear on my YouTube suggested. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reimagined, Redesigned, and Revamped</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-reimagined-redesigned-revamped/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christine Parry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-reimagined-redesigned-revamped/</guid>
        <description>Earlier this month, the Science Museum unveiled their latest exhibition, ‘Medicine: the Wellcome Collection’, a gallery that, put simply, showcases the history of medicine, taking up 3000 square metres of space, spanning over 500 years of history right up to the present day, and presenting with a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Shook: Becoming a Father Behind Bars</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-shook-becoming-father-behind-bars/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-shook-becoming-father-behind-bars/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
Shook is as close to a perfect play that I think I have ever seen. Set in a prison classroom, three convicts, all with pregnant girlfriends, are receiving lessons on how to be fathers. Opening with rapid wit and banter the play first comes across as an entertaining but fundamentally shallow …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Starcrawler Comfortably Blows Minds at Camden Show</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-starcrawler-comfortably-blows-minds-at-camden-show/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Freeman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-starcrawler-comfortably-blows-minds-at-camden-show/</guid>
        <description>3 stars
Ah, Underworld. So many incomplete memories of too many nights out. So many vivid memories of strange men standing just a bit too close when you’re just trying to have a night out with friends. Despite my current opinion of Underworld, it will always hold a special place in my …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Strike Action: Pensions and Pay</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-strike-action-pensions-and-pay/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-strike-action-pensions-and-pay/</guid>
        <description>At 60 universities across the UK, university staff who are members of the University and College Union (UCU) are currently staging an eight-day walkout and strike action in response to the ongoing disputes regarding pensions, pay, and working conditions.
The Imperial branch of the UCU, however, is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tech Headlines: 29th November 2019</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-tech-headlines-29th-november-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sudarshan Sreeram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-tech-headlines-29th-november-2019/</guid>
        <description>Cybertruck Unveil
Elon Musk announced Tesla’s new electric pickup truck - Cybertruck. The physical appearance of the truck sure caught everyone off guard. With a low-poly inspired futuristic aesthetic, this truck challenges the conventional design of modern vehicles in general, let alone pickup …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The All-Nighter Film List for December</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-all-nighter-film-list-for-december/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jameel Sardharwalla,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-all-nighter-film-list-for-december/</guid>
        <description>With the end of term looming I’m sure many of you are feeling a mix of fatigue, anxiety, and excitement; so what better to re-energise you for these last few weeks than an all-nighter of films?
ZOMBIELAND: DOUBLE TAP (19:00)
It’s been an incredible 10 years since the first film graced the screens …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
