<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/aranshaunak16/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/aranshaunak16/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Ice, Ice Baby
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-ice-ice-baby/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:02:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aran Shaunak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-ice-ice-baby/</guid>
        <description>Fact: Hot water freezes faster than cold water.
Once upon a time, Erasto Mpemba was making ice cream in his cookery class. The sign of a good scientist? He noticed that the mix froze faster if it was hot, rather than just eating it.
First observed in the 1960s, this experiment has been repeated many …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>High off life
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-high-off-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 14:55:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aran Shaunak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-high-off-life/</guid>
        <description>T ake your dealer off of speed dial. It turns out that human saliva contains a compound – called opiorphin – which is six times more powerful than morphine.
This compound is not itself an opiod, so it doesn’t act in exactly the same way as morphine. However, it chemically inhibits a number of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Moon of my life
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-moon-of-my-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 13:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aran Shaunak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-moon-of-my-life/</guid>
        <description>Fact: Your body has ‘tides’ because of the moon.
They are just really, really, really small.
The moon causes tides in the ocean by exerting a gravitational pull on the water, which changes over the course of a day as the relative positions of the earth and the moon change. The gravitational pull of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My sun and stars
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-my-sun-and-stars/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 15:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aran Shaunak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-my-sun-and-stars/</guid>
        <description>Fact: humans are 90% stardust.
Human beings are mostly made up of water, with a few other bits and pieces thrown in for good measure. That means we are largely made of Hydrogen atoms, followed by lots of Oxygen, a fair bit of Carbon, some Nitrogen and a sprinkling of some more interesting stuff. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Man’s Best Friend
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-mans-best-friend/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 13:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aran Shaunak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-mans-best-friend/</guid>
        <description>Fact: Dogs can smell cancer.
A charity called “Medical Detection Dogs” is undertaking the first clinical trial looking at using sniffer dogs to do something a little more holistic than seeking out drugs and sausages at Manchester Airport.
The procedure is simple – wee in a pot, pooch gives it a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Web of Lies
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-web-of-lies/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 14:03:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aran Shaunak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-web-of-lies/</guid>
        <description>Fact: Goats spin spider-webs.
OK, slight embellishment. Science can make goats that produce spider silk in their milk. Obviously having a few goats minding their own business is better than having millions of spiders in a farm all viciously tearing each other’s heads off – which is exactly what …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Two Frogs on a Bench
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-two-frogs-on-a-bench/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 16:36:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aran Shaunak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-two-frogs-on-a-bench/</guid>
        <description>Fact: You can win $1,000,000 if you have ‘supernatural abilities’.
The “Million Dollar Paranormal Challenge” is offered to anyone who can demonstrate a supernatural ability under agreed-upon scientific testing criteria. In 40 years, despite over 1000 applicants, no one ever won.
The prize was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I don&#39;t think you&#39;re ready for this jelly
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-i-dont-think-youre-ready-for-this-jelly/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 16:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aran Shaunak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-i-dont-think-youre-ready-for-this-jelly/</guid>
        <description>Fact: You can get glow-in-the-dark ice cream.
You might have heard somewhere that Tonic water glows under UV light, but the story of the glow-in-the-dark ice cream takes all that one step further. Its jellyfish flavoured!
Using the physics of fluorescence, animals can produce light by a phenomenon …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bro do you even lift?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-bro-do-you-even-lift/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:08:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Aran Shaunak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-bro-do-you-even-lift/</guid>
        <description>Fact: The strongest living thing on the planet is gonorrhea.
Neisseria gonorrhoeae (the bacterium that causes gonorrhea) is a force to be reckoned with, given it can pull with a force over 100,000 times its own body weight. For a human to compete, you’d have to shift over ten million kilos, which …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Secret to Immortality
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-the-secret-to-immortality/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aran Shaunak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-the-secret-to-immortality/</guid>
        <description>Fact: There is a jellyfish that can live forever.
Turritopsis dohrnii, a small blob floating in the sea off Japan, has been classified as the world’s only immortal organism, since it can develop to adulthood, reproduce and then go backwards in time to an earlier stage in its life cycle and start the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Play Your Cards Right
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-play-your-cards-right/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 14:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aran Shaunak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-play-your-cards-right/</guid>
        <description>Fact: If you shuffle a deck of cards, that precise order of cards has probably never happened before.
Actually, if every single person on earth (all 7 billion of us) had shuffled one deck of cards every second since the start of the universe – 13.7 billion years ago – we still wouldn’t even be close …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mankind is a virus
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-mankind-is-a-virus/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 12:11:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aran Shaunak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-mankind-is-a-virus/</guid>
        <description>Fact: We contains more DNA that makes viruses than DNA that makes humans.
No, this isn’t talking about Mr Smith’s famous quote about how humans are more like viruses than mammals. 5-8% of all human DNA contains genes that make virus proteins, while only ~1.5% of human DNA contains genes that make …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>When I was three I wanted to be...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-when-i-was-three-i-wanted-to-be/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 14:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Aran Shaunak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-when-i-was-three-i-wanted-to-be/</guid>
        <description>Fact: A 10-year old girl discovered a new molecule in her chemistry lesson.
Anyone who did chemistry at school will remember those ball-and-stick molecule toys that teachers used to try and get everyone enthusiastic about covalent bonding. But 10 year old Clara Lazen decided she knew more than her …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chester, the first published Felix
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-chester-the-first-published-felix/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 13:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aran Shaunak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-chester-the-first-published-felix/</guid>
        <description>Fact: There’s a cat that is co-author of a theoretical physics paper.
In 1975, American mathematician and physicist Professor Jack H. Hetherington wrote an entire paper (on low temperature physics, if you were wondering) on a typewriter, only to be told by his supervisor that it would be rejected by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brain Freeze
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-brain-freeze/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 14:49:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aran Shaunak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-brain-freeze/</guid>
        <description>Fact: ‘Brain freeze’ has a biological explanation.
It even has an unpronounceable name: sphenopalatine ganglioneuralgia. When something very cold touches the roof of your mouth (called the ‘palate’), it rapidly cools the blood in the small blood vessels around your sinuses. This causes them to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Breakfast | Take Two
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-breakfast-take-two/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 16:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aran Shaunak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-breakfast-take-two/</guid>
        <description>Fact: You can un-boil an egg.
Boiling an egg causes a fundamental change in the proteins that make up the egg white, which you’ll know if you ever had eggs and soldiers as a kid because a raw egg and a cooked egg look pretty different. The high temperature causes the proteins to lose their shape and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I once was blind but now I see
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-i-once-was-blind-but-now-i-see/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 12:54:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aran Shaunak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-i-once-was-blind-but-now-i-see/</guid>
        <description>Fact: blind people don’t see darkness. They see nothing. I’ll admit this seems counter-intuitive; most of us would shout “I can’t see anything” when stumbling around in the pitch-dark. But understanding blindness requires a bit more thought.
It does depend on the type of blindness. Acquired …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>When pineapples fight back
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-when-pineapples-fight-back/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 16:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aran Shaunak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-when-pineapples-fight-back/</guid>
        <description>Fact: pineapples are the only food to try to eat you while you eat them.
You read that right: pineapples are actually flesh eating monsters. The zombie apocolypse is upon us.
Pineapples contain an enzyme, called Bromelain, which is released when you chow down on your favorite tropical treat. It …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
