<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/editapileckyte/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/editapileckyte/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Scusi, we’re going to Italy: a trip to Verona &amp; Venice</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-scusi-we-re-going-to-italy-a-trip-to-verona-venice/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edita Pileckyte,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-scusi-we-re-going-to-italy-a-trip-to-verona-venice/</guid>
        <description>Italy is a perfect choice for your summer vacation since it has everything – from big famous cities to quiet lesser-known villages and beach towns. You can pop in for a quick weekend getaway or spend a few weeks touring all around the country, whatever floats your boat. It’s also easy to score …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Exploring San Francisco: the Golden City by the bay</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-exploring-san-francisco-the-golden-city-by-the-bay/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edita Pileckyte,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-exploring-san-francisco-the-golden-city-by-the-bay/</guid>
        <description>Getting around
Compared to many famous cities in the States, San Francisco is relatively small, so you can easily get around by foot. However, to get a more authentic experience you might want to opt for cycling, which has become increasingly popular in the past few decades – there’s even a Bike to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Beach better have my money: affordable seaside destinations</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-beach-better-have-my-money-affordable-seaside-destinations/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edita Pileckyte,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-beach-better-have-my-money-affordable-seaside-destinations/</guid>
        <description>With the upcoming summer break, many of us will want to get away from busy and polluted London and relax on the beach. I can’t count the times I was tempted to buy a plane ticket to Spain or Greece for a weekend just to treat myself to some sun and sea. However, flight costs can skyrocket to over …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Los Angeles, I’m yours: five days in Pacific paradise </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-los-angeles-i-m-yours-five-days-in-pacific-paradise/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edita Pileckyte,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-los-angeles-i-m-yours-five-days-in-pacific-paradise/</guid>
        <description>On the first day, we visited the beaches, starting from Santa Monica. It’s a separate city with lively streets, full of shops and diners to choose from. The beach is enormously wide and separated from the streets by tall cliffs. The Santa Monica pier offers a breath-taking view of the Pacific Ocean …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Paris mon amour: three days in the City of Lights</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-paris-mon-amour-three-days-in-the-city-of-lights/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edita Pileckyte,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-paris-mon-amour-three-days-in-the-city-of-lights/</guid>
        <description>Paris holds a special place in my heart because it was my first travel destination since I moved to London, and it made me fall in love with travelling. It was during the revision period for my January exams in 2nd year, when I got the idea, which seemed so crazy at the time, to just pack my bags …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The French Riviera – a dreamy Mediterranean seaside paradise!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-the-french-riviera-a-dreamy-mediterranean-seaside-paradise/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edita Pileckyte,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-the-french-riviera-a-dreamy-mediterranean-seaside-paradise/</guid>
        <description>As one of the most popular Mediterranean resorts, Nice does really live up to its expectations! Its main highlight is the azure sea, so blue it almost looks artificial and does justice to the region’s name. The only imperfection of the beach is that it’s made of sharp stones – quite uncomfortable to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grand Canyon and Death Valley: the pride of South-West USA</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-grand-canyon-and-death-valley-the-pride-of-south-west-usa/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edita Pileckyte,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-grand-canyon-and-death-valley-the-pride-of-south-west-usa/</guid>
        <description>During my three day stay in Las Vegas, I decided to visit two of the most famous North American national parks – Grand Canyon in Arizona and Death Valley in California. They were a huge contrast from the busy and posh Vegas, and were an integral part of my US experience. While one day is more than …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Behind the curtain of Hollywood</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-behind-the-curtain-of-hollywood/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edita Pileckyte,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-behind-the-curtain-of-hollywood/</guid>
        <description>Before visiting Los Angeles, I had heard numerous stories of how utterly disappointing the city is since “there’s nothing to do there”. But if you are determined to make the most of your trip, you can always find something interesting – for instance, besides the usual tourist spots, you can visit …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A new craze is taking over Los Angeles, and it just might be your Happy Place</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-a-new-craze-is-taking-over-los-angeles-and-it-just-might-be-your-happy-place/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edita Pileckyte,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-a-new-craze-is-taking-over-los-angeles-and-it-just-might-be-your-happy-place/</guid>
        <description>Currently, the people of Los Angeles are losing their minds over a new pop-up gallery called the Happy Place. Situated in the Arts District in Downtown LA, the place offers a perfect opportunity to forget about your everyday problems and promises to put a smile on your face. The project also prides …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>California on a budget</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-california-on-a-budget/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edita Pileckyte,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-california-on-a-budget/</guid>
        <description> After a draining year at Imperial, and quite possibly an internship-packed summer, most of us crave a vacation, preferably outside London. While coming back home is often enjoyable, going somewhere completely new can be even more appealing. One of the most popular travel destinations is the United …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London Calling! Felix’s guide to the capital’s best spots</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-london-calling-felix-s-guide-to-the-capital-s-best-spots/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edita Pileckyte,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-london-calling-felix-s-guide-to-the-capital-s-best-spots/</guid>
        <description>Starting at university, especially one as highly demanding as Imperial, can be both exciting and overwhelming. Most students often find themselves swamped with work from the second week of term, but it’s always worth remembering that by studying here you also live in one of the greatest and most …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
