<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rbg10/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rbg10/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix music present the best of the year so far: 2013
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-felix-music-present-the-best-of-the-year-so-far-2013/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 23:10:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Gray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-felix-music-present-the-best-of-the-year-so-far-2013/</guid>
        <description>2013 has been a year of labels for me. Whilst this may be somewhat rudimentary, I’ve really found labels to be an incredible source of new sounds in the year so far. I had to make a big effort to limit some of my favourite labels from this period (e.g. Opal Tapes, Blackest Ever Black) to just one …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Review: Shampoo Boy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-6-review-shampoo-boy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 19:47:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Gray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-6-review-shampoo-boy/</guid>
        <description>Blackest Ever Black, the aptly named London label that has been grabbing attention with crushingly dark electronic releases for the past few years, seems like an ideal home for Peter Rehberg (PITA, Editions Mego head), Christina Nemec, and Christian Schachinger’s new project Shampoo Boy.
One for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Drugs Survey
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-felix-drugs-survey/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 19:08:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Gray,Philip Kent,Philippa M Skett,Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-felix-drugs-survey/</guid>
        <description> The full version is available online.
Out of the 762 responses that we received, 54% said that they had tried illegal drugs. Splitting this into male and female showed that 57% of men said that they had taken drugs, whereas 49% of women said that they had.
 57% of men and 49% of women said that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cassette Culture: Opal Tapes Interview
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-8-cassette-culture-opal-tapes-interview/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 20:31:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Gray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-8-cassette-culture-opal-tapes-interview/</guid>
        <description>Within the past year experimental electronic music has exploded into the D.I.Y. cassette culture within the UK, previously dominated by (but by no means limited to) noise releases. Stephen Bishop, head honcho of prominent label Opal Tapes, spoke to me about its formation, the themes that run through …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Boiler Room bikes and b2bs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-28-boiler-room-bikes-and-b2bs/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 23:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Gray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-28-boiler-room-bikes-and-b2bs/</guid>
        <description>When I first considered writing an article on Boiler Room, I thought it would be redundant. I always thought that it’s just one of those things that everyone who would be interested knows about, but when I started chatting to people about it I realised this is not really the case. Considering how …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Bloody Valentine Live
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-my-bloody-valentine-live/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 00:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Gray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-my-bloody-valentine-live/</guid>
        <description>When ATP (All Tomorrow’s Parties) and My Bloody Valentine announced their live return to the UK, a single night at the Hammersmith Apollo in March, the internet immediately started buzzing. Tickets went up and were sold out in seconds. Another night was quickly added, where standing tickets also …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grouper’s Ghostly Maritime Explorations
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-groupers-ghostly-maritime-explorations/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 00:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Gray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-groupers-ghostly-maritime-explorations/</guid>
        <description>Reviews for Grouper’s The Man Who Died in His Boat (recorded in the same sessions as my favourite work of hers, Dragging a Dead Deer up a Hill) have had a bit of a tendency to focus on the concept behind the album. Liz Harris (Grouper) has said that it’s based on a teenage memory of peering inside …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UTR: Helm and Tropa Macaca
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-utr-helm-and-tropa-macaca/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 22:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Gray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-utr-helm-and-tropa-macaca/</guid>
        <description>Promoters and record label Upset The Rhythm have really been having a good run so far this year, throwing the phenomenal Pete Swanson (of Yellow Swans) and Mark Fell (of SND) event last Monday, and last night putting on a small show in The Sebright Arms for hot-topic Helm (on the hot-topic label …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>D-beat Review: Krömosom – Live Forever
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-d-beat-review-krmosom-live-forever/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 00:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Gray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-d-beat-review-krmosom-live-forever/</guid>
        <description>Within my university life I have had frequent exposure to cybergrind and noisecore, whilst maintaining particular passions for the more punk-routed powerviolence and the extreme grind stylings of The Gerogerigegege. That said, the first thing that struck me upon listening to Krömosom was the sheer …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>GODrec Present Wir Werden
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-godrec-present-wir-werden/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 22:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Gray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-godrec-present-wir-werden/</guid>
        <description>Towards the end of first term, an interesting email arrived in our inbox from God records, a small “Austrian label for new and experimental music”, promoting a Boris Hegenbart release which includes collaborations with 19 artists, such as Oren Ambarchi and Fred Frith. When the promo arrived however, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Movements in the deep of night
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-movements-in-the-deep-of-night/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:30:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Gray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-movements-in-the-deep-of-night/</guid>
        <description>Fellow Bristolian Vessel’s 2012 offering, Order of Noise, manages to successfully intertwine dark ambient, glitch, dub and techno to throw us back to those grimy Bristol moments where the stims have ran out and everyone is desperately caning the ketamine, milking the absolute last out of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Earth shattering performance
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-earth-shattering-performance/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 21:23:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Gray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-earth-shattering-performance/</guid>
        <description>Continuing my recent binge of church-based gigs, last Sunday I had a beautiful foray to The Union Chapel to see Earth’s tour, supported by Mount Eerie and the pretty obscure French Canadian Ô Paon. If you read my recent review of Nicolas Jaar at Roundhouse, you’ll be well aware that sweaty, active …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jaar does the rounds
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-jaar-does-the-rounds/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 22:11:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Gray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-jaar-does-the-rounds/</guid>
        <description>On Thursday the 3rd of February, my flatmate and I decided to take a risk. We decided to pay for a gig that cost more than £15 and wasn’t run by ATP – a risk we would come to bitterly regret. The gig in question was Nicolas Jaar’s _Clown &amp;amp; Sunset _showcase at Roundhouse, a pretty large venue. As …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
