<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ltr11/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ltr11/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Swap out those burgers for beans!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-swap-out-those-burgers-for-beans/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 12:01:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lauren Ratcliffe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-swap-out-those-burgers-for-beans/</guid>
        <description>Those late night burgers and sloppy kebabs may be doing far more dangerous things to your body than just expanding your waistline, research from Imperial suggests. A diet swap between American and African volunteers has indicated that one nation’s dietary habits leads to a greater risk of getting …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Kings’ of the Jungle De-Throned!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-4-kings-of-the-jungle-de-throned/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 16:27:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lauren Ratcliffe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-4-kings-of-the-jungle-de-throned/</guid>
        <description>New research in Borneo by researchers from Imperial College London suggests that clear cutting rainforests changes which types of species perform vital ecosystem functions. In logged forests, vertebrates instead of invertebrates appear to be contributing a greater amount to key processes such as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Facing difficult decisions in medicine
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-20-facing-difficult-decisions-in-medicine/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2015 00:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lauren Ratcliffe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-20-facing-difficult-decisions-in-medicine/</guid>
        <description>During some pregnancies, abnormal blood flow from the placenta can deprive the foetus of sufficient oxygen and nutrients to grow to its full potential. This condition is known as foetal growth restriction and affects up to 8% of all pregnancies, a total of 60,000 babies per year in Europe and the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Methods developed at Imperial could make burning fossil fuels guilt-free
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-13-methods-developed-at-imperial-could-make-burning-fossil-fuels-guilt-free/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 00:39:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lauren Ratcliffe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-13-methods-developed-at-imperial-could-make-burning-fossil-fuels-guilt-free/</guid>
        <description>If we are to avoid further aggravating climate change we need to find a way to store or transform the hundreds of billions of tonnes of carbon dioxide produced by power stations worldwide into something useful. A team at Imperial’s Department of Chemistry have done just this. Working with the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Climate Change is like an unwashed dish. Don’t believe me?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-climate-change-is-like-an-unwashed-dish-dont-believe-me/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 19:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lauren Ratcliffe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-climate-change-is-like-an-unwashed-dish-dont-believe-me/</guid>
        <description>You guys already know that global warming is not a myth, nor an April fools trick. It’s a growing concern that we and future generations are facing. Earth’s blood, so to speak, is on humanity’s hands and it is our responsibility to acknowledge, understand and find solutions to this challenge. I talk …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Artificial Intelligence with a Consciousness
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-artificial-intelligence-with-a-consciousness/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 14:54:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lauren Ratcliffe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-artificial-intelligence-with-a-consciousness/</guid>
        <description>Science fiction film Ex-Machina has recently hit cinemas worldwide, a psychological thriller to tantalise our over-active imaginations of a future where artificial intelligence has a consciousness. But how far are we from any of these ideas becoming reality? In Ex Machina audiences are supposed to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Have we entered a new human-dominated epoch…the Anthropocene?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-have-we-entered-a-new-human-dominated-epochthe-anthropocene/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 17:57:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lauren Ratcliffe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-have-we-entered-a-new-human-dominated-epochthe-anthropocene/</guid>
        <description>Sunset for the Holocene
Last week scientists confirmed that we have entered a new geological era called the Anthropocene. To put this into context the last epoch, known amongst geologists as the Holocene, began around 11,700 years ago after the Pleistocene, whose beginning was punctuated by the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dr Robin Carhart-Harris talks about LSD and the Psychedelic state Psychedelic State
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-dr-robin-carhart-harris-talks-about-lsd-and-the-psychedelic-state-psychedelic-state/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 00:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lauren Ratcliffe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-dr-robin-carhart-harris-talks-about-lsd-and-the-psychedelic-state-psychedelic-state/</guid>
        <description>Complete understanding behind the powerful effects of psychedelics on the mind has remained a mystery for many decades. Over 60 years has passed since the first discovery of lysergic acid diethylamide (LSD) and since then surprisingly little concrete knowledge of its effects on the brain has been …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Freshers’ Flu: the science behind the sniffles and snot
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-freshers-flu-the-science-behind-the-sniffles-and-snot/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 22:55:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lauren Ratcliffe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-freshers-flu-the-science-behind-the-sniffles-and-snot/</guid>
        <description>Freshers’ Week for most is a time full of new experiences, stepping out of your usual comfort zone and meeting more new people than you could hope to remember. There are very few instances in your life that you will speak to as many strangers in such a short period of time, turning awkward …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Shifting attitudes towards MDMA
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-shifting-attitudes-towards-mdma/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 21:28:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lauren Ratcliffe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-shifting-attitudes-towards-mdma/</guid>
        <description>MDMA, or for you chemists out there 3,4-methylenedioxmethamphetamne, more recognisably referred to as ecstasy is a prevalent and well-known drug. It’s no state secret that a majority of people who are reading this have encountered it - whether that be through occasional to regular recreational use …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Lunatics have taken over the Asylum
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-the-lunatics-have-taken-over-the-asylum/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 19:41:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lauren Ratcliffe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-the-lunatics-have-taken-over-the-asylum/</guid>
        <description>The UK Misuse of Drugs Act introduced in 1971 is widely regarded as the most epically failed governmental campaigns to prevent drug distribution and usage. By introducing complete prohibition it effectively promoted an underground black-market in drug trade, condemned addicts to conviction rather …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Waterboarding
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-waterboarding/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 23:52:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lauren Ratcliffe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-waterboarding/</guid>
        <description>Erika Craig is one of many upcoming artists in our generation. She began her career in California where she received her BA. During this time she also studied in an inspirational and architecturally rich city, Paris.
Erika has a style that you cannot help but admire. Both her technical skill and her …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get your tats out
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-28-get-your-tats-out/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 23:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lauren Ratcliffe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-28-get-your-tats-out/</guid>
        <description>If you were to get a tattoo what would it be and why? Think about it for a moment. Perhaps you already have one. Does it represent anything important to you or is it purely aesthetic?
For Danzig Daldaev, tattoos shaped his life. He was born in Russia in 1925 and condemned in 1948 by the KGB to work …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
