<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/gg2110/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/gg2110/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Beautiful beaches of Britain
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-4-beautiful-beaches-of-britain/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 17:01:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Giulia Gabrielli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-4-beautiful-beaches-of-britain/</guid>
        <description>Look behind the well-sculpted muscles of Ross Poldark and you’ll see the Cornish coastline. This is not the first time that a British beach has proven to be a co-star on a TV show.
I guess when you can’t boast the sun and the white sands, and when “it’s so bracing” (read “cold and miserable”) …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My new wind-swept, muscly hero
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-4-my-new-wind-swept-muscly-hero/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 16:58:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Giulia Gabrielli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-4-my-new-wind-swept-muscly-hero/</guid>
        <description>I rarely write an article about a programme and focus so much interest on its main character. Of course there are heartthrobs who keep you glued to the screen, but Ross Poldark is different. The reason why he is different, is that rarely such a hype has been built around a single character, to the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Remarkably uncatastrophic
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-3-remarkably-uncatastrophic/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 14:56:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Giulia Gabrielli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-3-remarkably-uncatastrophic/</guid>
        <description>I am not sure how high Channel 4’s ambitions for the show_ Catastrophe_ were. Writers and main actors Rob Delauney and Sharon Horgan sure seemed like a weird couple: Delauney a likeable, tall, American dude and Horgan a dead-pan and sarcastic Irish woman. Together they created a baby-script funny …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Awkward is a family trait
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-9-awkward-is-a-family-trait/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 19:37:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Giulia Gabrielli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-9-awkward-is-a-family-trait/</guid>
        <description>Jack Whitehall has returned for the second season of Backchat with Jack Whitehall. His attempt to break into chat shows, however, can only be summarised in one word: awkward. Be it because of the presence of his elderly father, or because of the strange formulation of the show, watching it without …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cucumber, Banana, Tofu: Channel 4’s new sex salad.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-9-cucumber-banana-tofu-channel-4s-new-sex-salad/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 19:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Giulia Gabrielli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-9-cucumber-banana-tofu-channel-4s-new-sex-salad/</guid>
        <description>At Christmas, Channel 4 aggressively started advertising its new LGBT drama, signed by producer Russell T Davies from Queer as Folk. Maybe it was because of the massive billboards on Cromwell Road, or the ever-present YouTube clips, but I feel there was a certain degree of anticipation behind this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Tis the season for stand-up comedy DVDs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-11-tis-the-season-for-stand-up-comedy-dvds/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 21:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Giulia Gabrielli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-11-tis-the-season-for-stand-up-comedy-dvds/</guid>
        <description>Chestnuts roasting on an open fire, it’s beginning to look a lot like Christmas, the goose is getting fat. In other words, though you may not know, not having ventured outside South Kensington since the second week of October, Santa is here!
And what better way to spend your December money, freshly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The thinking woman’s crumpet
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-the-thinking-womans-crumpet/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 19:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Giulia Gabrielli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-the-thinking-womans-crumpet/</guid>
        <description>Forget Brian Cox and David Attenborough. Forget science documentaries about space and animals, for a little while at least. There’s a new generation of TV presenters giving us insights into big cities, old jazz clubs and sacred rivers and we are definitely digging it.
Dr James Fox, art historian and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Revision 101: a short television guide to 20 minute breaks
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-revision-101-a-short-television-guide-to-20-minute-breaks/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 19:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Giulia Gabrielli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-revision-101-a-short-television-guide-to-20-minute-breaks/</guid>
        <description>Are you troubled by revision time? Do you find yourself sweating over notes and books, asking yourself who invented pre-Christmas exams? Well, we’re all in the same boat.
The revision period can be an intense time, when it seems like everything in the world revolves around your subject. Bottom line, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>David Attenborough has done it again
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-david-attenborough-has-done-it-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 20:42:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Giulia Gabrielli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-david-attenborough-has-done-it-again/</guid>
        <description>Although he doesn’t go out to the field anymore, nothing can keep David Attenborough away from TV. This autumn, he returns to the screens with the series_ Life Story_, an attempt to show how different animals share the same rituals and habits across species.
It may be said that the production goes a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is Mindy Kaling too ugly, or are you just too rude?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-17-is-mindy-kaling-too-ugly-or-are-you-just-too-rude/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 18:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Giulia Gabrielli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-17-is-mindy-kaling-too-ugly-or-are-you-just-too-rude/</guid>
        <description>After an incredibly well received debut, praised by viewers and critics alike, what is happening with The Mindy Project? After a bumpy second season that brought threats of cancellations, the Fox Network decided to renew the sitcom for another series.
This was largely due to the interest created by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>So you think you’re an Erasmuser?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-11-so-you-think-youre-an-erasmuser/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 23:00:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Giulia Gabrielli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-11-so-you-think-youre-an-erasmuser/</guid>
        <description>It may seem strange stuck on level 4 of the library, turning pages as silently as possible to avoid any evil stare of doom, but there are some Imperialites that leave for the mythological Erasmus year; and I am one of them. Last year I packed up my stuff in three bags and five boxes and left for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Miranda Effect
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-the-miranda-effect/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 01:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Giulia Gabrielli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-the-miranda-effect/</guid>
        <description>Every Monday night this term, I have patiently and loyally tuned in to watch the latest episode of Miranda. After the past couple of series of goofiness and misunderstandings, we’d all probably had enough of it. There’s only a certain amount of anthropomorphic fruit one can stand. However, after …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Memoir mash-up
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-memoir-mash-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 00:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Giulia Gabrielli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-memoir-mash-up/</guid>
        <description>I am currently looking through Audible.co.uk. This is the Amazon sister-company dedicated to providing audiobooks to the poor souls, such as myself, that have countless hours of free mental time, and a bank card. But, why do I have all this time? Since starting work at the Centre for Functional …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
