<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jh3609/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jh3609/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>One billion hungry: can we feed the world?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-22-one-billion-hungry-can-we-feed-the-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 14:35:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jill Humphries,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-22-one-billion-hungry-can-we-feed-the-world/</guid>
        <description>JH: What are the key threats to global food security?
Professor Sir Gordan Conway: The three main challenges we’ve got at the moment are: food price spikes, the persistence of a billion or more people suffering from chronic hunger and the need to feed a growing population in the face of a wide range …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>World’s lightest material made
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-22-worlds-lightest-material-made/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 14:30:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jill Humphries,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-22-worlds-lightest-material-made/</guid>
        <description>The lightest material to date has been created; weighing in at less than 10 milligrams per cubic centimetre, it is lighter than aerogels and dense foams. The Guinness world record beater has a density of just 0.9 milligrams per cubic centimetre, in perspective this is 100 times lighter than …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cyborg yeast is out to get you
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-22-cyborg-yeast-is-out-to-get-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 14:29:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jill Humphries,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-22-cyborg-yeast-is-out-to-get-you/</guid>
        <description>Scientists have succeeded in creating an artificial feedback loop between a computer and yeast. Algorithmic programs on the computer controlled flashes of light to start and stop gene expression, thus regulating how much protein was produced. This innovative technique could possibly be used in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Does Fairtrade actually work?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-22-does-fairtrade-actually-work/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 14:27:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jill Humphries,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-22-does-fairtrade-actually-work/</guid>
        <description>Yes
“Upon purchasing a certified product, we demonstrate our support for a fairer world” Tucked into a comforting chocolaty tub of Ben &amp;amp; Jerry’s recently? Needed a morning caffeine kick and grabbed a Starbucks mocha? Munched on a banana at lunch? Odds are, you’ve accidentally or purposefully …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It takes two to tango
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-22-it-takes-two-to-tango/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 14:24:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jill Humphries,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-22-it-takes-two-to-tango/</guid>
        <description>The word feminism itself does not include men into the equation. Yet, men should be just as active as women in the movement towards gender equality. This should be the accepted norm, which it appears to be at university, as proven by the high percentage of guys involved in the Feminist society. …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
