<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/syon_lee/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/syon_lee/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Cyrano de Bergerac: Love Letters to Language</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-cyrano-bergerac-love-letters-language/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-cyrano-bergerac-love-letters-language/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
I had no idea of what kind of show to expect, Swayed to attend by media buzz and the prospect Of seeing James McAvoy - live on stage! A welcome break from his golden age Of threequels and reboots, Green screens and CGI substitutes, Blockbuster, record-buster, So-called cinematic filibuster. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Do’s and Don’t of a Student Christmas Dinner: How to Keep the Festive Mood on a Student Budget</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-dos-donts-christmas-dinner-keep-festive-mood-student-budget/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,Zahra Abiola,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-dos-donts-christmas-dinner-keep-festive-mood-student-budget/</guid>
        <description>THE BIRD
A whole roast turkey is the usual fare for a Christmas dinner but unless you are ready to buy way ahead, have an inordinate amount of oven space, and you don’t mind the lengthy brining and cooking process, I would steer clear. A poorly cooked turkey is way worse than no turkey at all. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your Union is Standing Firm</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-dramsoc-macbeth-scores-macb/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-dramsoc-macbeth-scores-macb/</guid>
        <description>2 stars
I don’t remember much about Macbeth, having only studied it briefly in my early secondary school days. While I may have forgotten the plot and the characters’ names, I could never forget the feeling of empowerment I experienced after learning of my king-slayer potential wrought from the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Ultimate(?) Guide to Pasta Shapes</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-ultimate-guide-pasta-shapes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-ultimate-guide-pasta-shapes/</guid>
        <description>Simultaneously a destitute student’s staple and a feature in high-end restaurants, everyone understands pasta and, more importantly, everyone loves pasta.
However, even true love can get boring. Missionary and “words of affirmation” can only keep a relationship alive for so long. Likewise, fusilli …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I Love You, You’re Perfect, Now Change</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-i-love-you-youre-perfect-now-change/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-i-love-you-youre-perfect-now-change/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
Love is at the centre of all good tales. Every story ever told, every piece of art, is propelled by this strange notion of an attractive force between individuals, a force that can neither be defined nor explained. And yet that’s what I Love You… attempts to do by showcasing the almost …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tick, Tick… BOOM!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-28-tick-tick-boom/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-28-tick-tick-boom/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
Before there was Rent, there was 30&amp;frasl;90. Wait a second. Let me start again. Before there was Rent there was Boho Days, a… solo rock monologue? Ah, here we go. Before there was Rent, there was 30&amp;frasl;90, which was renamed to Boho Days and finally to tick, tick… BOOM!, an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Manga Exhibition at the British Museum</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-manga-exhibition-british-museum/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-manga-exhibition-british-museum/</guid>
        <description>Ask the uninitiated what manga is, and they’ll probably tell you something about “Japanese cartoons with the big eyes and crazy hair” or, if you’re my mum, “Japanese nerd stuff that’ll turn you into a shut-in NEET pervert”. For me, manga and anime were one of few cultural touchstones that I could …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AI: More than Worth It</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-ai-more-than-worth-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-ai-more-than-worth-it/</guid>
        <description>It has almost been seventy years since Alan Turing published the hugely influential paper ‘Computing Machinery and Intelligence’ where he first posits the basis of what we now know as the Turing test. In a mere lifetime, computers have gone from purely machines of calculation to pocket-sized marvels …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An interview with Anna Ridler, the artist behind Mosaic Virus and Myriad (Tulips)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-an-interview-with-anna-ridler-the-artist-behind-mosaic-virus-and-myriad-tulips/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-an-interview-with-anna-ridler-the-artist-behind-mosaic-virus-and-myriad-tulips/</guid>
        <description>For those unfamiliar with your work, how would you introduce yourself and describe your artwork?
I’m an artist. I like to work with technology, but not just because it is there. I think about what it can do and how it can add to what I’m making, about its associations and the connotations of using …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bear-ly Legal: Awkward Conversations with Animals I’ve F*cked</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-bear-ly-legal-awkward-conversations-with-animals-i-ve-f-cked/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-bear-ly-legal-awkward-conversations-with-animals-i-ve-f-cked/</guid>
        <description>There’s something to be said about dating animals. They’re straightforward, relatively predictable, and often more empathic than people. It’s probably why Bobby, played by producer Linus Karp, chose to lose his virginity to a dog he picked up on his way home from a party. But what possesses a man to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science Gallery: Spare Parts Review</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-science-gallery-spare-parts-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-science-gallery-spare-parts-review/</guid>
        <description>For those unfamiliar with the new Science Gallery at London Bridge, the project was conceived as an international network of public engagement spaces established in partnership with major local academic institutions. The first opened in Trinity College, Dublin, and currently, there are four such …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How do we mend the rift between science and art?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-how-do-we-mend-the-rift-between-science-and-art/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-how-do-we-mend-the-rift-between-science-and-art/</guid>
        <description>I am slightly ashamed to admit that after four years at Imperial, I had yet to attend a single conference. However, in the spirit of trying new things and expanding my horizons, I agreed to accompany my friend to Aesop’s Arts in Health Conference and Showcase. This neophiliac mentality was what …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
