<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sung_soo_moon/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sung_soo_moon/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>CONSUME! CONSUME! CONSUME! CONSUME! CONSUME! Then Die</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-consume-then-die/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-consume-then-die/</guid>
        <description>It’s the most wonderful time of the year… for the big fat cats to cash in on your appetite for greed and low self-esteem. Christmas is around the corner, and the capitalist gods have sent their finest to wring out every ounce of self-respect we have: Black Friday. Since its beginnings in mid-20th …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Us</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-us/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-us/</guid>
        <description>Two years have passed by since Jordan Peele’s directorial debut, Get Out. It was a critical and commercial success and earned Peele an Oscar for Best Screenplay. I love Get Out. The thrill of riding this rollercoaster of a movie in a packed screening was overwhelming. Peele impressively toyed with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Being John Malkovich</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-being-john-malkovich/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-being-john-malkovich/</guid>
        <description>I recently turned twenty. After battling through the bittersweet feelings of aging, a newfound existential angst and a sudden realisation of one’s mortality, I found it in myself to truly cherish this milestone and discover this treasure of a film from the year I was born.
Being John Malkovich is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oscars 2019: Felix Film’s take on the Winners, the Losers, and yearly scheduled general disappointment</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-oscars-2019-felix-film-s-take-on-the-winners-the-losers-and-yearly-scheduled-general-disappointment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mikhail Demtchenko,Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-oscars-2019-felix-film-s-take-on-the-winners-the-losers-and-yearly-scheduled-general-disappointment/</guid>
        <description>Best Picture
Academy Prediction:
Probably Green Book or The Favourite
What we want to win: I’d want to see Roma win, personally; maybe it might? BlacKkKlansman probably would win if this were ten years ago. Anything except A Star is Born.
The nominees for Best Picture are arguably the most diverse …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Memory Loss, Chopping off fingers, and Erotic musical numbers: A Perfect Valentine Trio</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-memory-loss-chopping-off-fingers-and-erotic-musical-numbers-a-perfect-valentine-trio/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aidan Chan,Sung Soo Moon,Mikhail Demtchenko,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-memory-loss-chopping-off-fingers-and-erotic-musical-numbers-a-perfect-valentine-trio/</guid>
        <description>Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind
Tis the season of romance! Whether you’re looking for a film for your next night in with your significant other, or to drown the bitter feeling of rejection, Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind is surely the answer. It’s a film that’s suitable for all couples, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Roma: a triumph of cinema or the pinnacle of home viewing?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-roma-a-triumph-of-cinema-or-the-pinnacle-of-home-viewing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-roma-a-triumph-of-cinema-or-the-pinnacle-of-home-viewing/</guid>
        <description>I have been anticipating Alfonso Cuaron’s new film, Roma, since its warm reception around the festival circuit last year. It’s been six years since Gravity, a film that swept the board with its accolades, both technical and artistic. After making several high-profile, comfortably budgeted, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s a Wonderful Felix Film Christmas: The Lowdown of Must Watch Christmas Films this Holiday Season </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-it-s-a-wonderful-felix-film-christmas-the-lowdown-of-must-watch-christmas-films-this-holiday-season/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mikhail Demtchenko,Aidan Chan,Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-it-s-a-wonderful-felix-film-christmas-the-lowdown-of-must-watch-christmas-films-this-holiday-season/</guid>
        <description>The Nightmare Before Christmas
Less of a nightmare, more of a dream for a Christmas movie choice
Sick of the Jingle Bells and the Christmas lights? Tired of fake white beards and elven tights? Well you are in luck my mates, for The Nightmare Before Christmas awaits. From the inexplicable mind of Tim …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don’t Burn Your Bridges Before You Get To Them!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-don-t-burn-your-bridges-before-you-get-to-them/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-don-t-burn-your-bridges-before-you-get-to-them/</guid>
        <description>The BFI London Film Festival last week drew to a close, showcasing films from newbie filmmakers and seasoned veterans from around the globe. I was lucky enough to catch Burning, a South Korean noir directed by Lee Chang-dong. Lee offers a three-handed hypnotic and tense drama with impressive …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BlacKkKlansman: A Klever koncious Komedy</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-blackkklansman-a-klever-koncious-komedy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-blackkklansman-a-klever-koncious-komedy/</guid>
        <description>Ah, the seventies — a vibrant era of yesteryear, whose key highlights include the heinous hairdos, sleaze-core fashion, disco music, and of course, the racial tension between white and black peoples of America. However, BlacKkKlansman is far from a period piece, as director Spike Lee embellishes …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is Kanye West going south?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-15-is-kanye-west-going-south/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-15-is-kanye-west-going-south/</guid>
        <description>Never far from controversy, Kanye West (now wanting to be known as Ye), has hit headlines again, provoking a lot of reaction from the internet following his appearance on the 44th season premiere of Saturday Night Live last week. Ye performed his single “I love it” with Lil Pump, as they danced …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Film’s Student Essentials</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-felix-film-s-student-essentials/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sung Soo Moon,Aidan Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-felix-film-s-student-essentials/</guid>
        <description>Y TU MAMA TAMBIEN
DIR: Alfonso Cuaron
SCRIPT: Alfonso Cuaron, Carlos Cuaron
Literally translating to “And Your Mother Too”, Y Tu Mama Tambien is a coming-of-age film set in Mexico about two young men and an older woman searching for an invented beach called “la Boca del Cielo”, or “Heaven’s Mouth”. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Isle of Dogs: A cute tail that lacks some bite</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-isle-of-dogs-a-cute-tail-that-lacks-some-bite/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-isle-of-dogs-a-cute-tail-that-lacks-some-bite/</guid>
        <description>It’s been four years since the release of The Grand Budapest Hotel, a commercial and critical success for director Wes Anderson. It’s a tough act to follow, but Isle of Dogs is a delightful addition to Anderson’s body of work – his offbeat filmmaking style translates impressively to animation, which …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In light of dark matter: oldest stars lead to detection</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-in-light-of-dark-matter-oldest-stars-lead-to-detection/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-in-light-of-dark-matter-oldest-stars-lead-to-detection/</guid>
        <description>Recent research conducted in Arizona State University suggests that we have the “first direct proof” that dark matter exists, as a team of astronomers analysed absorption lines from the oldest stars in the universe. Dark matter is an invisible stockpile of mass that we estimate to make up about 27% …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hard Sun – Five years until the world ends in this melodramatic miniseries</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-hard-sun-five-years-until-the-world-ends-in-this-melodramatic-miniseries/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-hard-sun-five-years-until-the-world-ends-in-this-melodramatic-miniseries/</guid>
        <description>From writer Neil Cross, who masterminded Luther, comes a series that gives a twist to the tradition of quintessentially British escapist police drama. The story follows Elaine Renko (Agyness Deyn) and Charlie Hicks (Jim Sturgess), two detectives who stumble upon a government leak describing ‘Hard …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Petition asks for Wetherspoons to take over Union bars and attacks cost saving claims as “complete bollocks”</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-14-petition-asks-for-wetherspoons-to-take-over-union-bars-and-attacks-cost-saving-claims-as-complete-bollocks/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-14-petition-asks-for-wetherspoons-to-take-over-union-bars-and-attacks-cost-saving-claims-as-complete-bollocks/</guid>
        <description>A petition demanding that the Union “replace Bug Light with an actual beer” has attracted 276 signatures at the time of going to press. Started last Friday, the petition claims rising prices are “ruining the experiences of virtually all Imperial students”.
The Union said that the move from Stella …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
