<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/stebo101/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/stebo101/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The Unknown Girl ties everything up in the end
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-the-unknown-girl-ties-everything-up-in-the-end/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 15:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Steve Bohnel,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-the-unknown-girl-ties-everything-up-in-the-end/</guid>
        <description>For about the first 90 minutes of The Unknown Girl, I sat rather unimpressed in my leather chair in one of the small theaters at Soho Screening Rooms. Then, as the last half hour unfolded, directors Jean-Pierre and Luc Dardenne tied together multiple plot lines like a beautiful bow on a Christmas …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fake news: you won’t believe what I think!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-fake-news-you-wont-believe-what-i-think/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 15:38:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Bohnel,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-fake-news-you-wont-believe-what-i-think/</guid>
        <description>If you’ve read my comment pieces in this paper around the time of the American election, then you know two facts: first, I’m American, and second, I’m pretty opinionated about our political landscape and how polarized it’s seemingly become.
Now, during recent weeks, more articles have been written …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ongoing investigation into Acton stabbing
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-ongoing-investigation-into-acton-stabbing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 11:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Steve Bohnel,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-ongoing-investigation-into-acton-stabbing/</guid>
        <description>The Metropolitan police are still searching for a minicab driver they believe played a role in the fatal stabbing of 18-year-old Khalid Safi on December 1st – which occurred near Woodward Buildings, one of Imperial College’s residence halls.
Safi, who was living in Southwark, was stabbed in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Library gets Dolly the Sheep statue
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-library-gets-dolly-the-sheep-statue/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 13:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Bohnel,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-library-gets-dolly-the-sheep-statue/</guid>
        <description>Students who have walked through the security gates at Central Library the past couple of weeks may have noticed a strange sculpture awaiting them before they turn into the main study areas.
That strange sculpture, however, is three students’ tribute to one of the most significant global engineering …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The US Election, a week on
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-the-us-election-a-week-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 14:26:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Bohnel,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-the-us-election-a-week-on/</guid>
        <description>It’s been about a week and a half since the U.S. election was held. By now, most of the world seems to know that Donald Trump is the president-elect of the United States. What isn’t as clear, however, is how much he will scale back from his hateful rhetoric and proposed policies during his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Electoral dysfunction
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-electoral-dysfunction/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 13:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Steve Bohnel,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-electoral-dysfunction/</guid>
        <description>Right before I boarded my flight from London Stansted Airport to travel to Rome for a short trip, I refreshed a Google search on my iPhone. My screen read the following: Hilary Clinton with 215 electoral votes, and Donald Trump with 244. Hours later, as I was chatting with two Londoners who were …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I’m American, but I’m not voting for Hillary or Donald
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-im-american-but-im-not-voting-for-hillary-or-donald/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 14:49:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Steve Bohnel,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-im-american-but-im-not-voting-for-hillary-or-donald/</guid>
        <description>I’m an idiot.
This is the first presidential election I can vote in, and it appears that unless I pay a huge amount of money to ship my absentee ballot over to Pennsylvania, my voice won’t be heard.
And even with that being said, my vote definitely wouldn’t have mattered, seeing as it would have …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
