<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/grumpy_bastard/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/grumpy_bastard/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>I Hate Phones</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-I-hate-phones/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-I-hate-phones/</guid>
        <description>No, you can’t have my number. Why? Oh, that’s because I don’t have a phone. Yes, that does make me a better person than you. Thanks for noticing! I’ve actually been living life without a phone for six months now, and I’ve really felt the benefits.
It’s not because I’m scared that the Chinese …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We Should All Stop Fucking Swearing</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-we-should-all-stop-fucking-swearing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-we-should-all-stop-fucking-swearing/</guid>
        <description>We live in a society. One that swears too much. We are bombarded by expletives on the internet, in film, music, television, literature (and some sub-par “journalism” outlets). It has corrupted the youth and rooted itself deep into modern popular culture. Profanity has taken control of us and invaded …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grumpy Bastard’s Elections</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-grumpy-bastard-s-elections/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-grumpy-bastard-s-elections/</guid>
        <description>I’m unsure how many of you are aware of this but apparently voting in the student elections opens at 12 am today. A keen follower of student politics myself, I am excited to find out just who my representatives to the Union are going to be. Despite several years watching every single team of sabbs …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fashion is not a real thing</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-fashion-is-not-a-real-thing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-fashion-is-not-a-real-thing/</guid>
        <description>I deeply despise fashion. Whether it’s the pretentious designers selling a branded brick for a tonne of money, or the gormless idiots that buy it, everything in the fashion world is designed to piss me off. Apparently, however, it is one of the things many people at Imperial enjoy and have a serious …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grumpy Bastard on Imperial Ethics</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-grumpy-bastard-on-imperial-ethics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-grumpy-bastard-on-imperial-ethics/</guid>
        <description>This week I’ve been unfortunate enough to be in the middle of Remembrance Day. In between the white and red poppy virtue signalling as hard as they possibly can. People are too busy trying to work out which wars are the right ones to remember and which ones should be ignored as immoral foreign …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grumpy Bastard on the Royals</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-grumpy-bastard-on-the-royals/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-grumpy-bastard-on-the-royals/</guid>
        <description>Someone once told me that bad news come in threes. That person, like all people, was almost definitely wrong: there is no limit on the number of bad things that can happen at once. As an example, this week featured an announcement that the Brexit negotiations will be extended, that a Saudi …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cull this rampant enthusiasm</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-cull-this-rampant-enthusiasm/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-cull-this-rampant-enthusiasm/</guid>
        <description>Welcome back to Imperial, I hope you’ve had a lovely summer and that you’re totally prepared for the year that lies ahead. However well prepared you think you are now, you definitely aren’t. There will come a time at some point this year when you experience that feeling as your brain exits through …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grumpy Bastard Welcomes you to Imperial</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-grumpy-bastard-welcomes-you-to-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-grumpy-bastard-welcomes-you-to-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to Imperial College London. I hope you understand that when pronounced correctly, those words sound “you’re not smart anymore,” or whatever “you’re not smart anymore” is in the language of your choice. We are, after all a hugely diverse community of individuals from countries all over the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grumpy Bastard and the World Cup</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-grumpy-bastard-and-the-world-cup/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-grumpy-bastard-and-the-world-cup/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the end of the year. Whether it’s your first, second, third, or even fourth year at this fine institution, I’m sure you have all arrived in the same manner: bedraggled, exhausted, and with the eyes of a survivor of an artillery barrage on the Western Font. For those of you still here …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grumpy Bastard on Love Island: a sexually-charged narcissist’s paradise</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-grumpy-bastard-on-love-island-a-sexually-charged-narcissist-s-paradise/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-grumpy-bastard-on-love-island-a-sexually-charged-narcissist-s-paradise/</guid>
        <description>Thank Jean-Claude Juncker, the exam season is nearly over. To those of you who have finished exams, may I extend my congratulations; and to those that have not, I shall laugh pityingly whilst sipping a scotch. May your efforts extend to barely attaining a pass this year.
I think that there are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Graduation is a waste of money, and we’re all going to die anyway</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-graduation-is-a-waste-of-money-and-we-re-all-going-to-die-anyway/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-graduation-is-a-waste-of-money-and-we-re-all-going-to-die-anyway/</guid>
        <description>This week all of the gormless morons who managed to make it through the whole of an Imperial postgraduate course graduated. As I looked through the crowd of students desperately navigating their parents and loved ones to the ceremony, to be seated nowhere near one another, it struck me that all of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grumpy Bastard hates marathons </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-grumpy-bastard-hates-marathons/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-grumpy-bastard-hates-marathons/</guid>
        <description>It’s exam season again. I hope you’re all excited for the downs that accompany it. At the moment, the main stress for me does not come from exams, but from the fact that as of Monday we have welcomed a new scaly skinned overlord into our midst. Nearly 1500 years after a lizard was slain on the 23rd …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Huel: An ingenious solution for modern life, or the 21st­-century workhouse gruel?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-huel-an-ingenious-solution-for-modern-life-or-the-21st-century-workhouse-gruel/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-huel-an-ingenious-solution-for-modern-life-or-the-21st-century-workhouse-gruel/</guid>
        <description>This week I’ve been feeling Christmassy, which is to say vindictive and hateful. It’s probably due to the snow falling all over campus that everyone is endlessly posting pictures of on every form of social media they can access. No one is going to get snowed in or freeze to death, which is all the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Staff strikes and workers rights – how can we bring true equality?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-23-staff-strikes-and-workers-rights-how-can-we-bring-true-equality/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-23-staff-strikes-and-workers-rights-how-can-we-bring-true-equality/</guid>
        <description>This week, Imperial has been shoved rudely into the modern age by encountering workers’ rights, an issue that has plagued employers since the Black Death wiped out the majority of the peasants. The immediate consequence of this was that the nobles and landlords had to lighten up on the oppression …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I am fed up with adverts from authoritarian states</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-12-i-am-fed-up-with-adverts-from-authoritarian-states/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-12-i-am-fed-up-with-adverts-from-authoritarian-states/</guid>
        <description>This week, I’ve been getting some wonderful adverts on YouTube. No more adverts for Muslim singles in my area or why Grammarly is the solution to all my writing problems. I particularly miss being told that now is the best time to invest in Bitcoin or how I can make $10,000 a day with a simple trick …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grumpy Bastard on Cycling</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-grumpy-bastard-on-cycling/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-grumpy-bastard-on-cycling/</guid>
        <description>This week, I have begun to cycle more. I’m a big fan of cycling because one of my favourite people in the whole of the UK is a large advocate of it. Yes, he might break ranks in the Tory cabinet and tell outright lies, but at least his hair looks fantastic perched on top of his head, like immaculate …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grumpy Bastard hates new Black Mirror</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-grumpy-bastard-hates-new-black-mirror/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-grumpy-bastard-hates-new-black-mirror/</guid>
        <description>I watched the fourth series of Black Mirror very recently. For our American and mentally impaired readers, note the use of the word series and not season, as I am referring to a television programme and not a time of year, or an attempt to make food taste edible. Americanisms are a very frustrating …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A travesty has occured at Imperial</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-a-travesty-has-occured-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-a-travesty-has-occured-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>The vegetarians, or vegans or whatever powerful fruit- and veg-based cult that apparently runs this university has struck again. If you, like myself, are a carnivore innocently minding your own business, you will have run into the horror that is meat-free Mondays. How is it that these green-fingered …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why Macedonia is relevant again</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-why-macedonia-is-relevant-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-why-macedonia-is-relevant-again/</guid>
        <description>Macedonia as a country has a very proud and ancient history. Originally the home of the Mycenaean Greeks, after their demise, Philip of Macedon arose to kick the shit out of Athens and Sparta and then bequeathed his army to his son. Better known as Alexander the Great, he was then able to beat the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A New Year’s Resolution to stamp out joy</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-a-new-year-s-resolution-to-stamp-out-joy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-a-new-year-s-resolution-to-stamp-out-joy/</guid>
        <description>Welcome back to the first Felix of 2018. For those of you expecting anything radically different from the paper this year, prepare to be disappointed: it will continue to pump out the same trite leftist bullshit as last year as it has nearly every year since the degenerates took over the paper. In …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Our 2017 roundup: the people that made this year shit</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-our-2017-roundup-the-people-that-made-this-year-shit/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-our-2017-roundup-the-people-that-made-this-year-shit/</guid>
        <description>Once more, Felix has dragged itself to the end of the year, like the bloated, self-satisfied piece of shit it is. If you weren’t already familiar with the events of this year, then you’ll be delighted to know that the writers have come up with a whole bunch of wonderfully smug retrospectives to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Weddings are shit and the Royals are lizards</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-weddings-are-shit-and-the-royals-are-lizards/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-weddings-are-shit-and-the-royals-are-lizards/</guid>
        <description>When I heard about the engagement of Miss Megahn Markle to Prince Harry, I was non-plussed. I have zero interest in other people’s happiness so I only noted the annoying way she spelt Megan. Extra letters are a classically pretentious way of trying to make something normal special. As a reminder to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Christmas is a really fucking awful time of year </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-christmas-is-a-really-fucking-awful-time-of-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-christmas-is-a-really-fucking-awful-time-of-year/</guid>
        <description>I hate a lot of things. Hate is a strong word, but it neatly describes how I feel about a plethora of experiences, objects and people that I endure on a daily basis. Or possibly extreme disgust. I’ve even begun discerning the different forms of hatred I feel. Gnawing, aching hatred at things you …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
