<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mtm10/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mtm10/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>College launches library redevelopment
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-12-college-launches-library-redevelopment/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 17:59:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-12-college-launches-library-redevelopment/</guid>
        <description>The College has announced plans for a major redevelopment of the Central Library. The project is scheduled to begin in a few weeks and is set to finish in late 2015, with work taking place mainly this summer and next summer to minimise disruption to students.
The plans have been informed by the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Authors To Look Out For
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-12-authors-to-look-out-for/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 13:27:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-12-authors-to-look-out-for/</guid>
        <description> Bolesław Prus Those who have read my previous articles for the Books Section already know of my love for the works of Bolesław Prus. Even in his native Poland he is not a particularly popular author, often obscured by his more popular, and populist, contemporary, Henryk Sienkiewicz. I, however, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College holds North Acton Consultation with students
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-6-college-holds-north-acton-consultation-with-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 02:36:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-6-college-holds-north-acton-consultation-with-students/</guid>
        <description>A consultation meeting concerning the new Imperial hall of residence was held last Wednesday. The plans for the hall, currently called One Victoria Road and located in North Acton, some five miles away from the South Kensington Campus, were first announced early last year. The outer shells of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bad blood Between Marsden and Brompton
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-16-bad-blood-between-marsden-and-brompton/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 01:40:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-16-bad-blood-between-marsden-and-brompton/</guid>
        <description>A dispute has broken out between Chelsea’s famous Royal Brompton and Royal Marsden hospitals. Late last year the Royal Brompton, a specialist heart and lung centre which collaborates on much of its research with Imperial College, publicly announced plans to sell off its Fulham Road building in order …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Summer Reading Picks
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-summer-reading-picks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 01:43:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-summer-reading-picks/</guid>
        <description>Hitchhiker’s Guide to the Galaxy
Douglas Adams
Douglas Adams’ famous humour series has appeared in many formats – a radio show, a TV series, a film. The books, however, remain many people’s favourite. The story follows everyman Arthur Dent, who is rescued from the demolition of the planet Earth in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Dying Earth
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-the-dying-earth/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 13:28:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-the-dying-earth/</guid>
        <description>Though I fancy myself reasonably well read in the field of science fiction and fantasy I must admit that there are quite a few classic authors of the genre whose work I haven’t read at all. Of these the one I probably felt most guilty about not checking out was Jack Vance. After all, he was a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Student Success in Cyber Security Challenge
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-21-imperial-student-success-in-cyber-security-challenge/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 02:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-21-imperial-student-success-in-cyber-security-challenge/</guid>
        <description>A first year Imperial computing student has taken the second place prize at this year’s Cyber Security Challenge. Luke Granger-Brown was one of 42 finalists taking part in the final round of the competition – the Cyber Security Masterclass, this year taking place in the old Cabinet War Rooms. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hipster House of Cards you won’t find on Netflix
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-hipster-house-of-cards-you-wont-find-on-netflix/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 05:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-hipster-house-of-cards-you-wont-find-on-netflix/</guid>
        <description>Few people could have escaped the popularity of the Netflix political drama series House of Cards. However, the US show is actually a remake of a 1990s British TV miniseries of the same name. While I have heard wonderful things about the remake I have always had somewhat of a fondness for British …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ancillary Justice
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-ancillary-justice/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 05:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-ancillary-justice/</guid>
        <description>Ancillary Justice, the debut novel of Ann Leckie, is one of those novels that had been recommended to me by pretty much everyone. However, as is often the case, my other commitments, and my impressively long reading list, made me put off picking up for quite a while. Now, having finally read it, I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Student mines Dogecoins
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-imperial-student-mines-dogecoins/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 04:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-imperial-student-mines-dogecoins/</guid>
        <description>An Imperial student used College computers to mine 30,000 Dogecoins. The Dogecoin, which was first introduced three months ago and is inspired by the popular Doge meme, is one of a number of cryptocurrencies set up following the spectacular success of Bitcoin. Such cryptocurrencies are not …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Healthcare NHS Trust appoints new chief executive
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-28-imperial-healthcare-nhs-trust-appoints-new-chief-executive/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 07:11:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-28-imperial-healthcare-nhs-trust-appoints-new-chief-executive/</guid>
        <description>The Imperial College Healthcare Trust, which runs five London hospitals including St Mary’s and Charing Cross. has announced the appointment of a new Chief Executive. High profile Australian healthcare administrator Dr Tracey Batten will take up the position at the start of April. This follows the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Star Cops: A sci-fi golden oldie
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-26-star-cops-a-sci-fi-golden-oldie/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 12:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-26-star-cops-a-sci-fi-golden-oldie/</guid>
        <description>First let me say – no, it’s not as bad as its name suggests. In fact it’s nothing like its name suggest. The show itself jokes about how bad a name it is in its very first episode. Star Cops is not some cheap police action-drama carelessly transplanted into a space setting. Instead, it is a very …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NekNominations - a fifth reported fatality
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-neknominations-a-fifth-reported-fatality/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 02:50:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-neknominations-a-fifth-reported-fatality/</guid>
        <description>A fifth person has been reported as having died after taking part in NekNomination online drinking game. Twenty year old Nottingham resident Bradley Eames posted a video of himself downing two pints of gin to Facebook. He died a few days, reportedly from alcohol poisoning, though police have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science Fiction and Fantasy Convention returns to Imperial on February 22
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-14-science-fiction-and-fantasy-convention-returns-to-imperial-on-february-22/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 05:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-14-science-fiction-and-fantasy-convention-returns-to-imperial-on-february-22/</guid>
        <description>The College is preparing to host top SF and fantasy writers at its annual convention, Picocon. This year award winning authors Sarah Pinborough and Charles Stross will also be joined by Imperial’s Professor David Southwood – Chair of the Royal Astronomical Society and patron of the SF Foundation. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cable and Willetts announce further cuts to English Higher Education Funding
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-14-cable-and-willetts-announce-further-cuts-to-english-higher-education-funding/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 05:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-14-cable-and-willetts-announce-further-cuts-to-english-higher-education-funding/</guid>
        <description>The government has announced that it will be cutting £946 million from its annual grant to English Higher Education Institutions. In the latest its grant letter to the Higher Education Funding Council for England (HEFCE) the Department for Business, Innovation &amp;amp; Skills announced that its final …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College publishes animal research action plan in responce to cruelty allegations
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-imperial-college-publishes-animal-research-action-plan-in-responce-to-cruelty-allegations/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 05:01:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-imperial-college-publishes-animal-research-action-plan-in-responce-to-cruelty-allegations/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College has published a new “Action plan for world class animal research”. This follows allegations made last April by the British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV) that the College was involved in unethical animal research. This led to College setting up an independent …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Graduating students leave thousands of pounds on print service
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-graduating-students-leave-thousands-of-pounds-on-print-service/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 04:58:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-graduating-students-leave-thousands-of-pounds-on-print-service/</guid>
        <description>A freedom of information request to Imperial College has revealed that undergraduate and taught postgraduate students graduating from Imperial College left over £13,465.09 of unused printer credit on the College’s system at the end of the 2012&amp;frasl;2013 academic year. This is significantly more …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gas leak fears in Royal College of Science building
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-gas-leak-fears-in-royal-college-of-science-building/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 04:56:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-gas-leak-fears-in-royal-college-of-science-building/</guid>
        <description>The Chemistry Department’s Royal College of Science building was closed for a short time last week as a result of a suspected gas leak. On the evening of Monday, January 22 all Chemistry staff and students were sent an email saying that the building would be closed until next morning as a result of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Neil Gaiman’s Sandman
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-neil-gaimans-sandman/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 04:50:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-neil-gaimans-sandman/</guid>
        <description>Comic books and graphic novels have a, not entirely undeserved, reputation for not being the finest example of modern literature. Poor plotting, tired characters and woeful dialogue still continue to plague the medium. However, there have always been a small number of creators – such as Alan Moore, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial academics on list of top UK practising scientists
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-imperial-academics-on-list-of-top-uk-practising-scientists/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 17:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-imperial-academics-on-list-of-top-uk-practising-scientists/</guid>
        <description>Two Imperial College researchers have been placed on list of 100 top practising scientists compiled by the Science Council. Professor Michelle Dougherty and Dr Ahmer Wadee join other well known scientists on the list, including Lord Martin Reese, Sir Paul Nurse and Dame Jocelyn Bell Burnell. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Car crash driver admits causing death of Imperial researcher
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-car-crash-driver-admits-causing-death-of-imperial-researcher/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 17:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-car-crash-driver-admits-causing-death-of-imperial-researcher/</guid>
        <description>An Australian man has admitted causing the death of two men, one of whom was the Imperial College researcher Dr Sean Barrett, by dangerous driving.
Dr Barrett, 36, had travelled to the West Australian city of Perth on October 16 2012 to attend a quantum physics conference but was in the country for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to Night Vale
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-welcome-to-night-vale/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-welcome-to-night-vale/</guid>
        <description>How to write a review of something whose own creator describes as “weird and impossible to describe”? At its simplest, Welcome to Night Vale, produced by Commonplace Books, is a fortnightly audio podcast in the format of a radio news broadcast from the fictional American desert town of Night Vale. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union Concert Hall refurbished with £220,000 grant
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-union-concert-hall-refurbished-with-220000-grant/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 09:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-union-concert-hall-refurbished-with-220000-grant/</guid>
        <description>Plans have been announced for a major refurbishment of the Imperial College Union Concert Hall, to be funded by a grant from the Harlington Trust. The space is currently used by a number of different groups, including the Drama, Musical Theatre and Cinema societies. The refurbishment is aimed at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>US Energy Secretary visits Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-us-energy-secretary-visits-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 09:36:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-us-energy-secretary-visits-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College was visited last week by US Energy Secretary Ernest Moniz. In a talk on Friday, January 17, at the Grantham Institute for Climate Change Dr Moniz outlined the US government’s current energy policy and its plans for achieving a low carbon future.
He was keen to stress that his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Free Books and Other Events from Sci-Fi Soc
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-free-books-and-other-events-from-sci-fi-soc/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 04:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-free-books-and-other-events-from-sci-fi-soc/</guid>
        <description>What could be better than curling up with a good book? That’s right, curling up with a good book that you got for free! That’s why the Science Fiction, Fantasy and Gothic Horror Society is bringing back our hugely popular Book Blind Date event. Last October we found new homes for over fifty great …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The best of festive TV
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-the-best-of-festive-tv/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 04:17:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-the-best-of-festive-tv/</guid>
        <description>SHERLOCK
There must have been few shows in recent memory that were so widely anticipated as series three of Sherlock. The first two series earned themselves a legion of fans for their clever stories, impeccable characterisation and fine acting from leads Benedict Cumberbatch, playing Holmes, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Funding for poorest students threatened
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-funding-for-poorest-students-threatened/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 03:04:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-funding-for-poorest-students-threatened/</guid>
        <description>An influential higher education think-tank has accused the government of betraying its commitment to social mobility by planning to cut funds given to universities as an incentive to attract students from financially disadvantaged backgrounds. Million+, a group of 22 British universities, claims …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Minister announces new research opportunities
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-minister-announces-new-research-opportunities/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 03:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-minister-announces-new-research-opportunities/</guid>
        <description>New funding for UK research institutions has been announced by the Minister of State for Universities and Science, David Willetts. During a visit to Imperial College last Friday, Willetts announced the formation of nineteen new Centres for Doctoral Training (CDT) which will be funded through the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chortle Festival
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-chortle-festival/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 22:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-chortle-festival/</guid>
        <description>I really wasn’t sure what to expect from the Chortle Comedy Books Festival – an event hosted by the comedy news website Chortle. After all, what would such an event even entail? It turns out that I needn’t have worried. The festival was an eclectic mix of comedy shows related to books and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Stars My Destination
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-the-stars-my-destination/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 18:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-the-stars-my-destination/</guid>
        <description>Despite my extensive familiarity with science fiction I had, until very recently, had a major gap in my knowledge of the field – the works of Alfred Bester. One of the foremost writers of the late Golden Age of the genre, he has influenced later writers such as Phillip K. Dick and William Gibson, as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Firefighters Plan Another Strike
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-12-firefighters-plan-another-strike/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2013 18:38:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-12-firefighters-plan-another-strike/</guid>
        <description>Firefighters in England and Wales are due to hold a strike this Wednesday as a response to proposed changes to the pension scheme. This will be the fourth such strike this year. The government proposed changes include cutting the pensions of those firefighters who retire early for health or fitness …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chortle Festival Comes to London
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-10-chortle-festival-comes-to-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2013 21:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-10-chortle-festival-comes-to-london/</guid>
        <description>The British comedy website Chortle has announced its first comedy book festival – which will take place in Ealing at the end of this month. The festival will open with a stand up gala in Ealing Town Hall, featuring hit comedians including Richard Herring and Shappi Khorsandi. This opening event will …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Immigration Bill discussed at Union Council
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-immigration-bill-discussed-at-union-council/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 09:09:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-immigration-bill-discussed-at-union-council/</guid>
        <description>The second meeting of the Union Council was held on Tuesday, October 29. The main issue of discussion was the Union’s response to the government’s Immigration Bill 2013-2014. Proposed by Home Secretary Theresa May on October 10 the Bill had its second reading on October 22 and is expected to pass …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>British Influence approaches the Union to make a stance on UKIP
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-british-influence-approaches-the-union-to-make-a-stance-on-ukip/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 09:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-british-influence-approaches-the-union-to-make-a-stance-on-ukip/</guid>
        <description>A pro-European Union campaign group has opened itself up to potential charges of breaches of charity regulations by contacting Imperial Union to ask for help in its campaign “to stop UKIP becoming the biggest party” in the 2014 European elections. In an email to the Union President and the Campaigns …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Union Council Session of the Year
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-18-first-union-council-session-of-the-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 20:41:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-18-first-union-council-session-of-the-year/</guid>
        <description>The first meeting of the Union Council was held in the Union Dining Hall last Monday. The Council, consisting of over two dozen student representatives – including the Management Group chairs and Constituent Union presidents, is the main policy making body of the Union and is subordinate to only the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Scalzi’s Old Man’s War
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-scalzis-old-mans-war/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 00:10:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-scalzis-old-mans-war/</guid>
        <description>John Scalzi is one of the highest profile science fiction authors alive. A prolific writer, he was also President of the Science Fiction and Fantasy Writers of America, consulted on the hit TV show Stargate Universe, maintains a hugely popular blog and is an outspoken activist for many good causes. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Soho Literary Festival
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-soho-literary-festival/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 02:03:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-soho-literary-festival/</guid>
        <description> Notes from my first literary festival Rather embarrassingly for the editor of the books section, I had never before been to a literary festival. I therefore jumped at the opportunity to visit the Soho Literary Festival, a small event being held, for the third time in as many years, at the Soho …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Return of the Soho Literary Festival
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-11-return-of-the-soho-literary-festival/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2013 10:55:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-11-return-of-the-soho-literary-festival/</guid>
        <description>The Soho Literary festival is to return for its third year at the Soho Theatre. Taking place at the end of this month (September 26-29) the festival is organised by _The Oldie _magazine, a publication well known for its regular literary lunches. With over thirty different events there is guaranteed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Health Centre confusion
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-health-centre-confusion/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 23:42:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-health-centre-confusion/</guid>
        <description>Angry responses have continued to pour in concerning the decision by the Imperial College Health Centre to stop treating Imperial postgraduates who live outside of the Centre’s catchment area. The Health Centre only receives money from the NHS to register patients living within this area but …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Report raises concerns over educational access
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-report-raises-concerns-over-educational-access/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 23:22:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-report-raises-concerns-over-educational-access/</guid>
        <description>A recent joint report from the Office for Fair Access (OFFA) and the Higher Education Funding Council for England (HEFCE) has raised concerns about the efforts made by elite English universities to increase numbers of students from low income backgrounds. The report, focusing on the 2011-2012 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>GPNAY – Union Council unanimously opposes the GPA
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-gpnay-union-council-unanimously-opposes-the-gpa/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 23:07:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-gpnay-union-council-unanimously-opposes-the-gpa/</guid>
        <description>The Union Council this week unanimously passed a paper opposing plans by a number of UK universities to replace the current system of degree classification with US style grade point averages (GPA). The group of twelve universities – including King’s College London and UCL, but not Imperial – first …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Death of an icon – Iain Banks
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-death-of-an-icon-iain-banks/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 22:33:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-death-of-an-icon-iain-banks/</guid>
        <description>Noted author Iain Banks has died aged 59. In a message released on Sunday, June 9, his wife said: “Iain died in the early hours this morning. His death was calm and without pain.”
Born in 1954 Banks first rose to prominence in 1984 with the publication of his debut novel The Wasp Factory. Following …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Space Merchants
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-the-space-merchants/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 22:32:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-the-space-merchants/</guid>
        <description>There is often a stigma attached to early works of science fiction (SF). They are often stereotyped as being poorly written and filled with bad science and bug-eyed monsters. While true for some works this is by no means universally the case. Early SF laid the groundwork for what the genre is today …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Re-mark for the grading system?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-6-re-mark-for-the-grading-system/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 15:45:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-6-re-mark-for-the-grading-system/</guid>
        <description>The Union is considering its response to plans by certain members of the Russell Group of elite universities to replace the current degree classification system with a US style grade point average (GPA). The system would involve students being assigned one of 14 letter grades, running from F- to A+, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let’s Talk About Homestuck
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-5-lets-talk-about-homestuck/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 11:23:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-5-lets-talk-about-homestuck/</guid>
        <description>I am an avid follower of many webcomics – both of those with standalone strips and those with longer running storylines. I have, however, found that for the most part, apart from the means of distribution, they don’t differ all that much from their print counterparts. Despite the many creators out …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Summer Short Reads
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-7-summer-short-reads/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2013 19:21:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-7-summer-short-reads/</guid>
        <description>Solaris Rising
Ian Whates (ed.)
Rebelion Publishing
£7.99
The 2011 anthology Solaris Rising was one of the finest collections of SF in recent years and a welcome return to the anthology game by the the Solaris imprint of Rebellion Publishing. Fans of the book will therefore be pleased to hear that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your Easter Reading
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-your-easter-reading/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 01:38:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-your-easter-reading/</guid>
        <description>The City and the City
China Miéville
 One of Miéville’s more recent works follows Inspector Tyador Borlu as he investigates a murder in the city of Beszel. Eventually his investigation leads him to Ul Qoma – a separate city that somehow occupies the same site as Beszel. This is a highly acclaimed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Controversial new imprints launched
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-controversial-new-imprints-launched/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 01:32:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-controversial-new-imprints-launched/</guid>
        <description>Random House, one of the ‘big six’ English language publishers, has launched a set of new digital-only imprints. Hydra will publish science fiction, fantasy and horror; Alibi will publish mystery fiction; Loveswept will publish romantic fiction; and Flirt will focus on “New Adult” work.
The terms of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your chance to meet the publishers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-your-chance-to-meet-the-publishers/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 23:57:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-your-chance-to-meet-the-publishers/</guid>
        <description>The Booksellers Association will be hosting its annual Academic, Professional and Specialist Bookselling (APS) Group Conference at the Old Ship Hotel, Brighton on March 13-14. The Association represents the interests of some 95% of British bookshops and its conference is aimed at helping academic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial students pay more to rent rooms in Parson’s House
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-imperial-students-pay-more-to-rent-rooms-in-parsons-house/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 01:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-imperial-students-pay-more-to-rent-rooms-in-parsons-house/</guid>
        <description>Concerns have been raised about potentially excessive rents at one of Imperial’s hall of residence. Imperial College rents the first three levels of Parsons House, located on the grounds of Charing Cross Hospital, from housing company A2 Dominion and then rents out individual rooms to students for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Richard Morgan’s Altered Carbon
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-28-richard-morgans-altered-carbon/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 18:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-28-richard-morgans-altered-carbon/</guid>
        <description>I had heard a lot of good things about Richard Morgan, but a glance through the blurbs of his novels didn’t turn up anything that I thought I would particularly enjoy. However, upon reading that Altered Carbon, his first book, had been voted as the fifth best SF novel of the twenty first century by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Anger over new halls
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-21-anger-over-new-halls/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 23:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-21-anger-over-new-halls/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London is planning to build a large hall of residence in North Acton that will potentially replace halls that are cheaper and located far closer to the South Kensington Campus. The North Acton Halls could be used as a replacement for Garden Halls and the halls in Evelyn Gardens, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Banned from UCL Union
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-8-banned-from-ucl-union/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 01:24:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-8-banned-from-ucl-union/</guid>
        <description>Imperial students were banned from the University College London Union (UCLU) following accusations of criminal damage and theft by Medics RAG during their Circle Line Pub Crawl.
The ban came to light on Saturday 2 February when a group of Imperial students were turned away from the UCLU, located on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A look at Doctor Who Fandom
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-a-look-at-doctor-who-fandom/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 00:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-a-look-at-doctor-who-fandom/</guid>
        <description>I have had, shall we say, an unsteady relation with Doctor Who. While occasionally brilliant far more often it is painfully frustrating or just plain disappointing. Whatever my personal views on the show, however, I have to admit that, over its extraordinarily long run, it has been both hugely …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Translation Unit under threat
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-translation-unit-under-threat/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2013 01:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-translation-unit-under-threat/</guid>
        <description>The Imperial College Management Board has announced the proposed closure of the College’s Translation Studies Unit (TSU). Founded in 2001 to provide teaching for the College’s new MSc in Scientific, Technical and Medical Translation, the only such degree in the country, it now oversees the studies …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Our pick of 2013
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-our-pick-of-2013/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 23:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-our-pick-of-2013/</guid>
        <description>The Ocean at the End of the Lane Neil Gaiman Released June 18
After eight long years genre favourite Neil Gaiman is finally set to return to adult fiction with The Ocean at the End of the Lane. Gaiman has been relatively quiet about this book but, as with his previous work, you should expect a well …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In the kingdom of the blind...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-in-the-kingdom-of-the-blind/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 22:55:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-in-the-kingdom-of-the-blind/</guid>
        <description>I don’t read much modern literary fiction so José Saramago’s Blindness is not something that I would usually pick up. I am, however, always looking to expand my horizons and so, having heard good things about the book, I decided to give it a go.
Set at an unspecified time in an unspecified country …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Inside the Centre
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-inside-the-centre/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 00:43:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-inside-the-centre/</guid>
        <description>Ray Monk has long been highly regarded as a skilled biographer. A philosopher himself, his 1991 biography of Wittgenstein won him the John Llewellyn Rhys Prize. In his latest work, however, Monk has chosen to explore the life of one of America’s most controversial scientists – Robert Oppenheimer. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Engineers left frustrated over exchange
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-17-engineers-left-frustrated-over-exchange/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 23:49:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-17-engineers-left-frustrated-over-exchange/</guid>
        <description>A foreign exchange scheme that, in previous years, had often allowed a student from each department in the Faculty of Engineering to study for a year at the University of California has this year drastically reduced its places. As a result of a decrease in the number of students at the University of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dr Who is coming to town
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-dr-who-is-coming-to-town/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 22:59:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-dr-who-is-coming-to-town/</guid>
        <description>Doctor Who is a contentious show. It is praised by some critics for its great imagination and the influence it has had on other SF programming. Others claim that it has never really gone beyond its original concept as a ‘family show’ – a term seen by many as a euphemism for ‘children’s programme’. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Journey to Earth’s Distant Future
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-a-journey-to-earths-distant-future/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 22:42:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-a-journey-to-earths-distant-future/</guid>
        <description>The Book of the New Sun is universally acclaimed as a speculative fiction classic, with its author, Gene Wolfe, having been recently awarded the title of Grand Master of the genre. However, seeing how it comes in at 1200 pages, I have never really had the time to read it. Finding myself with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Massive building project underway
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-massive-building-project-underway/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 00:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-massive-building-project-underway/</guid>
        <description>Any keen eyed students who were at Imperial last year will definitely notice the differences around campus, specifically the Mechanical Engineering Building. This is not a simple recladding to revamp the building’s look. It is in fact part of a major redevelopment of building on the South Kensington …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An international response
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-an-international-response/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 00:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-an-international-response/</guid>
        <description>Concerns have been raised about the high fees that Imperial charges international students. The average (excluding medicine) yearly undergraduate international fee is over £24,000. This is greater than most UK other UK universities – UCL charges £18,500 a year for laboratory based subjects while …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Return of the Classics
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-return-of-the-classics/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 23:07:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-return-of-the-classics/</guid>
        <description>Despite of, or perhaps because of, classics being so heavily emphasised in secondary education and being beloved of critics they are certainly not the most liked of books of ordinary people. They are often considered dry, irrelevant or just plain boring.
Some of my favourite books, however, are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A trip around America
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-a-trip-around-america/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 21:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-a-trip-around-america/</guid>
        <description>You can’t call yourself a fan of speculative fiction if you’ve never heard of Neil Gaiman. He has made a name for himself with his prolific writing, not only with novels but also for the screen and in comic books. Yet until recently I had never read any of his longer works. Wanting to remedy the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Lathe of Heaven
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-the-lathe-of-heaven/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 13:20:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-the-lathe-of-heaven/</guid>
        <description>There are few SF and fantasy authors who have won as many awards as Ursula Le Guin. For over 40 years she has been well known for writing thought provoking, intelligent stories and she is fast becoming one of my favourite authors. Having thoroughly enjoyed reading her Earthsea series of novels last …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial physicist dies in Perth
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-8-imperial-physicist-dies-in-perth/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2012 23:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-8-imperial-physicist-dies-in-perth/</guid>
        <description>An Imperial College physicist was killed in a car crash in Austalia in the early hours of 19 October 2012. Dr Sean Barrett, a Royal Society University Research Fellow and a member of the Controlled Quantum Dynamics Group, had been in the country for less than an hour when the taxi he was in was hit …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Uni applications fall
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-uni-applications-fall/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 23:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-uni-applications-fall/</guid>
        <description>Figures released by UCAS (Universities and Colleges Admissions Service) over the summer show that almost 44,000 less home students applied to study at UK universities for 2012 entry than did for 2011 entry, representing a drop of 8.7%. UCAS analysis suggests that, accounting for changes in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Moby Dick Big Read
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-moby-dick-big-read/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 02:45:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-moby-dick-big-read/</guid>
        <description>In the 160 years since its first publication, Moby Dick has become one of the most acclaimed novels in the English language. However, while most people have heard of the book and its most famous characters, few have actually read it. Now, however, artist Angela Cockayne and writer Philip Hoare, both …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Arthur Charles Clarke
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-arthur-charles-clarke/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 02:44:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-arthur-charles-clarke/</guid>
        <description>It’s no secret that Arthur C Clarke is one of my favourite authors of all time. Born in 1917 he is often considered, alongside Isaac Asimov and Robert Heinlein, as one of the Big Three authors of Golden Age science fiction.
He had a brilliant imagination yet always constrained himself to the realms …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Suffer from hayfever? A solution may be at hand...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-22-suffer-from-hayfever-a-solution-may-be-at-hand/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 12:18:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jacob Ward,Philippa M Skett,Annina M Sartor,Maciej Matuszewski,Mimi Li,Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-22-suffer-from-hayfever-a-solution-may-be-at-hand/</guid>
        <description> What is hayfever? A little history&amp;hellip;
First scientifically described in 1819 by John Bostock, hay fever, also known as allergic rhinitis, is an allergic reaction to small particles in the air that most commonly causes nasal inflammation but may also result in watery eyes and itching throat. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New campus approved
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-new-campus-approved/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:44:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-new-campus-approved/</guid>
        <description>Further development of the new Imperial West campus in White City is set to move forward following the recent granting of planning permission by local authorities. Zoe Mulholland, programme manager for the project, said that “she can confirm that Hammersmith and Fulham Council granted permission on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gentlemen Bastards?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-gentlemen-bastards/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:10:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-gentlemen-bastards/</guid>
        <description>Having been turned on to large scale heroic sword and sorcery fantasy by Patrick Rothfuss’ excellent and much acclaimed Kingkiller Chronicles I was very eager to read Scott Lynch’s similarly highly praised Gentleman Bastard series (currently consisting of The Lies of Locke Lamora and Red Seas Under …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Time to spare — try these five great new reads
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-time-to-spare-try-these-five-great-new-reads/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 20:35:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-time-to-spare-try-these-five-great-new-reads/</guid>
        <description>The Hydrogen Sonata
Iain. M Banks
The much anticipated latest novel in Iain M. Banks epic space opera series. As with all of Banks’ work, you can expect this to be an intelligent and highly engaging read. All the Culture novels are standalone so this is a great oppertunity to get into the series. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Healthcare Trust keep records poorly
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-healthcare-trust-keep-records-poorly/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 15:50:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-healthcare-trust-keep-records-poorly/</guid>
        <description>Record keeping problems at the Imperial College Healthcare Trust — which runs five London hospitals and is the largest NHS Trust in England — have led to long delays for critically ill patients. 900 patient records were found to be incomplete while over 3500 people had to wait longer than the 18 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dr Who’s underwhelming love Song
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-dr-whos-underwhelming-love-song/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 11:30:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-dr-whos-underwhelming-love-song/</guid>
        <description>I have previously expressed my mixed views of Doctor Who on these pages. I’ve been a regular viewer since the show’s revival in 2005 and honestly I’ve found, over the years, that the show’s episodes can be split into three categories. A third are good and entertaining in their own right, a third …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Earthsea — a truly magical series
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-earthsea-a-truly-magical-series/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 11:27:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-earthsea-a-truly-magical-series/</guid>
        <description>I’m generally not a big fantasy reader but I had heard a lot of good things about Ursula Le Guinn’s Earthsea series and so had very high expectations before I started reading it. I wasn’t disappointed. Whilst featuring many standard western fantasy elements − kings, wizards and dragons − the books …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Believe the hype
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-believe-the-hype/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 11:24:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-believe-the-hype/</guid>
        <description>I very much enjoy short works of fiction. What they may lack in depth compared to longer works they often make up for in greater focus. You can read the story in one sitting and not be distracted by any filler — making it easier for you to get to the core of the issues being explored.
Dan Simmons’ …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A heartwrenching and powerful read
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-a-heartwrenching-and-powerful-read/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 16:22:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-a-heartwrenching-and-powerful-read/</guid>
        <description>I don’t usually read a lot of contemporary literary fiction but I’m always looking to broaden my horizons and so I happily picked up Emma Donoghue’s Room when it was selected by the Imperial Book Club as our latest read.
The novel is narrated in first person by Jack, a five-year-old born after his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Gormenghast Trilogy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-the-gormenghast-trilogy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 19:46:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-the-gormenghast-trilogy/</guid>
        <description>How do I describe a work like Mervyn Peake’s Gormenghast Trilogy? The series, by its very nature, seems to resist description. While often classed as fantasy, and while it is clear that Peake has been a massive inspiration to later fantasy authors like China Miéville, I tend to reject this label. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science Challenge concludes at the House of Lords
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-science-challenge-concludes-at-the-house-of-lords/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 19:34:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-science-challenge-concludes-at-the-house-of-lords/</guid>
        <description>The results of the 2012 Science Challenge were announced at a reception at the House of Lords on 22 March. The Science Challenge, run annually by Imperial’s Royal College of Science Union, invited students from the College, as well as secondary schools around the country, to answer science based …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Day changes opposed at Council
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-4-college-day-changes-opposed-at-council/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2012 01:22:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-4-college-day-changes-opposed-at-council/</guid>
        <description>The latest meeting of the Student Union Council was held this Tuesday. One of the issues which dominated the meeting were the changes to the teaching day announced by the College Management Board on the 28th of March. The board has decided to phase out the current noon to 2pm undergraduate lunch …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Alastair Reynolds’ Pushing Ice
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-alastair-reynolds-pushing-ice/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 18:42:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-alastair-reynolds-pushing-ice/</guid>
        <description>While hard SF writers such as Asimov are some of the best known names in science fiction I feel that the sub-genre has been somewhat neglected of late. There are of course, several exceptions, some of the most notable of which have to be the works of Alastair Reynolds.
While best known for his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The End of Elections
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-16-the-end-of-elections/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2012 01:41:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-16-the-end-of-elections/</guid>
        <description>Voting in the Union’s “Big Elections” opened on Monday. As well as the Sabbatical, Student Trustee and Faculty Union Executive positions students can also use the Union’s online system to vote for members of their Departmental Society committee. 186 votes were cast in the first five minutes of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>No humans were harmed in the writing of this review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-no-humans-were-harmed-in-the-writing-of-this-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 21:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-no-humans-were-harmed-in-the-writing-of-this-review/</guid>
        <description>I have somewhat of a fondness for amusing lists. They’re a quick read and perfect whether you want to you want to wind down or just procrastinate. I was therefore interested to hear of Tastes like Human, the latest book by ‘The Shark Guys’ – Noel Boivin and Christopher Lombardo.
Having written for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Handmaid&#39;s Tale
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-a-handmaids-tale/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 20:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-a-handmaids-tale/</guid>
        <description>Margaret Atwood’s The Handmaid’s Tale often appears on people’s lists of recommended novels. Unfortunately, I have a somewhat bad record at reading must-read books so I only picked it up last week. Perhaps, however, I should begin to pay more attention to such highly recommended books since The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jacek Dukaj’s Ice
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-jacek-dukajs-ice/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 20:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-jacek-dukajs-ice/</guid>
        <description>I find it rather disappointing how so few of the books available to readers in this country are written by foreign language authors. Sure, you can find translations of all the French and Russian classics in the larger bookshops but not much from other countries and certainly nothing contemporary. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Some of the best science fiction you’ll ever read
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-some-of-the-best-science-fiction-youll-ever-read/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 21:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-some-of-the-best-science-fiction-youll-ever-read/</guid>
        <description>Orson Scott Card’s Ender’s Game is widely regarded as one of the greatest classics of the science fiction genre but I didn’t get round to reading it until last summer. Having read it, I have to say that the hype was fully justified and that it is, in fact, one of the best science fiction books that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Further concerns over Holland Club and Clayponds
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-further-concerns-over-holland-club-and-clayponds/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 23:11:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-further-concerns-over-holland-club-and-clayponds/</guid>
        <description>Further student concern about the closure of Clayponds and the proposed changes to the Holland Club have been revealed at the discussion forum on postgraduate accommodation and social space held by the Graduate Students’ Association (GSA) last Thursday.
Clayponds Village in South Ealing is currently …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New research into Alzheimer’s
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-new-research-into-alzheimers/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 20:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-new-research-into-alzheimers/</guid>
        <description>Alzheimer’s disease affects almost 30 million people around the world but it remains a poorly understood condition with no cure and few effective treatments. However, recent studies by scientists at Columbia and Harvard universities provide tantalising evidence of how the disease spreads through the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A call to arms in the fight to save our libraries
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-a-call-to-arms-in-the-fight-to-save-our-libraries/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 20:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-a-call-to-arms-in-the-fight-to-save-our-libraries/</guid>
        <description>I first found out about The Library Book in a small addendum to a piece in the Guardian byLucy Mangan, one of my favourite columnists, announcing that she was one of the contributors. Investigating further, I became even more interested upon finding out that the contributors also included such …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The pick of this year’s Picocon
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-the-pick-of-this-years-picocon/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 21:24:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Savell,Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-the-pick-of-this-years-picocon/</guid>
        <description> _Keeping it Real _by Justina Robson With a title like _Keeping it Real _and a cover illustration of a semi-cyborg super woman you might be forgiven for assuming the first book of Justina Robson’s _Quantum Gravity _series is the kind of escapist trash that has us all hating on Stephanie Meyer. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A moving reminder of simpler times
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-a-moving-reminder-of-simpler-times/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 21:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-a-moving-reminder-of-simpler-times/</guid>
        <description>I know what you’re thinking – surely this can’t be a review of a series of children’s stories in Felix. Well, if the television section can review My Little Pony I can review the Nicholas books. Indeed, while it can classified as children’s literature, I for one think that the main appeal of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Picocon returns to Imperial College
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-picocon-returns-to-imperial-college/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 22:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-picocon-returns-to-imperial-college/</guid>
        <description>The Science Fiction, Fantasy and Gothic Horror Society is preparing for its annual convention, Picocon, due to take place on Saturday 18 February at the Imperial College Union. Picocon has gone from strength to strength since it started in 1984 and this year’s event has all the makings of being one …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>10% cut in grant for clubs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-10-cut-in-grant-for-clubs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 00:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-10-cut-in-grant-for-clubs/</guid>
        <description>Last week the Union’s Executive Committee ruled to cut the grant available next year to the Clubs &amp;amp; Societies Board, the Representation &amp;amp; Welfare Board and the Executive itself by ten percent. The £33,820 total, the vast majority of which comes from the Clubs &amp;amp; Societies Board owing to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Kingkiller Chronicle
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-the-kingkiller-chronicle/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 20:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-the-kingkiller-chronicle/</guid>
        <description>I don’t generally read all that much fantasy, at least compared to science fiction, but I was drawn to Patrick Rothfuss’ Kingkiller Chronicle by a pair of very positive reviews in Locus and the Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction. I bought the first book in the series, The Name of the Wind, but …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Concerns over future of Humanities
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-concerns-over-future-of-humanities/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 22:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-concerns-over-future-of-humanities/</guid>
        <description>Concerns have been raised about the future of the Humanities department at Imperial by one of its lecturers, Didier Occhipinti. Mr Occhipinti, who teaches French at the College, was due to present a lecture to the Political Philosophy Society late last term but cancelled the event in protest of what …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Holmes like you’ve never read him before
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-holmes-like-youve-never-read-him-before/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 20:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-holmes-like-youve-never-read-him-before/</guid>
        <description>Given the latest upsurge in popularity for Sherlock Holmes, and the recent film and TV adaptations, I think that the time is right for a review of a Holmes story in this section. I’m not a huge fan of Holmes but I have read all of the stories Sir Arthur Conan Doyle wrote about him. It’s hardly a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An epic quest for truth
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-an-epic-quest-for-truth/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 20:11:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-an-epic-quest-for-truth/</guid>
        <description>Logicomix is a rather unusual book – an exploration of the early development of mathematical logic, interwoven with the profound story of the life of one of the greatest thinkers in the field – Bertrand Russell – all told in graphic novel format. A tall order for any work, but Logicomix manages it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How leaping lizards use their tails
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-how-leaping-lizards-use-their-tails/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 20:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-how-leaping-lizards-use-their-tails/</guid>
        <description>Ever since 1969, when J H Ostrom proposed that theropod dinosaurs used their tails to maintain balance during fast movement, scientists have suggested that a wide range of animals, from primates to rodents, use active motion of appendages such as arms or tails to stabilise their motion. Now a team …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
