<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/txl11/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/txl11/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>It doesn’t take much effort to vote
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-4-it-doesnt-take-much-effort-to-vote/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 16:14:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thomas Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-4-it-doesnt-take-much-effort-to-vote/</guid>
        <description>Conversations with friends around campus have reminded me that those of us keenly following the General Election are in the minority. Hardly surprising given that it’s exam season, but it doesn’t take much effort to go and vote next Thursday. What surprised me more was how people hadn’t registered, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Questions Live looks into the tough subjects
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-20-imperial-questions-live-looks-into-the-tough-subjects/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 00:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thomas Lim,Philip Kent,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-20-imperial-questions-live-looks-into-the-tough-subjects/</guid>
        <description> Last Wednesday saw the very first broadcast of Imperial Questions Live, a new current affairs debating programme asking the big questions on campus.
The show, broadcast from the brand new Media Centre in the West Basement of Beit Quad, was presented by fourth year EEE student, Thomas Lim. The panel …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Questions Live broadcasts on Wednesday
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-15-imperial-questions-live-broadcasts-on-wednesday/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2015 23:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thomas Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-15-imperial-questions-live-broadcasts-on-wednesday/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday 18th February the first Imperial Questions Live show will be broadcast. The first live show to be broadcast from the newly refurbished Media Suite which Imperial College Union redeveloped over the Summer, the show will be following a Question Time style format. Questions submitted in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Blackboard crashes during test
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-blackboard-crashes-during-test/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 00:43:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thomas Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-blackboard-crashes-during-test/</guid>
        <description>450 students were left confused and frustrated after Blackboard crashed during a Business Economics online test last Thursday. The test was scheduled to start at 18:00, and within ten minutes, students started reporting issues with their tests, such as images and formulae not loading as expected. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The darker side to student journalism
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-the-darker-side-to-student-journalism/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 20:29:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thomas Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-the-darker-side-to-student-journalism/</guid>
        <description>A recent article in _The Guardian _explored the world of student journalism, and the often strained relationship between student journalists and their Universities and Student Unions. One such story took place at Plymouth University last year, where the Editor faced thinly veiled threats from their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Office 365 roll out completes amidst technical hitches
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-office-365-roll-out-completes-amidst-technical-hitches/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 19:58:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thomas Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-office-365-roll-out-completes-amidst-technical-hitches/</guid>
        <description>A scheme which will move all undergraduate email accounts from the College’s data centre to Microsoft Office 365 will conclude today. On completion, every Undergraduate’s mailbox will be hosted in a Microsoft data centre, as part of their Office 365 product. The move promises a range of benefits, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Food outlet &#39;Fusion 54&#39; opens on Campus
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-17-food-outlet-fusion-54-opens-on-campus/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 14:44:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thomas Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-17-food-outlet-fusion-54-opens-on-campus/</guid>
        <description>On Monday, Fusion 54, a new food outlet opened its doors on the Sherfield Walkway.
Unlike all other food outlets within the campus, it is run privately and not affiliated with Taste Imperial or Imperial College Union. Members of the Imperial community will be familiar with its owners; the Bhasin …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students left in the dark over cuts to amenities funds
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-17-students-left-in-the-dark-over-cuts-to-amenities-funds/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 14:28:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,Thomas Lim,Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-17-students-left-in-the-dark-over-cuts-to-amenities-funds/</guid>
        <description>College has slashed the Amenity funds for Halls of Residence by a quarter of a million– a move that has sparked fury amongst Hall Seniors and Wardens throughout the first few weeks of term.
The amount allocated to all halls this year was just over £150,000, down from approximately £373,000 in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Seedcamp announce winners of SeedHack 4.0
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-seedcamp-announce-winners-of-seedhack-40/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 02:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thomas Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-seedcamp-announce-winners-of-seedhack-40/</guid>
        <description>Seedcamp is known as ‘the Harvard of Startup Accelerators’, and widely regarded as the top Accelerator in Europe. On top of their regular activities, they also run Seedhack a hackathon (where coders, designers and other startup-y types get together and ‘hack’ cool products together over a weekend). …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Food Co-op launching at Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-1-food-co-op-launching-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 18:21:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thomas Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-1-food-co-op-launching-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Imperial’s first food co-operative is starting next week! If you are looking for affordable food that benefits the producers and the planet then look no further! The aim of the co-op is to provide the Imperial College community with a one-stop shop for ethically sourced goods. We all know, and …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
