<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Review on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/tags/review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Review on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/tags/review/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Gandhi opera Satyagraha returns to London</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-gandhi-opera-satyagraha-returns-to-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anmol Patel,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-gandhi-opera-satyagraha-returns-to-london/</guid>
        <description>This year brings with it the highly anticipated third revival of Philip Glass’s iconic Satyagraha, an epic opera based on Mahatma Gandhi’s memoir My Experiments with Truth. Since its UK première 11 years ago, which broke box office records for 20th century opera, Satyagraha, which follows the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Amazing grace: John thrills at the National Theatre</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-amazing-grace-john-thrills-at-the-national-theatre/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-amazing-grace-john-thrills-at-the-national-theatre/</guid>
        <description>We are introduced to Pulitzer-winning playwright Annie Baker’s new play, John, by Mertis. Playing the aging proprietor of an Gettysburg bed &amp;amp; breakfast, Marylouise Burke, whose sense of comedic timing is impeccable, draws back the red velvet stage curtains with slow arthritic movements. In a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dance and acrobatics save the plot in this immersive Underworld</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-dance-and-acrobatics-save-the-plot-in-this-immersive-underworld/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-dance-and-acrobatics-save-the-plot-in-this-immersive-underworld/</guid>
        <description>Becoming Shades is one of several shows headlining VAULT Festival 2018. Billed as London’s answer to Edinburgh Fringe this festival showcases performances from new and emerging artists and is a veritable hotbed of alternative theatre. From 24th January to 18th March it takes over the labyrinth of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ISIS, 4Chan, and WhatsApp: Theatre for the Lulz</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-isis-4chan-and-whatsapp-theatre-for-the-lulz/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adam Gellatly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-isis-4chan-and-whatsapp-theatre-for-the-lulz/</guid>
        <description>The Believers Are But Brothers opens at the Bush Theatre, after an award-winning run at the Edinburgh Fringe in 2017. It tells the stories of three young men who, through their encounters online, become exposed to and enveloped by the murky waters of extremism. Two of the stories follow young …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>If you could live a beautiful dream, why would you wake up to reality?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-if-you-could-live-a-beautiful-dream-why-would-you-wake-up-to-reality/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-if-you-could-live-a-beautiful-dream-why-would-you-wake-up-to-reality/</guid>
        <description>I have never enjoyed Chinese opera. Chinese opera to Chinese youth nowadays is a bit like what Shakespeare is to English-speaking youth – something confined to the realm of literary studies. And if they are popularly enjoyed, often it is only in some form of modern adaptation.
For just three nights …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Last Flag Flying: Linklater’s latest </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-last-flag-flying-linklater-s-latest/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-last-flag-flying-linklater-s-latest/</guid>
        <description>If looking back teaches us one thing, it is that the past is a strange and foreign land. If we are to ascribe to the films of Richard Linklater a mission statement, however, it would be to make that land familiar. Or rather, familiar enough.
Linklater is a director who trades in nostalgia, an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Try a Little Tenderness: The Brothers Size at the Young Vic</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-try-a-little-tenderness-the-brothers-size-at-the-young-vic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-try-a-little-tenderness-the-brothers-size-at-the-young-vic/</guid>
        <description>Plays and movies don’t often get written about young, working class, black men; in the rare instances that they are the focus, the light in which they are shown can be less than flattering. Portrayals are often one-dimensional, heavy on aggression and toxic masculinity. In this landscape of facile …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Greg Barker’s Obama doc The Final Year is an exercise in hagiography</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-greg-barker-s-obama-doc-the-final-year-is-an-exercise-in-hagiography/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-greg-barker-s-obama-doc-the-final-year-is-an-exercise-in-hagiography/</guid>
        <description>There are many terrible things about Trump’s ascension to the presidency, which – despite the cries of those who say it was an ‘inevitable’ side effect of the rise in identity politics – still comes as a shock, a full year on from his inauguration. But one aspect of his rise to power which, while …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello darkness, my old friend: First Aid Kit’s Ruins</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-hello-darkness-my-old-friend-first-aid-kit-s-ruins/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-hello-darkness-my-old-friend-first-aid-kit-s-ruins/</guid>
        <description>The sad Swedish sisters are back with their fourth album, ten songs of crooning harmony and synth. Ruins is a breakup album so pure and candid it’ll have you crying into your ice cream about heartache that hasn’t even happened yet. The work is anything but stripped back – as with any of First Aid …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ode to an ambience, straight Frahm bald Nils</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-ode-to-an-ambience-straight-frahm-bald-nils/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack O&#39;Brien,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-ode-to-an-ambience-straight-frahm-bald-nils/</guid>
        <description>Nils Frahm stands out to fans of ambient music as an electronic producer and pianist ready to fill your brain with a tantalising fusion of classical composition and electronic reverb. He is an artist who since the mid-noughties, alongside his esteemed record label Erased Tapes, has brought forth …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rita, Sue and Bob Too – an exploration of power, class, and women’s voices</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-rita-sue-and-bob-too-an-exploration-of-power-class-and-women-s-voices/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-rita-sue-and-bob-too-an-exploration-of-power-class-and-women-s-voices/</guid>
        <description>It was the play that nearly didn’t happen. After the Royal Court’s founder Max Stafford-Clark was accused of sexual misconduct, a decision was made to cancel the upcoming production of Andrea Dunbar’s 1982 play Rita, Sue and Bob Too, which centres around the relationship between a married man and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Salieri versus God : Amadeus at the National Theatre</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-salieri-versus-god-amadeus-at-the-national-theatre/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-salieri-versus-god-amadeus-at-the-national-theatre/</guid>
        <description>Why do good things happen to terrible people? Who among us has not balked at the happiness and success of someone we consider to be objectively odious, absolutely awful? In the late Peter Shaffer’s classic 1979 play, the virtuoso composer Mozart’s very name – ‘Amadeus’, “beloved by God” – is an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Today’s Empires, Tomorrow’s Ashes is still relevant</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-today-s-empires-tomorrow-s-ashes-is-still-relevant/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-today-s-empires-tomorrow-s-ashes-is-still-relevant/</guid>
        <description>Margaret Thatcher famously referred to herself as practicing “conviction politics” in the months before her 1979 rise to the office of Prime Minister. She holds no candle to Winnipeg-based thrash-punk band Propagandhi, an all-vegan band so dedicated to environmentalism that they organize tours to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pandering to the collective</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-pandering-to-the-collective/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Suraj G,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-pandering-to-the-collective/</guid>
        <description>Panda Bear, born Noah Lennox, has become a prevalent figure within the indie music community. A purveyor of genres, Lennox and his artistic counterpart Avey Tare (Michael Portner) have created some of the wildest and most original compositions from the mysterious space they seem to occupy in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Blood and guts (and laughter) in ancient Rome</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-blood-and-guts-and-laughter-in-ancient-rome/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sandra Engardt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-blood-and-guts-and-laughter-in-ancient-rome/</guid>
        <description>Titus Andronicus, one of Shakespeare’s Roman plays, has this fall reached the London stage at the Barbican. It is the story of the fictive Roman general Titus Andronicus, who returns to Rome after having entrapped Tamora, Queen of the Goths, and her three sons. The eldest son will soon be killed, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>No one ever really thought they were still making  music together</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-12-no-one-ever-really-thought-they-were-still-making-music-together/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Suraj G,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-12-no-one-ever-really-thought-they-were-still-making-music-together/</guid>
        <description>After the seminal In Search Of&amp;hellip;, N.E.R.D.&amp;rsquo;s offerings throughout the noughties were but a string of disappointing releases. As the collective fell off everyone’s radar, its most prominent member, Pharrell Williams, began his meteoric rise to stardom, though Chad Hugo and Williams would …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pinocchio ends up a little wooden…</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-pinocchio-ends-up-a-little-wooden/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-pinocchio-ends-up-a-little-wooden/</guid>
        <description>The National Theatre’s winter production of Pinocchio is based on the 1940 Disney film, including songs from the original. Broadly following the original, it adds in some minor changes: Gepetto, the old and lonely puppet maker, longs for a child of his own even as he creates puppets for other …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>They’ve only gone and bloody done it</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-12-they-ve-only-gone-and-bloody-done-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-12-they-ve-only-gone-and-bloody-done-it/</guid>
        <description>As avid readers of the Best Music Section On Earth TM might already be aware, The Gizz made a legendary attempt to stick five albums out last year (the fourth of which, Polygondwanaland, was reviewed herein). We awaited with baited breath to see whether Stu &amp;amp; Co would deliver their fifth - as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Twilight Zone – between fact and fiction</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-the-twilight-zone-between-fact-and-fiction/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-the-twilight-zone-between-fact-and-fiction/</guid>
        <description>Between light and shadow, science and superstition, fear and knowledge is a dimension of imagination. An area we call the Twilight Zone.”
Amidst all the Christmas shows and pantomimes filling theatres in December, the Almeida Theatre takes on this brave adaptation of the early 1960s American sci-fi …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Antony and Cleopatra review — Antony Byrne and Josette Simon have fantastic chemistry in Royal Shakespeare Company staging</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-15-antony-and-cleopatra-review-antony-byrne-and-josette-simon-have-fantastic-chemistry-in-royal-shakespeare-company-staging/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-15-antony-and-cleopatra-review-antony-byrne-and-josette-simon-have-fantastic-chemistry-in-royal-shakespeare-company-staging/</guid>
        <description>This production of Antony and Cleopatra forms part of the Royal Shakespeare Company’s Rome MMXVII season and is one of four plays being performed at the Barbican Centre this winter. It continues the story told in Julius Caesar—also being performed at the Barbican this season —Octavius Caesar, Mark …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Never the same love twice</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-never-the-same-love-twice/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-never-the-same-love-twice/</guid>
        <description>We ask a lot of short stories — they need to make the reader, or, if on the stage, the audience, feel the same peaks and troughs of emotion as a lengthier work; they need to speak to us with the same profundity, take us on the same journey with far fewer resources at their disposal. Like the best …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Queens of the Stone Age flex their muscles</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-queens-of-the-stone-age-flex-their-muscles/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Freeman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-queens-of-the-stone-age-flex-their-muscles/</guid>
        <description>These people want you to be calm, but I don’t want you to be calm – I want you to take your fucking trousers off” lead singer Josh Homme’s Californian drawl crooned to the 20,000 strong crowd at the O2 Arena last Tuesday. Queens of the Stone Age, the legendary heavy rock band, embarked on the UK leg …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Alias Grace – Exploring the hidden identities of Victorian women</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-alias-grace-exploring-the-hidden-identities-of-victorian-women/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Praopan Kambhu Na Ayudhaya,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-alias-grace-exploring-the-hidden-identities-of-victorian-women/</guid>
        <description>Alias Grace is a six-part mini-series on Netflix. It is an adaptation of Margaret Atwood’s historical fiction novel about servant and convicted murderess, Grace Marks, played by Sarah Gadon. Similar to Atwood’s classic The Handmaids Tale, Alias Grace discusses the oppression of women. It is set in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cory Henry brought the funk back to London last week</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-cory-henry-brought-the-funk-back-to-london-last-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Pearson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-cory-henry-brought-the-funk-back-to-london-last-week/</guid>
        <description>Hosted at KOKO, the venue’s atmosphere was perpendicular to that of the typical Friday night. An empty smoking area and non-sticky floors paid tribute to the multi-layered theater environment as an ideal place to host a gig (though drinks prices were unfortunately the same as any regular Saturday, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>King Gizzard takes a field trip to Polygondwanaland</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-king-gizzard-takes-a-field-trip-to-polygondwanaland/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-king-gizzard-takes-a-field-trip-to-polygondwanaland/</guid>
        <description>The Gizz is back with their fourth effort of the year, and it sounds like they’ve been listening to too much Tool.
Fans of the the proggy indie hard rock outfit (like the B52s on crack) went into this year fresh off their fantastic effort Nonagon Infinity, in eager anticipation of the announced …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nai Palm lights up London with a killer solo set</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-nai-palm-lights-up-london-with-a-killer-solo-set/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Montgomerie-Corcoran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-nai-palm-lights-up-london-with-a-killer-solo-set/</guid>
        <description>For the first time London had Haitus Kyote’s lead singer, Nai Palm, at Koko to perform her own solo music in a night which defined her new direction with music. It was amazing just to see her on stage, and to finally hear her voice properly; she truly is one of the most impressive singers around …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Politics and the value of rhetoric in early Rome</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-politics-and-the-value-of-rhetoric-in-early-rome/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adam Gellatly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-politics-and-the-value-of-rhetoric-in-early-rome/</guid>
        <description>In his second longest play, Shakespeare chronicles the election to, and subsequent removal from, the position of consul – a magistrate wielding executive power – of Caius Martius Coriolanus, played here by Sope Dirisu.
Coriolanus is elected to consul by his fellow societal-elites: a war hero and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The new Taylor Swift album can’t come to the phone right now. Why? Oh, ‘cause it’s shit.</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-the-new-taylor-swift-album-can-t-come-to-the-phone-right-now-why-oh-cause-it-s-shit/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Suraj G,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-the-new-taylor-swift-album-can-t-come-to-the-phone-right-now-why-oh-cause-it-s-shit/</guid>
        <description>It’s not too long since the world was introduced to girl next door and singer-songwriter, Taylor Swift, with her guitar and her country tinged pop. Upon entering the scene, Swift instantly made massive waves in the music industry and pop culture, for better or worse, with singles like ‘You belong …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The unbearable melancholy of Bojack Horseman</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-the-unbearable-melancholy-of-bojack-horseman/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-the-unbearable-melancholy-of-bojack-horseman/</guid>
        <description>The third season of Bojack Horseman ended with the question of whether our problematic protagonist would ever be able to move on. Following the death of his co-star and on-screen daughter Sarah Lynn during their drug binge, Bojack sets off in his car, driving far away from those he has let down. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An aktual-ly good album this week</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-an-aktual-ly-good-album-this-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Suraj G,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-an-aktual-ly-good-album-this-week/</guid>
        <description>Born in Iran and raised in London, beat wizard Ashkan Kooshanejad, better known by his alias Ash Koosha, broke into the electronic scene with debut album Guud in 2015. Taking the freneticism of Flying Lotus’ signature LA beat weirdness further, it seemed to spectators that Koosha could do no wrong. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An indescribable pause: The Impressionists’ love letter to London</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-an-indescribable-pause-the-impressionists-love-letter-to-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-an-indescribable-pause-the-impressionists-love-letter-to-london/</guid>
        <description>With the news fixed on the movement of refugees in Europe, the Tate has turned to an earlier period in the continent’s history when war and political instability caused a surge of migration into London. Brexit in their crosshairs, the curators preface the new exhibition on Impressionists with the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First They Killed My Father: Angelina Jolie’s first directorial triumph</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-first-they-killed-my-father-angelina-jolie-s-first-directorial-triumph/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark Aduol,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-first-they-killed-my-father-angelina-jolie-s-first-directorial-triumph/</guid>
        <description>First They Killed My Father, subtitled A Daughter of Cambodia Remembers, tells the story of Cambodian author Loung Ung and her battle to stay alive under the brutal regime of the Khmer Rouge. Most films that deal with war often tend to hover around a particular incident during the conflict. Whether …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Weezer wheezes out another fucking travesty...</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-weezer-wheezes-out-another-fucking-travesty/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-weezer-wheezes-out-another-fucking-travesty/</guid>
        <description>Oh, Rivers. What an absolute shame, the mess you’ve ended up in. Weezer was hot shit in the ‘90s. The Blue Album spoke to a generation of individuals who felt introverted and alone. It was a dorky, confessional, energetic mess – and never once did the heart fail to shine through. Then, the story …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You can’t Trump the ALL-AMERIKKKAN BADA$$ </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-you-can-t-trump-the-all-amerikkkan-bada/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-you-can-t-trump-the-all-amerikkkan-bada/</guid>
        <description>For obvious reasons, Donald Trump’s presidency and the current hostile political climate in the US has provoked a knee-jerk response of protest and defiance from hip-hop culture. A plethora of rappers have recently adopted a more political approach through their music and 22-year-old Brooklyn rapper …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An exercise in unremitting tension and horror</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-an-exercise-in-unremitting-tension-and-horror/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-an-exercise-in-unremitting-tension-and-horror/</guid>
        <description>It seems that for Greek director Yorgos Lanthimos, who directed Dogtooth and The Alps before making his move into English-language cinema with 2015’s The Lobster, the term ‘clinical’ may be a compliment. Since his breakout feature back in 2009, Lanthimos has ploughed the same furrow, excelling in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cezanne Portraits at the National Portrait Gallery</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-c-zanne-portraits-at-the-national-portrait-gallery/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sandra Engardt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-c-zanne-portraits-at-the-national-portrait-gallery/</guid>
        <description>To be honest, I’ve never really understood the greatness of Cézanne. Another big male artist, but with an Impressionist style not as fairy-like as Monet and a technique not as cubistic as Picasso. An in between – someone who never really dedicated himself to any specific style.
Without any …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Music recommends…October</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-felix-music-recommends-october/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Lawrence,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-felix-music-recommends-october/</guid>
        <description>October has been full of fantastic releases: from synth pop to hip hop, from indie labels to industry juggernauts, from distinguished artists to new talent. Pay no mind to anyone who claims “there is no good music anymore”. At Felix we unfortunately don’t have the time to review everything good that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Future Hndrxx Tour: an enjoyable, if not all that memorable, performance</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-future-hndrxx-tour-an-enjoyable-if-not-all-that-memorable-performance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-future-hndrxx-tour-an-enjoyable-if-not-all-that-memorable-performance/</guid>
        <description>In February, Atlanta rapper Future surprised fans by releasing his eponymous fifth studio album with little advance warning. FUTURE is a seventeen-track trap offering that went straight to number one in its first week. However, although Future’s fans were satisfied, Future was not. A mere seven days …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Krept &amp; Konan abandon the London underground in their new mixtapes 7 Days and 7 Nights</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-krept-konan-abandon-the-london-underground-in-their-new-mixtapes-7-days-and-7-nights/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Montgomerie-Corcoran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-krept-konan-abandon-the-london-underground-in-their-new-mixtapes-7-days-and-7-nights/</guid>
        <description>Krept and Konan, the established rap duo from South London, put out a pair of albums two weeks ago in their first major releases since their return to the London music scene. The albums are drastically different in style: 7 Days feels more like a compilation of their attempts at different genres …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Luca Guadagnino serves us up a shimmering slice of young desire</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-luca-guadagnino-serves-us-up-a-shimmering-slice-of-young-desire/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-luca-guadagnino-serves-us-up-a-shimmering-slice-of-young-desire/</guid>
        <description>From Maggie Cheung slipping out onto the Hong Kong streets in her cheongsam, looking for some noodles to eat in In the Mood for Love, to the sparks illuminating the faces of the Danish ascetics in Babette’s Feast as they are served the meal of a lifetime, cinema and food have always been a powerful …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mindhunter – true crime binge TV</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-mindhunter-true-crime-binge-tv/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James T. Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-mindhunter-true-crime-binge-tv/</guid>
        <description>Mindhunter is a gritty 10 part Netflix crime drama set in 1977, based on John E. Douglas and Mark Olshaker’s book of the same name. Listing Charlize Theron and David Fincher among its producers, the show takes tips from both stars’ previous work, most notably the camera work and atmosphere, which …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Plunge: A clarion call to sexual liberation</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-plunge-a-clarion-call-to-sexual-liberation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-plunge-a-clarion-call-to-sexual-liberation/</guid>
        <description>In the time that has elapsed between the release of Fever Ray’s eponymous debut, and the surprise launch last week of her follow-up Plunge, much has changed. Eight years have gone by since Karin Dreijer, the musician and activist behind Fever Ray, as well as one-half of the brother-sister duo The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All the Little Lights: A Story That Needs Telling</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-all-the-little-lights-a-story-that-needs-telling/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-all-the-little-lights-a-story-that-needs-telling/</guid>
        <description>Jane Upton’s All the Little Lights looks at the world of child sexual exploitation from the perspective of the young girls who are most often its victims. It allows you to see the seemingly obvious factors at play in their lives – poverty, isolation, peer pressure – that make them vulnerable to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Like a Heartbeat Drives You Mad – short films on the dark side of love</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-like-a-heartbeat-drives-you-mad-short-films-on-the-dark-side-of-love/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Purdy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-like-a-heartbeat-drives-you-mad-short-films-on-the-dark-side-of-love/</guid>
        <description>Love can be troublesome, complex, and macabre, and Like a Heartbeat Drives You Mad offers extensive insight into this dark side of human intimacy. The series consists of ten short films shot from around the world, from Glasgow to Delhi, through which we witness an eclectic range of traumatic love …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mura Masa’s debut shows he’s one to watch</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-mura-masa-s-debut-shows-he-s-one-to-watch/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonah Beaudin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-mura-masa-s-debut-shows-he-s-one-to-watch/</guid>
        <description>Mura Masa’s self-titled debut album is a refreshing display of what our generation has to offer. The Guernsey-born DJ started making tunes from his bedroom and came onto the radar when he released his song ‘Lotus Eater’ on Soundcloud in 2014. Although he has only just turned 21 he has since …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nai Palm strikes out on her own</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-nai-palm-strikes-out-on-her-own/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Montgomerie-Corcoran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-nai-palm-strikes-out-on-her-own/</guid>
        <description>Singer, songwriter, and guitarist Nai Palm has come out with her debut solo album, Needle Paw: an intimate collection of covers and originals wrapped in rich harmonies that gives a slightly new perspective on her already established compositions, as well as introducing some new and more personal …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sally Potter’s dinner party from hell</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-sally-potter-s-dinner-party-from-hell/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lawrence Good,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-sally-potter-s-dinner-party-from-hell/</guid>
        <description>If you’d just been promoted to Shadow Minister for Health, wouldn’t you feel that a small party might be in order? Just a small get together with your nearest and dearest surely couldn’t hurt. Well, after watching The Party, it turns out you may want to reconsider.
A sharp and deeply funny chamber …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>St. John Sessions: Laurel Halo and Lee Gamble</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-st-john-sessions-laurel-halo-and-lee-gamble/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Lawrence,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-st-john-sessions-laurel-halo-and-lee-gamble/</guid>
        <description>Hyperdub is odd. It’s always been odd. But it has knitted itself so tightly into the fabric of London’s musical culture that when two of its artists play experimental sets in an 18th century church, it somehow feels perfectly natural.
I arrived at the St. John Church in Hackney to find a substantial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Hydra x Barbican present: Gas &#43; Huerco S.</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-the-hydra-x-barbican-present-gas-huerco-s/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Lawrence,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-the-hydra-x-barbican-present-gas-huerco-s/</guid>
        <description>Another night, another gig. This time at the temple of austere, brutalist beauty that is the Barbican. If you’re a fan of ambient music, this venue is a must – the sculpted wood of the concert hall reverberates with thick, earthy noise, immersing and inducing you into a trance-like state. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Lady from the Sea: An adaptation worth its salt?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-the-lady-from-the-sea-an-adaptation-worth-its-salt/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jenny Lea,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-the-lady-from-the-sea-an-adaptation-worth-its-salt/</guid>
        <description>Directed by Kwame Kwei-Armah – the British actor-cum-playwright and soon to be artistic director of the Young Vic – The Lady from the Sea tells a story of marital oppression and lost love. Calypso music plays and algae grows from the walls as Kwei-Armah relocates the play from 19th Century Norway to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An operatic nightmare of psychological trauma</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-an-operatic-nightmare-of-psychological-trauma/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-an-operatic-nightmare-of-psychological-trauma/</guid>
        <description>You Were Never Really Here
Dir: Lynne Ramsay. Script: Lynne Ramsay. Starring: Joaquin Phoenix, Ekaterina Samsonov, Judith Roberts, John Doman. 85 minutes
4.5 Stars
An unprecedented level of discussion was prompted when the line-up was announced for the Cannes Film Festival in the spring. The new …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brexit, greed, and the making of modern Britain</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-brexit-greed-and-the-making-of-modern-britain/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Waleed A El-Geresy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-brexit-greed-and-the-making-of-modern-britain/</guid>
        <description>There is more death in that kind of life and more life in that kind of death. That is the message of Saint George in reference to a life lived under the rule of the despotic dragon. On the face of things these two characters should be at the heart of an epic tale of heroism versus evil, but Rory …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chameleon Queen out in the open</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-chameleon-queen-out-in-the-open/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-chameleon-queen-out-in-the-open/</guid>
        <description>Writing a follow up to 2014’s gargantuan, Grammy-winning, self-titled album was never going to be an easy task for Annie Clark, so perhaps that’s why it took so long to do. Mind you, when you’re being hailed as the modern day Ziggy Stardust, you want to make sure you get things right. St. Vincent’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chasing intercontinental friendships</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-chasing-intercontinental-friendships/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-chasing-intercontinental-friendships/</guid>
        <description>Historically, collaborative albums have generally been reserved for ageing legends. Lou Reed &amp;amp; Metallica. Jay Z &amp;amp; Kanye. Eno &amp;amp; Byrne. Eno &amp;amp; Fripp. Eno &amp;amp; Cale. But if you haven’t got a string of successful glam albums and the invention of ambient music under your belt, these can …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>J. Cole’s 4 Your Eyez Only tour</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-j-cole-s-4-your-eyez-only-tour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-j-cole-s-4-your-eyez-only-tour/</guid>
        <description>J. Cole’s 4 Your Eyez Only tour touched down in London town early this week, with the Dreamville front man selling out two nights at the O2 Arena. Cole was supported by his labelmates Ari Lennox, EARTHGANG (whose recent Rags-EP is worth a listen and whose Robots EP drops on Friday), and J.I.D. (who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Looking for love in the lonely city</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-looking-for-love-in-the-lonely-city/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-looking-for-love-in-the-lonely-city/</guid>
        <description>Olivia Laing in her exceptional book, The Lonely City, remarks, “So much of the pain of loneliness is about concealment. But&amp;hellip;what’s so shameful about wanting?”. Loneliness, and the barriers we set up even as we try to forge new connections are at the centre of David Eldridge’s new play. In …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Slowdive prove to be worth the wait</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-slowdive-prove-to-be-worth-the-wait/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Hannah Cudmore,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-slowdive-prove-to-be-worth-the-wait/</guid>
        <description>It feels as fun, and as relevant playing together now as it did when we first started” said Slowdive’s Neil Halstead about their much-anticipated single ‘Star Roving’ upon its release in January. This was the band’s first new material in 22 years. Slowdive, a shoegaze band from Reading known for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Deep Dive into DAMN.</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-deep-dive-into-damn/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-deep-dive-into-damn/</guid>
        <description>Since dropping back-to-back classics with 2012’s good kid, m.A.A.d city (GKMC) and 2015’s To Pimp a Butterfly (TPAB), Kendrick Lamar has been relatively quiet – I would go as far as to say that we’ve had to put up with polished mediocrity in his absence. He did surprise fans with Untitled Unmastered …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sondheim’s classic Follies revived in London</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-sondheim-s-classic-follies-revived-in-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-sondheim-s-classic-follies-revived-in-london/</guid>
        <description>In Follies, the shine has rubbed off from the Weisman Theatre. The musical sees a group of retired chorus girls who once performed there gather to bid farewell to their old haunt before it is demolished. It is a love letter to the New York of old, the glamour of Broadway and the pain of reaching …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Death of Stalin: Armando Iannucci returns</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-the-death-of-stalin-armando-iannucci-returns/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-the-death-of-stalin-armando-iannucci-returns/</guid>
        <description>Scotsman Armando Iannucci is the finest political satirist of the 21st century. Through his television shows The Thick of It and it’s American adaptation Veep, he has shown a propensity for mocking politicians who ostensibly claim to have the interests of the people at heart, while actually only …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Weird music made weirder</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-weird-music-made-weirder/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Lawrence,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-weird-music-made-weirder/</guid>
        <description>Footwork is no longer confined to underground venues in the South Side of Chicago. The twisted style of house music has evolved to become a muse for electronic music producers across the globe, infecting deep into the rosters of prominent UK labels such as Hyperdub and Planet Mu. This expansion of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Marvel Universe’s small screen efforts make for forgettable television</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-marvel-universe-s-small-screen-efforts-make-for-forgettable-television/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-marvel-universe-s-small-screen-efforts-make-for-forgettable-television/</guid>
        <description>After two years and five seasons worth of episodes between the characters, Marvel’s darker and grittier street level heroes finally come together Avengers-style. However, after all the build-up and a lacklustre performance from Iron Fist, the biggest question was whether Defenders would be able to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bold, vibrant, poignant: the unrealised genius of Jean-Michel Basquiat</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-bold-vibrant-poignant-the-unrealised-genius-of-jean-michel-basquiat/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-bold-vibrant-poignant-the-unrealised-genius-of-jean-michel-basquiat/</guid>
        <description>Hailed as a ‘radiant child’, Jean-Michel Basquiat erupted onto the 1980s New York art scene in as a teenager. He was just 18 when he began to scrawl poetic graffiti on the streets of New York with one of his school friends Al Diaz as SAMO© – a contraction of ‘same old, same old shit’. When the duo …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Diverse influences make for a remarkable LP</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-diverse-influences-make-for-a-remarkable-lp/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-diverse-influences-make-for-a-remarkable-lp/</guid>
        <description>Wolf Alice is a band with a diverse set of influences. There are detectable traces of shoegaze, pop, folk, punk, grunge, and indie, to name just a few components of the musical palette brought to bear on this album.
There is never a dull minute as Ellie Roswell &amp;amp; co. leap from phrase to phrase, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mad about the boy: Jane Eyre returns to the NT</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-mad-about-the-boy-jane-eyre-returns-to-the-nt/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-mad-about-the-boy-jane-eyre-returns-to-the-nt/</guid>
        <description>Jane Eyre opens with a scream – it’s one of the moments I think most after I leave the theatre. It is at once all the things I find difficult about the performance, and what seems essential to the spirit of the original novel which is itself a howl for women’s independence and self-determination. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Off-kilter prog-funk is one for the superfans</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-off-kilter-prog-funk-is-one-for-the-superfans/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-off-kilter-prog-funk-is-one-for-the-superfans/</guid>
        <description>Bass legend Les Claypool returns with the only band to earn its own ID3 genre tag. The band is known for off-kilter prog-funk with metal roots. Trademark syncopated riffs return with newfound minimalism. This album conceptually focuses on the “desaturating seven”, a band of goblins who chase …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rhodes must fall </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-rhodes-must-fall/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lizzie E Riach,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-rhodes-must-fall/</guid>
        <description>Told through a series of compelling monologues, The Fall is a dramatisation of the real events surrounding a group of activist students studying at the University of Cape Town (UCT), several decades after apartheid. Specifically, it tells the story behind the fall of the statue of colonialist Cecil …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Royal Academy shows the links between two titans</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-royal-academy-shows-the-links-between-two-titans/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-royal-academy-shows-the-links-between-two-titans/</guid>
        <description>Salvador Dali and Marcel Duchamp are both regarded as two of the twentieth century’s most influential artists, but are often seen as polar opposites. Although their personal and professional lives have been studied extensively in literature, this exhibition at the Royal Academy is the first to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Relatively un-miraculous</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-relatively-un-miraculous/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-relatively-un-miraculous/</guid>
        <description>This psych-pop album is neither particularly psychedelic nor particularly poppy, instead preferring fairly unimaginative composition and over-reliance on production.
I mean, there’s nothing /wrong/ with it. The band members are objectively skilled musicians, who play clearly and effectively …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
