<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/qm413/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/qm413/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>E3 2017 | Follow up
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-e3-2017-follow-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 17:06:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Qasim Mahmood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-e3-2017-follow-up/</guid>
        <description>Microsoft had a few more reveals, including PlayerUnknown’s Battlegrounds, State of Decay 2, Minecraft in 4K and DragonBall FighterZ. They then proceeded to an extended look at Sea of Thieves, Rare’s open-world pirate game, which featured treasure hunting, riddle solving and a large-scale naval …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>E3 2017 | What to expect
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-e3-2017-what-to-expect/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:30:47 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Qasim Mahmood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-e3-2017-what-to-expect/</guid>
        <description>The biggest gaming event of the year is right around the corner; all the biggest gaming companies will be taking the stage to announce their plans for the upcoming year and showcase brand new games and consoles.
First up of the big three is Microsoft, and they are in the most interesting position of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gangsta riot | Yakuza 0
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-gangsta-riot-yakuza-0/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 17:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Qasim Mahmood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-gangsta-riot-yakuza-0/</guid>
        <description>The Yakuza games have always been immensely popular in Japan, so much so that their central protagonist, Kiryu Kazuma, is considered a mascot of PlayStation. However, they unfortunately have never found their footing here in the West and are largely unheard of. If, like me, you have never played a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Game Review | The Last Guardian
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-game-review-the-last-guardian/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 15:54:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Qasim Mahmood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-game-review-the-last-guardian/</guid>
        <description>This is, without a doubt, a truly phenomenal game. Created by the minds over at genDESIGN (previously Team ICO), it bears a striking resemblance to both of their previous games, Ico and Shadow of the Colossus. In Ico you played a boy guiding a helpless young girl through a castle in an attempt to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Game spotlight | Persona 5
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-game-spotlight-persona-5/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Qasim Mahmood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-game-spotlight-persona-5/</guid>
        <description>There are very few games which I have absolute faith in. I was incredibly sceptical about both Final Fantasy XV and also The Last Guardian, which was my personal Game of the Year 2016; in fact, I was almost convinced at least one of them would be a massive train wreck. Even games like Nioh and Nier: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The release of two giants
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-the-release-of-two-giants/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 16:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Qasim Mahmood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-the-release-of-two-giants/</guid>
        <description>Ten years is a very long time. Ten years ago in 2006, the Xbox 360 had been out for a year and both the Wii and PS3 were released. Call of Duty 4: Modern Warfare released the following year, thus starting the boom of first person shooters. The original iPhone didn’t even release until 2007; instead, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Do all colours look the same?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-do-all-colours-look-the-same/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 14:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Qasim Mahmood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-do-all-colours-look-the-same/</guid>
        <description>Colour is an illusion. When we look at any object, likely the first thing we notice about it is its colour. Colours are incredibly important to our understanding of the world, and we use them all the time in art, film, photography, and in science. Despite all this however, it is a fact that colours …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are you making the Switch?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-are-you-making-the-switch/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 17:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Qasim Mahmood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-are-you-making-the-switch/</guid>
        <description>The year is 2016, and the Wii U has been doing incredibly badly worldwide for a number of years. In March, Nintendo announced a partnership with a Japanese mobile provider, DeNA, to provide some of their intellectual properties on mobile platforms. While this came as a big surprise, it was the news …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
