<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/marie_jones/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/marie_jones/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>ICXCAC bring home second place from Poznań</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-icxcac-bring-home-second-place-from-pozna/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie Jones,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-icxcac-bring-home-second-place-from-pozna/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Cross Country and Athletics team won a superb silver trophy at the Economic Five Race in Poznań, Poland, on Sunday 7th April, adding to their 2019 collection of successes.
On Friday 5th April, 12 of their finest runners took an early plane to Poznań, one of Poland’s major cities. At …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bombs dropped during WWII had effects even at the “edge of space”</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-bombs-dropped-during-wwii-had-effects-even-at-the-edge-of-space/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie Jones,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-bombs-dropped-during-wwii-had-effects-even-at-the-edge-of-space/</guid>
        <description>World War II is widely known to be the most devastating and deadly war in the history of mankind. However, the study of its impacts beyond Earth is very recent and could play a major role in improving modern technologies. In a study published last month, professor of astrophysics Chris Scott and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICESat-2, NASA’s new satellite to measure the melting of ice</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-icesat-2-nasa-s-new-satellite-to-measure-the-melting-of-ice/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie Jones,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-icesat-2-nasa-s-new-satellite-to-measure-the-melting-of-ice/</guid>
        <description>On Saturday the 15th of September, NASA launched their newest laser, the ICESat-2, which stands for “Ice, Cloud and land Elevation Satellite”. In orbit 500 km above our heads, the satellite’s main mission is to measure the alarming evolution of ice melting in the poles.
Since 2009 and the end of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Could platypus milk help beat antibiotic resistance?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-could-platypus-milk-help-beat-antibiotic-resistance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie Jones,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-could-platypus-milk-help-beat-antibiotic-resistance/</guid>
        <description>In 2014, the World Health Organisation warned the international community of the threat of antibiotic resistance. Due to an excessive use of antibiotics – mostly fed to food-producing animals – bacteria are able to develop resistance, which they then transmit to the next generation of bugs, who can …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
