<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/alicepeberdy/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/alicepeberdy/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Children of Blood and Bone takes a step forward for representation, but is stuck in YA romance</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-children-of-blood-and-bone-takes-a-step-forward-for-representation-but-is-stuck-in-ya-romance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Peberdy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-children-of-blood-and-bone-takes-a-step-forward-for-representation-but-is-stuck-in-ya-romance/</guid>
        <description>Young Adult books can get a lot of bad rap. In some ways, I can see why, but then releases like Tomi Adeyemi’s debut Children of Blood and Bone make me question the stigma.
Zélie should have magical abilities, but a ruthless king destroyed magic and killed anyone with powers before she could develop …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix recommends Valentine&#39;s reads… or the books to help you to forget about romance</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-felix-recommends-valentine-s-reads-or-the-books-to-help-you-to-forget-about-romance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,Alice Peberdy,Indira Mallik,Pavan Inguva,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-felix-recommends-valentine-s-reads-or-the-books-to-help-you-to-forget-about-romance/</guid>
        <description> Written on the Body by Jeanette Winterson
 The first question is, who is the narrator? She or he is never named, and their gender never revealed. &amp;ldquo;Why is the measure of love loss?&amp;rdquo; asks the opening sentence, and throughout the book we are taken through the narrator’s clandestine …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2017 roundup: the best books of the year</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-2017-roundup-the-best-books-of-the-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Alice Peberdy,Katie Cook,Clemens Jakubec,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-2017-roundup-the-best-books-of-the-year/</guid>
        <description>What was the best thing you read this year? Four of our Books Writers give their thoughts:
Morning and Evening, by Jon Fosse
Jon Fosse to tell the story of the Norwegian fisherman Johannes in only a hundred pages. To be exact, we only learn about the two most significant events in his life: his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Tis the season to be reading</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08--tis-the-season-to-be-reading/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,Alice Peberdy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08--tis-the-season-to-be-reading/</guid>
        <description>Got a family member you need to get a last-minute gift for? Why not get them a book – at least it&amp;rsquo;s easy to wrap!
This is Going To Hurt, by Adam Kay
Have a healthcare professional among your family and friends? Even if you don’t, they are sure to enjoy this hilarious journal by ex-doctor, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hollywood has brought Atwood’s dystopia to the screen, and now into reality</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-hollywood-has-brought-atwood-s-dystopia-to-the-screen-and-now-into-reality/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Peberdy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-hollywood-has-brought-atwood-s-dystopia-to-the-screen-and-now-into-reality/</guid>
        <description>It seems the morning news is scarcely without another allegation of sexual assault these days. Harvey Weinstein has inspired many stars, mostly women, to share their stories of abuse by people with power. Finally, these hard-hitting topics may finally be discussed at a meaningful level through their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ali Smith’s Autumn is more than just a post-Brexit manifesto</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-ali-smith-s-autumn-is-more-than-just-a-post-brexit-manifesto/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Peberdy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-ali-smith-s-autumn-is-more-than-just-a-post-brexit-manifesto/</guid>
        <description>Books which lack speech marks always scare me. It can seem like they’re trying too hard just to break a rule and look contemporary. But I should never have doubted Ali Smith, in whose new book, Autumn, it feels entirely appropriate. It freed the author to skip between characters and to entwine her …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>H.G. Wells’ little-known South Ken connection</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-h-g-wells-little-known-south-ken-connection/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Peberdy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-h-g-wells-little-known-south-ken-connection/</guid>
        <description>Imagine the Imperial freshers of the past; ponder where their college career led them. Research is probably first to mind – medicine, teaching, banking… Arts? We’re scientists, not robots! Great academics are often churned out, but our university also produced one of the fathers of science fiction, …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
