<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/aymeric_regnier/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/aymeric_regnier/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>ICXCAC Success at the Brighton 10k</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-ICXCAC-success-at-Brighton-10k/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Minty Hampden-Martin,Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-ICXCAC-success-at-Brighton-10k/</guid>
        <description>On Sunday 17th November, a rowdy group of 56 of Imperial’s finest specimens woke up in the wee hours to catch their 6:36 train from London Bridge. While most would cringe at the idea of such an early wakke-up on their rest day, the ICXCAC runners all rose to the challenge and (nearly all) made it on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICXCAC go to Snowdonia for their Annual Trail Pilgrimage</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-ICXCAC-go-to-Snowdonia-for-annual-trail-pilgrimage/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-ICXCAC-go-to-Snowdonia-for-annual-trail-pilgrimage/</guid>
        <description>Many clubs and societies have their own traditions that they cherish: for some, a varsity match that they usually win, others have a sunny picnic by the beach, some have a WILD social; for Cross-Country and Athletics, the first weekend of November holds a special place in the heart of most regulars: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Members of ICXCAC Return to Parliament, and they Mean Business</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-members-icxcac-return-parliament-mean-business/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-members-icxcac-return-parliament-mean-business/</guid>
        <description>Leaves are turning brown, leaves are fallilng down, weather turns chilly and the the fields are getting muddy - it’s time for some Cross-Country.
Last year, Imperial’s Cross-Country teams absolutely dominated the field, winning the Women’s league with the Men’s team coming in second place behind the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICXCAC: A Tale of Two Summer Tours</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-icxcac-tale-two-summer-tours/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-icxcac-tale-two-summer-tours/</guid>
        <description>After a very successful year which saw the Women’s A team winning the London Universities Cross-Country League, the Women’s B team coming 3rd and the Men’s A coming in 2nd place and athletes performing extremely well individually at BUCS, the Cross-Country and Athletics Club hit the mountains twice …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hyde Park Relays returns with aplomb</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-hyde-park-relays-returns-with-aplomb/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Hart,Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-hyde-park-relays-returns-with-aplomb/</guid>
        <description>On Saturday 9th February, the much anticipated 70th annual edition of the Hyde Park Relays, hosted by Imperial College Cross Country and Athletics, smashed onto the scene.
With over 80 teams and nearly 500 participants, it was once again a roaring success for the club.
This event holds a special …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get your running shoes on, it’s the Hyde Park Relays!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-get-your-running-shoes-on-it-s-the-hyde-park-relays/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Hart,Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-get-your-running-shoes-on-it-s-the-hyde-park-relays/</guid>
        <description>The Hyde Park Relays are the largest annual student relays in the UK and have seen over 500 competitors take to the paths of the iconic Hyde Park in Central London every year since 1949 to complete 5km laps in men’s or mixed teams of 6 and women’s teams of 4. This year’s edition is set to be even …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICXC regain Bannister Cup in final LXCL of 2018</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-icxc-regain-bannister-cup-in-final-lxcl-of-2018/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-icxc-regain-bannister-cup-in-final-lxcl-of-2018/</guid>
        <description>Last Wednesday, 14th November, just two weeks after Mitcham Common’s sunny race, London’s sturdy athletes took out their spikes once more to compete in this term’s (and 2018’s) final LUCA Cross-Country League race, the much-anticipated Wimbledon Common.
With laps being longer than average at 4.7km, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>There and Back Again: A Trail Runner’s Tale from Northern Wales</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-there-and-back-again-a-trail-runner-s-tale-from-northern-wales/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-there-and-back-again-a-trail-runner-s-tale-from-northern-wales/</guid>
        <description>It seems we at ICXCAC just can’t get enough of soggy weather, lack of central heating, and world-renowned banter. And so, on Friday 2nd November, 15 of London’s finest and rowdiest decided to travel to Imperial’s infamous St Mary’s Mountain Hut in Rhyd-Ddu, Northern Wales, the international hub for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cross-Country Makes Gains at Mitcham Common</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-09-cross-country-makes-gains-at-mitcham-common/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-09-cross-country-makes-gains-at-mitcham-common/</guid>
        <description>Just two weeks after the first cross-country race of the London University’s XC League at Parliament Hill, the rowdy Imperial runners woke up on Halloween to find the sun shining and their calendars showing the highlight of their upcoming day: a lovely race at Mitcham Common.
The course is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gold and Silver for London’s finest </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-gold-and-silver-for-london-s-finest/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-gold-and-silver-for-london-s-finest/</guid>
        <description>Last Wednesday, Imperial took on the last LUCA (London Universities and Colleges Athletics) race of the cross-country season, fielding over 30 runners and finishing top of the league for the women and in 2nd place for the men.
As per usual, the club met at Beit in the early afternoon for the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>For BUCS sake!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-for-bucs-sake/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-for-bucs-sake/</guid>
        <description>Last weekend, ICXCAC took on the BUCS Cross-Country Championships, along with other universities from all around the UK. Imperial fielded a staggering 63 runners – ICXCAC’s largest BUCS team to date and the largest of all teams competing on Saturday!
The club’s members awoke early on Saturday …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICXCAC take on LUCA Indoors Championships with over 50 athletes</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-icxcac-take-on-luca-indoors-championships-with-over-50-athletes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-icxcac-take-on-luca-indoors-championships-with-over-50-athletes/</guid>
        <description>After taking on several Cross-Country races as well as the Brighton 10K, ICXCAC went on to compete at the London Universities and Colleges Athletics (LUCA) Indoors Championships on the 25th of November. As usual, the runners decided to meet up at Beit before making their way to the event. However, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Harder, better, faster, stronger</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-harder-better-faster-stronger/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-harder-better-faster-stronger/</guid>
        <description>For those of you who are only just tuning in, Imperial College’s Cross-Country and Athletics Club has been absolutely smashing their races this season, with many more events still to come. Last week, they took on the 3rd race of the London Universities and Colleges Cross-Country League, and didn’t …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The more the merrier: ICXCAC fields another huge turnout at Mitcham Common race</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-the-more-the-merrier-icxcac-fields-another-huge-turnout-at-mitcham-common-race/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-the-more-the-merrier-icxcac-fields-another-huge-turnout-at-mitcham-common-race/</guid>
        <description>As the sun rose on the first morning of November, the Cross-Country runners woke up and – looking at their alarm – saw it was already time to grab their kit for the second London Universities and Colleges (LUCA) race of the season. The race would take place at Mitcham Common in South London, just …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
