<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/csw09/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/csw09/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Venture Catalyst Challenge ‘13 &amp; ICStartup: just the start
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-1-venture-catalyst-challenge-13-icstartup-just-the-start/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 21:02:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Wood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-1-venture-catalyst-challenge-13-icstartup-just-the-start/</guid>
        <description> Have you ever looked at the entrepreneurial activities offered by universities such as Harvard (The Harvard innovation Lab), MIT ($100K Entrepreneurship Competition) and Stanford (The BASES $150K challenge) and wondered why Imperial doesn’t have more of this kind of stuff going on?
America has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Newitt would be interesting
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-newitt-would-be-interesting/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 01:18:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Wood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-newitt-would-be-interesting/</guid>
        <description> he annual Newitt Lecture, hosted by the Chemical Engineering department, was given by Edward Davey MP, Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change on Wednesday evening. This was the first time that the lecture has been given by a politician – rather than a chemical engineer – a clear signal …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A very chunky review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-a-very-chunky-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 23:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Wood,Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-a-very-chunky-review/</guid>
        <description>It definitely sounds as if it’s going to be amazing. The fudge is actually pretty nice. The problem is when you compare it to just a normal Chunky: doesn’t add so much that you think it’s revolutionary. Okay, we know that it’s not exactly supposed to be pioneering new grounds, but, still, some …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What’s the link between Jamie Oliver, London’s gyms and Divine Chocolate?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-whats-the-link-between-jamie-oliver-londons-gyms-and-divine-chocolate/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2013 02:09:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Wood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-whats-the-link-between-jamie-oliver-londons-gyms-and-divine-chocolate/</guid>
        <description> The term “social enterprise” was first coined during the late 70s. The idea is simple. A social enterprise is a business where social aims come first, and profit comes second. Yes, you read that right – social aim first, profit second. Social entrepreneurs are business minded people who are a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Internship decisons: City? ... Or Charity?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-internship-decisons-city-or-charity/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 00:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Wood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-internship-decisons-city-or-charity/</guid>
        <description> Intro Everyone wants one. Some people seem to want one more than they want their degree. And some lucky people alrealy have one. Gone are the days when Imperial students wasted their summers away in Kavos indoors watching Crystal Maze repeats, in these ‘tough times’ it’s all about the summer …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Highlight EVERYTHING
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-highlight-everything/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 22:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Wood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-highlight-everything/</guid>
        <description>This week many of you will have been camping out in the Library preparing for exams. (I feel your pain.) This is the first time in 4 years that I am not sitting exams this January (fist punch) and so instead of frantic cramming I’ve taken some time to look into some of the best, and the worst, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The London Climate Forum 2012
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-the-london-climate-forum-2012/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 02:07:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Wood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-the-london-climate-forum-2012/</guid>
        <description>The London Climate Forum is the UK’s largest student led conference on climate change and sustainability. Bringing together leading thinkers from politics, business, campaigning, media, science and engineering, it will be a chance for young people and students to find out how they can be part of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Better than the Olympics”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-better-than-the-olympics/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 20:59:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Wood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-better-than-the-olympics/</guid>
        <description>Last Friday, the game famous for ending disputes amongst friends and acquaintances worldwide arrived at Imperial. In what can only be described as probably the most eventful lunchtime of the term so far, Imperial played host to the inaugural Imperial College London Rock Paper Scissors Championship …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A tour of some of the best places in South Kensington
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-a-tour-of-some-of-the-best-places-in-south-kensington/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 11:47:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Wood,Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-a-tour-of-some-of-the-best-places-in-south-kensington/</guid>
        <description>Intro
It can be incredibly easy to end up spending all of your life just sitting in the library and only sampling JCR, SCR (if you’re lucky enough to be let in), Library Café, and, of course, all of the departmental cafés. Thing is, we happen to live around a whole load of amazing cafés. So sit …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Volunteering: why should students get involved?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-volunteering-why-should-students-get-involved/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 19:58:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Wood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-volunteering-why-should-students-get-involved/</guid>
        <description>As the academic year draws to a close, final projects are handed in, and the last few exams are sat, it’s only natural to reflect on the year gone by. Most of us have clocked up more library hours than we care to remember and spent too many nights in Metric that we wish we remembered more of. We’ve …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A French love affair
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-a-french-love-affair/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 20:36:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Wood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-a-french-love-affair/</guid>
        <description>Anyone that knows me well will know that over the past few months I have fallen hopelessly in love. Forgive me for using such a tired cliché, but it really was love at first sight. Yes, since the moment I first clasped my eyes on a Chanel handbag, I was infatuated.
I have a friend who is a designer …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gate crashing the Oxford Climate Forum
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-gate-crashing-the-oxford-climate-forum/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 23:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Wood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-gate-crashing-the-oxford-climate-forum/</guid>
        <description>Very early on Saturday morning, whilst Freshers were making their way home from Fabric, I was venturing across London for an entirely different reason. I was battling my way through the bitterly cold morning air so that I could catch a train from London Paddington to Oxford in order to attend the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Become a vegetarian, save the world!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-become-a-vegetarian-save-the-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 23:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Wood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-become-a-vegetarian-save-the-world/</guid>
        <description>Sustainability is a hot topic. Yet despite all the recent conventions and talks on sustainability, it’s still hard to know what living sustainably really means.
So this year I am conducting my own sustainability experiment. I am calling it ‘12 Sustainable Months of 2012’, and my mission is to find …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
