<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/dr710/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/dr710/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Shacking up with Business
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-shacking-up-with-business/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 02:09:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Deepka Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-shacking-up-with-business/</guid>
        <description>We all know that estate agents and landlords aren’t exactly a student’s best friend, and many of us have personally fallen victim of pushy sales tactics, resulting in a less than ideal but extortionately expensive student flat. Such experiences prompted Ben, a final year student at Bournemouth …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to stop wasting time
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-how-to-stop-wasting-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 12:39:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Deepka Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-how-to-stop-wasting-time/</guid>
        <description>This week I met Dr. Magdalena Bak-Maier, a personal development and learning expert, executive coach to top level scientists and entrepreneurs, and author of Get Productive. The premise of the book is simple: instead of feeling overwhelmed by having too much to do, you can learn how to use your …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Putting a Katz amongst the pigeons
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-putting-a-katz-amongst-the-pigeons/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 22:43:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Deepka Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-putting-a-katz-amongst-the-pigeons/</guid>
        <description>Jason Katz, a renowned investment banker who turned his hand to private equity, visited Imperial College to share his knowledge and advice in an event organised by the Imperial Speaker’s Club and the Imperial Investment Club.
Katz, clad in casual business attire, began to address the audience in his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Veni, Vidi, Vinci
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-veni-vidi-vinci/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 22:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>George Howard,Deepka Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-veni-vidi-vinci/</guid>
        <description>We would never claim to have an impressive bank of knowledge of the arts, however this did not reduce the sheer excitement felt when, against all odds, we secured a set of, now hallowed, tickets to the Leonardo da Vinci exhibition.
Since November, more than half of the Old Master’s existing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dazed &amp; Confused at Somerset House
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-dazed-confused-at-somerset-house/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 21:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Deepka Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-dazed-confused-at-somerset-house/</guid>
        <description>It is odd to think that around the time of my birth, some 20 years ago, Jefferson Hack and John ‘Rankin’ Waddell were on the brink of producing the first issue of what was to become one of my favourite magazines during my late teens and beyond. Granted, Dazed &amp;amp; Confused started as a rather …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Potential College Day revisions outlined
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-potential-college-day-revisions-outlined/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 19:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Deepka Rana,Maciej Matuszewski,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-potential-college-day-revisions-outlined/</guid>
        <description>The College Day Working Party has outlined its latest recommendations towards the structure of the day. Imperial College Union, while open to some of the recommended changes, has taken the opportunity to reinforce the importance of student input in the face of significant changes. On the other hand, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why should you go into teaching?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-why-should-you-go-into-teaching/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 19:48:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,Matthew N Colvin,Navid Nabijou,Deepka Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-why-should-you-go-into-teaching/</guid>
        <description>Can you think of any reason why an Imperial student might want to become a teacher?” “They got a third class, maybe?” This response from a second year mathematician may well sum up the opinions of some Imperial students, and indeed a section of society’s wider opinion of the profession. We’ve all …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Summer Ball survey results reveal students&#39; concerns with event
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-felix-summer-ball-survey-results-reveal-students-concerns-with-event/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 00:30:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Deepka Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-felix-summer-ball-survey-results-reveal-students-concerns-with-event/</guid>
        <description>“Errrm&amp;hellip;where were all the people?” was one of the many questions asked after last year’s Summer Ball. With less than half the expected turnout and a 6-ﬁgure loss, it will come as no surprise that the initial results of the Felix survey are looking rather bleak.
As Felix reported previously …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Physics students create popular revision ‘wiki’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-physics-students-create-popular-revision-wiki/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 20:57:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Deepka Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-physics-students-create-popular-revision-wiki/</guid>
        <description>Physics students Deep Shah, Kin-Hing Lo, and Victor See have developed the ‘Imperial Physics Wiki’, a website which allows students to share lecture notes and past-paper solutions. The collaborative website is built upon the same technology behind Wikipedia. It’s fully integrated into the Imperial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Faculty elections swing around
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-18-faculty-elections-swing-around/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 09:09:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Deepka Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-18-faculty-elections-swing-around/</guid>
        <description>Although the biggest results have already been announced this Tuesday for the Imperial College Union elections, election fever is far from over, with nominees vying for the votes for positions on the committees of the RCSU, CGCU and ICSMSU. All three unions are running their own election for members …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Exeter declares £9,000 fees
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-exeter-declares-9000-fees/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 20:09:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Deepka Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-exeter-declares-9000-fees/</guid>
        <description>The University of Exeter has announced plans to raise its undergraduate fees to £9,000, the new threshold set by the government last December.
This comes weeks after Imperial College officially revealed plans to raise its fees, however Exeter’s news marks it as the first non-Russell Group University …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College steps back from 8am lectures
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-college-steps-back-from-8am-lectures/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 21:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Deepka Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-college-steps-back-from-8am-lectures/</guid>
        <description>Last Wednesday saw the first meeting of the committee in charge of discussing the possibility of changing college hours. Members of the committee, a mix of representatives for students, staff and Imperial College had the opportunity to begin debating the feasibility of changing college hours and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>From the Archives: Extending the College day
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-from-the-archives-extending-the-college-day/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 17:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Deepka Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-from-the-archives-extending-the-college-day/</guid>
        <description>Few will remember the glorious days when a working day at Imperial College was limited between the times of 9.30am and 5.30pm. However proposals to axe this ‘slackers’ paradise were brought forward in the early nineties, causing great agitation amongst students and staff alike. Sound familiar?
A …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kennedy Institute to close
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-kennedy-institute-to-close/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Deepka Rana,Yilin Wei,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-kennedy-institute-to-close/</guid>
        <description>The Kennedy Institute of Rheumatology, one of the world’s leading research centres in rheumatology, currently housed within the Faculty of Medicine of Imperial College will be relocated to Oxford University in what Felix has been told is a sensitive matter for the Faculty.
In November last year, an …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
