<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/dt1209/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/dt1209/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Duke Nukem Forever
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-duke-nukem-forever/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 21:21:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dexter Tarr,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-duke-nukem-forever/</guid>
        <description>Yes, eventually I get to it. Of course, technically speaking this game has been picked up to be carried to completion by Gearbox Studios, mainly by being incredibly famous for just never showing up.
Some of the keener nerds amongst you (I say this as a proud member of the clan) may have seen the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lord of the Rings: White Council
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-lord-of-the-rings-white-council/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 21:18:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dexter Tarr,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-lord-of-the-rings-white-council/</guid>
        <description>Thinking of a single reason why they didn’t make this game is really hard. If they were worried that it wasn’t going to sell enough copies to make it viable I really hope they’re reading this because I will commit right here to buying enough copies to make it worth it.
In fact it’s hard to find out …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Starcraft Ghost
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-starcraft-ghost/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 06:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dexter Tarr,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-starcraft-ghost/</guid>
        <description>Some of the people who read this with a further interest in gaming (i.e. you’ve been on the internet and googled ‘video games’) will be aware that Starcraft 2 in South Korea is like cocaine on Wall Street – it’s really addictive and everyone is doing it. This game is so huge over there that you can …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fallout 3 Van Buren
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-fallout-3-van-buren/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 21:09:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dexter Tarr,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-fallout-3-van-buren/</guid>
        <description>Hush up fanboys and those sad enough to try and pick a fight with static print, I’m gonna say it, they cancelled_ Fallout 3_. Not the one you or I played/saw/read about/licked etc. No, this game was in development by Black Isle Studios, the inventors of more cancelled games than ones to actually …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dirty Harry, the game
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-dirty-harry-the-game/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 20:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dexter Tarr,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-dirty-harry-the-game/</guid>
        <description>No, I kid you not, they were really going to make a Dirty Harry game. To be set in between the first two films, the game was to focus on SFPD Inspector Harry Callahan as he pursues the serial killer Scorpio. One of the creative aims driving its production was to further develop the character of …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
