<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/tvfelix/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/tvfelix/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Grand Design’s 100th episode
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-grand-designs-100th-episode/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 02:40:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix TV,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-grand-designs-100th-episode/</guid>
        <description>One hundred episodes in and Kevin appears to be going soft. The once heavily-critical McCloud whole-heartedly embraces the irrefutably crazy Lee and Graham who are embarking on the restoration and redesign of a central London water tower. With a build period of eight months, the construction site …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Review: The Newsroom UK Premiere
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-7-10-review-the-newsroom-uk-premiere/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2012 11:43:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix TV,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-7-10-review-the-newsroom-uk-premiere/</guid>
        <description>It seems a long time ago that Aaron Sorkin was last on our TV screens. After the success of The West Wing, everyone expected Studio 60 on the Sunset Strip to be the next step towards greatness for the burgeoning screenwriter. Unfortunately, the show flopped within the first few episodes and was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Today your diary entry will read: “took a prozzie hostage and was shot by three armed bastards!”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-today-your-diary-entry-will-read-took-a-prozzie-hostage-and-was-shot-by-three-armed-bastards/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 21:32:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix TV,George Barnett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-today-your-diary-entry-will-read-took-a-prozzie-hostage-and-was-shot-by-three-armed-bastards/</guid>
        <description>Alex Drake (the smoking hot Keeley Hawes) is a trained police psychologist and negotiator who has recently been researching the case of Sam Tyler, an officer who claimed to have been sent back to 1973 after being hit by a car in 2006.
In the first two of the five series (Life On Mars), Tyler was in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Downton smashes Spooks in ratings
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-downton-smashes-spooks-in-ratings/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 12:49:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix TV,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-downton-smashes-spooks-in-ratings/</guid>
        <description>The second series of ITV’s latest (and very successful) foray into the world costume drama began towards the end of the summer break, with its first episode clocking up over ten million viewers. But why? This unusually high figure is rarely reached by similar programming on the BBC, and ITV aren’t …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What We Watched
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-28-what-we-watched/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 11:36:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix TV,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-28-what-we-watched/</guid>
        <description>Given that we have months of freedom in which one could watch anything one wanted to on TV, I thought that I might bring back a brilliant and unique series from the depths of Dave and Dave-ja-vu.
Blackadder – which stars the hilarious Rowan Atkinson in its title role – is a fantastic sitcom based …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Two Girls One Cup
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-28-two-girls-one-cup/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 11:34:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix TV,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-28-two-girls-one-cup/</guid>
        <description>Two Girls One Cup is a scatological fantasy drama centered around a solitary cup, which is shared by the two girls named in the title. Produced by Brazilian company MFX Media in 2007, it is the notorious work of the self-described “compulsive fetishist” Marco Fiorito. What a dirty bastard he is. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Made in Shitville
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-13-made-in-shitville/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2011 13:33:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix TV,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-13-made-in-shitville/</guid>
        <description>I had no intention to watch “Made in Chelsea”, but being otherwise unoccupied, along with the fact that it was playing on my friend’s laptop in front of me, I found myself succumbing to three episodes thereof. It was painful.
For those who have yet to see it, ‘Made in Chelsea’ is a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What We Watched...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-5-what-we-watched/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 23:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix TV,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-5-what-we-watched/</guid>
        <description>The words &amp;ldquo;Period Drama&amp;rdquo; usually conjure up a rose-tinted image of vast country estates, sunshine and happy endings. The fact that The Tudors isn&amp;rsquo;t shown at prime time may lead one to believe that it is just more of the aforementioned – possibly a repeat; rather than the fact that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Not the worst way to avoid revision
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-4-25-not-the-worst-way-to-avoid-revision/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2011 09:27:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix TV,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-4-25-not-the-worst-way-to-avoid-revision/</guid>
        <description>In this overture episode to the sixth series of Doctor Who, the Doctor (Matt Smith) is quite dramatically struck down by an alien attired in a 1960s space suit. For a blissful moment I thought Matt Smith was going to be replaced by someone rather less irritating, but sadly he turns up again a couple …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Take Me Out. Errr, actually please don&#39;t
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-12-take-me-out-errr-actually-please-dont/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2011 12:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix TV,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-12-take-me-out-errr-actually-please-dont/</guid>
        <description>After last Friday’s crime extravaganza I decided to watch something a little different this week – game shows aren’t really my cup of tea, but according to the comments I receive from people who read my column, it’s better when I dislike things. Hosted by the fantastically amusing Paddy McGuinness …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best in Class: Crime
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-best-in-class-crime/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 20:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix TV,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-best-in-class-crime/</guid>
        <description>Why is it that we love crime so much? Obviously when one is the victim of such offences (give me five minutes and a rounders bat with the bastard who stole my bike&amp;hellip;) it’s a little different, but crime fiction persistently tops the books, films and TV charts. It’s probably the most popular …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hey, Rastamouse, where&#39;s that cheese me like?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-hey-rastamouse-wheres-that-cheese-me-like/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 20:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix TV,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-hey-rastamouse-wheres-that-cheese-me-like/</guid>
        <description>Give it up for the &amp;lsquo;Easy Crew&amp;rsquo; – &amp;ldquo;der to make de bad tings good&amp;rdquo; – Rastamouse, Scratchy and Zooma in CBeebies&amp;rsquo; new series titled Rastamouse. The show seems to be popular with adults too, with the widely held theory that &amp;ldquo;cheese&amp;rdquo; actually means …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What We Watched...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-what-we-watched/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 20:12:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix TV,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-what-we-watched/</guid>
        <description>It&amp;rsquo;s that time when all the post-Christmas series are coming to an end, and writing this column is really difficult when there&amp;rsquo;s sod all on telly, so a couple of the shows could possibly be repeats. They should be just as good as when they were first broadcast though so no complaining. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What We Watched
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-28-what-we-watched/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2011 14:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix TV,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-28-what-we-watched/</guid>
        <description>This week&amp;rsquo;s TV treated us to two chilling new episodes of the brilliantly gory Silent Witness, which starts with womanising Harry taking a trip to Budapest to perform a second post mortem on a Romanian prostitute who suspiciously turned up looking cadaverous in the River Danube. I have always …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
