<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/bayan_al_balushi/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/bayan_al_balushi/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>A family against the Sicilian Mafia</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-a-family-against-the-sicilian-mafia/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bayan Al Balushi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-a-family-against-the-sicilian-mafia/</guid>
        <description>Imagine, if you will, Sicily of the early twentieth century; an island whose main source of income is agriculture, its residents mainly peasants. Against this backdrop, we are introduced to the five Sacco brothers, who are part of an honest, hard-working, recently landed family. Their father, Luigi, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jennifer Tseng brings a freshness to well-worn tropes in this engaging debut</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-15-jennifer-tseng-brings-a-freshness-to-well-worn-tropes-in-this-engaging-debut/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bayan Al Balushi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-15-jennifer-tseng-brings-a-freshness-to-well-worn-tropes-in-this-engaging-debut/</guid>
        <description>Mayumi and the Sea of Happiness, the new novel from Jennifer Tseng, follows Mayumi, a forty-one-year-old librarian, married with a child, who begins an affair with an unnamed seventeen-year-old boy who she meets in the library. Despite being aware of the potential consequences of her decision, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>One Hundred Shadows leaves us in the dark</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-one-hundred-shadows-leaves-us-in-the-dark/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bayan Al Balushi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-one-hundred-shadows-leaves-us-in-the-dark/</guid>
        <description>This ethereal short novel seamlessly weaves elements of fantasy with reality, producing a work of fiction that is as bizarre as it is engrossing. Author Hwang Jungeun affords us a small glimpse into the lives of Eungyo and Mujae, two friends working at electronic stores.
During a day out, Eungyo is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“What would you have done?”</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02--what-would-you-have-done/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bayan Al Balushi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02--what-would-you-have-done/</guid>
        <description>The Reader is one of those books that one can discuss at length and would make a good choice for a book club, but I’ll try to keep it short though I have much to say.
The story is told from the first person perspective of Michael Berg and begins with him having contracted hepatitis at the age of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Debut novel challenges traditions of the Arab world</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-debut-novel-challenges-traditions-of-the-arab-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bayan Al Balushi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-debut-novel-challenges-traditions-of-the-arab-world/</guid>
        <description>The first time I heard of this book was when I watched the author being interviewed on an Arab channel. Not having watched the interview from the beginning, I didn’t know what the novel was about, but I was intrigued by their discussion of Arab culture and traditions. When I learnt that the book …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
