<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/elina_michaelidou/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/elina_michaelidou/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Top tips for visiting the Greek Islands on a budget</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-top-tips-for-visiting-the-greek-islands-on-a-budget/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elina Michaelidou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-top-tips-for-visiting-the-greek-islands-on-a-budget/</guid>
        <description>Dreaming of visiting the Greek Islands but don’t have all you need to enjoy an Instagram-perfect trip (i.e. money)? Don’t worry, you can still take your memorable shots and experience Greece to its maximum while travelling on a budget if you follow the following tips.
Travel off-peak
Or at least …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London from above: Felix’s guide to the best views</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-london-from-above-felix-s-guide-to-the-best-views/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elina Michaelidou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-london-from-above-felix-s-guide-to-the-best-views/</guid>
        <description> The London Eye
 The London Eye is one of the most famous attractions in London, where you can see views of Big Ben, the Houses of Parliament, and other Westminster buildings unfold along the River Thames. It has 32 capsules that run non-stop when the attraction is open, and each of them can carry …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Exploring Copenhagen (the happiest place on Earth!?)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-exploring-copenhagen-the-happiest-place-on-earth/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elina Michaelidou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-exploring-copenhagen-the-happiest-place-on-earth/</guid>
        <description>This time two years ago, I was on my way to a spontaneous trip to Copenhagen. The spring term had just started, and on Friday of week one, we hopped on an Uber to go to the airport as quickly as possible. I finished my last lecture of the day at 6pm, and the flight was to depart at 8.45pm. I had to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lights will guide you home: catching the northern lights in the UK</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-lights-will-guide-you-home-catching-the-northern-lights-in-the-uk/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elina Michaelidou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-lights-will-guide-you-home-catching-the-northern-lights-in-the-uk/</guid>
        <description>The UK has quite a few spots where the northern lights, or Aurora Borealis, are visible. As you may have guessed already, you have higher chances to see them somewhere up north, particularly in Scotland. However, you’ll be surprised to learn that Aurora Borealis has been noticed as south as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The hidden side of Cyprus</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-the-hidden-side-of-cyprus/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elina Michaelidou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-the-hidden-side-of-cyprus/</guid>
        <description>Last month, I found myself at Troodos square in the mountainous part of Cyprus. It wasn’t my first time there (I usually go twice a year) but this time was different. Whilst walking in a small park there, I noticed a sign to the Atalanti Nature Trail, which reminded me that I wanted to visit the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Time to get your hops up: Felix’s guide to Hop-on Hop-off bus tours</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-time-to-get-your-hops-up-felix-s-guide-to-hop-on-hop-off-bus-tours/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elina Michaelidou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-time-to-get-your-hops-up-felix-s-guide-to-hop-on-hop-off-bus-tours/</guid>
        <description>A Hop-on Hop-off bus tour is a city sightseeing tour, usually on a double-decker bus with the upper level left open. The tour involves a free audio guide in different languages, with the number and variety of the languages depending on the city that the tour bus operates in. In large cities, the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
