<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rg2112/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rg2112/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Forever Restless by Brutality Will Prevail
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-forever-restless-by-brutality-will-prevail/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 17:17:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Robert Garside,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-forever-restless-by-brutality-will-prevail/</guid>
        <description>Plagued by member changes and after releasing a couple of pretty disappointing albums at the end of 2014, Brutality Will Prevail’s stock had taken a real hit. As one of UK Hardcore’s leading lights in the early 2000’s they built up a following alongside other alumni such as Hang the Dastard, Last …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rob’s Sad Playlist
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-robs-sad-playlist/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Robert Garside,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-robs-sad-playlist/</guid>
        <description> Disintegration Moving onto the more melodramatic side of sad, The Cure take us into the wilderness that is Disintegration. With the disconcerting glass smashing samples, unwavering drum machine and self indulgent vocals, the song is weirdly mesmerising. If you like this sort of thing but fancy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Garside’s window-smashing soundtrack
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-garsides-window-smashing-soundtrack/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 14:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Robert Garside,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-garsides-window-smashing-soundtrack/</guid>
        <description> G.L.O.S.S – G.L.O.S.S (We’re from the Future) Hardcore punk music has always been chronically male dominated and well known for its macho culture. G.L.O.S.S (Girls Living Outside Society’s Shit) used their sole release to rail against the sexism and homophobia people face in this scene, discussing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Future of the Left crowdfund peace
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-future-of-the-left-crowdfund-peace/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 09:14:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Robert Garside,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-future-of-the-left-crowdfund-peace/</guid>
        <description>From their formation of the ashes of the wonderful Mclusky in 2005, Welsh noisy alt-rock savants Future of the Left have generated a reputation for absurd lyrics, excellent musicianship and live shows that Pitchfork would label as incendiary. A reputation justified by their fifth album The Peace …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Elections 2016: Mates or Manifestos?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-elections-2016-mates-or-manifestos/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 11:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Robert Garside,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-elections-2016-mates-or-manifestos/</guid>
        <description>Last week, Theresa Davey wrote an interesting article about the nature of union elections and how they are, essentially, a popularity contest.
This is a real danger associated with student elections when, due to the short election period, it is difficult for the candidates with well thought-out …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Racism is so metal
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-racism-is-so-metal/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 12:39:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Robert Garside,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-racism-is-so-metal/</guid>
        <description>This article is something I need to get off my chest. I love heavy music with aggressive themes, from Black metal to hardcore to grind – I love it all. I love the catharsis and thrill that a pounding drum and palm muted guitar line can provide but sometimes the shit that comes with it really makes …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FELIX’s Mercury Prize picks
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-felixs-mercury-prize-picks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 09:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,Peter Munton,Robert Garside,Fred S Fyles,Cale E Tilford,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-felixs-mercury-prize-picks/</guid>
        <description> _In Colour_Jamie xx Oh Jamie, you can do no wrong. Not in my eyes, the eyes of anyone who went outdoors this summer who was inundated with your invariably uplifting ‘Good Times’, and presumably, not in the eyes of the Mercury Music Prize people.
The flabbergasting combo of Jamie Smith, dance hall …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS album of the week
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-ams-album-of-the-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 04:38:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Robert Garside,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-ams-album-of-the-week/</guid>
        <description>Ed: OK, so technically this week it’s EP of the week rather than album. Sorry. Since releasing Kingdom of Dogs in 2009 and Island Living in 2010, Welsh four piece Bastions have showcased a talent for writing bleak, arty and desperate songs, a talent they expanded on for their 2011 full length …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
