<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/adamgellatly14/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/adamgellatly14/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Macbeth at the National Theatre</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-22-macbeth-at-the-national-theatre/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adam Gellatly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-22-macbeth-at-the-national-theatre/</guid>
        <description>Director Rufus Norris’s adaptation of Macbeth is perfect. Truly, I mean it. If I were to go through each individual aspect of the production, from the acting to the costumes, I would not change a single thing. But, did it leave me pondering a scene for hours after it had ended? Did it hit an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ISIS, 4Chan, and WhatsApp: Theatre for the Lulz</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-isis-4chan-and-whatsapp-theatre-for-the-lulz/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adam Gellatly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-isis-4chan-and-whatsapp-theatre-for-the-lulz/</guid>
        <description>The Believers Are But Brothers opens at the Bush Theatre, after an award-winning run at the Edinburgh Fringe in 2017. It tells the stories of three young men who, through their encounters online, become exposed to and enveloped by the murky waters of extremism. Two of the stories follow young …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2017 in review: the Arts editors take you through the best exhibitions and shows in London this year</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-2017-in-review-the-arts-editors-take-you-through-the-best-exhibitions-and-shows-in-london-this-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,Adam Gellatly,Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-2017-in-review-the-arts-editors-take-you-through-the-best-exhibitions-and-shows-in-london-this-year/</guid>
        <description>It’s a strange feeling, when you feel like you know an artist, that you have a reasonable understanding of his work, to then discover him afresh. But exactly what I experienced at Tate Britain in February, when the gallery put on the largest ever arrangement of Hockney’s work.
David Hockney, The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Clash of Cultures: Phoenix Editors special</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-clash-of-cultures-phoenix-editors-special/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,Adam Gellatly,Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-clash-of-cultures-phoenix-editors-special/</guid>
        <description>Phoenix, Felix ’s sister arts publication, returns this week with a teaser 8-page pullout. Arts Editors Indira Malik and Adam Gellatly and Felix Editor-in-Chief Fred Fyles talk to Phoenix Editors Liliane Laborde-Edozien, Catherine Webb, and Joy Aston about their plans for the magazine and their love …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Politics and the value of rhetoric in early Rome</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-politics-and-the-value-of-rhetoric-in-early-rome/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adam Gellatly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-politics-and-the-value-of-rhetoric-in-early-rome/</guid>
        <description>In his second longest play, Shakespeare chronicles the election to, and subsequent removal from, the position of consul – a magistrate wielding executive power – of Caius Martius Coriolanus, played here by Sope Dirisu.
Coriolanus is elected to consul by his fellow societal-elites: a war hero and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Clash of Cultures: Can the arts thrive in the science dominated campus of Imperial?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-clash-of-cultures-can-the-arts-thrive-in-the-science-dominated-campus-of-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adam Gellatly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-clash-of-cultures-can-the-arts-thrive-in-the-science-dominated-campus-of-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Adam: Readers will know you as the current Editor of Felix, but you were involved in the Arts Section at the paper before that. Can describe how that involvement came about?
Fred: I’ve always been interested in arts and culture. I grew up in London and when I was younger I went to the theatre a lot …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Clash of Cultures: IC Radio</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-clash-of-cultures-ic-radio/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adam Gellatly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-clash-of-cultures-ic-radio/</guid>
        <description>In the second instalment of the series, IC Radio Station Manager Sebastian Gonzato sat down with Arts Editor (and former IC Radio Station Manager) Adam Gellatly, to discuss the role radio has to play in the arts at Imperial.
Adam: Can you describe what being involved in radio entails, what artistic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Arts editors completely destroy box office incomes!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-arts-editors-completely-destroy-box-office-incomes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,Adam Gellatly,Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-arts-editors-completely-destroy-box-office-incomes/</guid>
        <description>National Theatre: Entry Pass
The NT offers an Entry Pass to those aged 16 - 25. After registering and providing proof of age, you’ll be entitled to a whole range of NT delights including access to exclusive workshops and events, and discounts in the NT bookshops, cafes, backstage tours and prop …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get to know your friendly neighbourhood Arts team!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-get-to-know-your-friendly-neighbourhood-arts-team/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,Adam Gellatly,Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-get-to-know-your-friendly-neighbourhood-arts-team/</guid>
        <description>INDIRA
Painting, making up stories, and endlessly ambitious crafts projects have been part of my life since early childhood. My writing in particular however never really found a focus until I came to Imperial. Maybe it was watching too much Gilmore Girls during my formative years, but the one thing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where’s the culture at?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-where-s-the-culture-at/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,Adam Gellatly,Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-where-s-the-culture-at/</guid>
        <description>GREEN PARK
Royal Academy: Best known for its annual extravaganza - the Summer Exhibition - the RA hosts a whole range of exhibitions. Upcoming shows not to be missed are Jasper Johns; ‘Something Re-sembling Truth’, and Dali/Duchamp, an exhibition that will explore how their outlook on art and life …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Roman Tragedies: A medieval masterpiece for a Facebook Live world
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-20-roman-tragedies-a-medieval-masterpiece-for-a-facebook-live-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 21:36:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adam Gellatly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-20-roman-tragedies-a-medieval-masterpiece-for-a-facebook-live-world/</guid>
        <description>Enobarbus is a dying man. So overcome with grief at having betrayed his closest friend, Mark Antony, to Octavius Caesar, he can no longer bear to live. His cries and pleas for forgiveness are translated from Dutch to English courtesy of surtitles. A cameraman follows him as he stumbles across the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hockney makes a splash at this Tate Britain retrospective
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-hockney-makes-a-splash-at-this-tate-britain-retrospective/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adam Gellatly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-hockney-makes-a-splash-at-this-tate-britain-retrospective/</guid>
        <description>Logistically alone, the new David Hockney exhibition at Tate Britain is a marvel. Nearly 150 pieces spanning the breadth of Hockney’s career – paintings, sketches, photography, video, and drawings – have been assembled in a thirteen-room experience. Many of the pieces have been borrowed from David …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>King Lear is a hit and miss at the Barbican
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-king-lear-is-a-hit-and-miss-at-the-barbican/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 15:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adam Gellatly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-king-lear-is-a-hit-and-miss-at-the-barbican/</guid>
        <description>How does a creative team begin to tackle the momentous task of reincarnating a play that has been performed and studied for centuries? Do they period dress the stage and cast, and risk being forgotten in the plethora of Shakespeare productions? Or do they approach the play from an entirely new angle …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Children is a triumph of acting and staging
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-the-children-is-a-triumph-of-acting-and-staging/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 14:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adam Gellatly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-the-children-is-a-triumph-of-acting-and-staging/</guid>
        <description>From the moment The Children – written by Olivier Award winner, Lucy Kirkwood – begins, the on-stage chemistry between Rose and Hazel is a joy to behold. Played by Francesca Annis and Deborah Findlay respectively, the juxtaposition between the calm and uptight exterior of Rose and the scatterbrain …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cohen’s light has gone dark, but the night will not have him
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-cohens-light-has-gone-dark-but-the-night-will-not-have-him/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 15:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adam Gellatly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-cohens-light-has-gone-dark-but-the-night-will-not-have-him/</guid>
        <description>This is not strictly a review. Given the circumstances it can’t be. Instead, it is a look at how an album takes on a new life when its creator passes away so shortly after its release – or, more appropriately, how an album allows for the continuation of a life that is no more. If you read …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Harrogate
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-harrogate/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 14:33:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,Adam Gellatly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-harrogate/</guid>
        <description>After its successful debut at HighTide Festival in Suffolk last year, Harrogate - written by Al Smith and directed by Richard Twyman – arrives in London at the Royal Court to kick off its UK wide tour. The one act play, coming in at just over 80 minutes, finds itself perfectly suited to the cosy …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
