<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ignatius_roy_hillcoat_nalletamby/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ignatius_roy_hillcoat_nalletamby/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The dangers of vaping</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-the-dangers-of-vaping/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ignatius-Roy Hillcoat-Nalletamby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-the-dangers-of-vaping/</guid>
        <description>E-cigarettes, often advertised as an aid for smoking cessation, may actually encourage young adults to take up smoking, new research suggests.
E-cigarettes are growing in popularity, both in the US and UK, with vaping shops opening on every other street corner. E-cigarettes provide the same smoking …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Rocky Balboa of the animal kingdom </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-the-rocky-balboa-of-the-animal-kingdom/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ignatius-Roy Hillcoat-Nalletamby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-the-rocky-balboa-of-the-animal-kingdom/</guid>
        <description>Competition and conflict is the bread and butter of the natural world. Individuals of almost every species compete for resources such as mating sites, partners, and food. The competition is fierce – often involving physical conflict with costly outcomes. Due to its costs, individuals assess …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Some of the biggest tech announcements of 2017 </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-some-of-the-biggest-tech-announcements-of-2017/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ignatius-Roy Hillcoat-Nalletamby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-some-of-the-biggest-tech-announcements-of-2017/</guid>
        <description>March 2017 saw the phoenix that is Nintendo rise from its ashes with the release of its new console the Nintendo Switch. Marketed as a truly versatile game console, the Switch can be played in three modes – TV mode for the traditionalists who like a big TV, tabletop mode for when a big TV screen …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The James Dyson Award – upgrading the world one clever project at a time </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-the-james-dyson-award-upgrading-the-world-one-clever-project-at-a-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ignatius-Roy Hillcoat-Nalletamby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-the-james-dyson-award-upgrading-the-world-one-clever-project-at-a-time/</guid>
        <description>In September 2017, shortlisted entries for this year’s Dyson Award were announced. For those of you who don’t know, the Dyson Award is an international award for current and recently graduated design engineering students, coordinated by the James Dyson Foundation. The main purpose of the award is to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The October 4th Google Event: Pixel 2 and More</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-the-october-4th-google-event-pixel-2-and-more/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ignatius-Roy Hillcoat-Nalletamby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-the-october-4th-google-event-pixel-2-and-more/</guid>
        <description>Google announced a host of new products in San Francisco on the 4th of October this year. Everyone eagerly awaited the announcement, particularly the unveiling of the company’s second flagship smartphone, the Pixel 2. However, in true Google fashion, there were a few surprises in the announcement …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
