<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Paula_rowińska on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/paula_rowi%C5%84ska/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Paula_rowińska on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/paula_rowi%C5%84ska/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Coffee? It’s in your genes!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-coffee-it-s-in-your-genes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paula Rowińska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-coffee-it-s-in-your-genes/</guid>
        <description>Bitter equals poisonous - at least according to our brain. There seems to exist only one exception from this evolutionary dislike for bitterness: coffee. Why many of us cannot even imagine a morning without a cup of espresso or latte, although its bitter taste should make our body issue a poison …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fear is in the Air</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-fear-is-in-the-air/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paula Rowińska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-fear-is-in-the-air/</guid>
        <description>How old should one be to watch Harry Potter? What about The Hunger Games? Or Transformers? So far, age ratings for movies depended on subjective opinions.
However, researchers at the Max Planck Institute for Chemistry in Mainz suggested that we could base the age classification on the isoprene …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Trolley Problem: What Would You Choose?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-the-trolley-problem-what-would-you-choose/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paula Rowińska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-the-trolley-problem-what-would-you-choose/</guid>
        <description>Researchers from the MIT Media Lab’s Scalable Cooperation group have surveyed over 2 million citizens from over 200 countries about morally difficult decisions that autonomous vehicles might have to make. Participants played ‘Moral Machine’, an online game designed by the researchers. In a series of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pick and Choose</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-pick-and-choose/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paula Rowińska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-pick-and-choose/</guid>
        <description>Neuroscientists from Johns Hopkins University studied how our brains help us make spontaneous food choices at buffets, in restaurants or in front of our own fridge. The research on rats helped them identify a brain region that could be responsible for our food decisions, according to the paper in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Birth of words</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-birth-of-words/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paula Rowińska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-birth-of-words/</guid>
        <description>A team of linguists and geographers from the Centre for Corpus Research at the University of Birmingham traced the geographical roots of emerging words in American English. Among 8.9 billion words used in 980 million Tweets posted in the US they identified 54 new words, which were rare in October …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2018 Nobel Prize in Medicine: the fight against cancer</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-2018-nobel-prize-in-medicine-the-fight-against-cancer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paula Rowińska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-2018-nobel-prize-in-medicine-the-fight-against-cancer/</guid>
        <description>The 2018 Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine went to James P. Allison and Tasuku Honjo for the “discovery of cancer therapy by inhibition of negative immune regulation.”
Be it bacteria, virus or cancer cell, no foreign molecule can expect a warm welcome to our body. T-cells, a type of white blood …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Prime time</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-prime-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paula Rowińska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-prime-time/</guid>
        <description>Had you recently visited the maths department, you would have felt like during the World Cup: students and researchers engaged in heated discussions while watching a 45-minute-long video. Only instead of a football game, we followed a lecture broadcast from Heidelberg in Germany.
On Monday 24th …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We were born to be lazy</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-we-were-born-to-be-lazy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paula Rowińska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-we-were-born-to-be-lazy/</guid>
        <description>Researchers from the Brain Behaviour Laboratory designed an experiment to understand why the couch attracts us so much more than a good workout. The group led by Matthieu Boisgontier discovered that the human brain might innately prefer the lack of physical activity.
The human kind would not have …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
