<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/yw3410/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/yw3410/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>YELP@Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-yelpimperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 23:44:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yilin Wei,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-yelpimperial/</guid>
        <description>The statistics. Around one in three private school pupils achieves a grade of A* or A at A-level compared to 10.6% for state schools, despite roughly only making up 10% of all those in education. 54.8% of those in state schools leave GCSE level without passes of A* to C in the basic subjects english …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>£9,000 fees conditions revealed
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-9000-fees-conditions-revealed/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 19:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yilin Wei,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-9000-fees-conditions-revealed/</guid>
        <description>The Office for Fair Access (Offa) has published new guidelines that could force universities charging over £6,000 in tuition fees to invest a percentage into fair access schemes.
Universities are advised to spend between 15% to 30%, based on the proportion of under-represented students, of any extra …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Visa “victory” for scientists
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-visa-victory-for-scientists/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 20:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yilin Wei,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-visa-victory-for-scientists/</guid>
        <description>Last week, the government announced alterations to the proposals to curb immigration to reflect the importance of research to the UK amid much fanfare from activists and campaigners. The change will see a new restricted ‘certificate of sponsorship’ (‘CoS’) system where researchers are favoured …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Student visa plans attacked
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-student-visa-plans-attacked/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 19:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yilin Wei,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-student-visa-plans-attacked/</guid>
        <description>Listen carefully. Do you hear that? That is the sound of the seismic shift in government policy which will define the higher education sector for the next decade. And, worryingly, it does not sound good.
The 31st of January marked the end of the consultation period for the review of the student …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jewish and Muslim student ‘ambassadors’ to promote interfaith relations
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-jewish-and-muslim-student-ambassadors-to-promote-interfaith-relations/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 18:36:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yilin Wei,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-jewish-and-muslim-student-ambassadors-to-promote-interfaith-relations/</guid>
        <description>The introduction of 18 Muslim and Jewish students acting as “campus ambassadors” in 10 universities across the UK is hoped to promote more interfaith relationships between the two communities.
The Israeli-Palestinian conflict is possibly the most controversial of our time and is often the cause of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kennedy Institute to close
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-kennedy-institute-to-close/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Deepka Rana,Yilin Wei,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-kennedy-institute-to-close/</guid>
        <description>The Kennedy Institute of Rheumatology, one of the world’s leading research centres in rheumatology, currently housed within the Faculty of Medicine of Imperial College will be relocated to Oxford University in what Felix has been told is a sensitive matter for the Faculty.
In November last year, an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>So what happens at an occupation?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-so-what-happens-at-an-occupation/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 21:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yilin Wei,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-so-what-happens-at-an-occupation/</guid>
        <description>As the parliamentary vote on tuition fees draws nearer, the intensity of the student protests against higher fees, education cuts and the scrapping of the EMA has rapidly increased. With occupations of university buildings happening all across the country, the reactionary protests have morphed into …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Do overseas students welcome higher tuition fees for home students?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-do-overseas-students-welcome-higher-tuition-fees-for-home-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 21:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yilin Wei,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-do-overseas-students-welcome-higher-tuition-fees-for-home-students/</guid>
        <description>Proposals to increase the tuition fee cap to £9000 per year for EU and home students were attacked by over 50,000 students protesting on the streets of London last week. However, the opinions of one particular group of students who also have a stake in this matter have mostly been ignored..
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>No help for volunteers as Outreach takes budget cut
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-no-help-for-volunteers-as-outreach-takes-budget-cut/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 22:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,Yilin Wei,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-no-help-for-volunteers-as-outreach-takes-budget-cut/</guid>
        <description>The Imperial Volunteering Centre (IVC) is to be almost entirely scrapped due to funding difficulties caused by a cut by the Higher Education Funding Council for England (HEFCE) and also a large reduction in the Outreach department budget. Heather Jones, Deputy President (Clubs &amp;amp; Societies) and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The growing visa crisis at Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-the-growing-visa-crisis-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 18:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yilin Wei,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-the-growing-visa-crisis-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>The 20th of October. Thousands of protestors are rallying outside Westminster in an effort to convince the government that their proposed cuts to the scientific budget would have fatal implications on the world class reputation and research of UK universities. They succeeded. The result was George …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Record number of students miss out on university, says UCAS
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-record-number-of-students-miss-out-on-university-says-ucas/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 20:02:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yilin Wei,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-record-number-of-students-miss-out-on-university-says-ucas/</guid>
        <description>After record numbers of applicants to university this year, figures released by UCAS have shown that a staggering 30.4% of students have not managed to secure a place.
A total of 688,310 people applied, whereas only 479,057 have been accepted, leaving 209,253 people who have missed out. Of these, …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
