<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Album on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/tags/album/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Album on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/tags/album/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello darkness, my old friend: First Aid Kit’s Ruins</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-hello-darkness-my-old-friend-first-aid-kit-s-ruins/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-hello-darkness-my-old-friend-first-aid-kit-s-ruins/</guid>
        <description>The sad Swedish sisters are back with their fourth album, ten songs of crooning harmony and synth. Ruins is a breakup album so pure and candid it’ll have you crying into your ice cream about heartache that hasn’t even happened yet. The work is anything but stripped back – as with any of First Aid …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ode to an ambience, straight Frahm bald Nils</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-ode-to-an-ambience-straight-frahm-bald-nils/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack O&#39;Brien,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-ode-to-an-ambience-straight-frahm-bald-nils/</guid>
        <description>Nils Frahm stands out to fans of ambient music as an electronic producer and pianist ready to fill your brain with a tantalising fusion of classical composition and electronic reverb. He is an artist who since the mid-noughties, alongside his esteemed record label Erased Tapes, has brought forth …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Today’s Empires, Tomorrow’s Ashes is still relevant</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-today-s-empires-tomorrow-s-ashes-is-still-relevant/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-today-s-empires-tomorrow-s-ashes-is-still-relevant/</guid>
        <description>Margaret Thatcher famously referred to herself as practicing “conviction politics” in the months before her 1979 rise to the office of Prime Minister. She holds no candle to Winnipeg-based thrash-punk band Propagandhi, an all-vegan band so dedicated to environmentalism that they organize tours to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pandering to the collective</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-pandering-to-the-collective/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Suraj G,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-pandering-to-the-collective/</guid>
        <description>Panda Bear, born Noah Lennox, has become a prevalent figure within the indie music community. A purveyor of genres, Lennox and his artistic counterpart Avey Tare (Michael Portner) have created some of the wildest and most original compositions from the mysterious space they seem to occupy in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>King Gizzard takes a field trip to Polygondwanaland</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-king-gizzard-takes-a-field-trip-to-polygondwanaland/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-king-gizzard-takes-a-field-trip-to-polygondwanaland/</guid>
        <description>The Gizz is back with their fourth effort of the year, and it sounds like they’ve been listening to too much Tool.
Fans of the the proggy indie hard rock outfit (like the B52s on crack) went into this year fresh off their fantastic effort Nonagon Infinity, in eager anticipation of the announced …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The new Taylor Swift album can’t come to the phone right now. Why? Oh, ‘cause it’s shit.</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-the-new-taylor-swift-album-can-t-come-to-the-phone-right-now-why-oh-cause-it-s-shit/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Suraj G,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-the-new-taylor-swift-album-can-t-come-to-the-phone-right-now-why-oh-cause-it-s-shit/</guid>
        <description>It’s not too long since the world was introduced to girl next door and singer-songwriter, Taylor Swift, with her guitar and her country tinged pop. Upon entering the scene, Swift instantly made massive waves in the music industry and pop culture, for better or worse, with singles like ‘You belong …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An aktual-ly good album this week</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-an-aktual-ly-good-album-this-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Suraj G,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-an-aktual-ly-good-album-this-week/</guid>
        <description>Born in Iran and raised in London, beat wizard Ashkan Kooshanejad, better known by his alias Ash Koosha, broke into the electronic scene with debut album Guud in 2015. Taking the freneticism of Flying Lotus’ signature LA beat weirdness further, it seemed to spectators that Koosha could do no wrong. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Weezer wheezes out another fucking travesty...</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-weezer-wheezes-out-another-fucking-travesty/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-weezer-wheezes-out-another-fucking-travesty/</guid>
        <description>Oh, Rivers. What an absolute shame, the mess you’ve ended up in. Weezer was hot shit in the ‘90s. The Blue Album spoke to a generation of individuals who felt introverted and alone. It was a dorky, confessional, energetic mess – and never once did the heart fail to shine through. Then, the story …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Music recommends…October</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-felix-music-recommends-october/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Lawrence,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-felix-music-recommends-october/</guid>
        <description>October has been full of fantastic releases: from synth pop to hip hop, from indie labels to industry juggernauts, from distinguished artists to new talent. Pay no mind to anyone who claims “there is no good music anymore”. At Felix we unfortunately don’t have the time to review everything good that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Krept &amp; Konan abandon the London underground in their new mixtapes 7 Days and 7 Nights</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-krept-konan-abandon-the-london-underground-in-their-new-mixtapes-7-days-and-7-nights/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Montgomerie-Corcoran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-krept-konan-abandon-the-london-underground-in-their-new-mixtapes-7-days-and-7-nights/</guid>
        <description>Krept and Konan, the established rap duo from South London, put out a pair of albums two weeks ago in their first major releases since their return to the London music scene. The albums are drastically different in style: 7 Days feels more like a compilation of their attempts at different genres …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Plunge: A clarion call to sexual liberation</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-plunge-a-clarion-call-to-sexual-liberation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-plunge-a-clarion-call-to-sexual-liberation/</guid>
        <description>In the time that has elapsed between the release of Fever Ray’s eponymous debut, and the surprise launch last week of her follow-up Plunge, much has changed. Eight years have gone by since Karin Dreijer, the musician and activist behind Fever Ray, as well as one-half of the brother-sister duo The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mura Masa’s debut shows he’s one to watch</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-mura-masa-s-debut-shows-he-s-one-to-watch/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonah Beaudin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-mura-masa-s-debut-shows-he-s-one-to-watch/</guid>
        <description>Mura Masa’s self-titled debut album is a refreshing display of what our generation has to offer. The Guernsey-born DJ started making tunes from his bedroom and came onto the radar when he released his song ‘Lotus Eater’ on Soundcloud in 2014. Although he has only just turned 21 he has since …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nai Palm strikes out on her own</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-nai-palm-strikes-out-on-her-own/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Montgomerie-Corcoran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-nai-palm-strikes-out-on-her-own/</guid>
        <description>Singer, songwriter, and guitarist Nai Palm has come out with her debut solo album, Needle Paw: an intimate collection of covers and originals wrapped in rich harmonies that gives a slightly new perspective on her already established compositions, as well as introducing some new and more personal …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chameleon Queen out in the open</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-chameleon-queen-out-in-the-open/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-chameleon-queen-out-in-the-open/</guid>
        <description>Writing a follow up to 2014’s gargantuan, Grammy-winning, self-titled album was never going to be an easy task for Annie Clark, so perhaps that’s why it took so long to do. Mind you, when you’re being hailed as the modern day Ziggy Stardust, you want to make sure you get things right. St. Vincent’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chasing intercontinental friendships</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-chasing-intercontinental-friendships/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-chasing-intercontinental-friendships/</guid>
        <description>Historically, collaborative albums have generally been reserved for ageing legends. Lou Reed &amp;amp; Metallica. Jay Z &amp;amp; Kanye. Eno &amp;amp; Byrne. Eno &amp;amp; Fripp. Eno &amp;amp; Cale. But if you haven’t got a string of successful glam albums and the invention of ambient music under your belt, these can …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Deep Dive into DAMN.</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-deep-dive-into-damn/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-deep-dive-into-damn/</guid>
        <description>Since dropping back-to-back classics with 2012’s good kid, m.A.A.d city (GKMC) and 2015’s To Pimp a Butterfly (TPAB), Kendrick Lamar has been relatively quiet – I would go as far as to say that we’ve had to put up with polished mediocrity in his absence. He did surprise fans with Untitled Unmastered …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Weird music made weirder</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-weird-music-made-weirder/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Lawrence,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-weird-music-made-weirder/</guid>
        <description>Footwork is no longer confined to underground venues in the South Side of Chicago. The twisted style of house music has evolved to become a muse for electronic music producers across the globe, infecting deep into the rosters of prominent UK labels such as Hyperdub and Planet Mu. This expansion of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Diverse influences make for a remarkable LP</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-diverse-influences-make-for-a-remarkable-lp/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-diverse-influences-make-for-a-remarkable-lp/</guid>
        <description>Wolf Alice is a band with a diverse set of influences. There are detectable traces of shoegaze, pop, folk, punk, grunge, and indie, to name just a few components of the musical palette brought to bear on this album.
There is never a dull minute as Ellie Roswell &amp;amp; co. leap from phrase to phrase, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Off-kilter prog-funk is one for the superfans</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-off-kilter-prog-funk-is-one-for-the-superfans/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-off-kilter-prog-funk-is-one-for-the-superfans/</guid>
        <description>Bass legend Les Claypool returns with the only band to earn its own ID3 genre tag. The band is known for off-kilter prog-funk with metal roots. Trademark syncopated riffs return with newfound minimalism. This album conceptually focuses on the “desaturating seven”, a band of goblins who chase …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Relatively un-miraculous</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-relatively-un-miraculous/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-relatively-un-miraculous/</guid>
        <description>This psych-pop album is neither particularly psychedelic nor particularly poppy, instead preferring fairly unimaginative composition and over-reliance on production.
I mean, there’s nothing /wrong/ with it. The band members are objectively skilled musicians, who play clearly and effectively …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
