<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/xerxes_chong_xian/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/xerxes_chong_xian/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Big Daddy Oil outearns Apple and Google, wants more</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-big-daddy-oil-outearns-apple-and-google-wants-more/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xerxes Chong Xian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-big-daddy-oil-outearns-apple-and-google-wants-more/</guid>
        <description>The month of April marked a historic moment for the financial markets. The Saudi Arabian Oil Company (Saudi Aramco) had its debut international bond issuance. A titan in the world of oil and gas, whose pulse is closely monitored by financial markets as a proxy to the health of one the world’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Debt and Equity: 2 sides of the same coin</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-debt-and-equity-2-sides-of-the-same-coin/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xerxes Chong Xian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-debt-and-equity-2-sides-of-the-same-coin/</guid>
        <description>Just as a plant needs water for growth, so does a business require capital to expand. Debt and equity are two sides of the same coin. A company may choose to finance itself with debt or equity or a combination of the two. The company approaches banks or investors for a loan and/or to sell a stake of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Spy Who Went Public: Aston Martin lists on LSE</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-the-spy-who-went-public-aston-martin-lists-on-lse/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xerxes Chong Xian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-the-spy-who-went-public-aston-martin-lists-on-lse/</guid>
        <description>On 3rd October 2018, the iconic British marque synonymous with James Bond debuted on the London Stock Exchange, a milestone for the historically troubled carmaker, with a past marred by several bankruptcies. The shares were priced at £19, valuing the company at £4.3bn. While most IPOs are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dark Pools: Evil place or a market place?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-dark-pools-evil-place-or-a-market-place/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xerxes Chong Xian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-dark-pools-evil-place-or-a-market-place/</guid>
        <description>Dark pools. The words invoke an atmosphere of secrecy and evil, harkening back to myths of murky waters and ancient terrors that lurk within. Throw in the modern element of trading and most imagine clandestine deals involving dubious characters straight out of The Godfather. The reality is less …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Country’s Piggy Bank</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-a-country-s-piggy-bank/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xerxes Chong Xian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-a-country-s-piggy-bank/</guid>
        <description>We’ve all heard the age-old advice; save up for a rainy day, spend a little less, invest that money and have enough to retire. Your favourite car, that house in the countryside, that trip to the Maldives you’ve been planning since the days of eating lunch at your desk. The message is clear, invest …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
