<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sarah_wong/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sarah_wong/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Can’t Stop, Won’t Stop: Science on why we can’t stop eating</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-can-t-stop-won-t-stop-science-on-why-we-can-t-stop-eating/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-can-t-stop-won-t-stop-science-on-why-we-can-t-stop-eating/</guid>
        <description>I lied to myself again: “I will just have one more,” as I engulfed the whole bag of crisps. Interestingly, this gluttonous behaviour can be explained by science, so we are not to be blamed entirely.
In the brain, there are two main types of neurones that impact our appetite in the hypothalamus: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bacteria in poop: the key to losing weight?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-bacteria-in-poop-the-key-to-losing-weight/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-bacteria-in-poop-the-key-to-losing-weight/</guid>
        <description>Summer is officially over and, temporarily, we don’t need our summer bodies. However, losing weight is not just about looking nice on sandy beaches; obesity is one of the key risk factors that causes cardiovascular disease and other chronic diseases.
Obesity is a multi-facet condition: genetics, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Does reciting the Ten Commandments reduce cheating behaviour?  </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-does-reciting-the-ten-commandments-reduce-cheating-behaviour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-does-reciting-the-ten-commandments-reduce-cheating-behaviour/</guid>
        <description>Farewell summer, and welcome to a new academic year! On the bright side, Halloween and Christmas are upon us, and you get to catch up with all your friends. On the downside, however, is the university-associated stress: coursework, presentations and examinations. Even for the post-graduates amongst …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Want to eat more healthily? Try putting on some ambient music</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-want-to-eat-more-healthily-try-putting-on-some-ambient-music/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-want-to-eat-more-healthily-try-putting-on-some-ambient-music/</guid>
        <description>When choosing our food, our conscious self is never in full control – I always let my cravings get the best of me. For instance, when I am sad I eat ice-cream; when I smell a pizza, I will instantly want to eat one. But have you ever considered how our hearing can impact on food choices?
In London, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Puppy science: Why they are so cute? </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-puppy-science-why-they-are-so-cute/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-puppy-science-why-they-are-so-cute/</guid>
        <description>I don’t know about all of you reading this, but I am crazy about puppies! However, have you ever wondered why they look so incredibly adorable, especially at a young age?
According to a recent collaborative study between the US and the Netherlands, puppies have evolved to be cute because their life …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stressed Mother, Stressed Child?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-stressed-mother-stressed-child/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-stressed-mother-stressed-child/</guid>
        <description>Before any of us were born, the only way we could get information from outside was via the senses of our mother. In terms of evolution, it would be greatly beneficial if we could respond to the external stimulation our mother’s sensed, since it would increase our chances of survival. This process of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science at the gym: the molecular basis of metabolism</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-science-at-the-gym-the-molecular-basis-of-metabolism/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-science-at-the-gym-the-molecular-basis-of-metabolism/</guid>
        <description>Exercise is good for you, we all know that. You don’t need to read an article on it – or do you? I guess the main question is, do you know how to exercise effectively?
The standard answer about the effects of exercising is that it trains heart muscles to become stronger, enabling it to pump …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Looking after your mental health in exam season</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-looking-after-your-mental-health-in-exam-season/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-looking-after-your-mental-health-in-exam-season/</guid>
        <description>Exam season is perceived as dark and full of danger. It is highly likely that you are feeling anxious, and living off energy drinks in the library – or perhaps you are one of the post-docs that survived exams since you have the time to read this! Nevertheless, this article still concerns you: maybe …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lab-grown heart  used for drug safety testing</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-lab-grown-heart-used-for-drug-safety-testing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-lab-grown-heart-used-for-drug-safety-testing/</guid>
        <description>Currently, drug safety testing has to be initially conducted on animals, before trials in humans begin. While animal models have proven to be useful, in some respects, they do not wholly mimic human reactions. One of my lecturers’ favourite examples is thalidomide – a mild sleeping tablet that was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Quickening: Why you need that kick</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-quickening-why-you-need-that-kick/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-quickening-why-you-need-that-kick/</guid>
        <description>I am not a mother myself, but I imagine having a tiny human kicking and moving around in your womb can feel quite uncomfortable. At some point, you may, out of frustration, wonder: why do they move around so much?! A research group co-led by Paula Murphy from Trinity College Dublin has been able to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I can show you the world: How gene therapy brightens the future for eye diseases</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-i-can-show-you-the-world-how-gene-therapy-brightens-the-future-for-eye-diseases/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-i-can-show-you-the-world-how-gene-therapy-brightens-the-future-for-eye-diseases/</guid>
        <description>You may have your mother’s eyes, or your father’s nose, as genetics plays a significant role in determining physical traits such as height and eye colour. But genes can also determine other things: diseases! Cystic fibrosis is an example of a disease that has a genetic basis, meaning that the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>From skin cells to stem cells?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-05-from-skin-cells-to-stem-cells/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-05-from-skin-cells-to-stem-cells/</guid>
        <description>Stem cells are unspecialised cells that can develop to form almost all cell types in your body – just like Mystique in X-men. Similar to the movies, this ‘shapeshifting’ ability makes these types of cells extremely valuable in medicine. From generating new skin for burn victims, to creating new …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How brain chemicals make you crave alcohol</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-23-how-brain-chemicals-make-you-crave-alcohol/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-23-how-brain-chemicals-make-you-crave-alcohol/</guid>
        <description>After a demanding week at university, it is finally Friday and your friends have suggested to go for drinks later that evening. ‘Ok… just one drink’, you replied, but several hours later you are smashed, and walking in a straight line is practically impossible! It is apparent that a hangover is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Work hard, play harder – how playing can improve STEM subjects</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-work-hard-play-harder-how-playing-can-improve-stem-subjects/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-work-hard-play-harder-how-playing-can-improve-stem-subjects/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London is a science, technology, engineering, and mathematics (STEM) focused university with, sadly, an uneven male to female ratio. However, the imbalance of gender in STEM subjects is not localised to Imperial – this trend can be seen across the globe. Whilst efforts had been made …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hedgehog helps cancer stem cells survive</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-hedgehog-helps-cancer-stem-cells-survive/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-hedgehog-helps-cancer-stem-cells-survive/</guid>
        <description>Having to treat cancer once is enough, but stubborn tumours often have a habit of coming back, with cancer stem cells (CSC) as the likely culprits. These notorious cells have the ability to self-renew and to give rise to all cell types found in cancer samples, contributing to tumour heterogeneity …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Organs-on-chips to study anti-cancer effects of drugs</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-organs-on-chips-to-study-anti-cancer-effects-of-drugs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-organs-on-chips-to-study-anti-cancer-effects-of-drugs/</guid>
        <description>While our iPhones get bigger by the generation, scientists are striving to keep things small in order to cut down on the cost of research. An example would be an ‘organ-on-chip’, where aspects of an organ are mimicked on a piece of polymer that is the size of your palm! The application of this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The upcoming hair dye revolution</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-the-upcoming-hair-dye-revolution/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-the-upcoming-hair-dye-revolution/</guid>
        <description>My aunt recently dyed her hair black, claiming that it would make her look younger. While her statement is highly debatable, it is certain that fashion consciousness is on the rise, leading to the growth of the hair dyeing industry. However, except for the chemists amongst us, people rarely put much …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can writing a to-do list really make you fall asleep faster?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-can-writing-a-to-do-list-really-make-you-fall-asleep-faster/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-can-writing-a-to-do-list-really-make-you-fall-asleep-faster/</guid>
        <description>Everybody has one of those nights where you stare at the ceiling in the dark, thinking about the books that you have to return by Friday, the present that you have to get grandpa for his birthday next week… the list goes on and on – and you just cannot sleep! If you can relate, this article may hold …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Learning to grow old gracefully: the inevitability of ageing</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-learning-to-grow-old-gracefully-the-inevitability-of-ageing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-learning-to-grow-old-gracefully-the-inevitability-of-ageing/</guid>
        <description>Ageing, or senescence, was considered an inescapable fate of living organisms in the past, where stories of immortality remained in the realm of science fiction. However, in recent years, scientists have developed compelling theories to propose a genetic basis to ageing, implying a means to either …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
