<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/cl3510/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/cl3510/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>They came, sword and conquered
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-they-came-sword-and-conquered/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 00:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charlotte C Levin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-they-came-sword-and-conquered/</guid>
        <description>The guys started on Saturday, facing Bristol. Their opponents had lost one of their main fencers, but gained an international who held his ground well in foil and epee. Whilst the epeeists found the going tough, losing their match 32-45, the foilists were able to even out the score through a 45-35 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Double BUCS Fencing Champions
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-25-double-bucs-fencing-champions/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2011 14:56:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charlotte C Levin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-25-double-bucs-fencing-champions/</guid>
        <description>Imperial Fencing’s first teams came to the BUCS Championships semi-finals with an amazing season in the bag. Both of the teams were undefeated in their leagues and had confidently gone through their knock out rounds. In everyone’s mind were the double silvers from last year, where both men and women …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Videogames &#43; Music = AWESOME
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-18-videogames-music-awesome/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 08:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charlotte C Levin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-18-videogames-music-awesome/</guid>
        <description>Have you ever felt like going to a pub, having a couple of pints, playing some old style video games and hanging out with friends? Yes? Well, you’re not alone. Two guys, Nicholas Thurgood (Nicky) and David Lightfoot (Dave), have just started running a monthly event called Nintendisco. The basic idea …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fencing: Men’s firsts discover the concept of a clean sweep while advancing to BUCS semi-final
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-fencing-mens-firsts-discover-the-concept-of-a-clean-sweep-while-advancing-to-bucs-semi-final/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 21:27:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charlotte C Levin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-fencing-mens-firsts-discover-the-concept-of-a-clean-sweep-while-advancing-to-bucs-semi-final/</guid>
        <description>Men’s first fencing team had a visit by University of Bath’s first team on Wednesday afternoon.
With the women’s advancement to the semi-finals of BUCS Championships just an hour earlier, the men wanted to keep their pride and join the ladies in Sheffield.
The match started a bit later than planned, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fencers wipe the floor at BUCS league
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-fencers-wipe-the-floor-at-bucs-league/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 20:39:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charlotte C Levin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-fencers-wipe-the-floor-at-bucs-league/</guid>
        <description>The second and final weekend of Men’s and Women’s, BUCS Southern Premier League took at place at Ethos on the 28th-29th January. Going into the weekend both Imperial teams looked strong contenders for their respective titles, being undefeated in the first weekend. Expectations on further victories …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Fencing keep their run of victories intact
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-imperial-fencing-keep-their-run-of-victories-intact/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 20:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charlotte C Levin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-imperial-fencing-keep-their-run-of-victories-intact/</guid>
        <description>It’s a Saturday morning in Cambridge as Imperial Fencing’s first men’s team arrive at the sports venue. Ahead of them lays their first BUCS weekend of the year, with matches against University of Oxford, University of Cambridge, Bristol University and University of London Union (ULU).
They’re first …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial fencers return with medals of two metals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-imperial-fencers-return-with-medals-of-two-metals/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 20:52:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charlotte C Levin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-imperial-fencers-return-with-medals-of-two-metals/</guid>
        <description>It was a crisp Saturday morning as a group of Imperial fencers headed out to St Paul’s School Sports Hall for the London Team Trophy.
The number of entries for the competition was its highest ever, with 16 epee teams, 16 foil teams and 12 sabre teams, making the competition the second biggest team …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
