<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jlc14/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jlc14/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Cultural appropriation should not be an excuse to limit cultural exchange</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-30-cultural-appropriation-should-not-be-an-excuse-to-limit-cultural-exchange/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jian Chew,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-30-cultural-appropriation-should-not-be-an-excuse-to-limit-cultural-exchange/</guid>
        <description>I read with appreciation Chimdi Igwe’s response to my article on cultural appropriation, but take slight to his saying my article was satirical at best. It was meant to be entirely satirical, from head to toe.
The reason I disagree with the notion of cultural appropriation is due to my experience …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Starting a great crusade against cultural appropriation</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-starting-a-great-crusade-against-cultural-appropriation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jian Chew,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-starting-a-great-crusade-against-cultural-appropriation/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday morning I woke up to the news that, horror of horrors, a white girl in America wore a qipao/cheongsam to her prom. Social Justice Warriors (SJWs) on the internet were lambasting and criticising her for culturally appropriating a traditional (actually classical: it only came into …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Making my life great again
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-making-my-life-great-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 15:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jian Chew,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-making-my-life-great-again/</guid>
        <description>As I watched Trump’s inauguration ceremony at fivesixeight, where I work, and observed exuberant Americans celebrating with champagne, I got thinking about my life. It’s been in a rut lately, just doing my tutorial sheets, coursework, revising, cooking my meals, feeling homesick over Chinese New …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I&#39;m sorry. I made a mistake.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-im-sorry-i-made-a-mistake/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jian Chew,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-im-sorry-i-made-a-mistake/</guid>
        <description>After the publishing of my article last week, I was informed that The Telegraph article on which I based my own, which was picked up from The Daily Mail, was a gross misrepresentation of SOAS Student Union’s campaign. Reading the official SU statement, I am here to retract my previous article and to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Decolonising philosophy? SOAS, get real!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-decolonising-philosophy-soas-get-real/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jian Chew,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-decolonising-philosophy-soas-get-real/</guid>
        <description>So The Telegraph reported that the SOAS’s Student Union wants the university to decolonise its philosophy to remove Plato, Descartes and Kant. I read it just after having a pint of ale at Eastside to forget the tragedy that was my Structural Mechanics paper and my Asian flush made my face redder …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Decolonising my mind, decolonising my life
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-28-decolonising-my-mind-decolonising-my-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 15:02:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jian Chew,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-28-decolonising-my-mind-decolonising-my-life/</guid>
        <description>Last Tuesday I watched a viral video showing Social Justice Warriors (SJWs) at the University of Cape Town, South Africa, decrying science as racist because it was developed by European scientists and isn’t applicable to Africa. Also, magic is real and science cannot explain how witch doctors can …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In defence of ales
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-in-defence-of-ales/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 09:48:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jian Chew,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-in-defence-of-ales/</guid>
        <description>Every Friday I pick up a copy of FELIX to glance at the headline, look at the centrefold to see if I recognise anyone in it, quietly complain to myself that my half-hearted attempts at developing a six-pack have yet to succeed, read Hangman, lament the fact that it&amp;rsquo;s only one page long, and …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
