<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/as906/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/as906/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Educating the masses on Funding
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-educating-the-masses-on-funding/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 20:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrew Tranter,Alex Savell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-educating-the-masses-on-funding/</guid>
        <description>Higher Education Funding (HEF) is certainly not sexy. Like British Politics it has all the charisma of your average British politician. But it is important. It’s important because defining the future of how Universities receive funding is something that will affect thousands of young people who (for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Higher Education Fees Debate - Tuition Fees
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-6-higher-education-fees-debate-tuition-fees/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 02:42:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Savell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-6-higher-education-fees-debate-tuition-fees/</guid>
        <description>So, I am the poor schmuck who has to try to sell Tuition fees to the people already most disenfranchised with them. It’s my job to tell you all why running up a debt of £9000 per year on tuition fees (alongside other costs) is the best idea out there… oh, and I get 750 words to make that sale, 60 of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ArtsFest is Coming, Look Busy!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-19-artsfest-is-coming-look-busy/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 17:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Savell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-19-artsfest-is-coming-look-busy/</guid>
        <description>Yes the biggest event of the union calendar has arrived. And I don’t mean the Big Elections. ArtsFest sees our scientists’ paradise turned over to our Artistic under culture for a week of something different. The festivities this year include lunchtime concerts, an art exhibit, singing, dancing, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lions Rampant at Polo Nationals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-29-lions-rampant-at-polo-nationals/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 15:44:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Savell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-29-lions-rampant-at-polo-nationals/</guid>
        <description>I’d like to say that there is some really good reason for how long this article has taken to come out. You’d think given this is my personal highest achievement at the Polo Nationals in the last 5 years that I’d have managed to get it out quickly. But no, life and, more annoyingly, work goes on. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Nano Flower
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-the-nano-flower/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 14:38:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Savell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-the-nano-flower/</guid>
        <description>In just a day’s time Peter Hamilton will be arriving for Sci-Fi’s annual convention, Picocon. Before that we finish off our look at the Greg Mandel series with a look at the final novel in that series; The Nano Flower. Set fifteen year’s after A Quantum Murder there’s plenty that’s changed in that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Quantum Murder
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-a-quantum-murder/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 22:39:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Savell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-a-quantum-murder/</guid>
        <description>Don’t get me wrong, I have not done a U-Turn on the Greg Mandel series in the last week; I am neither an Italian, nor a member of a Coalition Government. I am still an advocate of the series and of the man, and will be in avid attendance when he speaks at the Sci-Fi Society’s Picocon Convention in a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Jewel in the Coronet
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-the-jewel-in-the-coronet/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 01:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Savell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-the-jewel-in-the-coronet/</guid>
        <description>If my undergrad is anything to go by most people don’t spend a huge amount of time in Notting Hill Gate. You might make it up to Edgeware Road or into Bayswater for a year but for the most part those I know spend most of their time hanging out in Fulham or Shepherd’s Bush. Everything in Notting Hill …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Mindstar was Rising
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-a-mindstar-was-rising/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 00:24:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Savell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-a-mindstar-was-rising/</guid>
        <description>To those that follow the science fiction scene Peter Hamilton will most likely be a name that sets bells ringing. For me the name stand up next to all the other modern giants; Banks, Reynolds, Baxter and so on and Hamilton’s Night’s Dawn Trilogy will be familiar to many as the sort of epic space …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Preserving your judgement
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-preserving-your-judgement/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 12:34:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Savell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-preserving-your-judgement/</guid>
        <description>It’s a hard thing, striking a balance between hotel dining room and proper restaurant. The prospect instantly calls to mind several possibilities: the over cushioned, shag-pile of a seaside resort; or the soulless, whitewashed canteen – scrubbed so hard it removed all personality in its quest to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC Polo “wets” appetite
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-ic-polo-wets-appetite/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 21:24:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Savell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-ic-polo-wets-appetite/</guid>
        <description>This year’s summer weather wasn’t the greatest for polo and for the first time in a number of years the weather forecast looked extremely grim when we headed off to Royal Leamington Spa for the Schools and Universities Polo Nationals. On the upside the Jubilee weekend fell perfectly to give us a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ponies, snow and a broken jaw at polo nationals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-ponies-snow-and-a-broken-jaw-at-polo-nationals/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 21:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Savell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-ponies-snow-and-a-broken-jaw-at-polo-nationals/</guid>
        <description>It’s actually getting pretty tough to remember how many polo nationals I’ve been to these days. However, this year, with a new venue in the Midlands, we were expecting something a bit different and a bit special. With some stunning new club shirts courtesy of the extremely generous Rydges Hotel …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The pick of this year’s Picocon
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-the-pick-of-this-years-picocon/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 21:24:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Savell,Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-the-pick-of-this-years-picocon/</guid>
        <description> _Keeping it Real _by Justina Robson With a title like _Keeping it Real _and a cover illustration of a semi-cyborg super woman you might be forgiven for assuming the first book of Justina Robson’s _Quantum Gravity _series is the kind of escapist trash that has us all hating on Stephanie Meyer. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sticks, balls and deepest darkest Bristol
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-25-sticks-balls-and-deepest-darkest-bristol/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2011 15:14:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Savell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-25-sticks-balls-and-deepest-darkest-bristol/</guid>
        <description>The problem with starting a tournament on a Thursday during reading week is that we don’t get a reading week. As such it was a somewhat slapdash crew that converged on Clevedon for the University Polo Nationals. Despite what might charitably be described as an exuberant driving style from one of our …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
