<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/dww07/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/dww07/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Reverse-aging would make life unfair. More unfair than it already is
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-reverse-aging-would-make-life-unfair-more-unfair-than-it-already-is/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 21:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Daniel W L Wan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-reverse-aging-would-make-life-unfair-more-unfair-than-it-already-is/</guid>
        <description>Let’s start by confirming the fact that what scientists managed to achieve with those mice will probably never be emulated in humans.
Call me a sceptic, but let’s call off all hope for any sort of bona fide ‘reverse-aging treatment’ for humans in the foreseeable future. I mean, we’re so far away …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Ode to the City
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-2-an-ode-to-the-city/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2010 07:17:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Daniel W L Wan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-2-an-ode-to-the-city/</guid>
        <description>This is a tough job. Combine the thousands of clubs there are in London with the overbearing feeling that I’m approaching a very premature mid-life crisis and you’ll understand why introducing London’s nightlife to a Fresher is incredibly difficult.
Not only do different people dance on different …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College staff member attack&#39;s student&#39;s guest at Union
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-21-college-staff-member-attacks-students-guest-at-union/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 21:39:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Daniel W L Wan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-21-college-staff-member-attacks-students-guest-at-union/</guid>
        <description>Violence erupted at the Union on Friday night after a guest of an Imperial student was left with a bloody face after being attacked by a member of College staff on his last day of work.
Reports from the night suggest the attack was unprovoked and sudden, and occurred at around 1.30am as the Union …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Honeymoon period? There wasn&#39;t one
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-8-honeymoon-period-there-wasnt-one/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 16:44:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Daniel W L Wan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-8-honeymoon-period-there-wasnt-one/</guid>
        <description>All I bloody hear is the clock ticking. We all know what that sounds like, and we all know what the stabbing sounds of each second, ‘tick’ or ‘tock’, means. Time is slipping away, and there’s just about nothing we can do to stop it (short from building a DeLorean and taking a joyride with Marty …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fighting for Libel Reform
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-8-fighting-for-libel-reform/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 16:10:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Daniel W L Wan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-8-fighting-for-libel-reform/</guid>
        <description>As Imperial alumnus Simon Singh prepares to return to College to give a guest lecture on the libel laws in science of which he has fallen foul of, the Government have announced the commencement of a working group on libel reform.
Singh announced his support of potential reform to guests of the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
