<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ad4013/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ad4013/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The Lives of Others | Master of None S2
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-lives-of-others-master-of-none-s2/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 17:03:24 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-lives-of-others-master-of-none-s2/</guid>
        <description>Two years ago, comedian Aziz Ansari debuted his Netflix original series, Master of None. The show proved to be a critical darling, charming viewers with its mix of insightfulness, comedy, and genuineness. After its stellar first season, the series took a one year break; only recently did it return …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Death in Dreamland | Archer S8
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-death-in-dreamland-archer-s8/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:08:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-death-in-dreamland-archer-s8/</guid>
        <description>The ever popular action-spy-office-whatever comedy returns for yet another season; one that again opts to change the show’s setting altogether. Given the show’s relatively niche premise, and its ever-falling viewership, it’s quite impressive that it has made it this far. It has even managed to be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Course Correction | Doctor Who
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-course-correction-doctor-who/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:21:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-course-correction-doctor-who/</guid>
        <description>Halfway into the latest season of Doctor Who, set to be Peter Capaldi and showrunner Steven Moffat’s last, we have yet to be disappointed. After a rocky few seasons, the show began to show signs of recovery with last Christmas’ delightful, superhero themed fix. The first six episodes of series ten …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Worthy of Worship | American Gods
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-worthy-of-worship-american-gods/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 17:14:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-worthy-of-worship-american-gods/</guid>
        <description>After a tumultuous five years in development hell, Neil Gaiman’s post-modern blend of Americana and folklore has finally found its way to TV courtesy of Starz and Amazon. American Gods, an adaptation of Gaiman’s 2001 novel by the same name, is at its heart an examination of faith and the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jack’s back | Samurai Jack
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-jacks-back-samurai-jack/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 17:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-jacks-back-samurai-jack/</guid>
        <description>After an 11 year hiatus, cult-classic Samurai Jack makes a long awaited return to our screens. Wandering samurai Jack is still locked in an uphill battle against the demon Aku, and still stuck in a hellish future spawned from him. Genndy Tartakovsky’s aesthetic delight begins in media res, as had …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Life with Archie | Riverdale
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-life-with-archie-riverdale/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 15:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-life-with-archie-riverdale/</guid>
        <description>You can now add Riverdale to the increasing list of media adaptations of various forms of literature. Like most recent adaptations, Riverdale also goes for a darker and edgier feel; however in this case, this approach pulls off and actually works spectacularly well. Riverdale is based upon the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Peace, Love, and Death Metal | Nos Amis
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-peace-love-and-death-metal-nos-amis/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 15:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-peace-love-and-death-metal-nos-amis/</guid>
        <description>Colin Hanks’ directorial debut, Nos Amis, is a powerful albeit atypical music documentary. Opting to focus on the humanity of its subjects far more than their music, this HBO production follows the band Eagles of Death Metal as they attempt to recover from their ordeal at the Bataclan. An impactful …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Seeing Green
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-seeing-green/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:32:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-seeing-green/</guid>
        <description> Remember the good old days, when we had the environment themed shows like Captain Planet? Well, if you miss that era, here are some shows that’ll help you get your fill of green TV.
Zoo Zoo is a bizarre little beast that works wonderfully as a TV show precisely because all of its individual …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Criminally short | The Benefits of Gusbandry
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-criminally-short-the-benefits-of-gusbandry/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 15:56:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-criminally-short-the-benefits-of-gusbandry/</guid>
        <description>Built from the ground up by creator Alicia J. Rose, this series of ten-ish minute shorts chronicles the ever-evolving relationship between 40-something Oregonite Jackie, and her so-called ‘gay husband’, River. Now, to the uninitiated (as I was) this may conjure up images of cringe-worthy sitcom …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The rising chorus of South Asian voices
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-the-rising-chorus-of-south-asian-voices/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 17:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-the-rising-chorus-of-south-asian-voices/</guid>
        <description>Last Saturday, Aziz Ansari continued his meteoric rise to prominence by being the first person of South Asian descent to host SNL. In his speech, he highlights the rise of a so-called ‘lower-case KKK’; the subtle resurgence and renormalisation of white supremacy. Now more than ever, he suggests, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Problematic faves | J Cole and Jesse Hughes
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-problematic-faves-j-cole-and-jesse-hughes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:21:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-problematic-faves-j-cole-and-jesse-hughes/</guid>
        <description>Alas, poor Jermaine. Forest Hills Drive was a huge success, the wider public had recognised your musical and lyrical talent, and you were being mentioned in the same breath as the likes of Kendrick; you’d made it big. Why did you have to sabotage it all by taking shots at Yeezy? Now, beef is nothing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Trivial Pursuits | Sherlock
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-trivial-pursuits-sherlock/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:43:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-trivial-pursuits-sherlock/</guid>
        <description>After last year’s somewhat disappointing bait and switch, Sherlock has finally returned with a full season this holiday period. The Six Thatchers picks up immediately where we left off at the end of the previous episode, with the government leaping into action over Moriarty’s seeming return. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Crowning Glory | The Crown
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-crowning-glory-the-crown/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 15:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-crowning-glory-the-crown/</guid>
        <description>The Crown isn’t just one of the most anticipated shows of the year, but if the rumors of its budget of £100 million an episode are true, it’s also one of the most expensive. This is Netflix’s attempt at trying out something more traditional yet different (at least by Netflix standards) at the same …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Best of TV
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-the-best-of-tv/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 15:12:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-the-best-of-tv/</guid>
        <description> 1. Bojack Horseman The typically sharp and piercing animated Netflix show continues to enthrall. This year, we watched Bojack struggling to deal with a resurgence in his fame, as all his friends gradually drift away.
This season graced us with an absolutely beautiful silent underwater episode; …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Worst of TV
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-the-worst-of-tv/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 15:09:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-the-worst-of-tv/</guid>
        <description> 1. MacGyver Because apparently some people still haven’t been completely burned by the idea of rebooting 80s franchises, here comes MacGyver. A completely half-assed, badly acted cash grab, this series barely feigns an attempt at emulating its ideal. There’s no suspense, and the pacing is bizzare. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Grand Tour
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-the-grand-tour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 15:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-the-grand-tour/</guid>
        <description>Top Gear is dead. Long Live Top Gear? Following Jeremy Clarkson’s, lets face it, rightful dismissal from the BBC and the subsequent decline of Top Gear’s quality, fans have been hanging their hopes on The Grand Tour. Thankfully, the new series does not disappoint. Well, mostly.
The series begins …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Big Talk | Speechless
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-big-talk-speechless/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 15:06:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-big-talk-speechless/</guid>
        <description>Ever since the success of the show, ABC seems to have made ‘Modern Family’ its motto. Leading the charge on diverse sitcoms, in recent years it has put out excellent shows like Black-ish, Fresh off the boat and, now, Speechless. This sitcom follows the DiMeo family as they relocate to a new town in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Revolutionary viewing
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-revolutionary-viewing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 14:29:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-revolutionary-viewing/</guid>
        <description> TURN: Washington’s Spies One of AMC’s suite of dramas it hoped would take the reigns from Mad Men, TURN takes viewers to the American Revolutionary War. The show follows the Culper Ring, an unlikely group of farmers who banded together to help George Washington win the war. Be warned though, it is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Albert Camus | The Rebel
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-albert-camus-the-rebel/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 14:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-albert-camus-the-rebel/</guid>
        <description>In Rick Famuyiwa’s Dope, Jay-Z’s Blueprint is described as the &amp;ldquo;punctuation mark to 90s Hip-hop&amp;rdquo;. It seems to me that, in many ways, Albert Camus’ The Rebel is the punctuation mark to 19th, and early 20th century philosophy. Camus is often regarded, rightly, as an absurdist and, more …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>TV mourns for Adonaïs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-tv-mourns-for-adonas/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 15:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-tv-mourns-for-adonas/</guid>
        <description>    Marianne O&amp;#39;Leary   Television has, historically speaking, been a fairly progressive medium. Whether it was Star Trek in the 60s pushing for minority rights, or shows like Will &amp;amp; Grace and Ellen normalising and publicising LGBT rights in the 90s, TV has frequently been willing and capable …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Tick
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-the-tick/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 17:55:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-the-tick/</guid>
        <description>Before Deadpool was a mote in creator Rob Liefeld’s eye, beloved superhero parodies have long been a cult favourite. As part of Amazon’s latest round of original programming, The Tick returns to our screens, now played by Peter Serafinowicz, in a decidedly more complex adaptation compared to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Good Place
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-the-good-place/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 17:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-the-good-place/</guid>
        <description>Becker, Ted Danson’s underrated late 90s sitcom gem, was something of a staple of my formative years. So, naturally, when a new sitcom with his involvement was announced, I took notice. The Good Place follows one Eleanor Shellstrop, played by Kristen Bell, who dies in a freak erectile …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Humans 2.0: Human Harder
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-1-humans-20-human-harder/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 00:09:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-1-humans-20-human-harder/</guid>
        <description>After Humans first premiered in the summer of 2015, few knew what exactly to expect. The show clearly had significant acting clout behind it, and its subtle marketing campaign was quick to pique the interest of the viewing public. Sure enough, the series managed to live up to, and even surpass, its …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Kardashian kingdom
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-1-the-kardashian-kingdom/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 00:07:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-1-the-kardashian-kingdom/</guid>
        <description>The Kardashians’ long standing affair with the media began in 1994, when Robert Kardashian Sr. thrust the family into the limelight defending his friend O. J. Simpson. In the following decades, members of the clan have appeared sporadically throughout various media. Kim Kardashian, in particular, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Half a century of boldly going...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-14-half-a-century-of-boldly-going/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 10:30:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Selin Olenik,Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-14-half-a-century-of-boldly-going/</guid>
        <description> Fifty years ago, as the spectre of the Cold War loomed over the world and the first battles of the civil rights movement were being fought, a corny, slightly overacted show with bold utopian and egalitarian aspirations made its way onto the prime-time lineup. Trek wore its heart on its sleeve, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Charting the Evolution of South Park
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-10-charting-the-evolution-of-south-park/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 12:42:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-10-charting-the-evolution-of-south-park/</guid>
        <description>For the last twenty years, Comedy Central has graced our screens with a getaway from the crassness of modern life: the idyllic Colorado town of South Park. It may seem remarkable that a show with such seemingly low effort animation has made it two decades but, as any watcher will tell you, the lack …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your summer of binge watching
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-your-summer-of-binge-watching/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 09:33:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-your-summer-of-binge-watching/</guid>
        <description>Summer’s here, which means actual free time again without the constant spectre of revision hanging over your head. You might be wondering just what to do with it all. Well, there’s always the classic fall-back; say ‘screw it’ and watch some TV. Here’s a list of eight great shows to help you do just …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This Week on Game of Thrones
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-this-week-on-game-of-thrones/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 09:04:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-this-week-on-game-of-thrones/</guid>
        <description>It’s a fairly eventful week in the most recent, unfortunately weaker, episode of Game of Thrones. Right off the bat, we’re treated to perhaps one of the biggest reveals in the series; the origin of the White Walkers. The problems start here, because this scene sorely lacks the gravitas it requires …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This week on Game of Thrones
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-this-week-on-game-of-thrones/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 10:17:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-this-week-on-game-of-thrones/</guid>
        <description>Following last week’s relatively uneventful, measured episode, Game of Thrones cranks the dial up to eleven with this one. Last time was the safety briefing; now we’ve hit the first drop on the rollercoaster.
We open in Winterfell of old, as Bran and the Three-eyed Raven watch the previous …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The People vs O.J. Simpson
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-the-people-vs-oj-simpson/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 12:06:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-the-people-vs-oj-simpson/</guid>
        <description>The year of 1994 was a wildly different time. Institutional racism in America was under the limelight following the release of footage of police brutality against an unarmed black man. The public imagination was infatuated with a murder trial that didn’t quite make sense and seemed to unfairly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Vinyl grooves
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-vinyl-grooves/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 11:55:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-vinyl-grooves/</guid>
        <description>This show really snuck up on me. HBO seems to have pushed it out without the sort of fanfare one would expect; especially given the names attached to this project. When Martin Scorsese and Mick Jagger say they’re doing something together, you pay attention. So, I decided to give the two hour …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Triumph of War and Peace
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-the-triumph-of-war-and-peace/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 11:58:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-the-triumph-of-war-and-peace/</guid>
        <description>When it was announced that the BBC would be producing another adaptation of Tolstoy’s epic tome, I, like many others, was intrigued. Then came the news that veteran showrunner Andrew Davies, who has written or produced for the likes of everything from Bridget Jones to Pride and Prejudice, would be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Retro Retrospective: Mad Men
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-8-retro-retrospective-mad-men/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 17:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-8-retro-retrospective-mad-men/</guid>
        <description>Last year marked the end of lots of things; Jon Stewart’s run on the Daily Show, Bill Cosby’s career, Meek Mill’s career, 2014, and many beloved TV shows. Of these, one was Mad Men, a series I discovered, binge watched, and fell in love with, all in the space of about two weeks. Centring on the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mozart in the Jungle
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-mozart-in-the-jungle/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 12:45:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-mozart-in-the-jungle/</guid>
        <description>If you followed this year’s Golden Globes, you might’ve been surprised by Mozart in the Jungle sweeping the Best Television series – Comedy, and Best Actor in a Television series – Musical or Comedy categories. By virtue of being an Amazon Original, this show has flown under most people’s radars.
I …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
