<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/kmw13/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/kmw13/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix is shortlisted for Club of the Year at imperial College Union Awards 2015
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-19-felix-is-shortlisted-for-club-of-the-year-at-imperial-college-union-awards-2015/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 13:33:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-19-felix-is-shortlisted-for-club-of-the-year-at-imperial-college-union-awards-2015/</guid>
        <description>Felix was shortlisted for Club of the Year at Monday’s Union Awards ceremony, much to the club&amp;rsquo;s delight. Sadly Felix closly missed out on taking the award home, which went instead to Islamic Society, but all were very deserved of the award.
The other shortlisted societies were A Cappella, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>State of the art gym for Woodward
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-4-state-of-the-art-gym-for-woodward/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2015 23:15:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-4-state-of-the-art-gym-for-woodward/</guid>
        <description>A leading fitness equipment company has agreed a deal with Imperial College London to design and kit-out a new state of the art gym in the new Woodward halls in Acton. Pulse Fitness, who have also created gyms at 500 further and higher education institutions in the country, including King’s College …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial signs research deal in Qatar
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-4-imperial-signs-research-deal-in-qatar/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2015 23:14:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-4-imperial-signs-research-deal-in-qatar/</guid>
        <description>On Tuesday 2nd June, Imperial College London signed an agreement with Qatar University (QU) and the Qatar Shell Research and Technology Centre (QSTRC) that covered corrosion prevention in wet sour gas pipelines.
The signing took place at Qatar University. The deal was signed by representatives from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Study by Imperial Professor raises fears for diabetes screening in India
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-study-by-imperial-professor-raises-fears-for-diabetes-screening-in-india/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 01:03:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-study-by-imperial-professor-raises-fears-for-diabetes-screening-in-india/</guid>
        <description>A study conducted by a team including a professor from Imperial College London has suggested that the large-scale diabetes screening programme in India will result in the public health system being overwhelmed.
The programme, which aims to screen the general population for type two diabetes, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An IPL Contract, an Autobiography, and a lack of trust: the Kevin Pietersen saga
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-21-an-ipl-contract-an-autobiography-and-a-lack-of-trust-the-kevin-pietersen-saga/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2015 20:25:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-21-an-ipl-contract-an-autobiography-and-a-lack-of-trust-the-kevin-pietersen-saga/</guid>
        <description>If Andrew Strauss thought he’d have a pleasant honeymoon period in his new Director of Cricket role at the England and Wales Cricket Board (ECB), Kevin Pietersen had other ideas. As Strauss was partaking in his first interview with the media in the role Kevin Pietersen was piling the pressure on, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>International Students boost economy by £2.3 billion
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-21-international-students-boost-economy-by-23-billion/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2015 20:08:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-21-international-students-boost-economy-by-23-billion/</guid>
        <description>A report by London First has said that overseas students in London alone contribute as much as £2.3 billion to the economy. The report also claims that students from abroad are made to feel “unwelcome”. It goes on to argue that migration targets should be reclassified and students should be given …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Citizen Science Project Expands
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-21-imperial-citizen-science-project-expands/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2015 19:57:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-21-imperial-citizen-science-project-expands/</guid>
        <description>Open Air Laboratories (OPAL), a citizen science project run by Imperial College London, has expanded to cover the entirety of the United Kingdom.
The project, which was initially launched in 2007, is being rolled out across Wales, Northern Ireland and Scotland courtesy of a grant from the Big …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Late resurgence not good enough for Medics
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-19-late-resurgence-not-good-enough-for-medics/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 23:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-19-late-resurgence-not-good-enough-for-medics/</guid>
        <description>A late resurgence from the Imperial Medicals was not enough to prevent a victory for the Imperial College team in the first ever Varsity fixture held at The Stoop for women’s rugby. It was a low scoring game of ten-a-side rugby that was decided on a few beautiful breakaway tries. For long periods of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Late tries add gloss to College victory
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-19-late-tries-add-gloss-to-college-victory/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 23:39:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-19-late-tries-add-gloss-to-college-victory/</guid>
        <description>Two dominant periods at the start and end of the match ensured that Imperial College claimed a more than comfortable victory over the Imperial Medicals at The Stoop on Wednesday. Having scored an early penalty, the College then put away two unanswered tries before the Medics hit back to give …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s time for football fans to reap the benefits
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-its-time-for-football-fans-to-reap-the-benefits/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 19:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-its-time-for-football-fans-to-reap-the-benefits/</guid>
        <description>A
fortnight ago, the Premier League unveiled their latest deal for broadcast rights in the United Kingdom. In an increase of a massive (and unexpected) 70%, the deal for 2016-2019 is valued at £5.1 billion. This keeps the Premier League comfortably at the top of the revenue charts of football …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Four mouth-watering clashes at this World Cup
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-four-mouth-watering-clashes-at-this-world-cup/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 22:57:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-four-mouth-watering-clashes-at-this-world-cup/</guid>
        <description> Australia v England Melbourne Cricket Ground, 14th February
The first game in Australia in the tournament is one of the biggest there can be. Both sides will be looking to make an early statement to their group about what to expect.
India v Pakistan Adelaide Oval, 15th February
The opening weekend …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is the best format?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-what-is-the-best-format/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 22:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-what-is-the-best-format/</guid>
        <description>If there is one thing that can be said about the ICC Cricket World Cup, it’s that over the years, the International Cricket Council (ICC) themselves have been very unsure over what the best format is. A large amount of this has been down to the debate over how many teams there should be in the World …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Come, let’s live the dream again”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-come-lets-live-the-dream-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 22:43:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-come-lets-live-the-dream-again/</guid>
        <description> Pool A England Best World Cup Performance: Final (1987, 1992)
ODI Ranking: 5
Key Player: After England installed him as captain Eoin Morgan will be desperate to prove that the decision to remove Alistair Cook as captain is justified.
But also look out for: Alex Hales and Jos Buttler are explosive …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial win The Bhangra Showdown
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-imperial-win-the-bhangra-showdown/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 21:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-imperial-win-the-bhangra-showdown/</guid>
        <description>Last week the team from Imperial College London won The Bhangra Showdown (TBS) at Wembley Arena. The event, which was in its eighth year, was organised by seven committee members from the Imperial Punjabi Society. In previous years the competition has been held at the Hammersmith Apollo, and was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bus drivers to go on strike on Thursday
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-4-bus-drivers-to-go-on-strike-on-thursday/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 13:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-4-bus-drivers-to-go-on-strike-on-thursday/</guid>
        <description>On Thursday 5th February bus drivers will go on strike in a protest over pay. It will be the second time this year that a strike has taken place this calendar year over the issue, and a further two walkouts are scheduled for February 13th and February 16th.
Transport for London (TfL) has released a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Taking another step into the smartphone world
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-taking-another-step-into-the-smartphone-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 18:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-taking-another-step-into-the-smartphone-world/</guid>
        <description>This week Felix released the latest version of its app for iPhone. It includes a major revamp of the way it works, adding benefits both in its user interface and in its engine for the user. Today Felix Technology takes a look at what we should expect from the latest addition to _Felix_’s digital …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NBA Star John Amaechi visits Ethos
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-nba-star-john-amaechi-visits-ethos/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 01:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-nba-star-john-amaechi-visits-ethos/</guid>
        <description>National Basketball Association (NBA) star John Amaechi visited Imperial College London’s sports centre Ethos last week as part of a promotional drive for the Global Games London. Amaechi is widely regarded as one of the best British players in NBA history.
Amaechi had attended the event as part of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Women’s rugby team to headline at the Stoop
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-womens-rugby-team-to-headline-at-the-stoop/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 00:49:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-womens-rugby-team-to-headline-at-the-stoop/</guid>
        <description>The Women’s Rugby team have been asked to play their Varsity match after the JPR Williams Cup at the Stoop in Twickenham. The match, which will take place on 18th March, will be contested with ten players a side. It will be 20 minutes each way, to form a 40-minute match. The logistics of the rest of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>KP, Southampton and Roger Federer. What have you missed in sport?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-16-kp-southampton-and-roger-federer-what-have-you-missed-in-sport/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 15:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-16-kp-southampton-and-roger-federer-what-have-you-missed-in-sport/</guid>
        <description>A lot has happened in football over the Christmas holidays. From a position of relative strength Chelsea drew against Southampton and lost to Tottenham to allow Manchester City back into the title race. After the Tottenham defeat Chelsea and Manchester City could in fact only be separated by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All change come elections time
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-16-all-change-come-elections-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 13:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-16-all-change-come-elections-time/</guid>
        <description>Plans have been announced to change election regulations for clubs that have more than 150 members. Under the changes, clubs that hit the criteria would have to hold their committee elections as part of the Big Elections. Despite this, voting would still only be available for members of that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Here’s what you may have missed! Felix wraps up a stellar 2014
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-12-heres-what-you-may-have-missed-felix-wraps-up-a-stellar-2014/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 13:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-12-heres-what-you-may-have-missed-felix-wraps-up-a-stellar-2014/</guid>
        <description>It has been a busy year for Imperial College, with the Union and the University alike giving Felix lots of material and good reason to go to print (most of the time).
In January, College announced it would be conducting its Residential Experience Review, something we would see the results of this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Liverpool, Tiger Woods and doping – the World Sport Column
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-11-liverpool-tiger-woods-and-doping-the-world-sport-column/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 23:41:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-11-liverpool-tiger-woods-and-doping-the-world-sport-column/</guid>
        <description>Liverpool saw their Champions League dreams end with a 1-1 draw against Basel. Brendan Rodgers’ team needed to win to qualify, but will instead have to settle with the Europa League. Arsenal, who had already qualified, thumped Galatasaray 4-1, with Aaron Ramsey scoring an early contender for goal of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What sport should you look out for this Christmas?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-11-what-sport-should-you-look-out-for-this-christmas/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 23:39:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-11-what-sport-should-you-look-out-for-this-christmas/</guid>
        <description>Football
_Sunday 21st December: _
_Liverpool vs Arsenal. _
Liverpool have had a poor start to the season, and Arsenal have not looked secure, despite qualifying for the last 16 in the Champions League.
_Sunday 28th December: _
_Tottenham v Man Utd. _
Right in the middle of the busy Christmas season, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>#PutOutYourBats, Chelsea and Jules Bianchi – the World Sport Column
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-putoutyourbats-chelsea-and-jules-bianchi-the-world-sport-column/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 20:54:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-putoutyourbats-chelsea-and-jules-bianchi-the-world-sport-column/</guid>
        <description>Cricketer Phillip Hughes was laid to rest at his funeral in his hometown in Macksville, New South Wales, on Wednesday. Australian captain Michael Clarke gave an emotional eulogy after acting as a pall bearer. Hughes, who would have turned 26 on Sunday, was struck by a bouncer last Tuesday, and died …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Phil Hughes, Lewis Hamilton and SPOTY - the World Sport Column
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-phil-hughes-lewis-hamilton-and-spoty-the-world-sport-column/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 01:08:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-phil-hughes-lewis-hamilton-and-spoty-the-world-sport-column/</guid>
        <description>In the early hours of Thursday, Australia batsman Phil Hughes was pronounced dead at St Vincent’s Hospital in Sydney. He had been struck on the side of the head by a bouncer from New South Wales bowler Sean Abbott in a Sheffield Shield match on Wednesday. In response, Cricket Australia chose to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Phil Hughes: The world mourns death of young batsman
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-phil-hughes-the-world-mourns-death-of-young-batsman/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 00:56:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-phil-hughes-the-world-mourns-death-of-young-batsman/</guid>
        <description>8th March 2009, Kingsmead, Durban. An Australian batsman is entertaining the crowd with a superb hundred. It was his second of the game, and meant that he, at the age of 20, became the youngest man to score two hundreds in a Test Match. It was just his second test match. This week, we mourn his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>World News: Ferguson unrest calms on Thanksgiving
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-world-news-ferguson-unrest-calms-on-thanksgiving/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 00:51:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-world-news-ferguson-unrest-calms-on-thanksgiving/</guid>
        <description>The St Louis suburb of Ferguson was calm on Thanksgiving morning, after two nights or protests. The suburb has been unsettled since 9th August when police officer Darren Wilson shot and killed civilian Michael Brown. Mr Wilson, who shot Brown six or seven times said that he “feared for his life”. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BT is moving back into mobile. Panic stations?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-bt-is-moving-back-into-mobile-panic-stations/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 00:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-bt-is-moving-back-into-mobile-panic-stations/</guid>
        <description>On Monday Spanish newspapers reported that BT were in talks with Telefonica over a potential takeover of O2. It later emerged that BT are also discussing the purchase of EE from French company Orange S.A. and German company Deutsche Telekom. But what would this mean for us? Should we be worried, or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College returns to top of the Research Council Grants Table
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-imperial-college-returns-to-top-of-the-research-council-grants-table/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 00:38:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-imperial-college-returns-to-top-of-the-research-council-grants-table/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College has returned to the top of the league table for research council income for the year 2013-14. It is the fourth time in the last five years that the College has topped the table, having been in third place for the year 2012-2013.
In this edition of the league table, Imperial was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students march for Free Education
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-21-students-march-for-free-education/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2014 13:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-21-students-march-for-free-education/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday thousands of student protesters took part in a march against student tuition fees. The protests turned violent when the students reached Parliament Square.
Signs seen around Parliament Square included the slogans “books not bombs” and “free education, tax the rich”.
Some students were …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Has the ‘Big Four’ become a ‘Big Two’?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-20-has-the-big-four-become-a-big-two/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 21:35:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-20-has-the-big-four-become-a-big-two/</guid>
        <description>Last week Novak Djokovic won his third consecutive ATP World Tour Finals title whilst also in the process securing the World Number One ranking for the year. Apart from a minor (and temporary) blip against Japanese player Kei Nishikori in the semi-final, Djokovic swept aside all those in his way …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Local News: Dog saves owner from house fire in Shepherd&#39;s Bush
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-20-local-news-dog-saves-owner-from-house-fire-in-shepherds-bush/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 20:22:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-20-local-news-dog-saves-owner-from-house-fire-in-shepherds-bush/</guid>
        <description>A dog saved its owners from a fire after the smoke alarm failed. ‘Smokey’ the dog, as nicknamed by the firemen who rescued the family, woke the rest of the house when smoke began to fill the ground floor property, located on Stanlake Road in Shepherd’s Bush.
Mr Hughes, one of the tenants of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FIFA, Rohit Sharma and Andy Murray - the World Sport Column
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-fifa-rohit-sharma-and-andy-murray-the-world-sport-column/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 21:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-fifa-rohit-sharma-and-andy-murray-the-world-sport-column/</guid>
        <description>FIFA has released the results of its inquiry into corruption and the World Cup bidding saga. In a shocking turn of events, the document claims that Qatar was totally innocent in the bid, and criticises the FA for its part in the matter. The lawyer who wrote the document and sent it to FIFA has said …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Diabetes walk is a sweet sucess
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-diabetes-walk-is-a-sweet-sucess/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 20:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-diabetes-walk-is-a-sweet-sucess/</guid>
        <description>On November 7th, nearly 21,000 people took part in WALK2014, a walk to raise awareness of diabetes, in Abu Dhabi. The walk was organised by the Imperial College London Diabetes Centre (ICLDC). It is estimated that over 150 million steps were taken in total during the walk, which was at the Yaz …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In case you missed it...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-in-case-you-missed-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 21:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-in-case-you-missed-it/</guid>
        <description>South African football captain Senzo Meyiwa was killed by armed robbers in his girlfriend’s house. It is believed that he was trying to defend his girlfriend before the robbers demanded his mobile phone; a shot was fired in the ensuing altercation. The South African police have launched a major …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>RAG tells Rugby: ‘We don’t want your junk’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-rag-tells-rugby-we-dont-want-your-junk/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 22:09:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-rag-tells-rugby-we-dont-want-your-junk/</guid>
        <description>In light of recent events surrounding Imperial College Rugby Club, the RAG committee chose to remove the team from their naked calendar for 2015.
RAG Chair Ben Fernando said: “Following conversations with the Union, we made the decision to pull the photo from the calendar.” Fernando said that he …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In case you missed it in the world of sport
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-in-case-you-missed-it-in-the-world-of-sport/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 19:28:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-in-case-you-missed-it-in-the-world-of-sport/</guid>
        <description>In the Champions League Arsenal blew a 3-0 lead to only draw against Anderlecht at the Emirates. Liverpool’s game at Real Madrid was the source of much discussion, as manager Brendan Rodgers opted to field a much changed eleven against the Galacticos. The Reds lost 1-0.
Lewis Hamilton won the United …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>US Midterm vote disaster for Obama
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-us-midterm-vote-disaster-for-obama/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 18:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-us-midterm-vote-disaster-for-obama/</guid>
        <description>On Tuesday night the Republicans took a majority in the Senate in the mid-term elections in the United States. This, along with their strengthening majority in the House of Representatives, means that the Republican party now has control over both houses for the first time since 2006. The results …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A-level results can&#39;t be finalised &#34;until October&#34;
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-24-a-level-results-cant-be-finalised-until-october/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2014 12:24:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-24-a-level-results-cant-be-finalised-until-october/</guid>
        <description>Universities have been told that they shouldn’t view exam results as “finalised” until the end of October. OCR, a leading exam results board, added to the statement saying that all results “remain provisional” until all re-marks are complete. Re-marks aren’t fully finished until the end of October, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NBA legend Kareem Abdul-Jabbar joins diabetes campaign
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-17-nba-legend-kareem-abdul-jabbar-joins-diabetes-campaign/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 14:53:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-17-nba-legend-kareem-abdul-jabbar-joins-diabetes-campaign/</guid>
        <description>NBA legend Kareem Abdul-Jabbar announced this week that he will be kicking off a diabetes week in the United Arab Emirates. Imperial College London’s Diabetes Centre (ICLDC) is the title partner of the Take a Step for Diabetes Week, which this year will start on the 28th October.
CEO of the ICLDC …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NUS rejects motion to condemn Islamic State
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-17-nus-rejects-motion-to-condemn-islamic-state/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 14:48:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-17-nus-rejects-motion-to-condemn-islamic-state/</guid>
        <description>The National Union of Students (NUS) has rejected a motion condemning Islamic State after a stirring speech by Black Students Officer Malia Bouattia, in which she asserted that passing the motion would be akin to “a justification for war and blatant Islamaphobia (sic)”. The motion said that the NUS …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students left in the dark over cuts to amenities funds
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-17-students-left-in-the-dark-over-cuts-to-amenities-funds/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 14:28:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,Thomas Lim,Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-17-students-left-in-the-dark-over-cuts-to-amenities-funds/</guid>
        <description>College has slashed the Amenity funds for Halls of Residence by a quarter of a million– a move that has sparked fury amongst Hall Seniors and Wardens throughout the first few weeks of term.
The amount allocated to all halls this year was just over £150,000, down from approximately £373,000 in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who is the new Universities Minister Greg Clark?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-7-16-who-is-the-new-universities-minister-greg-clark/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 03:09:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-7-16-who-is-the-new-universities-minister-greg-clark/</guid>
        <description>Today Prime Minister David Cameron appointed Greg Clark to the post of Universities Minister, after David Willetts resigned yesterday. But who is Greg Clark? Felix takes a look.
Name: Greg Clark
MP for: Royal Tunbridge Wells since 2005
Age: 46
Previous Ministerial Posts: - Minister of State for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>University Minister resigns in reshuffle
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-7-15-university-minister-resigns-in-reshuffle/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2014 02:51:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-7-15-university-minister-resigns-in-reshuffle/</guid>
        <description>Conservative MP David Willetts has resigned his post as Universities Minister as part of the current cabinet reshuffle. Mr Willetts was previously the Shadow Universities Minister and the Shadow Education Minister. His replacement will be Greg Clark.
Incumbent Education Minister Michael Gove has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Le Tour returns to London
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-7-8-le-tour-returns-to-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2014 11:07:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-7-8-le-tour-returns-to-london/</guid>
        <description>On Monday the Tour de France returned to London after a seven year absence as German Marcel Kittel won his second stage in three days in a sprint finish on the Mall.
The race concludes the Tour&amp;rsquo;s brief stay in Britain, which saw the riders begin in Leeds before today&amp;rsquo;s stage from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Does discrimination dominate in India?” – A Response
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-does-discrimination-dominate-in-india-a-response/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 13:11:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-does-discrimination-dominate-in-india-a-response/</guid>
        <description>Having read Christy Kelly’s article last week asking “Does discrimination dominate in India?”, I couldn’t help but think of the simple answer: yes. In a civilised country like India the treatment of women and “untouchables” is not only completely unacceptable, but also completely unforgivable. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Huxley Bins Set on Fire!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-huxley-bins-set-on-fire/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 11:25:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-huxley-bins-set-on-fire/</guid>
        <description>It is reported that at some point last week there was a fire in the Huxley building, which is home to both the Mathematics and Computing departments.
In an e-mail sent to students in the Computing Department last Friday; the College said, “An incident was recently reported of a cigarette butt …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Info Adds to EIE Exam Scandal
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-new-info-adds-to-eie-exam-scandal/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 10:58:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-new-info-adds-to-eie-exam-scandal/</guid>
        <description>More information has come to light on the scandal that hit the final exam for first year students on the Electronic and Information Engineering (EIE) course. Last week the students sat their Operating Systems paper, but moments after the exam started there were fits of laughter as the department had …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Professor is Inventor of the Year
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-professor-is-inventor-of-the-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 10:35:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-professor-is-inventor-of-the-year/</guid>
        <description>[Tabloid Special Edition]
Chris Toumazou, professor of Electrical and Electronic Engineering, has won the Inventor of the Year award for Research at the European Inventor Awards. Professor Toumazou won the award for his work on a new device called the SNP Doctor, which uses “small silicon microchips …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What can we do about FIFA?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-12-what-can-we-do-about-fifa/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 14:27:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-12-what-can-we-do-about-fifa/</guid>
        <description>It shows the sort of crisis that FIFA is in that, two days away from the start of their flagship tournament (the World Cup in Brazil for the few of you who are not already aware of it), there have been calls from all of Europe’s football leaders demanding that FIFA President Sepp Blatter step down …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College improves in Guardian League Tables
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-6-college-improves-in-guardian-league-tables/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 02:39:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-6-college-improves-in-guardian-league-tables/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College have moved up four places to 5th in the latest Guardian University League Table. The college overtook Universities such as Surrey, London School of Economics, University College London and Durham. The Guardian’s league table is based on numerous factors, including Student to staff …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Innovations in bid to raise £150 million via investment
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-6-imperial-innovations-in-bid-to-raise-150-million-via-investment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 02:38:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-6-imperial-innovations-in-bid-to-raise-150-million-via-investment/</guid>
        <description>Imperial Innovations, a company based at Imperial College, is planning to issue new shares on the stock market in a bid to raise up to £150 million. The firm, which is listed on the AIM stock market (a sub market of the London Stock Exchange), intends to use the money to fund future investments in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oxford Student Union in NUS U-Turn
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-2-oxford-student-union-in-nus-u-turn/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 12:41:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-2-oxford-student-union-in-nus-u-turn/</guid>
        <description>The Oxford Union (OUSU) has declared last week’s vote on whether to continue to affiliate with the National Union Students void amid controversy over “ballot stuffing”. The ‘no’ vote had won the referendum by a slender 128 votes last week, but it has since emerged that more than 1000 votes for ‘no’ …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Yoyo secure seed funding worth $5m
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-2-yoyo-secure-seed-funding-worth-5m/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 12:37:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-2-yoyo-secure-seed-funding-worth-5m/</guid>
        <description>Yoyo, the mobile payment app that launched last year, has managed to secure seed funding for $5m (nearly £3m), in what is considered to be one of the biggest funding deals in Europe so far this year. The firms to have invested in Yoyo include Imperial Innovations, Firestartr and Telefonica. Yoyo, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Slip, a Headbutt and David Moyes...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-19-a-slip-a-headbutt-and-david-moyes/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2014 13:28:47 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonathan Pratt,Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-19-a-slip-a-headbutt-and-david-moyes/</guid>
        <description> 5 Moments that defined the title race - Jonny Pratt City 4-1 United (September)
After a shaky start to the season City showed their intent, with a thorough defeat of their closest rivals, who had been doing alright till this point.
City 2-1 Liverpool (December)
Chelsea 2-1 Liverpool
Liverpool lose …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial sign pledge to be more open about animals in research
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-16-imperial-sign-pledge-to-be-more-open-about-animals-in-research/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 01:43:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-16-imperial-sign-pledge-to-be-more-open-about-animals-in-research/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday, Imperial became one of the 72 organisations to sign a Concordat on Animal Research within the United Kingdom. The Concordat, which promises that the organisations will be transparent about their experiments on animals, follows an opinion poll conducted in 2012. This poll showed that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial falls in latest ranking table
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-16-imperial-falls-in-latest-ranking-table/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 01:38:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-16-imperial-falls-in-latest-ranking-table/</guid>
        <description>This week the Complete University Guide (CUG) released their latest ranking table for Universities within the United Kingdom. Imperial College saw their ranking diminish from 4th to 6th – a drop that saw the College overtaken in the standings by St Andrews and Durham, who took 4th and 5th …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Royal Society of Chemistry awards five prizes to Imperial Professors
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-16-royal-society-of-chemistry-awards-five-prizes-to-imperial-professors/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 01:36:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-16-royal-society-of-chemistry-awards-five-prizes-to-imperial-professors/</guid>
        <description>This week five Imperial chemists were rewarded for their contributions to chemical sciences with prizes from the Royal Society of Chemistry.
The winners, who are Dr Matthew Fuchter, Professor Iain McCulloch, Professor Milo Shaffer, Professor Molly Stevens and Dr Edward Tate, have been awarded their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Medics take the JPR Williams Cup at Varsity
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-17-medics-take-the-jpr-williams-cup-at-varsity/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2014 17:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-17-medics-take-the-jpr-williams-cup-at-varsity/</guid>
        <description>Imperial Medicals RFC regained the JPR Williams Cup with a comprehensive 37-11 victory over Imperial College Union RFC in the flagship rugby union match under the floodlights at the Twickenham Stoop. The day wasn’t all bad for ICU however, as they won Varsity as a whole with more victories than …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix on the move!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-29-felix-on-the-move/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 16:24:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-29-felix-on-the-move/</guid>
        <description>ME: Introduce yourself!
KW: I am a first year Computing student from London. I currently reside in the Southside Halls of Residence.
ME: What is your position in Felix?
KW: I am the sports editor. I follow most sports, particularly football, cricket and tennis, so I felt that when the opportunity …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Thank you very much... Goodbye.”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-thank-you-very-much-goodbye/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 23:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-thank-you-very-much-goodbye/</guid>
        <description>On Thursday 16th November 1989, a sixteen-year-old took guard in his first innings for India and faced one of the most feared bowling attacks in the world. He was dismissed by fellow debutant Waqar Younis for 15, but everyone knew that there was something special about this schoolboy – the youngest …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Ashes Column
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-19-the-ashes-column/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2013 18:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-19-the-ashes-column/</guid>
        <description>If there is one thing that almost seems certain, it is that England face a much tougher task than the one they undertook during the summer. With the addition of George Bailey (who showed strong form in the recent one-day series in India), Australia’s batting looks a bit stronger. England’s bowling …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President of Republic of Korea visits Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-president-of-republic-of-korea-visits-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 03:39:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-president-of-republic-of-korea-visits-imperial/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday November 6th, the President of the Republic of Korea, Park Geun-hye, came on a visit of Imperial College, in order to make a speech outlining her vision for scientific partnership with “leading scientific nations, such as the UK”. She gave her speech at the UK-Korea Creative Economy and …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
