<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/books/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Editors’ Top Picks of the Decade</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-editors-top-picks-of-decade/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-editors-top-picks-of-decade/</guid>
        <description>When Breath Becomes Air by Paul Kalanithi
Image Above
Poetic, poignant, and profound, Paul Kalanithi’s memoir as a neurosurgeon diagnosed with Stage IV metastatic lung cancer is unbelievably powerful in Kalanithi’s quest to answer the difficult question of what makes a life worth living. It’s a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My life with Michael: 10 Years of Thriller Live, Written by Gary Lloyd</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-my-life-with-michael-10-years-of-thriller-live-written-gary-lloyd/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-my-life-with-michael-10-years-of-thriller-live-written-gary-lloyd/</guid>
        <description>2.5 stars
It seems quite ironic to me that the author, despite the title, has never actually met Michael Jackson. In fact, this admission comes as the very first sentence of the book. With this out of the way, the book focuses on the long-running (10 years, to be exact) West End show, Thriller …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Albert Camus’ The Myth of Sisyphus</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-albert-camus-myth-of-sisyphus/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-albert-camus-myth-of-sisyphus/</guid>
        <description>Albert Camus begins with a strong statement, “There is but one truly serious philosophical problem and that is suicide,” which immediately catches my attention. My problem with philosophy has always been its irrelevance, that is, whether you think one way or the other has little effect on how the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Celeste Ng’s Debut Novel: Everything I Never Told You</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-celest-ngs-debut-novel-everything-i-never-told-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-celest-ngs-debut-novel-everything-i-never-told-you/</guid>
        <description>Celeste Ng once again has taken me on a bumpy ride of secrets and fears that will leave me absolutely breathless with Everything I Never Told You. Ng is the kind of writer who has keen eyes for one’s deepest and darkest desires, and you can feel every character’s flesh and blood as if you’re living …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Celeste Ng’s Little Fires Everywhere</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-celeste-ngs-little-fires-everywhere/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-celeste-ngs-little-fires-everywhere/</guid>
        <description>It’s been a while since Celeste Ng’s best-selling novels have been sitting on my shelf, but I have never figured out the right moment to read it - these are stories I knew I would love, the kind that I would want to read on a Sunday afternoon, with a cup of chamomile tea and a fine plate of vanilla …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Man Booker Prize 2019 Shortlist: The Testaments</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-man-booker-prize-2019-shortlist-testaments/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-man-booker-prize-2019-shortlist-testaments/</guid>
        <description>The Testaments is a sequel to Margaret Atwood’s 1985 dystopian novel, The Handmaid’s Tale. It is set 15 years after the first, in the same totalitarian state of Gilead, where a fertility crisis and patriarchal fundamentalism have come together to foster a society where women are legally subordinate, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Review of Petals of Blood</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-a-review-of-petals-of-blood/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-a-review-of-petals-of-blood/</guid>
        <description>In a sentence, Petals of Blood is a story of change through the eyes of those oppressed. The author, Ngũgĩ wa Thiong’o, uses the murder, by arson, of three prominent figures in an emerging town to frame the narrative of the transformation of a backward (or unblemished?) village into a prospering (or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Becoming: An Intimate Conversation with Michelle Obama</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-becoming-an-intimate-conversation-with-michelle-obama/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-becoming-an-intimate-conversation-with-michelle-obama/</guid>
        <description>Michelle Obama brought the European leg of her book tour for her memoir, Becoming, to London on 14th April in emphatic fashion. Stepping out at London’s O2 arena to Alicia Keys’ ‘Girl on Fire’, the former US First Lady was met with rapturous applause and a standing ovation from a 15,000-stong …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Ghost Map: dive into the 1854 London cholera outbreak</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-the-ghost-map-dive-into-the-1854-london-cholera-outbreak/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-the-ghost-map-dive-into-the-1854-london-cholera-outbreak/</guid>
        <description>The setting of this book - a cholera outbreak in Victorian England revolving around cesspools contaminations - is not particularly the most attractive thing in the world, yet it’s fascinating to see the story behind how we came to understand that cholera is water-borne, how it established the base …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>So You’ve Been Publicly Shamed: The guillotine of modern life?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-so-you-ve-been-publicly-shamed-the-guillotine-of-modern-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-so-you-ve-been-publicly-shamed-the-guillotine-of-modern-life/</guid>
        <description>As suggested by the title itself, So You’ve Been Publicly Shamed explores the world of the internet with compassion seemingly absent and every flaw amplified. In it, the author Jon Ronson details his interviews with those who were victims of ruthless attacks, perhaps for a bad joke or an immature …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A trip down memory lane: two mini reviews</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-a-trip-down-memory-lane-two-mini-reviews/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavan Inguva,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-a-trip-down-memory-lane-two-mini-reviews/</guid>
        <description>Before starting at Imperial, I took a short holiday to India to visit friends and family. For those of you who don’t know, India is an amazing place to buy books. You can get original prints of many books for a fraction of the price compared to any western country. Obviously I took this chance to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Left Off the Shelf</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-left-off-the-shelf/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rahul Mehta,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-left-off-the-shelf/</guid>
        <description>Despite the power of prose and verse to drag us from our seat on the Tube (or grim university flat) to the Victorian slums or outer sectors of the Galactic Empire, British literature is still being held back. While the characters in books transcend time and space, the non-fictional people who write …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ferrante Reviewed</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-ferrante-reviewed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-ferrante-reviewed/</guid>
        <description>There are some books that you want to devour as fast as possible, sleep becomes secondary to being carried along the twists and turns of a novel’s relentless plots. Other books are to be savoured, each sentence in its perfect composition wondered over. Very rarely, a book is both. The Neapolitan …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mary Oliver: a poet that speaks to all</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-mary-oliver-a-poet-that-speaks-to-all/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-mary-oliver-a-poet-that-speaks-to-all/</guid>
        <description>When Krista Tippett interviewed the late poet Mary Oliver on her radio show ‘On Being’ back in 2015, she referred to Oliver’s poem ‘Wild Geese’ as “a poem that has saved lives”. This might seem an exaggerated claim, but for me at least, it holds some truth.
For a teenager in the last year of school, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How science got women wrong</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-how-science-got-women-wrong/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Hiu Wai Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-how-science-got-women-wrong/</guid>
        <description>The first time I noticed this book was when it was nominated for the Reading Women Award for Nonfiction in 2017. It opens the discussion on how society affects gender-related biological and behavior studies. It deals with three topics I am interested in: feminism, science, and history (and it is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science fiction authors come to Imperial!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-science-fiction-authors-come-to-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Harry Black,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-science-fiction-authors-come-to-imperial/</guid>
        <description>On 16th February, the Imperial College Science Fiction and Fantasy society will be holding their 36th Picocon, a yearly convention and celebration of science fiction and fantasy media. This year’s theme is ‘intrigue’, and three science fiction authors will be in attendance as Guests of Honour. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Death Register: a review</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-death-register-a-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-death-register-a-review/</guid>
        <description>Death Register is a novel outside my literary comfort zone. It follows the formative years of Chauncey Knuckle and his group of friends, growing up in the city of Montego Bay. It explores their relationships with their peers, their families and their teachers against the intensely homophobic and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Of Missed Opportunities and Vanity: Books from the Balkans</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-of-missed-opportunities-and-vanity-books-from-the-balkans/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavan Inguva,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-of-missed-opportunities-and-vanity-books-from-the-balkans/</guid>
        <description>Normally, I would start off by sharing how I serendipitously came across a beautiful bookstore or an author, or book, related to the country I am travelling to. This isn’t one of those occasions. The two books I write about here came to me in a far more dubious manner. The first book was stuck in my …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Joy to your bookshelf</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-joy-to-your-bookshelf/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-joy-to-your-bookshelf/</guid>
        <description>Eleanor Oliphant is Completely Fine by Gail Honeyman
Winner of the British Book Awards, this stunning debut novel by Gail Honeyman delves deep into loneliness, connections and the power of kindness. The theme of isolation is one that is rarely explored in contemporary culture; as Honeyman puts it, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Overstory: a giant redwood of a novel</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-the-overstory-a-giant-redwood-of-a-novel/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Stroud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-the-overstory-a-giant-redwood-of-a-novel/</guid>
        <description>This is not our world with trees in it. It’s a world of trees, where humans have just arrived.”
Ecological catastrophe, perhaps the biggest issue of our generation, has never been more vividly portrayed than in Richard Powers’s twelfth novel The Overstory. After making his name with the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>TS Eliot Prize 2018: an ‘intensely political’ shortlist</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-ts-eliot-prize-2018-an-intensely-political-shortlist/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-ts-eliot-prize-2018-an-intensely-political-shortlist/</guid>
        <description>The TS Eliot Prize in poetry is one of the most prestigious poetry prizes for the English language. Last year, to celebrate the 25th year of the prize, the winner’s prize money was increased to £25,000 - making it the most valuable prize in British poetry. It is no surprise then that the prize is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>William Carlos Williams: poet, doctor, writer</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-william-carlos-williams-poet-doctor-writer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-william-carlos-williams-poet-doctor-writer/</guid>
        <description>Family doctor, poet, novelist, playwright and occasional translator – William Carlos Williams wore many hats in his life as both a man of medicine and a man of letters. There seems to be a strange compulsion amongst doctors to write, as though their creative energies need some outlet which medicine …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Man Booker Prize winner: Milkman a “challenging” read</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-man-booker-prize-winner-milkman-a-challenging-read/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gautam Kambhampati,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-man-booker-prize-winner-milkman-a-challenging-read/</guid>
        <description>The first thing one notices about Anna Burns’ Milkman is the lack of names. The closest thing our protagonist gets to one is “middle sister”, and the setting is only ever referred to obliquely, and its characters by sobriquet. There is one particularly fantastic early scene in which middle sister’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>More than just a memoir: Gurmit Singh K.S. on his environmental and social activism in Malaysia</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-more-than-just-a-memoir-gurmit-singh-k-s-on-his-environmental-and-social-activism-in-malaysia/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>J Y Gan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-more-than-just-a-memoir-gurmit-singh-k-s-on-his-environmental-and-social-activism-in-malaysia/</guid>
        <description>The publication of Rachel Carson’s Silent Spring back in 1962 launched the international environmental movement; one can only wonder what book she would come up with if she were alive to witness the present developing world.
Thankfully, her life’s work inspired a generation of staunch …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Man Booker Prize 2018: a rundown of the shortlist</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-the-man-booker-prize-2018-a-rundown-of-the-shortlist/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-the-man-booker-prize-2018-a-rundown-of-the-shortlist/</guid>
        <description>Milkman, by Anna Burns
Anna Burns is the first Northern Irish writer to win the coveted prize – previous Irish writers have all been from the Republic. She is also the first female writer to win since 2013, when Eleanor Catton won for The Luminaries. The Booker’s chair of judges, philosopher Kwame …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A family against the Sicilian Mafia</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-a-family-against-the-sicilian-mafia/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bayan Al Balushi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-a-family-against-the-sicilian-mafia/</guid>
        <description>Imagine, if you will, Sicily of the early twentieth century; an island whose main source of income is agriculture, its residents mainly peasants. Against this backdrop, we are introduced to the five Sacco brothers, who are part of an honest, hard-working, recently landed family. Their father, Luigi, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ayaan Hirsi Ali: The woman who is not afraid to speak her mind</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-ayaan-hirsi-ali-the-woman-who-is-not-afraid-to-speak-her-mind/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Peter Shatwell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-ayaan-hirsi-ali-the-woman-who-is-not-afraid-to-speak-her-mind/</guid>
        <description>One morning in Amsterdam, on November 2nd 2004, a man wakes up, has his breakfast, and hops onto his old black bicycle to head to work at his film production company. Meanwhile, another man lies in wait in a doorway, carrying two knives and a handgun. As the cyclist trundles down the Linnaeusstraat …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix recommends autumn reading</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-felix-recommends-autumn-reading/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-felix-recommends-autumn-reading/</guid>
        <description>Normal People by Sally Rooney
Longlisted for the Man Booker Prize this year, Rooney’s second novel follows less than a year after her celebrated debut Conversations with Friends. The praise heaped on Conversations applies to her new novel – witty and elegant, both novels are testament to Rooney’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix recommends – reading for summer days</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-15-felix-recommends-reading-for-summer-days/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-15-felix-recommends-reading-for-summer-days/</guid>
        <description>Mrs Dalloway by Virginia Woolf
Virginia Woolf’s most well-known work crackles with a vibrant energy and zest. Set on a ‘Wednesday in mid-June’, it remains one of the best portrayals of London in the early summer, full of the vibrant optimism that characterises long days in the city. Taking place …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jennifer Tseng brings a freshness to well-worn tropes in this engaging debut</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-15-jennifer-tseng-brings-a-freshness-to-well-worn-tropes-in-this-engaging-debut/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bayan Al Balushi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-15-jennifer-tseng-brings-a-freshness-to-well-worn-tropes-in-this-engaging-debut/</guid>
        <description>Mayumi and the Sea of Happiness, the new novel from Jennifer Tseng, follows Mayumi, a forty-one-year-old librarian, married with a child, who begins an affair with an unnamed seventeen-year-old boy who she meets in the library. Despite being aware of the potential consequences of her decision, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Iliac Crest – An unsettling tale of disappearance and mystery</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-15-the-iliac-crest-an-unsettling-tale-of-disappearance-and-mystery/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-15-the-iliac-crest-an-unsettling-tale-of-disappearance-and-mystery/</guid>
        <description>In literature, disappearance tends to be a primarily active phenomenon, with individuals making the choice to leave their family and friends behind. While it is not necessarily a consensual act – ‘disappear’ implies people are left behind, who are often searching for the missing individual – the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Disoriental – A multi-generational study of identity</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-disoriental-a-multi-generational-study-of-identity/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-disoriental-a-multi-generational-study-of-identity/</guid>
        <description>The father of a friend of mine has a story about growing up between cultures. Born in England to a Greek-Cypriot family, he lived in London until he was a few years old, before going to Cyprus for about six months. Surrounded by family members, all chattering away in Greek, the English he had …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Theory of Bastards: the short distance between man and animal</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-theory-of-bastards-the-short-distance-between-man-and-animal/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-theory-of-bastards-the-short-distance-between-man-and-animal/</guid>
        <description>There is something slightly off-putting about our simian cousins – those gorillas, chimpanzees, and bonobos who seem so human-like and yet also so distant from us. We know that many such species behave in ways similar to humans – they exhibit complex social behaviour, are self-aware, and are able to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>One Hundred Shadows leaves us in the dark</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-one-hundred-shadows-leaves-us-in-the-dark/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bayan Al Balushi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-one-hundred-shadows-leaves-us-in-the-dark/</guid>
        <description>This ethereal short novel seamlessly weaves elements of fantasy with reality, producing a work of fiction that is as bizarre as it is engrossing. Author Hwang Jungeun affords us a small glimpse into the lives of Eungyo and Mujae, two friends working at electronic stores.
During a day out, Eungyo is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Philip Roth: Mourning the loss of an American literary giant</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-philip-roth-mourning-the-loss-of-an-american-literary-giant/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-philip-roth-mourning-the-loss-of-an-american-literary-giant/</guid>
        <description>You’re looking, as you begin, for what’s going to resist you. You’re looking for trouble. Sometimes in the beginning uncertainty arises not because the writing is difficult, but because it isn’t difficult enough.”
These words were spoken by the late American author Philip Roth, who died earlier this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pure Hollywood: a long-anticipated UK debut proves to be worth the wait</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-pure-hollywood-a-long-anticipated-uk-debut-proves-to-be-worth-the-wait/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-pure-hollywood-a-long-anticipated-uk-debut-proves-to-be-worth-the-wait/</guid>
        <description>California, despite its associations in popular culture with dreaming and love and soul, can be an inhospitable place; the beauty of the sunshine that gives the state its nickname is tempered by its power – to dessicate, oppress, and crack open, like asphalt rutted open by an eternal summer. In her …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mistaken Identity – how should the left move forward from identity politics?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-mistaken-identity-how-should-the-left-move-forward-from-identity-politics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-mistaken-identity-how-should-the-left-move-forward-from-identity-politics/</guid>
        <description>In June 2015, an interview conducted by KXLY, a small news outlet located in the city of Spokane, Washington, sparked heated debate across the world. For the first eight minutes, Jeff Humphrey, the interviewer, speaks to Rachel Dolezal, president of the local NAACP chapter, about hate crimes she’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science for Heretics review – the heretics have not got it right</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-science-for-heretics-review-the-heretics-have-not-got-it-right/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Clemens Jakubec,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-science-for-heretics-review-the-heretics-have-not-got-it-right/</guid>
        <description>The scientific method is not absolute. Every good scientist should be aware of that. However, for scientists, science and the scientific method have proven to be the most effective ways of moving towards a more objective view on the universe around us. Barrie Condon is such a scientist. He is a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Devil’s Dance – dancing on the border between imagination and reality</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-the-devil-s-dance-dancing-on-the-border-between-imagination-and-reality/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-the-devil-s-dance-dancing-on-the-border-between-imagination-and-reality/</guid>
        <description>The death of Islam Karimov, the dictatorial leader of Uzbekistan, nearly two years ago, dropped the country into a quagmire of uncertainty. The leader, who had held power for 27 years, was widely criticised for his use of torture, crackdown on press freedoms, and a 2005 massacre in which around 400 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Children of Blood and Bone takes a step forward for representation, but is stuck in YA romance</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-children-of-blood-and-bone-takes-a-step-forward-for-representation-but-is-stuck-in-ya-romance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Peberdy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-children-of-blood-and-bone-takes-a-step-forward-for-representation-but-is-stuck-in-ya-romance/</guid>
        <description>Young Adult books can get a lot of bad rap. In some ways, I can see why, but then releases like Tomi Adeyemi’s debut Children of Blood and Bone make me question the stigma.
Zélie should have magical abilities, but a ruthless king destroyed magic and killed anyone with powers before she could develop …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Japanese literature through the ages</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-japanese-literature-through-the-ages/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavan Inguva,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-japanese-literature-through-the-ages/</guid>
        <description>I have become quite partial to Japanese literature as a literary category. Most examples share overarching similarities in aesthetic flavour, such as the notion of impermanence of being, which derive from both cultural and religious developments throughout Japanese history. These sensitivities, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are we living under the tyranny of science?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-are-we-living-under-the-tyranny-of-science/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Bennie,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-are-we-living-under-the-tyranny-of-science/</guid>
        <description>I’ve noticed posters around college, and have been leafleted with a manifesto. At first, I was a little taken aback by their stance: ‘We believe the scientific method is dogmatic and prescriptive, and it restricts creativity of thought in science.’ The group, calling themselves the ‘Against Method …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>La Belle Sauvage: Dust after Darkness</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-la-belle-sauvage-dust-after-darkness/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Waleed A El-Geresy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-la-belle-sauvage-dust-after-darkness/</guid>
        <description>Another year, another Philip Pullman series! Well, not really. The last world-renowned series that Pullman released was His Dark Materials, and what a series it was. But that was all too long ago. Those familiar with His Dark Materials might think of it as the atheist’s take on Narnia. Those who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An intellectual perspective on progress and positivity in Enlightenment Now</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-an-intellectual-perspective-on-progress-and-positivity-in-enlightenment-now/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Clemens Jakubec,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-an-intellectual-perspective-on-progress-and-positivity-in-enlightenment-now/</guid>
        <description>Where is the world headed? Are things getting better or are we approaching a darker period of human history? In his new book Enlightenment Now: The Case for Reason, Science, Humanism, and Progress, American cognitive linguist Steven Pinker makes the case for a more positive outlook for the future of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Willis’ macabre and amusing science fiction classic</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-willis-macabre-and-amusing-science-fiction-classic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yang Guo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-willis-macabre-and-amusing-science-fiction-classic/</guid>
        <description>How might one interact with people from the distant past if one were allowed to time travel there? This was the question posed by Connie Willis in her science fiction novel, The Doomsday Book. The novel is set in Oxford University, at around Christmas time, 2053. A young woman called Kivrin, a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Raising the portcullis: uncovering queer literature</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-raising-the-portcullis-uncovering-queer-literature/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-raising-the-portcullis-uncovering-queer-literature/</guid>
        <description>The book that first led me to the wonderful world of queer literature was Oranges are Not the Only Fruit by Jeanette Winterson. As one of our A level texts, Oranges provided me with a first hand account of what it was like to grow up as a lesbian girl, especially within a conservative, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Black, lesbian, mother, warrior, poet’</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22--black-lesbian-mother-warrior-poet/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22--black-lesbian-mother-warrior-poet/</guid>
        <description>Speaking at a conference on modern language in 1977, in a speech that would later be published as The Transformation of Silence into Language and Action, the poet-activist Audre Lorde reckoned with her mortality.
A few weeks prior, she said, she’d undergone a mastectomy to remove a tumour that in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The essential rainbow reading list</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-the-essential-rainbow-reading-list/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-the-essential-rainbow-reading-list/</guid>
        <description>A lengthy reading list, I think, is a quintessential part of the coming out story of every bookish queer person. From tentative forays into Sarah Waters’s debauched Victoriana to focused study of Virginia Woolf’s fabulously winding sentences, we use books to try and find ourselves, to build a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix recommends Valentine&#39;s reads… or the books to help you to forget about romance</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-felix-recommends-valentine-s-reads-or-the-books-to-help-you-to-forget-about-romance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,Alice Peberdy,Indira Mallik,Pavan Inguva,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-felix-recommends-valentine-s-reads-or-the-books-to-help-you-to-forget-about-romance/</guid>
        <description> Written on the Body by Jeanette Winterson
 The first question is, who is the narrator? She or he is never named, and their gender never revealed. &amp;ldquo;Why is the measure of love loss?&amp;rdquo; asks the opening sentence, and throughout the book we are taken through the narrator’s clandestine …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Menasse’s ruminations on pigs and politics in the European Union</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-menasse-s-ruminations-on-pigs-and-politics-in-the-european-union/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Clemens Jakubec,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-menasse-s-ruminations-on-pigs-and-politics-in-the-european-union/</guid>
        <description>Is it possible to write a novel about the European Union? Not just a book about the history of the European Union with boring facts and figures about its multiple conventions and contracts, but a proper novel with characters that could symbolise the European Union. That is the question that Robert …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Contemplating troubled pasts in the City of Literature</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-contemplating-troubled-pasts-in-the-city-of-literature/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavan Inguva,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-contemplating-troubled-pasts-in-the-city-of-literature/</guid>
        <description>The seeds of this article were sowed over December break, during a weekend I spent in Hamburg, Germany and a visit to Lubeck (Birthplace of Thomas Mann), followed by a week in Poland.
I only found out when in Krakow, that it is designated a UNESCO city of literature. This made more sense after …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“What would you have done?”</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02--what-would-you-have-done/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bayan Al Balushi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02--what-would-you-have-done/</guid>
        <description>The Reader is one of those books that one can discuss at length and would make a good choice for a book club, but I’ll try to keep it short though I have much to say.
The story is told from the first person perspective of Michael Berg and begins with him having contracted hepatitis at the age of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Debut novel challenges traditions of the Arab world</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-debut-novel-challenges-traditions-of-the-arab-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bayan Al Balushi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-debut-novel-challenges-traditions-of-the-arab-world/</guid>
        <description>The first time I heard of this book was when I watched the author being interviewed on an Arab channel. Not having watched the interview from the beginning, I didn’t know what the novel was about, but I was intrigued by their discussion of Arab culture and traditions. When I learnt that the book …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Strong contenders for 2017 T. S. Eliot Prize for poetry</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-strong-contenders-for-2017-t-s-eliot-prize-for-poetry/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-strong-contenders-for-2017-t-s-eliot-prize-for-poetry/</guid>
        <description>The T. S. Eliot Prize, awarded by the Poetry Book Society, is arguably one of the most prestigious poetry prizes in the world. Awarded every year to a poetry collection in English first published in the UK or Ireland, it has seen many household names winning in the past, including Ted Hughes, Carol …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2017 roundup: the best books of the year</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-2017-roundup-the-best-books-of-the-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Alice Peberdy,Katie Cook,Clemens Jakubec,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-2017-roundup-the-best-books-of-the-year/</guid>
        <description>What was the best thing you read this year? Four of our Books Writers give their thoughts:
Morning and Evening, by Jon Fosse
Jon Fosse to tell the story of the Norwegian fisherman Johannes in only a hundred pages. To be exact, we only learn about the two most significant events in his life: his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kazuo Ishiguro, winner of 2017 Nobel Prize in Literature, is master of words and the heart</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-kazuo-ishiguro-winner-of-2017-nobel-prize-in-literature-is-master-of-words-and-the-heart/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-kazuo-ishiguro-winner-of-2017-nobel-prize-in-literature-is-master-of-words-and-the-heart/</guid>
        <description>I first encountered Kazuo Ishiguro’s writing back in high school, in the form of his short story collection Nocturnes. I had won some book vouchers, and was browsing the local bookstore for something worth buying when I came across this slim volume. Five Stories of Music and Nightfall, it read, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Literature should not just be about ‘dead white men’</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-literature-should-not-just-be-about-dead-white-men/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-literature-should-not-just-be-about-dead-white-men/</guid>
        <description>Much has been written so far about ‘decolonising’ the English Literature curriculum, after Cambridge University’s English undergraduate Lola Olufemi wrote an open letter imploring her faculty to broaden their curriculum to include non-white writers. The letter, signed by around 150 students, called …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Tis the season to be reading</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08--tis-the-season-to-be-reading/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,Alice Peberdy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08--tis-the-season-to-be-reading/</guid>
        <description>Got a family member you need to get a last-minute gift for? Why not get them a book – at least it&amp;rsquo;s easy to wrap!
This is Going To Hurt, by Adam Kay
Have a healthcare professional among your family and friends? Even if you don’t, they are sure to enjoy this hilarious journal by ex-doctor, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Seeing the world through literature – so many books, so little time</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-seeing-the-world-through-literature-so-many-books-so-little-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavan Inguva,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-seeing-the-world-through-literature-so-many-books-so-little-time/</guid>
        <description>Seeing another part of the world is quite an exciting prospect for anyone: different foods, culture, history, and – most importantly – visiting beautiful bookstores and discovering authors you would not have heard of otherwise. Picking up a book, albeit translated to English, by a local author has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Decolonising the canon: Felix recommends</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-decolonising-the-canon-felix-recommends/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-decolonising-the-canon-felix-recommends/</guid>
        <description>Trumpet, by Jackie Kay
Kay’s only novel Trumpet is in a class of its own, and one of the most unconventional books I’ve ever read. Joss Moody is a renowned jazz musician whose death sparks a frantic seeking of truth by his son and the public about his ‘true’ identity and gender. It explores the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A women’s alternative to the Booker</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-a-women-s-alternative-to-the-booker/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katie Cook,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-a-women-s-alternative-to-the-booker/</guid>
        <description>If you’re only going to read the winner of one fiction prize each year, the Women’s Prize for Fiction will always be your best bet. Each year the prize honours one female author whose novel has made the greatest impact on the literary world in the past year. The prize began when in 1991 it was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hollywood has brought Atwood’s dystopia to the screen, and now into reality</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-hollywood-has-brought-atwood-s-dystopia-to-the-screen-and-now-into-reality/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Peberdy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-hollywood-has-brought-atwood-s-dystopia-to-the-screen-and-now-into-reality/</guid>
        <description>It seems the morning news is scarcely without another allegation of sexual assault these days. Harvey Weinstein has inspired many stars, mostly women, to share their stories of abuse by people with power. Finally, these hard-hitting topics may finally be discussed at a meaningful level through their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In the relentless tread of time, a man searches for the greater miracle of life </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-in-the-relentless-tread-of-time-a-man-searches-for-the-greater-miracle-of-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Clemens Jakubec,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-in-the-relentless-tread-of-time-a-man-searches-for-the-greater-miracle-of-life/</guid>
        <description>Freedom – a word as awe-inspiring as it is undefined. There are many ways of tackling the issue of what freedom means on a general as well as on a personal level. In his 2013 novel The Greater Miracle Thomas Glavinic sheds light on the problem of freedom from a very personal perspective.
The novel …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In the words of a young poet finding her feet</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-in-the-words-of-a-young-poet-finding-her-feet/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-in-the-words-of-a-young-poet-finding-her-feet/</guid>
        <description>What do we know of someone else’s life, besides what they choose to reveal to us? What more of a life that was tragically cut short, and has remained an enigma since?
In a newly-published tome of never-before-seen letters by 20th-century poet Sylvia Plath, we steal glimpses of a young, gifted poet …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The koala bear as a metaphor for life, death, and the struggle to survive </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-the-koala-bear-as-a-metaphor-for-life-death-and-the-struggle-to-survive/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Clemens Jakubec,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-the-koala-bear-as-a-metaphor-for-life-death-and-the-struggle-to-survive/</guid>
        <description>The animal was not black. It was not strong. It was lazy and had furry ears, a creature, that people laughed about. The best one could say about the animal was, that it was cute.” The koala is usually not an animal that people tend to spend a lot of time thinking about. Nevertheless, swiss author …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Immerse yourself in the tumultuous sea of this 20th century historical drama</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-immerse-yourself-in-the-tumultuous-sea-of-this-20th-century-historical-drama/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavan Inguva,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-immerse-yourself-in-the-tumultuous-sea-of-this-20th-century-historical-drama/</guid>
        <description>A lot of great literature has served as excellent snapshots into the culture and attitudes of the society that the author describes. Yukio Mishima’s Sea of Fertility Tetralogy is a perfect example of that. The tetralogy consists of Spring Snow, Runaway Horses, The Temple of Dawn, and The Decay of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In defence of ‘difficult’ books</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-in-defence-of-difficult-books/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ned Summers,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-in-defence-of-difficult-books/</guid>
        <description>There is no criticism more widely levelled against book and author than that of difficulty. I was prompted to write this article because of a one-star Goodreads review of Thomas Pynchon’s The Crying of Lot 49. It began:
“A classic English majors only book, aka people like talking about this book and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ali Smith’s Autumn is more than just a post-Brexit manifesto</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-ali-smith-s-autumn-is-more-than-just-a-post-brexit-manifesto/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Peberdy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-ali-smith-s-autumn-is-more-than-just-a-post-brexit-manifesto/</guid>
        <description>Books which lack speech marks always scare me. It can seem like they’re trying too hard just to break a rule and look contemporary. But I should never have doubted Ali Smith, in whose new book, Autumn, it feels entirely appropriate. It freed the author to skip between characters and to entwine her …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hope amid darkness in Philip Pullman’s new series</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-hope-amid-darkness-in-philip-pullman-s-new-series/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Natasha Manuelpillai,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-hope-amid-darkness-in-philip-pullman-s-new-series/</guid>
        <description>Known for his trilogy His Dark Materials, a fixture of many of our teenage bookshelves, Pullman is no stranger to the best-seller charts. La Belle Sauvage is the much-anticipated first volume of The Book of Dust, which Pullman discussed with BBC broadcaster and fellow author Cerys Matthews at a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Words of migratory flight</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-words-of-migratory-flight/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-words-of-migratory-flight/</guid>
        <description>The world is a fleeting glory”, reads Asha Lul Mohamud Yusuf’s poem, The Scab. To the more than 110,000 Somali-born immigrants living in the UK, many of whom fled the Somali Civil War as refugees, this cannot be more true. Stability is an illusion when one has to witness one’s own country torn apart …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An evening discussion with the Booker Prize nominees</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-an-evening-discussion-with-the-booker-prize-nominees/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-an-evening-discussion-with-the-booker-prize-nominees/</guid>
        <description>It was the night before the announcement of the 2017 Man Booker Prize winner, and it was the first time the shortlisted writers had all come together in the same space. In the Royal Festival Hall, where all six shortlisted writers sat next to each other on stage, the anticipation was palpable amid …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How a terrible beauty is born</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-how-a-terrible-beauty-is-born/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Astrid Zong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-how-a-terrible-beauty-is-born/</guid>
        <description>Be-monster not thy feature,” says Albany to Goneril; “proper deformity seems not in the fiend so horrid as in woman.” In King Lear, what renders Goneril’s ruthlessness particularly chilling is the juxtaposing presence of inhumanity – or, in Albany’s Elizabethan conception, unfemininity – in someone …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On Kazuo Ishiguro</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-on-kazuo-ishiguro/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gracie Holt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-on-kazuo-ishiguro/</guid>
        <description>There was a time when, as an adult, I did not read books. Then one evening, when I lay awake overthinking and analysing, I realised what this meant. If I continued at my current rate of reading 0.75 books a year on holiday, then I would likely die not having read 100 books. I was then suddenly aware …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All the best books coming out this term</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-all-the-best-books-coming-out-this-term/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-all-the-best-books-coming-out-this-term/</guid>
        <description>The Floating World, by C. Morgan Babst (October 17th)
Normally I don’t find this kind of books fascinating – I sometimes add them to my to-be-read (TBR) list, but they just stay there forever. However, this book has something… probably the parents who abandon their daughter in the middle of a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Saunders explores the limbo between life and death in debut novel</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-saunders-explores-the-limbo-between-life-and-death-in-debut-novel/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Bennie,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-saunders-explores-the-limbo-between-life-and-death-in-debut-novel/</guid>
        <description>I was fearful when I heard about Lincoln in the Bardo almost a decade ago. I’m not a fan of historical novels and was aware of the difficulties that come with moving from short stories to novels. My fears were unfounded, George Saunders’ first novel is a triumph. To even call it a historical novel …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Timeless’ recommendations for Autumn reading...</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13--timeless-recommendations-for-autumn-reading/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13--timeless-recommendations-for-autumn-reading/</guid>
        <description>Adulthood is a Myth, by Sarah Andersen
I know you are stuck in between two assignments and three textbooks to read, so you definitely don’t have a lot of time to lose reading ‘for pleasure’, but I think that you can find five minutes here and there to realise that you are not the only one who has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gaiman’s London is never where you think it is</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-gaiman-s-london-is-never-where-you-think-it-is/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-gaiman-s-london-is-never-where-you-think-it-is/</guid>
        <description>Neil Gaiman has an uncanny knack for picking out the essence of a place.
In American Gods, Gaiman weaved the battle between ancient gods and modern greed into an epic tale of contemporary America. Neverwhere, in my opinion, should be read by everyone who lives in London. Richard, the protagonist, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>H.G. Wells’ little-known South Ken connection</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-h-g-wells-little-known-south-ken-connection/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Peberdy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-h-g-wells-little-known-south-ken-connection/</guid>
        <description>Imagine the Imperial freshers of the past; ponder where their college career led them. Research is probably first to mind – medicine, teaching, banking… Arts? We’re scientists, not robots! Great academics are often churned out, but our university also produced one of the fathers of science fiction, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ken Kesey – Author, revolutionary, and counter-cultural icon of the 1960s</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-ken-kesey-author-revolutionary-and-counter-cultural-icon-of-the-1960s/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Purdy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-ken-kesey-author-revolutionary-and-counter-cultural-icon-of-the-1960s/</guid>
        <description>As Cold War tension and paranoia reached its height in the mid-1950s, the American government entered into the most obscure stretch of the arms race – development of a weapon that could be used as means of mass mind control. During this search psychedelics drugs such as LSD were discovered and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Notes from the Underground
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-notes-from-the-underground/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 12:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Darije Custovic,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-notes-from-the-underground/</guid>
        <description>“I am a sick man&amp;hellip; I am an angry man. I am an unattractive man.”
This is the opening line of Dostoyevsky’s early work Notes From the Underground. They are the words of the unnamed narrator, the fictive author of the titular notes written from “underground” – his term for his own self-imposed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Authors To Look Out For
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-12-authors-to-look-out-for/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 13:27:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-12-authors-to-look-out-for/</guid>
        <description> Bolesław Prus Those who have read my previous articles for the Books Section already know of my love for the works of Bolesław Prus. Even in his native Poland he is not a particularly popular author, often obscured by his more popular, and populist, contemporary, Henryk Sienkiewicz. I, however, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Summer Reading Picks
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-summer-reading-picks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 01:43:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-summer-reading-picks/</guid>
        <description>Hitchhiker’s Guide to the Galaxy
Douglas Adams
Douglas Adams’ famous humour series has appeared in many formats – a radio show, a TV series, a film. The books, however, remain many people’s favourite. The story follows everyman Arthur Dent, who is rescued from the demolition of the planet Earth in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Notes to a Fresher 3
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-7-notes-to-a-fresher-3/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 12:44:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-7-notes-to-a-fresher-3/</guid>
        <description>Advice translated by the Mouth of the Eye of Queen’s Tower, scribed by the Hand of the Eye of Queen’s Tower
I sigh as I – the Eye of Queen’s Tower – frown down upon the throng in Sherfield. I sigh because it is lunchtime, and once more, there is a queue, nay, a brawl, of thirty hungry, snarling …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Dying Earth
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-the-dying-earth/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 13:28:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-the-dying-earth/</guid>
        <description>Though I fancy myself reasonably well read in the field of science fiction and fantasy I must admit that there are quite a few classic authors of the genre whose work I haven’t read at all. Of these the one I probably felt most guilty about not checking out was Jack Vance. After all, he was a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ancillary Justice
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-ancillary-justice/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 05:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-ancillary-justice/</guid>
        <description>Ancillary Justice, the debut novel of Ann Leckie, is one of those novels that had been recommended to me by pretty much everyone. However, as is often the case, my other commitments, and my impressively long reading list, made me put off picking up for quite a while. Now, having finally read it, I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tea &amp; Coffee Truths
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-tea-coffee-truths/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 03:23:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-tea-coffee-truths/</guid>
        <description>One day I may look back on my life and realise that my first love was not a person but a place&amp;hellip;
Our world is full, bursting and strained like never before. We have the power to suppress disease, pacify hunger, come and go as we so choose. Things have grown, unfurled like ivy tendrils that are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Singularity Sky
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-singularity-sky/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 03:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Rivlin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-singularity-sky/</guid>
        <description>It’s hard to decide whether Singularity Sky is hard or soft sci-fi. Inherent to the setting of the book is faster-than-light (FTL) travel and an omnipotent, post-singularity AI. However that stuff is all really just a backdrop to incredibly nerdy (and delightful) discussions of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Charles Stross
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-charles-stross/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 03:20:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph Henderson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-charles-stross/</guid>
        <description>I am writing about Charles Stross because of the upcoming Picocon science fiction convention, which he will be attending as one of the Guests of Honour. He has contributed to the Science Fiction and Fantasy field with his novels, his blogging, and his roleplaying work.
Of these three things, the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Immoralist
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-14-the-immoralist/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 03:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-14-the-immoralist/</guid>
        <description>Despite being published in 1902 I find that this novel reads as though it were fifty years ahead of its time. The tone of Gide’s writing is sparse, conservative and yet at times overwhelmingly beautiful. For a writer with an aversion to the novel in his formative years, Gide has blended meter, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Neil Gaiman’s Sandman
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-neil-gaimans-sandman/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 04:50:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-neil-gaimans-sandman/</guid>
        <description>Comic books and graphic novels have a, not entirely undeserved, reputation for not being the finest example of modern literature. Poor plotting, tired characters and woeful dialogue still continue to plague the medium. However, there have always been a small number of creators – such as Alan Moore, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to Night Vale
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-welcome-to-night-vale/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-welcome-to-night-vale/</guid>
        <description>How to write a review of something whose own creator describes as “weird and impossible to describe”? At its simplest, Welcome to Night Vale, produced by Commonplace Books, is a fortnightly audio podcast in the format of a radio news broadcast from the fictional American desert town of Night Vale. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A story of loss and beauty
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-a-story-of-loss-and-beauty/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 03:50:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>vp1312,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-a-story-of-loss-and-beauty/</guid>
        <description>Anyone familiar with Donna Tartt knows that her works take time; her debut, The Secret History, took her eight years to complete and her following novel, The Little Friend, a decade. Anyone familiar with Donna Tartt also knows that the wait is completely justified and worth it. The Goldfinch, her …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Raw Words: Part Two
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-raw-words-part-two/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 22:11:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-raw-words-part-two/</guid>
        <description>The years continued to roll on, expanding until my childhood reverie waned. Ireland continued to be a panacea of opportunity. By 2008 Dad had replaced the BMW with a Range Rover. It consumed the driveway with its girth.
I remember being gathered around the television. The Madines were having a quiet …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chortle Festival
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-chortle-festival/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 22:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-chortle-festival/</guid>
        <description>I really wasn’t sure what to expect from the Chortle Comedy Books Festival – an event hosted by the comedy news website Chortle. After all, what would such an event even entail? It turns out that I needn’t have worried. The festival was an eclectic mix of comedy shows related to books and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Raw Words: Part One
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-raw-words-part-one/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 16:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-raw-words-part-one/</guid>
        <description>“As you go through life Shane, remember one thing. There’s a price to pay for everything.” The words of Aodhán Madine, my father, once spoken flippantly, now touch a raw nerve. Time has passed and they’re like daggers, sharpened by the whetstone of the crash.
We were happy back then. Through the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Stars My Destination
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-the-stars-my-destination/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 18:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-the-stars-my-destination/</guid>
        <description>Despite my extensive familiarity with science fiction I had, until very recently, had a major gap in my knowledge of the field – the works of Alfred Bester. One of the foremost writers of the late Golden Age of the genre, he has influenced later writers such as Phillip K. Dick and William Gibson, as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chortle Festival Comes to London
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-10-chortle-festival-comes-to-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2013 21:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-10-chortle-festival-comes-to-london/</guid>
        <description>The British comedy website Chortle has announced its first comedy book festival – which will take place in Ealing at the end of this month. The festival will open with a stand up gala in Ealing Town Hall, featuring hit comedians including Richard Herring and Shappi Khorsandi. This opening event will …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The dangers of being strange
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-the-dangers-of-being-strange/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 09:46:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-the-dangers-of-being-strange/</guid>
        <description>Imagine a white hot day blazing around you, created by blinding and numbing sunlight, all colours scrubbed cleaner and brighter and the air too hot to breathe. As I read L’etranger – usually translated as either The Stranger or The Outsider – a similar atmosphere appeared to surround me, created by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are they worse than animals?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-are-they-worse-than-animals/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 09:33:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Grant,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-are-they-worse-than-animals/</guid>
        <description>What does investment banking look like from the point of view of a wide eyed money hungry graduate? Anyone considering going into this avenue of finance after graduation should seriously consider giving this book a read to gain some insight into what kind of work and lifestyle you can expect. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Take nothing for granted
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-take-nothing-for-granted/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 00:14:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Erbacher,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-take-nothing-for-granted/</guid>
        <description>“In the world according to Garp, we are all terminal cases. “ This motif, recurring multiple times throughout the novel, is perhaps somewhat overdramatised, yet painfully accurate. From the first page through to the last one, the reader is infected with the subtle anticipation that the characters …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
