<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sf305/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sf305/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>There aren’t enough intellectuals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-there-arent-enough-intellectuals/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 21:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-there-arent-enough-intellectuals/</guid>
        <description>The world is ruled by aggressive simpletons. We have all met jobsworths and nice guys, people who run things according to the first thing that comes into their head, rather than thinking it through.
The first example of this I came across in the political arena was the monarchy debate. There are a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to be a woman
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-how-to-be-a-woman/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 21:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-how-to-be-a-woman/</guid>
        <description>I had been resisting reading this book for a while. Partly because I have no desire to lose the meat and two veg, and partly because publishers are canny enough to know their target audience and design the cover accordingly. Having worked for a bookshop as an undergraduate I also know that the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Time for change
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-time-for-change/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 20:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-time-for-change/</guid>
        <description>Back in the dear old early 14th century, “the pox” was considered a punishment from God. If you had it, you were evil and it was a just fate. You had wronged. You had failed. You deserved to die. The trouble with this idea was that there came a time when it struck a lot of people that this was not …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I want an armstice
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-18-i-want-an-armstice/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 00:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-18-i-want-an-armstice/</guid>
        <description>Last week, we marked the death of millions of soldiers. They had all died in action at some point in the last 93 years, since the start of the First World War. The eleventh day of the eleventh month has been marked in this way for years. In fact, only a handful of people currently alive today were …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The death of Bad Science
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-the-death-of-bad-science/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 20:46:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-the-death-of-bad-science/</guid>
        <description>Bad Science is dead. It has fallen off its bench. It has gone to meet its supervisor. It is an ex-science. Sadly, I am not talking about a humane rounding-up of charlatans, quacks, homoeopathists, and people who like to compete as to who has the best imaginary friend. I am talking about Ben …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The barbarians are at the gate
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-8-8-the-barbarians-are-at-the-gate/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 13:52:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-8-8-the-barbarians-are-at-the-gate/</guid>
        <description>Everyone thinks Morrisons is for cheap northerners. At least, according to a recent report, Morrisons think that people think that they are for cheap northerners. So, they have started selling black Italian truffles.
Said truffles are a mere snip at £99/kg. Well outside the budget of the average …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The death of print media
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-7-22-the-death-of-print-media/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 10:33:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-7-22-the-death-of-print-media/</guid>
        <description>I am not a journalist. I have never hacked a phone, written a meticulously-researched piece about an obscure detail concerning Princess Diana that would only be published because she was she, or lain doggo in one of Boris Johnson’s rhododendron bushes with pencil and paper at the ready to record …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>So hungry I could eat a horse
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-so-hungry-i-could-eat-a-horse/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 21:14:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-so-hungry-i-could-eat-a-horse/</guid>
        <description>Hunger has taken me to many weird places – Zone 6, meat free foods and even Ginster’s pasties. What I have not done is eat a donkey’s cock as Paul Merton almost did on his documentary series about China. But if I were really hungry, would I?
Having ridden horses for a while, including a few …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why drive?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-why-drive/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 21:08:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-why-drive/</guid>
        <description>I have yet to take helicopter gunships seriously. Whenever I hear about them—which has been regularly since the business in Libya kicked off—I immediately think they are referring to something out of science fiction, or at least Bucky O’Hare.
As you might imagine, this is a far cry from commuting on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The minefield of social etiquette
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-the-minefield-of-social-etiquette/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 20:29:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-the-minefield-of-social-etiquette/</guid>
        <description>How many times have you ever wanted to tell someone who is apologising to you, to **** off? Not because they slept with your best friend, but just because of the grovelling, sickening nature of it. I amaze myself about how fervently I want to sometimes. But equally, how often has an apology barely …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why does it always rain on me?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-why-does-it-always-rain-on-me/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 20:10:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-why-does-it-always-rain-on-me/</guid>
        <description>Like recovering alcoholics everywhere, Britain has woken up to the declaration of droughts in several parts of the Kingdom. Queendom. Whatever it is – it is dry. It is also the first half of June after a stinking cold winter. It is tempting to strike up something British and indignant about why the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flimsy Facebook friends
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-11-flimsy-facebook-friends/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2011 17:28:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-11-flimsy-facebook-friends/</guid>
        <description>Deleting people is a growing form of therapy. Perhaps happily, this is not the latest jargon for serial-killing, but is a synonym for a re-appraisal of ‘Facebook friends’. Facebook friends – those people you like or love, but also those people who have got married and not told you, even after the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cuts to equipment funding
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-cuts-to-equipment-funding/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 18:14:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-cuts-to-equipment-funding/</guid>
        <description>Research in engineering and science disciplines took another blow last week when it was announced that a second round of research budget cuts would be effective on research proposals submitted after 1st May 2011.
Following recommendations from the Wakeham review on higher education funding, funding …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cheap chicken
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-27-cheap-chicken/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 13:57:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-27-cheap-chicken/</guid>
        <description>Cheap Chicken will never die. If anything it is on the increase, despite McDonald’s and the ubiquitous beef burger having been around longer even than most of us. The trouble is that it is looking as though its days may well be numbered, not least because various things have now clipped its wings. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I want a good war...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-i-want-a-good-war/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 05:54:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-i-want-a-good-war/</guid>
        <description>There is nothing like the threat of being shot in the head, for reassurance. And whether or not the threat of that has befallen you, and I hope not, on the world’s stage there seems to be something of a trend of conflict resolution and a supremacy of liberal ideals. The conflict in northern Ireland …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Convenience for the poor?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-convenience-for-the-poor/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 15:03:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-convenience-for-the-poor/</guid>
        <description>It is just fat pikeys that shop in Greggs. Surely? I mean, it must only be they who demand an opening time of 0700 on weekdays, freshly-baked multi-grain loaves, Empire biscuits, and roasted chicken sandwiches complete with delicate slivers of red onion. Must be. There is no other answer, clearly. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s all an Olympic waste of time
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-its-all-an-olympic-waste-of-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 08:49:24 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-its-all-an-olympic-waste-of-time/</guid>
        <description>I was in two minds about buying my Olympics tickets for some time. This was a chance to see some great riding. But champing at the bit, I was not.
As one may expect, tickets were not cheap and of course I wanted good value for money. Seeing good horse-and-rider combinations strut their stuff is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What’s the fuss with truffles?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-21-whats-the-fuss-with-truffles/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2011 10:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-21-whats-the-fuss-with-truffles/</guid>
        <description>Truffles have always sounded slightly removed from anything I eat on a regular basis. Not because they were impossible to get hold of, just something I was unlikely to stumble across. And if, like me and Daniel Barenboim, you are more immediately interested in the impossible rather than the very …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A medical adventure: the beginning
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-a-medical-adventure-the-beginning/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 20:34:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-a-medical-adventure-the-beginning/</guid>
        <description>MRI machines make a peculiar sort of layered whirring noise, both when one is in them and one is waiting to be in one. At other times too, I should think, but I did not stick around for those.
First, I was waiting there. The cheery woman took my forms, checked over the sundry details, sat me in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fancy food stylings en français
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-fancy-food-stylings-en-franais/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 21:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-fancy-food-stylings-en-franais/</guid>
        <description>Samuel Furse
As avid readers of the Comment section will know, I recently finished my PhD. I had not thought much about what came after, as there was a peculiar type of feeling that it might never end, for a while. It did, and in so happening I wanted to celebrate. The agèd Ps (they do not yet know …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why attack nurses?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-why-attack-nurses/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 20:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-why-attack-nurses/</guid>
        <description>I feel for nurses. I don’t mean the sort of nurses who wear fishnets and appear readily in a Google images search, I mean the sort which work in hospitals up and down the country. After a recent report from a nursing ombudsman, this profession is in for yet another bashing for reasons I can only …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Should we worry about climate change?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-should-we-worry-about-climate-change/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 21:22:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-should-we-worry-about-climate-change/</guid>
        <description> Charles Betts
The end of the world always seems to be approaching. The Millennium Bug was supposed to turn every computer on the planet mental, activating every nuclear bomb and killing us all on verse two of Auld Lang Syne. The UK chief medical officer told us in 2005 that bird flu would wipe out …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Russian Service or French?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-russian-service-or-french/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 20:24:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-russian-service-or-french/</guid>
        <description>One of the things all the top chefs say is that one of the reasons they are in the job is because they like putting a plate of food in front of someone. A good recent example of this is Nigel Slater, whose early life was dramatised on the BBC over Christmas – arguably more for the gay kiss than for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An edible adventure...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-an-edible-adventure/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 19:49:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-an-edible-adventure/</guid>
        <description>I eat. Shocking stuff, you may be thinking, but it gives me a certain problem. Fortunately I have no life-threatening difficulties – I am not allergic to nuts, wheat or milk. I am allergic to Gillian McKeith, but that is another story. What you should perhaps know is that I am tall. I also take a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Want to save the planet and eat meat? Eat Man
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-want-to-save-the-planet-and-eat-meat-eat-man/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 20:27:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-want-to-save-the-planet-and-eat-meat-eat-man/</guid>
        <description>One thing that is often said by vegetarians is that meat farming is not sustainable. Figures are not (scientifically) clear, though what is obvious is that farm production of animals for human consumption requires a lot more in the way of nitrogenous input than for arable farming – not least because …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is the first year of a degree a waste of time?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-is-the-first-year-of-a-degree-a-waste-of-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 21:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-is-the-first-year-of-a-degree-a-waste-of-time/</guid>
        <description>Oh goody! Another subject to rant on about in a pedantic and pompous tone of voice. Well, more like splitting hairs in a self-important manner really. Either way, the headline “Is the first year of a degree a waste of time?” is the sort of trashy headline calculated to get Radio Four listeners …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Were the French right to strike?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-were-the-french-right-to-strike/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 19:09:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-were-the-french-right-to-strike/</guid>
        <description>Samuel Furse
Yawn yawn, the French are on strike again, and I and others are left wondering what the point is. This time at least, it appears to be some sort of principle, though whether this raises them above the level of London Underground tube drivers striking is questionable. The majority of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Freshers’ initiations are a chance to do something special that we should embrace
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-freshers-initiations-are-a-chance-to-do-something-special-that-we-should-embrace/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 19:51:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-freshers-initiations-are-a-chance-to-do-something-special-that-we-should-embrace/</guid>
        <description>A couple of years ago, at some rather remote university in England, a student died as a result of an initiation ceremony, apparently involving physical activity and alcohol. The details were never quite made clear, but it left many universities and colleges across the land with no option but to ban …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
