<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/helenmoneykyrle/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/helenmoneykyrle/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>All in Good Time: In Due Course But Without Haste</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-all-in-good-time-in-due-course-but-without-haste/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Helen Money-Kyrle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-all-in-good-time-in-due-course-but-without-haste/</guid>
        <description>Written by Bill Naughton in the 60s, All in Good Time follows the story of young newly-weds Arthur and Violet as they negotiate the beginnings of married life. But money is tight and they are forced to move in with Arthur’s good-natured but overbearing parents. Laden with innuendo, the storyline …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Luna Terra Sol</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-luna-terra-sol/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Helen Money-Kyrle,Marta Wolinska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-luna-terra-sol/</guid>
        <description>On the evening of Friday 8th February, the Union Concert Hall was filled with a lively audience for the greatly anticipated annual Imperial College Charity Fashion Show: Luna, Terra, Sol. Sponsored by Godiva and organised by the Fashion and Design Society in collaboration with ICU RAG, the event …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Better Late than Never | Happy Halloween</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-12-better-late-than-never-happy-halloween/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Helen Money-Kyrle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-12-better-late-than-never-happy-halloween/</guid>
        <description>If you’re looking for original improv or sketch comedy, you need to look no further than Bristol. Alright, maybe that’s quite far, but it was absolutely worth the coach journey from London Victoria to Bristol for what was a memorable Saturday evening entertainment at the Bristol Improv Theatre. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>La Bohème | One of opera’s great classics</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-la-boh-me-one-of-opera-s-great-classics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,Helen Money-Kyrle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-la-boh-me-one-of-opera-s-great-classics/</guid>
        <description>The romanticised notion of the struggling artist – impoverished but ingenious, penniless but praiseworthy – was a big hit with the public when La Bohème first premiered in 1896. As a uni student living on a budget, the plight of Rodolfo (Jonathan Tetelman), Marcello (Nicholas Lester), Colline (David …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Take a Mate to the Tate Late</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-take-a-mate-to-the-tate-late/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Helen Money-Kyrle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-take-a-mate-to-the-tate-late/</guid>
        <description>So you’ve survived your first week in London. You’re probably feeling a little squeezed for cash, but just because you’ve spent all your money on curly fries doesn’t mean you can’t still enjoy the excitement of being in a capital city. So, if you’re craving a wallet-friendly culture-fix, why not …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Definitive Guide to Autumn in the Capital</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-the-definitive-guide-to-autumn-in-the-capital/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Helen Money-Kyrle,Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-the-definitive-guide-to-autumn-in-the-capital/</guid>
        <description>Now until 7 October 2018
Frieze London and Frieze Masters art fairs in Regents Park.
Now until 13 October 2018
The Globe is still running open air performances; with £5 standing tickets it’s not to be missed!
Now until December 2018
Caledonian Express at the Pleasance – the best shows of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best of the Edinburgh Fringe Festival 2018</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-20-best-of-the-edinburgh-fringe-festival-2018/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Helen Money-Kyrle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-20-best-of-the-edinburgh-fringe-festival-2018/</guid>
        <description>Linda
Seated in a cosy Underbelly venue, we are told the story of Linda, an average 57-year-old woman who is selected to travel to Mars. We hear not from Linda herself; instead her story is told through the people around her, showing us some of the challenges she faced and revealing why she might …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Thomas Cole – Will we lose our Eden?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-15-thomas-cole-will-we-lose-our-eden/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Helen Money-Kyrle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-15-thomas-cole-will-we-lose-our-eden/</guid>
        <description>Born in 1801 during the height of the Industrial Revolution, Thomas Cole was to become one of the greatest landscape painters in American history. Having grown up in Lancashire, England, he moved to America with his family at the age of seventeen, determined to become a painter. Still well-known in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fashioned from Nature, but at what cost?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-fashioned-from-nature-but-at-what-cost/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Helen Money-Kyrle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-fashioned-from-nature-but-at-what-cost/</guid>
        <description>Fashion is unnatural – and distinctly human. Whether you pay much attention to it or not, the clothes that you wear express something about your individuality and, in turn, each of us have a personal and subjective response to fashion.
The V&amp;amp;A’s Fashioned from Nature exhibition makes you aware …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Romeo and Juliet | Updated and abridged
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-romeo-and-juliet-updated-and-abridged/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Helen Money-Kyrle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-romeo-and-juliet-updated-and-abridged/</guid>
        <description>Regardless of whether you&amp;rsquo;re madly in love, or frankly you&amp;rsquo;ve had enough of it this week, there&amp;rsquo;s still something inherently appealing about the tragic tale of Romeo and Juliet.
Squeezed into a running time of just one hour, the National Theatre’s interpretation sets a shortened …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
