<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/im808/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/im808/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>N_Polytope: Behaviours in Light &amp; Sound After Iannis Xenakis
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-n_polytope-behaviours-in-light-sound-after-iannis-xenakis/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 14:56:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-n_polytope-behaviours-in-light-sound-after-iannis-xenakis/</guid>
        <description>In an abandoned swimming pool somewhere in the northern perimeter of Berlin, lights burst to the rhythm of acoustic ricochets. A bizarre choreography of light and sound imitates patterns of synchrony and predation found in the animal kingdom.
The source of this erratic audiovisual experience is a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Turkey on the tipping point
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-7-turkey-on-the-tipping-point/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 13:58:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-7-turkey-on-the-tipping-point/</guid>
        <description>This week in Turkey, peaceful demonstrations against the demolition of Istanbul’s Gezi Park rapidly escalated into nationwide protests against the increasingly conservative measures enacted by prime minister Recep Tayyip Erdoğan. The disproportionate dispersion tactics used by the police catalysed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You Don&#39;t Have To Call It Music #8
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-30-you-dont-have-to-call-it-music-8/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 13:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-30-you-dont-have-to-call-it-music-8/</guid>
        <description>or: it don&amp;rsquo;t have to mean a thing.
Jazz has always been a little different. Scattering this way and that, each instrument wriggles its way on to the scene and bears it all in turn. Yet despite all its quirks, it often gets tied down by its melodic, rhythmic and compositional structures.
In …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You Don&#39;t Have To Call It Music #7
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-23-you-dont-have-to-call-it-music-7/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2012 00:22:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-23-you-dont-have-to-call-it-music-7/</guid>
        <description>or: RRRRrrrrxxxqtqttqtxxckkkkhhhhzzzzzzzz&amp;hellip;blip.
Punk rarely alluded to any sort of musical ambition. Its approach to independent thought and communal outreach empowered the youth to carve themselves a place in the world. Like the pioneers of experimental music decades before, their sound was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You Don&#39;t Have To Call It Music #6
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-you-dont-have-to-call-it-music-6/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 21:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-you-dont-have-to-call-it-music-6/</guid>
        <description>or: I ain&amp;rsquo;t thick, it&amp;rsquo;s just a trick.
Music has often been trimmed with philosophical considerations, or in the case of rock &amp;amp; roll or funk, sexual liberation. However, these ideologies more often than not play second fiddle to the tunes themselves. One could just as easily accept or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You Don’t Have To Call It Music #5
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-you-dont-have-to-call-it-music-5/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 14:20:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-you-dont-have-to-call-it-music-5/</guid>
        <description>or: ears make music too, you know?
Following France and Germany, the third post-war musical revolution took place in North America. Unlike the preceding movements – concrète and elektronische – the American vanguard did not gather in a single studio. Instead its ranks converged primarily on two …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Happy birthday, John Cage!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-happy-birthday-john-cage/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 14:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-happy-birthday-john-cage/</guid>
        <description>4’33’’ of silence, in three parts, for one piano.
The performer goes on stage, sits at his piano and closes the keyboard. When it’s over, he gets up, bows and leaves.
Perhaps the most controversial piece of music ever written, John Cage’s 4’33’’ is not a comedy routine, but a call to listening. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You Don’t Have To Call It Music #4
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-you-dont-have-to-call-it-music-4/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 23:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-you-dont-have-to-call-it-music-4/</guid>
        <description>or: drums are from Africa, synths are from Germany
While the Parisian advocates of musique concrète exposed the song of every day sounds, elsewhere in Europe, the avant garde was focusing on the musical potential of electricity. Despite their use of the tape reel as a medium for sampling and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You Don’t Have To Call It Music #3
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-you-dont-have-to-call-it-music-3/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 03:11:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-you-dont-have-to-call-it-music-3/</guid>
        <description>or: how the Berlin Wall made it to Broadway.
Towards the end of the 1920s, some, including Stravinsky, were alluding to the possibility of writing music for gramophones as had been done for violins or pianos before. The new paradigm came with the new technologies developed after WWII, namely …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You Don’t Have To Call It Music #2
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-you-dont-have-to-call-it-music-2/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:35:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-you-dont-have-to-call-it-music-2/</guid>
        <description>Classical music has been all but abandoned by the generations following the XX Century iconoclasts. Swept aside by the hormonal avalanche of the baby boomers, modern music since Elvis turned to Africa for salvation from the amorphous excursions of the decades before. Percussion has informed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You Don’t Have To Call It Music #1
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-you-dont-have-to-call-it-music-1/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 21:25:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-you-dont-have-to-call-it-music-1/</guid>
        <description>or: what the atom bomb and the death of God have to do with birds and brutalism.
I was brought up to disown classical music. When I wanted rock &amp;amp; roll, I got baroque. Admire convention as sacrosanct and do not touch. Unfortunately, it took years for me to gain any sort of interest in classical …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You Don’t Have To Call It Music #0
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-you-dont-have-to-call-it-music-0/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 11:33:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-you-dont-have-to-call-it-music-0/</guid>
        <description>Music is wonderful, wouldn’t you agree? It stirs up a great deal in one’s being. It makes the foot tap, the heart beat slower and faster, and floods the mind with memories and emotions. Beyond a psychophysiological episode, it actually tells us a lot about ourselves and our humanity, when other …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A night at Le QuecumBar
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-3-a-night-at-le-quecumbar/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 15:53:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-3-a-night-at-le-quecumbar/</guid>
        <description>One lazy summer evening, I proposed to my friends that we check out a jazz bar just down the street from our place, but which we had never been to in two years of living there. Le QuecumBar is a 1930s inspired gypsy jazz bar which hosts some of the best known players of the style first performed by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rhythm is the Ritalin
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-rhythm-is-the-ritalin/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 21:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-rhythm-is-the-ritalin/</guid>
        <description>Why is there rhythm in music? To some, this question may seem utterly superfluous, but is arrhythmic music really so unfathomable? The heartbeat is itself a periodic throb, as is breathing. It appears that rhythm is an integral part of vitality and perhaps this is why we are so attracted to it.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reviewed in 60 Seconds
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-reviewed-in-60-seconds/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 21:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Hunter,Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,Alexandra Ramadan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-reviewed-in-60-seconds/</guid>
        <description>David Bowie - The Rise And Fall of Ziggy Stardust and the Spiders from Mars
Having been released 40 years ago, this review is probably a bit late. For those of you who are less than familiar with the work of David Bowie this album is a great place to start.
_The Rise and Fall of Ziggy Stardust and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>No exit from reality
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-no-exit-from-reality/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 11:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-no-exit-from-reality/</guid>
        <description>Music, like all art, is a creative outlet addressing two domains: affronting reality and escaping it. The first can be witnessed in the efforts of the punk movement to criticize the values of modern society, or as a means of raising awareness and capital for charitable causes. The second aims to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Head down Spank Alley
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-27-head-down-spank-alley/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 12:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-27-head-down-spank-alley/</guid>
        <description>Who’s in the Spank Alley? Matt: I’m Matt, first year PhD student and I play the drums Jermyn: Jermyn, 3rd year Biochemistry, undergraduate. I play the saxophone. Faris: I’m Faris. I’m a 3rd year PhD student and I play the piano. Jordan: Jordan, also 3rd year PhD. Bass. Eugene: Eugene. I’m a 3rd year …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Inescapable Fate
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-27-inescapable-fate/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 12:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-27-inescapable-fate/</guid>
        <description>How long has the band been going? I really should know this… I’ve been playing with them for a couple of years, but they were already together for a few years before that.
Wow. So it’s a quite a long standing band then. Yeah, but it’s… piss poor, because we’ve only played about 5 or 6 gigs. Just far …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wolf Tracks
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-wolf-tracks/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 21:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-wolf-tracks/</guid>
        <description>Who’s who? Ran: I’m Ran, lead singer and I sometimes play acoustic guitar on some of the songs. Louie: I’m the drummer. Luke: I’m Luke, I play guitar. Henry: Henry and I play the bass.
So I heard you guys all met in halls? Luke: Yeah. We were all in Wilson last year. Me and Louis lived next door to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Howlin’ Circus
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-howlin-circus/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 20:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-howlin-circus/</guid>
        <description>So you guys just had rehearsal. How did it go? Sonam: It was good. As usual. Working on new songs.
How do your songs come about? Jamie: Different guys will write different kinds of songs and then we try to bring it together and kind of bring it all together to make a common sound.
So you prefer to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Apocalypse at the Union
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-apocalypse-at-the-union/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 21:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-apocalypse-at-the-union/</guid>
        <description>Following the interlude at the _Felix Music Night _last weekend, Music Tech Society return to Metric next Saturday 26 November with their first We Are Metric night of the year. Given the Union’s new policy on clubs &amp;amp; societies requiring a special theme in order to host a night, what better way …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Music Tech warm up KABLAAM &amp; boil after-party
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-music-tech-warm-up-kablaam-boil-after-party/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 20:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-music-tech-warm-up-kablaam-boil-after-party/</guid>
        <description>When I first encountered Music Tech, I thought I had seen the light. Finally some people were playing (and making) good music to go out to. No longer had I excuses to swallow inane “party party” muzak, when such an alternative was close at hand. My first evening with the lot was driven by a hazy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Be sure not to miss... NegativWobblyLand
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-be-sure-not-to-miss-negativwobblyland/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 20:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-be-sure-not-to-miss-negativwobblyland/</guid>
        <description>San Francisco cut/paste sound collage pioneers NegativLand team up with fellow Fog City resident Wobbly for an evening of home made electronics. The collaboration is centred around the exploitation of The Booper, a fully analogue device put together from salvaged radio and amplifier parts, creating …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Music Night: KABLAAM
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-28-felix-music-night-kablaam/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 10:30:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-28-felix-music-night-kablaam/</guid>
        <description>Imperial’s music scene is certainly underground. The bright morning sunshine rarely reaches its dark recesses and its artists receive little attention. The Felix Music Nights are our way of celebrating this under-appreciated scene and also fostering it; bringing more students into the tent and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Piano drops in Iceland
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-piano-drops-in-iceland/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 11:27:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-piano-drops-in-iceland/</guid>
        <description>Tim Hecker’s latest outpouring, Ravedeath, 1972, wraps around the billows of an organ in a church in Reykjavik. Sampled and reconfigured, casting a brume of disbelief, its song is suspended like a gasp in deep sleep. The sounds disintegrate like a snowball melting in your hand. Each remaining echo …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Nurse With Wound List
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-28-the-nurse-with-wound-list/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 11:29:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-28-the-nurse-with-wound-list/</guid>
        <description>1979 holds the key to the farthest reaches of musical conception. That year, Nurse With Wound released their debut album Chance Meeting on a Dissecting Table of a Sewing Machine and an Umbrella. Their music is the aural equivalent to the paintings of Salvador Dalí, stretching the mind and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Music Tech bring the noise to 19.02
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-music-tech-bring-the-noise-to-1902/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 19:58:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-music-tech-bring-the-noise-to-1902/</guid>
        <description>My first experience with Music Tech Society resulted in internal haemorrhaging. I was a fresher and just arrived at uni after a particularly interesting summer. It was Friday of Fresher’s Week and Music Tech were doing a night at dB’s (as it was still called then). This was also my first exposure to …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
