<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Music on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Music on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/music/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>A Brief History of Jazz </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-brief-history-jazz/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-brief-history-jazz/</guid>
        <description>By the time this newspaper came into existence, jazz was already old – or at least middle aged. Louis Armstrong had defined improvisation, swing had already been and gone, replaced by frantic bebop, cool jazz and eventually fusion. Genres like rock and soul had begun to rear their heads, offshoots …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Amnioverse: A Perfect Album Listening Experience</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-amnioverse-a-perfect-album-listening-experience/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-amnioverse-a-perfect-album-listening-experience/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
I don’t think I’d be offending anyone by saying that most listeners of electronic music focus more on singles than albums. When you listen to Hybrid Minds or Bicep you normally wouldn’t play the whole album start to finish. However, there are electronic albums that actively work against …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FKA Twigs - Live</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-FKA-twigs-live/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-FKA-twigs-live/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
FKA twigs’ gig didn’t start until 9:30, by which point a large portion of the audience frustrated, having waited for over 2 hours. The curtains raised bit by bit, riling the crowd further. “This show had better be good” muttered someone behind me, thankfully, it was.
Twigs’ vocals were …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hip Hop: The Genre Of The Decade</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-hiphop-genre-of-decade/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-hiphop-genre-of-decade/</guid>
        <description>Undeniably, hip hop dominated this decade, having established itself as one of the most diverse yet hereditary forced in modern culutre. I asked Hip Hop Soc members to pick their top 20 albums of the decade. This pretty banging consensus list is the result:
20. Barter 6 - Young Thug (2015)
19. 4:44 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Computers Took our Music Away</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-how-computers-took-our-music-away/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-how-computers-took-our-music-away/</guid>
        <description>Putting the history of a whole genre of music to paper is a mammoth task, especially for a genre as fluid and diverse as electronic music, so please forgive any oversight I may have made in trying to accomplish it. It is a story of technical innovation, experimentation, and of people coming …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rock Throughout the Ages</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-rock-throughout-ages/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Freeman,Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-rock-throughout-ages/</guid>
        <description>The roots of rock as a genre are buried deep in the other sounds of the 50s: blues, jazz, R&amp;amp;B and country, amalgamated together to form its own unique genre, known as rock and roll. This began in the deep south of the states, where the first electric guitars began to make a heavy impact on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>1/3 analogue, 1/3 digital, 1/3 nature: Dominik Eulberg</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-third-analogue-third-digital-third-nature-dominik-eulberg/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-third-analogue-third-digital-third-nature-dominik-eulberg/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
Dominik Eulberg, the 41-year-old recluse birdwatcher, who happens to also make some of the best German techno, says that he feels drawn to the animalistic aspects of the genre. The sweating, the entranced dancing, the rapture when the crescendo lifts your feet off the ground. He brought all …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Starcrawler Comfortably Blows Minds at Camden Show</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-starcrawler-comfortably-blows-minds-at-camden-show/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Freeman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-starcrawler-comfortably-blows-minds-at-camden-show/</guid>
        <description>3 stars
Ah, Underworld. So many incomplete memories of too many nights out. So many vivid memories of strange men standing just a bit too close when you’re just trying to have a night out with friends. Despite my current opinion of Underworld, it will always hold a special place in my …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Top 10 Rap Albums of 2019</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-top-10-rap-albums-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-top-10-rap-albums-2019/</guid>
        <description>Straight up: the UK killed it this year. We’ve finally reached a point where the best outputs of the rap scene at home is legitimately comparable to the best of the US’s. Asides from the four banging albums that make this top 10 list, this year saw the release of great UK projects like Kojey …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Two New Tunes for You</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-two-new-tunes-for-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-two-new-tunes-for-you/</guid>
        <description>Last month LA based Funk group The Pendletons released their debut LP: 2 Steps Away. A delightful blend of tight grooves, thick bass and slick 70’s-style horn sections. The record as a whole draws heavily on its funk and disco influences, with a distrincly vintage compositional style, still taking …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Used to Be Lonely’ is keeping me company</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-used-to-be-lonely-is-keeping-me-company/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-used-to-be-lonely-is-keeping-me-company/</guid>
        <description>This summer Whitney released their second album – Forever Turned Around. A beautifully intimate project focusing on change in personal relationships. It’s definitely an album for the summer, but I believe Forever Turned Around is just as great at warming the spirit in the cold winter months. It’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FKA Twigs Makes Album - is Good</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-fka-twigs-makes-album-is-good/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-fka-twigs-makes-album-is-good/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
Tahliah Barnett, aka FKA Twigs quickly rose from ‘Video Girl’ to adored songstress in the mid 10’s, earning critical acclaim and a cult following from a series of releases including her 2014 record LP1. Here, atmospheric synthesisers and industrial drums left plenty of space for Twig’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Old Blue Last Hit by Furious Punk Noise</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-old-blue-last-hit-furious-punk-noise/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Freeman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-old-blue-last-hit-furious-punk-noise/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
I hiked up to Shoreditch last week to catch one of my favourite bands at the moment, Girls in Synthesis, as they played one of the ‘Fifty Fest’ shows to promote the new music on the bill for Brighton’s The Great Escape Festival.
Before GiS came The Cool Greenhouse, who offered up low-key …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Big Thief steal the top spot with ‘Not’</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-big-thief-steal-top-spot-not/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-big-thief-steal-top-spot-not/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
I recently discovered a a new personalized playlist Spotify creates called “On Repeat”. As the name suggests, this contains the 30 songs you’ve been playing most over the last 30 days.
While this initially served as a slightly unnerving reminder of the reams of data I willingly give to big …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Days of Abandon: Shimmering Sounds Tinged with Sad Mopery</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-days-abandon-shimmering-sounds-tinged-sad-mopery/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ambika Bharadwaj,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-days-abandon-shimmering-sounds-tinged-sad-mopery/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
In their third album, Days of Abandon, The Pains of Being Pure at Heart almost ditched their last album’s heart bursting intensity. Frontman Kip Berman, once a starry-eyed “heart on his sleeve” daydreamer serenading anyone in earshot, now sounds like a young romantic who has seen his share …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Denis Sulta takes us to the Xanadu of dance</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-denis-sulta-takes-xanadu-dance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-denis-sulta-takes-xanadu-dance/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
We turn the corner, the gray lake at Canada Water still at the back of our minds. It’s pouring it down, and the group consensus is that we won’t miss the outside world for the next 10 hours. We’re going into the void. That is how every new Printworks adventure feels.
I’m not explicitly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FEET OF CLAY (Some More Rap Songs)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-feet-of-clay-some-more-rap-songs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Louie Ghalib,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-feet-of-clay-some-more-rap-songs/</guid>
        <description>I have been following Earl Sweatshirt’s career religiously since his 2015 project I Don’t Like Shit, I Don’t Go Outside. Sure, I knew of him because I was a fan of Tyler, The Creator and Odd Future, and I listened to tracks he made that featured Frank Ocean and Vince Staples, but I initially became …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Lowdown on BBC Introducing LIVE</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-lowdown-BBC-introducing_LIVE/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-lowdown-BBC-introducing_LIVE/</guid>
        <description>For twelve years BBC Introducing has been helping upcoming artists break into the industry. Every year the BBC holds an event (BBC Introducing LIVE), a relative candy shop for musicians to get insider information from the insiders themselves. Alumni of the service include Little Simz, Ed Sheeran, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nearer my God: Foxing’s Transcendental Rock Show</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-nearer-my-god-foxing-transcendental-rock-show/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonathan Lu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-nearer-my-god-foxing-transcendental-rock-show/</guid>
        <description>I saw several bands live over the summer. Florence + The Machine and The National’s anthemic chamber pop at BST in front of thousands in Hyde park, Black Midi drawing a respectable crowd at EartH despite having released virtually no music (I also wrote a review for their show I’m sure nobody read) …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Thank you for the warm welcome back” - My Chemical Romance and Rage Against the Machine announce reunions!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-MCR-and-RatM-announce-reunions/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Freeman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-MCR-and-RatM-announce-reunions/</guid>
        <description>It’s been a hefty week in music news, after the shock announcement of a reunion from emo-legends My Chemical Romance shortly followed by a similar post from the rap-metallers Rage Against the Machine.
MCR fans were overwhelmed on Halloween after MCR socials posted about ‘Return’, their first show in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cigarettes After Sex - Cry: A Collection of Ruminations on Love </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-cigarettes-after-sex-cry-collection-ruminations-love/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ambika Bharadwaj,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-cigarettes-after-sex-cry-collection-ruminations-love/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
With their second album, Cigarettes After Sex are back with more noir dream-pop, echoey guitars, and amazing vocals. Greg Gonzalez sounds deep in love, as he whispers the lyrics, slow-as-molasses, in songs like “Pure” &amp;amp; “Touch”. His penchant for lovely, lilting melodies, and the sound, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>JESUS... This Record is Disappointing</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-jesus-this-record-disappointing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-jesus-this-record-disappointing/</guid>
        <description>1.5 stars
Kanye West needs no introduction. By the time this is published he will undoubtedly have kicked up a fresh onslaught of headlines that even dedicated fans must be jaded with at this point. In other news, research suggests that narcissists are more likely to be successful than people with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nick Cave’s Piercing Exploration of Grief</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-nick-caves-piercing-exploration-grief/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cara Burke,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-nick-caves-piercing-exploration-grief/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
Hunched among a small crowd in Rough Trade East, bags on our laps and posters bundled awkwardly around us, we heard Nick Cave and the Bad Seed’s Ghosteen for the first time. It was the album’s premiere and I was at an album playback party only a week after its release had been casually …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pony: Sterilisation of Bedroom Pop or an Intentional Shift in Creative Direction?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-pony-sterilisation-bedroom-pop-intentional-shift-creative-direction/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-pony-sterilisation-bedroom-pop-intentional-shift-creative-direction/</guid>
        <description>3 stars
There are lots of bedroom pop artists breaking into the mainstream these days (Clairo, Gus Dapperton, Boy Pablo, Omar Apollo, etc.), but the undisputed king is Rex Orange County. After featuring on Tyler, the Creator’s Flower Boy, Rex leapt from 500 followers on SoundCloud to being one of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sick Boy Lookalike Bringing the Disco Vibes</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-sick-boy-lookalike-bringing-disco-vibes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-sick-boy-lookalike-bringing-disco-vibes/</guid>
        <description>The white hair, the Scottishness, the pomp he brings to his sets – a lot of the elements of 26-year-old Hector Barbour’s alter ego point to the man from Trainspotting. But while the difficult path that Hector was on may well have led him to the same kind of sorry existence that his on-screen …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Loyle Carner Starter Pack: A &#39;How To&#39; Guide</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-loyle-carner-starter-pack-how-to-guide/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-loyle-carner-starter-pack-how-to-guide/</guid>
        <description>I should start by saying that I do enjoy Loyle Carner’s music. It’s just that since the release of Not Waving, But Drowning his musical formula has become annoyingly apparent. The guy has talent and lots of people get something from his music, but he ain’t immune to criticism. Now that I’ve …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>50 Years Young – Led Zeppelin II Celebrates Half a Century of Blowing People’s Minds</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-50-years-young-led-zeppelin-2-celebrates-half-century-blowing-peoples-minds/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Freeman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-50-years-young-led-zeppelin-2-celebrates-half-century-blowing-peoples-minds/</guid>
        <description>Led Zeppelin II was formed out of incessant pressure from their record label Atlantic Records, who wanted to ride on the hype of Led Zeppelin’s first album, Led Zeppelin, released 7 months beforehand in March 1969. The important consequence of this meant that recording occurred throughout the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Interview with Imperial’s very own Roy Juxon </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-interview-imperials-own-roy-juxon/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-interview-imperials-own-roy-juxon/</guid>
        <description>Felix: So when did this all start?
RJ: Still pretty recently actually. I only really got into it during my gap year. That’s when I did my Walland Hill EP, just before going travelling. But I hadn’t really done any music until January this year.
Felix: Really? Ever?
RJ: So, I used to produce drum and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Big Riffs, Small Ideas: Foals are Far too Comfortable to Leave the Stadium Rock Arena</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-big-riffs-small-ideas-foals-too-comfortable-leave-stadium-rock-arena/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-big-riffs-small-ideas-foals-too-comfortable-leave-stadium-rock-arena/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
Early this year, following four years of relentless touring, Oxford-based indie quartet, Foals, teased that they had a new album ready. This was not to be any ordinary album, however, as they had recorded simply too much material for one record, meaning it would have to be released in two …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Decimal Man Still CRUSHing it After Over Four Years</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-decimal-man-still-crushing-after-four-years/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-decimal-man-still-crushing-after-four-years/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
Floating Points is a man with a PhD from UCL. Now, I wouldn’t want to set the bar TOO high but FP’s friend Dan Snaith, a.k.a. Caribou, a.k.a. Daphni, has a PhD from Imperial, as does Brian May. Looking at musicians with doctorates from the most (un?)prestigious London universities, that is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Foundations of Hip Hop: The Memphis Underground</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-foundations-hip-hop-memphis-underground/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Avish Vijayaraghavan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-foundations-hip-hop-memphis-underground/</guid>
        <description>Memphis hip hop emerged from the underbelly of Memphis, Tennessee in the early 90s. While the genre was distinctly underground, it has pervaded through decades of hip hop that followed. Characterised by dark lo-fi production, triplet flows, and repetitive hooks, the subject matter consisted mainly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>JOHN is Out Here (on the Fringes)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-JOHN-is-out-here-on-fringes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Freeman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-JOHN-is-out-here-on-fringes/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
JOHN, often known as JOHN (TIMESTWO) as both members of the duo are called John, have a brand spanking new album out. And as unimaginative as their band name is, this album is far from the same. Based out of Crystal Palace, South London, JOHN rode into the current post-punk wave along with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Danny Brown Lets Us Down</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-danny-brown-lets-us-down/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-danny-brown-lets-us-down/</guid>
        <description>3 stars
Danny Brown has become something of a legend of the underground hip-hop circuit this decade, with the ability to rhyme almost anything, an imppecable wit and a penchant for insane beats. On epic albums like XXX and Atrocity Exhibition Brown explores his lifestyle as a drug dealer-turned drug …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fresh tracks!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-fresh-tracks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-fresh-tracks/</guid>
        <description>Lapalux laid the foundation of his discography on glitchy, rough, and voided ambient sounds. While not considered “experimental”, his style certainly didn’t draw in the more mainstream crowds. However, his most recent release demonstrates a calmer and more collected direction. This track is supposed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Introducing GioLeo: Imperial’s New Rap Duo</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-introducing-gioleo-imperials-new-rap-duo/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-introducing-gioleo-imperials-new-rap-duo/</guid>
        <description>Rapper and producer aren’t ever words that I associate with MechEng, and yet this last Saturday I sat down with Gio: MechEng student and lead vocalist of trap duo GioLeo. Along with fellow engineer Leo, the pair have been producing music together since the end of last year. Beginning this July under …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sleep: The Snoozefest in Kentish Town</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-sleep-snoozefest-kentish-town/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Freeman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-sleep-snoozefest-kentish-town/</guid>
        <description>1.5 stars
Last Friday night: a dreary evening, where all I wanted as we headed off to Kentish Town was for my heart, body and soul to be warmed by heavy rock. Luckily, we were heading to the lovely O2 Forum Kentish Town, a theatre-turned-venue which tonight was hosting the 90s stoner rock legends …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The anomalous King Gizzard and the Lizard Wizard </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-anomalous-king-gizzard-and-lizard-wizard/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Freeman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-anomalous-king-gizzard-and-lizard-wizard/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
As the chuggy riff of ‘Self-Immolate’ broke out over Alexandra Palace last Saturday, someone threw an entire pint down me. Not the best start to one of the best gigs I’ve been to in a long time, but certainly a memorable one. This night was definitely memorable for the band playing as well: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Strawberries &amp; Creem Festival 2019</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-07-31-strawberries-creem-festival-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-07-31-strawberries-creem-festival-2019/</guid>
        <description>Felix was in attendance as Strawberries &amp;amp; Creem, the up-and-coming independent festival, made its return, bringing its signature line-up of house and R&amp;amp;B, and Noughties throwbacks. Despite a severely muddy site due to heavy rainfall over the days leading up to the festival, revellers’ …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Music’s astronomical anthems</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-felix-music-s-astronomical-anthems/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-felix-music-s-astronomical-anthems/</guid>
        <description>Next month will mark 50 years since the Apollo 11 Moon landing/Stanley Kubrick pulled off the world’s most elaborate lampoon (delete as appropriate). To celebrate, here’s a select few celestial bangers to blast you out of this world.
‘Space Oddity’, David Bowie
Honestly, this whole list could very …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Half a century of Hot Buttered Soul</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-half-a-century-of-hot-buttered-soul/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhidian Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-half-a-century-of-hot-buttered-soul/</guid>
        <description>The 1960s were the decade of soul. While the huge commercial success of Motown opened up white audiences previously inaccessible to black recording artists, soul extended far beyond Detroit. The distinctive Southern soul sound found its voice through Memphis’s Stax Records. In an era of segregation, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reverb: society events made easier</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-reverb-society-events-made-easier/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-reverb-society-events-made-easier/</guid>
        <description>As the year draws to a close, many societies will begin the transition to a new committee. Running a society at Imperial is not easy, and perhaps the hardest part of running a society is planning the associated events. A lot of things have to be taken into consideration when preparing for them. You …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The noisy, discordant sound of history: Black Midi</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-the-noisy-discordant-sound-of-history-black-midi/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonathan Lu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-the-noisy-discordant-sound-of-history-black-midi/</guid>
        <description>Black Midi had released very little music as I walked down the steps to the EartH concert hall. In fact, when I first heard of the band from a friend of a friend of the band at a gig a year ago, they had released no music at all.
Much of the band’s following has been formed in a similar way, through …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Five reasons to visit Strawberries &amp; Creem Festival</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-five-reasons-to-visit-strawberries-creem-festival/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-five-reasons-to-visit-strawberries-creem-festival/</guid>
        <description>Strawberries &amp;amp; Creem, the up-and-coming independent festival returns to Cambridge’s Haggis Farm on Saturday 15th June with its signature line-up of house, hip-hop and R&amp;amp;B, and Noughties throwbacks. Speaking to Felix, Cambridge University graduate Chris Jammer - the festival co-founder (who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mac DeMarco’s Indie-Indie-Label Breakthrough</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-mac-demarco-s-indie-indie-label-breakthrough/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Neel Le Penru,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-mac-demarco-s-indie-indie-label-breakthrough/</guid>
        <description>Here comes the cowboy / Here comes the cowboy / Here comes the cowboy,” ad infinitum. The lyric(s) of the album opener and title track of Mac DeMarco’s fifth full-length studio record — and his first under his own label rather than long-term partners Captured Tracks — leave one thinking that this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Review: Kohncertino</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-review-kohncertino/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Timothy Kang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-review-kohncertino/</guid>
        <description>Well, Imperial unquestionably has no shortage of orchestras, bands or music groups. However, there’s a new orchestra which has been growing in the past few months: Kohncertino. Led by first-year maths student Michael Kohn, Kohncertino held its debut concert on Saturday 16th March, at St Gabriel’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A big fish in an even bigger pond</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-a-big-fish-in-an-even-bigger-pond/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-a-big-fish-in-an-even-bigger-pond/</guid>
        <description>This March, Australia will be the centre of gravity for psych rock and Formula 1 fans alike. But no matter how hot Ferrari are looking, in my heart I doubt that the action on the black asphalt of Albert Park will be able to overshadow what’s hiding in the grooves of the new Pond LP. Here’s why.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A sonic odyssey that mystifies as much as it inspires</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-a-sonic-odyssey-that-mystifies-as-much-as-it-inspires/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dario Mongiardi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-a-sonic-odyssey-that-mystifies-as-much-as-it-inspires/</guid>
        <description>Adorned with a cowboy hat and staring longingly into the camera during the promo video, the elder Knowles sister knows how to build hype for an album, following it up by providing us with another experimental and soulful LP. Its demo-like quality and cryptic lyrics may discourage new listeners, but …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>After a six year break from the music scene, Dido is still on my mind</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-after-a-six-year-break-from-the-music-scene-dido-is-still-on-my-mind/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shervin Sabeghi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-after-a-six-year-break-from-the-music-scene-dido-is-still-on-my-mind/</guid>
        <description>A warm cup of tea on a cold day – this is how I’d best sum up Dido. Though unassuming both in the recording studio and out, she’s managed to feature twice on the list of the top ten best-selling albums of the noughties and wrack up four BRIT Awards. Her first two albums No Angel and Life for Rent …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Father of 4 does not Offset Migos’s solo album efforts</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-father-of-4-does-not-offset-migos-s-solo-album-efforts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-father-of-4-does-not-offset-migos-s-solo-album-efforts/</guid>
        <description>For the more devout Migos fans, and for Atlanta locals, Offset has consistently been seen as the stand out member, despite Quavo clearly becoming established as the head of the group since their mainstream breakthrough. More recently, Offset has experienced more widespread attention for reasons …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Justice has been served, and it sounds amazing</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-justice-has-been-served-and-it-sounds-amazing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-justice-has-been-served-and-it-sounds-amazing/</guid>
        <description>So, I sit down in the Woodward study room ready to sink my teeth into some epidemiology, cut to three hours later and I finally start working. This wasn’t your average YouTube/Facebook/ “really need to reply to these week-old emails” kind of procrastination - this was JUSTICE!
You all know Justice, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Psychodrama Review</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-psychodrama-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,Simran Kukran,Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-psychodrama-review/</guid>
        <description>1. Psycho
What a way to kick off the album. A truly building track, Dave and the instrumentation become one as the listener is guided through the three main psyches that Dave will expand on throughout the album. Not only does he switch up his flow, content and delivery with each transition, but he …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reasserting indie rock dominance - Part 1</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-reasserting-indie-rock-dominance-part-1/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-reasserting-indie-rock-dominance-part-1/</guid>
        <description>Too young to fully engage with the monumental breakthrough of Arctic Monkeys, but too old to care the slightest bit about the 1975, Foals were MY band. Despite only receiving my backing in earnest following their third album (2013’s Holy Fire ), they soundtracked such a pivotal part of my …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Powerful lyricism and unbridled virtuosity</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-powerful-lyricism-and-unbridled-virtuosity/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elizabeth Thong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-powerful-lyricism-and-unbridled-virtuosity/</guid>
        <description>PROGRAMME:
STRAVINSKY: Suite for Small Orchestra Nos.1 and 2
KORNGOLD: Violin Concerto
DVOŘÁK: Symphony No.9, From the New World
Seeking New Horizons II: New Discoveries is the second of a three-part series celebrating the composers who pushed the musical boundaries of the period. The Royal …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ariana Grande’s thank u, next is a mature and conscientious pop classic</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-ariana-grande-s-thank-u-next-is-a-mature-and-conscientious-pop-classic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Large,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-ariana-grande-s-thank-u-next-is-a-mature-and-conscientious-pop-classic/</guid>
        <description>I thoroughly enjoyed Ariana Grande’s last album, Sweetener. With a majority of the production handled by Pharrell, the project had an eccentric and colourful atmosphere, and was far more interesting than your standard pop album. And it didn’t just sound great; considering the context of the release …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The man with the Midas touch, ante-ambient</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-the-man-with-the-midas-touch-ante-ambient/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-the-man-with-the-midas-touch-ante-ambient/</guid>
        <description>Apart from creating the Windows 95 start-up sound, Brian Eno is perhaps best known for pioneering the genre of ‘ambient music’, where extended instrumental compositions slowly loop and bubble, creating soundscapes that are intricate yet discreet. His work in this area went on to directly inspire …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kendrick vs Kendrick: To Pimp A Butterfly or good kid m.A.A.d city?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-kendrick-vs-kendrick-to-pimp-a-butterfly-or-good-kid-m-a-a-d-city/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-kendrick-vs-kendrick-to-pimp-a-butterfly-or-good-kid-m-a-a-d-city/</guid>
        <description>Ten years ago today, the name Kendrick Lamar meant no more than anyone else’s. The now 31-year-old rapper was still going by K-Dot and would shortly receive a career-changing cosign from Lil Wayne. Today he is one of the best known and certainly most respected artists in music. With twelve Grammys …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NeighbourHOOD Grammys 2019</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-neighbourhood-grammys-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,Lé Osikomaiya,Jamell Samuels,Jamil Wallace-Williams,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-neighbourhood-grammys-2019/</guid>
        <description>Album of the Year | Daytona, Pusha T
“It was written like Nas but it came from Quentin”
Nominations | ASTROWORLD, Travis Scott | Invasion of Privacy, Cardi B | Black Panther, Various Artists | FM!, Vince Staples | Victory Lap, Nipsey Hussle | Book of Ryan, Royce da 5’9’’
ASTROWORLD marked Travis’ …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Noonday Dream revisited: How one gig opened my eyes to the full beauty of Ben Howard’s latest album</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-noonday-dream-revisited-how-one-gig-opened-my-eyes-to-the-full-beauty-of-ben-howard-s-latest-album/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Large,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-noonday-dream-revisited-how-one-gig-opened-my-eyes-to-the-full-beauty-of-ben-howard-s-latest-album/</guid>
        <description>Ben Howard has had an interesting change in sound throughout his releases. His debut, Every Kingdom, was full of uplifting indie-folk songs with sing-along choruses and a (generally) carefree tone. His next release, The Burgh Island EP, marked a change in mood hinted at by the cover art; these songs …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bad luck for Ben Howard fans</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-bad-luck-for-ben-howard-fans/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Large,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-bad-luck-for-ben-howard-fans/</guid>
        <description>It’s easy to forget that Ben Howard released an album last year. It came and went, with no hit singles and an understated sound almost unrecognisable compared to the cheery beach-folk of his debut. The nature of this quiet and underdiscussed release is what makes the decision to perform these new …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>James Blake’s Assume Form doesn’t quite take shape</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-james-blake-s-assume-form-doesn-t-quite-take-shape/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-james-blake-s-assume-form-doesn-t-quite-take-shape/</guid>
        <description>With production for names including Kendrick Lamar, Travis Scott and Oneohtrix Point Never under his belt in 2018 one would expect Blake’s 4th effort to sound sublime, but after a few listens you might wonder if perhaps he’s spreading himself too thin. Whilst there is a lot on Assume Form to enjoy, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kobala Revisited: Afriquoi storm XOYO</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-kobala-revisited-afriquoi-storm-xoyo/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-kobala-revisited-afriquoi-storm-xoyo/</guid>
        <description>Afriquoi describe themselves simply as an “afro supergroup” who perform “live African dance music fusing Congolese guitar + Gambian kora virtuosity with UK electronic sensibilities”. Its band members: Andre Marmot (on percussion), Jally Kebba Susso (kora), Fiston Lusambo (guitar), Andre Espeut …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The wicked WIZRD of Sauce</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-the-wicked-wizrd-of-sauce/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-the-wicked-wizrd-of-sauce/</guid>
        <description>Future has always been a hit-making machine. Earlier in his career he adopted (and simultaneously established) a decidedly pimpish Atlanta trapper sound. Since then, Future has achieved ridiculous international recognition, the DJ Eskimo tags long gone. What set him apart from a Wacka Flaka or a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The man who shocked the world</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-the-man-who-shocked-the-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-the-man-who-shocked-the-world/</guid>
        <description>Three years ago last week, David Robert Jones passed away at the age of 69. I remember it perfectly, as it was the day I had my first exam as an Imperial undergraduate. The night before I had been listening to Blackstar, the surprise avant-garde album that he had released only two days earlier, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Andy’s Top Ten Most Anticipated Albums of 2019</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-andy-s-top-ten-most-anticipated-albums-of-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-andy-s-top-ten-most-anticipated-albums-of-2019/</guid>
        <description>Ordinarily I would kick off the year writing about my top ten most anticipated hip-hop albums. However, as I’ve mentioned before, I was left quite underwhelmed by hip-hop in 2019 and I’m struggling to come up with ten hip-hop albums I’m really looking forward to this year. As a result, I’m expanding …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Home-grown Imperial band heads to New Cross for single release party</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-08-home-grown-imperial-band-heads-to-new-cross-for-single-release-party/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-08-home-grown-imperial-band-heads-to-new-cross-for-single-release-party/</guid>
        <description>Inspired by acts such as Alabama Shakes and fuzz-fuelled bands of the 90s such as Dinosaur Jr and My Bloody Valentine, Candy’s Room merge together strong rhythmic grooves with psychedelic textures to create a new style of pop music.
Musicians Nathaniel and Miles (Chemical Engineering, 2nd year) have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Andy’s Top Ten Hip-Hop Albums of 2018</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-andy-s-top-ten-hip-hop-albums-of-2018/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-andy-s-top-ten-hip-hop-albums-of-2018/</guid>
        <description>I don’t actually think 2018 has been a very good year for hip-hop. There were very few ambitious projects dropped this year and not enough artists took risks with their music. J. Cole’s KOD is a prime example. Although a very good album, with it being featureless again, it felt like he produced much …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Earl Sweatshirt’s back at it with some rap songs</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-earl-sweatshirt-s-back-at-it-with-some-rap-songs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-earl-sweatshirt-s-back-at-it-with-some-rap-songs/</guid>
        <description>With his critically acclaimed debut Earl dropping at just 16, Thebe Kgositsile has a strong claim to the familiarity with his audience the title of his latest release - Some Rap Songs presumes. With a 24 minute run time (admittedly less surprising in 2018) and eerily blurred selfie as its cover, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial’s albums of the year, 2018</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-imperial-s-albums-of-the-year-2018/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music Writers,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-imperial-s-albums-of-the-year-2018/</guid>
        <description>Everything Is Love
The Carters
It’s a piece of a Jean-Michel state of mind, with Mona Lisa right behind. Embedded in a celebration of black love we are given the final piece to a love story that started with Beyoncé’s Lemonade and JAY-Z’s 4:44. Assembling succinctly as The Carters we see the world’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I bet tubas look good on the dancefloor</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-i-bet-tubas-look-good-on-the-dancefloor/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bobbi Lang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-i-bet-tubas-look-good-on-the-dancefloor/</guid>
        <description>How often have you dreamt of a live show consisting of just the Arctic Monkeys’ first album, cover to cover? If your answer is like mine – nigh on every night – then ten-piece brass band, the Old Dirty Brasstards, have got your back. With four trumpets, three trombones, two percussionists, and a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bangers, Bops, and Chunes</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-bangers-bops-and-chunes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Mitcham,Jiangxuan Chen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-bangers-bops-and-chunes/</guid>
        <description>Do you know what the BBC in BBC Music stands for? If you guessed ‘Bangers, Bops, and Chunes’…you’d be completely wrong, but I’d applaud your guess, as this is what BBC Music provides the British music scene with daily. There’s a huge spectrum of British musicians who now dominate the charts and are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Courtney Barnett tells us how she really feels</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-courtney-barnett-tells-us-how-she-really-feels/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-courtney-barnett-tells-us-how-she-really-feels/</guid>
        <description>Courtney Barnett has been crafting witty, mid-paced indie gems for half a decade; on a mild Wednesday evening she treated Brixton to a well-deserved outing of her latest material. After an all-Australian warm up roster, featuring the three-guitar jangle-juggernaut that is Rolling Blackouts Coastal …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Marie Davidson pours out her soul</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-marie-davidson-pours-out-her-soul/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucille Calmon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-marie-davidson-pours-out-her-soul/</guid>
        <description>While Marie Davidson’s albums have always been personal, Working Class Woman leaves a different feeling. She said that it is “an album where I have started to work with my psyche, trying to access a level of my consciousness that I was not aware of before.”
And indeed, it reads as her most personal …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nine Dutch Guys Bring the Heat to Blustery Camden</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-nine-dutch-guys-bring-the-heat-to-blustery-camden/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tobi Ampapa,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-nine-dutch-guys-bring-the-heat-to-blustery-camden/</guid>
        <description>Jungle By Night may not be a name on everyone’s radar - but they more than should be. The nine-piece instrumental collective, hailing from Amsterdam, has a sound that lies somewhere in the middle of jazz, afrobeat (I’m talking your uncle’s favourite Fela) and funk. The group has been steadily making …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>No money? No problem. On the art of living life as a penniless music-lover in London.</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-no-money-no-problem-on-the-art-of-living-life-as-a-penniless-music-lover-in-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sabina Nowakowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-no-money-no-problem-on-the-art-of-living-life-as-a-penniless-music-lover-in-london/</guid>
        <description>When I came to London four years ago, I was far more excited about the capital’s rich music scene than I was about starting university. Naturally, I expected life in the big city to be more expensive than the Polish countryside. Little did I know, however, the size of the difference was far greater …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Riz Ahmed Is Synonymous With Brown Excellence</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-riz-ahmed-is-synonymous-with-brown-excellence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-riz-ahmed-is-synonymous-with-brown-excellence/</guid>
        <description>If you’re brown, woke (shut the fuck up it’s a meme to be woke) or from London, and especially if you’re all three, chances are you know Riz Ahmed to be a Desi messiah. Riz began his trajectory towards this status after appearing in 2010’s Four Lions, a now cult classic comedy following the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The music you didn’t even know you needed</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-the-music-you-didn-t-even-know-you-needed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-the-music-you-didn-t-even-know-you-needed/</guid>
        <description>I’m mad, I’m riled up and it’s all you guys’ fault. Why am I angry? I’ll tell you. The Friday before last I was ecstatic because I was going to Fat Freddy’s Drop at O2 Brixton. Talking to people from IC on the day and explaining what glory I was soon to witness I realised not a single goddamn person …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A new muse-cal direction</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-a-new-muse-cal-direction/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maryna Voloshyna,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-a-new-muse-cal-direction/</guid>
        <description>Three years after the conclusion of Drones, the English “rock” band Muse returns with their eighth studio album, Simulation Theory. Unlike anything they have released before, Simulation Theory is a polariser that will fragment their fanbase with its shockingly foreign soundscapes of electronic rock …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A surprise Kamikaze for fans, critics and mumble rappers</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-your-filename/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>J Y Gan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-your-filename/</guid>
        <description>Eminem released the album, as the title suggests, without warning or promotion of any sort as opposed to Revival which was heavily marketed before its release in December 2017. Kamikaze was released on the final day of August this year, marking his shortest recording period in between albums. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is Post Malone culpable for exploiting hip-hop?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-is-post-malone-culpable-for-exploiting-hip-hop/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jordan Bunke,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-is-post-malone-culpable-for-exploiting-hip-hop/</guid>
        <description>The 2010s have marked a significant shift in the music industry and music consumption in two interesting ways: platform and genre. Consumers are increasingly moving away from purchasing music, whether vinyl, CDs, or downloads, and moving towards streaming. As part of their efforts to accurately …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An album to cure your autumnal anguish</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-an-album-to-cure-your-autumnal-anguish/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-an-album-to-cure-your-autumnal-anguish/</guid>
        <description>The nights are colder, the days are shorter, and there isn’t much new music being released. Guess what I’m most upset about. As the icy winter chill grows, my mind has gone back to one of my favourite albums of the summer just gone, Slide by George Clanton. Clanton’s been creating for years but …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hands up if you like being absolutely scared shitless</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-hands-up-if-you-like-being-absolutely-scared-shitless/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Large,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-hands-up-if-you-like-being-absolutely-scared-shitless/</guid>
        <description>Preface to this review: I’ve never been into heavy music, but I love horror films. It’s undeniably a bit insane to subject yourself to two hours of fear (I recently saw Hereditary in the cinema and thought I was going to die), but the visceral emotion good horror elicits is what makes it so …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Samm Henshaw takes us to church</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-samm-henshaw-takes-us-to-church/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-samm-henshaw-takes-us-to-church/</guid>
        <description>I recently had the pleasure of being in attendance as Samm Henshaw treated fans to a phenomenal one-off show.
Samm Henshaw rose to popularity following the success of his two-part Sound Experiment EP projects, the most recent of which was released in 2016. Samm has since largely been on the road, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BBC Music Introducing Live</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-07-bbc-music-introducing-live/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Mitcham,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-07-bbc-music-introducing-live/</guid>
        <description>The BBC is no stranger to treating the musical taste buds of music lovers across the capital. Organising what can only be considered the ‘Big Macs’ of musical events, the BBC have continuously jam-packed big names into their events boasting impressive flavours over a whole spectrum of genres. This …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pieces of a Man is introspective, indulgent, and inaccessible</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-pieces-of-a-man-is-introspective-indulgent-and-inaccessible/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Large,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-pieces-of-a-man-is-introspective-indulgent-and-inaccessible/</guid>
        <description>Two years after his ambitious but inconsistent and occasionally preachy release The Healing Component, Mick Jenkins has dropped a new album, Pieces of a Man. Four singles were released prior to the album’s unveiling, but the best two of these were inexplicably not included on it. This is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Everybody wants to change the world:  Looking at the White Album’s Legacy 50 Years on</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-everybody-wants-to-change-the-world-looking-at-the-white-album-s-legacy-50-years-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-everybody-wants-to-change-the-world-looking-at-the-white-album-s-legacy-50-years-on/</guid>
        <description>Exactly fifty years ago, the year 1968 was to be the beginning of the end for the Beatles. Lennon had finally escaped the clutches of chronic acid tripping, partly due to his burgeoning love for Yoko Ono, partly due to the retreat the band made to Rishikesh where they were meant to have sworn off …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mutation as a form as music</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-mutation-as-a-form-as-music/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Suraj G,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-mutation-as-a-form-as-music/</guid>
        <description>Rules are suffocating, their mere existence a constraint, bound by our own machinations. To create is to liberate. To break rules is to break free. Bach should be terrified of Ornette Coleman, and I’d reckon Chaplin would be dizzy after a Harmony Korine film.
Ambient music exists at the very end of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Minimum to maximum, ambient to aggressive</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-minimum-to-maximum-ambient-to-aggressive/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Suraj G,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-minimum-to-maximum-ambient-to-aggressive/</guid>
        <description>Aggression has, for the most part, been a matter of force or damage. They yell, the guitars scream, the drums roar. All a product of man’s basest tendencies, a primitive release. Reining it back, Live 2002, is in many ways a controlled exploration of the impulses preceding the violence. Its …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>REDUXER: Turning Water Into Wine</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-reduxer-turning-water-into-wine/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-reduxer-turning-water-into-wine/</guid>
        <description>Last June, the Leeds based indie rock band alt-J released their 3rd studio album, RELAXER. And it wasn’t good. Don’t get me wrong, I love alt-J just as much as the next guy; ‘Left Hand Free’ will forever get my feet tapping and my air drums rocking. But RELAXER was like looking in a fun-house mirror …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fresh albums: Thee Oh Sees, Gregory Alan Isakov</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-fresh-albums-thee-oh-sees-gregory-alan-isakov/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-fresh-albums-thee-oh-sees-gregory-alan-isakov/</guid>
        <description>The new Isakov album is out today&amp;hellip;
And I haven’t listened to it yet because I’m writing this piece on a Wednesday. But it’s spawned enough singles to be recommended to me on Spotify anyhow as an EP, “Dark, Dark, Dark,” after the lead single on the album. And boy howdy, isn’t he dreamy?
Isakov …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Hippo in the room: toxic masculinity </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-the-hippo-in-the-room-toxic-masculinity/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-the-hippo-in-the-room-toxic-masculinity/</guid>
        <description>Following up a debut LP as well-received and enjoyable as Landmark was bound to be a tough job for Hippo Campus. The American Midwest’s breeziest indie rock band have not shied away from the pressure though, and have just released a record that – despite not being a big departure from their previous …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>With a new Chance the Rapper project supposedly on the way, let us revisit his iconic Acid Rap  mixtape</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-with-a-new-chance-the-rapper-project-supposedly-on-the-way-let-us-revisit-his-iconic-acid-rap-mixtape/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-with-a-new-chance-the-rapper-project-supposedly-on-the-way-let-us-revisit-his-iconic-acid-rap-mixtape/</guid>
        <description>In 2016, we witnessed Chance the Rapper’s spiritual rebirth as “lil Chano from 79th” on the prophetic ‘Ultralight Beam’; a moment that would formally introduce a more sober, sweet as Sunday Candy, family man of a gospel-rapper-Chano, who the mainstream would come to adore following the release of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Every Microsoft Windows startup sound, ranked</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-every-microsoft-windows-startup-sound-ranked/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-every-microsoft-windows-startup-sound-ranked/</guid>
        <description>The Windows boot sounds are unknown gems of the music world. Brian Eno was a collaborator!
12. Windows 98 Plus!
Legitimately awful. I can’t believe the marketing theme thought this was a good idea. If I heard this noise out of my computer, I’d try to put it out with a fire extinguisher.
11. Windows …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get the strap! 50 Cent storms O2 arena</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-get-the-strap-50-cent-storms-o2-arena/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-get-the-strap-50-cent-storms-o2-arena/</guid>
        <description>The crowd who turn out to see the O2 arena stop of 50 Cent’s Get Rich or Die Tryin’ 15th anniversary tour is probably the most diverse I have ever seen at a show. Aside from the Power theme tune or 50’s Instagram feed, I’ve been largely out of touch with his work for about a decade. Despite this, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New term, hoo dis? The 2018 album prospectus</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-new-term-hoo-dis-the-2018-album-prospectus/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-new-term-hoo-dis-the-2018-album-prospectus/</guid>
        <description>It’s no secret that music is released. But figuring out what’s coming out, and when, can be a bit of a chore. I’ve curated a list of albums over the horizon our readers might care to listen to (if only for jokes).
Coheed and Cambria.
Vaxis – Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures.
2015’s The Color Before …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to the pleasuredome</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-welcome-to-the-pleasuredome/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,Henry Eshbaugh,Asad Raja,Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-welcome-to-the-pleasuredome/</guid>
        <description>My friend Kunal from Singapore calls me the grime guy. I like the way that sounds so I don’t correct him. In truth, as far as grime or UK rap goes, I consider myself a semi-casual listener (you won’t catch me listening to anyone less niche than, like, Ghetts). Though I stay open to most genres, US …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>While you were away...</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-while-you-were-away/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,Henry Eshbaugh,Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-while-you-were-away/</guid>
        <description>Family of Aliens
The third full-length effort by this indie pop quartet packs all the wholesome family-friendly goodness that fans have come to expect, but not without a wicked sense of humour and a quirky, sci-fi inflected glaze. A new crisply produced electronic vibe replaces their traditionally …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>God save the Childqueen</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-god-save-the-childqueen/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-god-save-the-childqueen/</guid>
        <description>There is a double pleasure in discovering the music of LA psychedelic-soul artist Kadhja Bonet. There is, first of all, the joy to be found in the music: warm and inviting, completely drenched in a sticky sense of pleasant nostalgia, the songs seem to have been beamed to us directly from the 1970s. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kids See Ghosts is a return to form for Kanye West</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-kids-see-ghosts-is-a-return-to-form-for-kanye-west/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-kids-see-ghosts-is-a-return-to-form-for-kanye-west/</guid>
        <description>This self-titled release marks the first collaboration project from hip hop’s biggest contemporary influencers, Kid Cudi and Kanye West, who have dubbed themselves Kids See Ghosts. This moniker and album title, as well as the album art, which was the work of Takashi Murakami (who has previously …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Man on Blonde: a masterpiece revisited</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-man-on-blonde-a-masterpiece-revisited/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ben Man,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-man-on-blonde-a-masterpiece-revisited/</guid>
        <description>The artist known as Frank Ocean, born Christopher Breaux, was born and raised in New Orleans, Louisiana. He studied English at New Orleans University, writing music on the side, before Hurricane Katrina destroyed his studio and uprooted his life. Ocean made the decision to move to Los Angeles to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Resistance to this album is futile</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-resistance-to-this-album-is-futile/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Pearson,Tams Lu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-resistance-to-this-album-is-futile/</guid>
        <description>Who are the Manic Street Preachers? They’re hailed as indie rock kings. They’re known for a slick bit of politics. Resistance is Futile gives us that, but better. Building off their old classics ‘Motorcycle Emptiness’ and ‘A Design For Life’, this eagerly anticipated album opens with ‘People Give …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
