<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/frank_leggett/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/frank_leggett/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Professor Jonathan Haskel appointed to Bank of England position</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-professor-jonathan-haskel-appointed-to-bank-of-england-position/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Frank Leggett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-professor-jonathan-haskel-appointed-to-bank-of-england-position/</guid>
        <description>Professor Jonathan Haskel has been appointed to the Bank of England’s Monetary Policy Committee (MPC). He will be one of nine members responsible for making a range of decisions, such as setting interest rates.
Haskel will replace Ian McCafferty as one of four external MPC members when McCafferty’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Postgraduate timetabling audit reveals Wednesday afternoons still not free</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-postgraduate-timetabling-audit-reveals-wednesday-afternoons-still-not-free/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Frank Leggett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-postgraduate-timetabling-audit-reveals-wednesday-afternoons-still-not-free/</guid>
        <description>An audit into postgraduate Wednesday afternoons – which are supposed to be reserved for free time – has found that they are widely used for teaching.
The audit was carried out by Nick Burstow, Imperial College Union’s Deputy President (Education), and Luke McCrone, President of the Graduate …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial alumnus new Malaysian Health Minister</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-imperial-alumnus-new-malaysian-health-minister/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Frank Leggett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-imperial-alumnus-new-malaysian-health-minister/</guid>
        <description>Dr Dzulkefly Ahmad has been sworn in as the new Health Minister for Malaysia under Tun Dr Mahathir bin Mohamad’s new government.
Dr Dzulkefly – who completed his doctorate in toxicology at Imperial College London in the early 1990s – is a member of Parti Amanah Negara (National Trust Party) a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Dean of Faculty of Medicine announced</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-new-dean-of-faculty-of-medicine-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Frank Leggett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-new-dean-of-faculty-of-medicine-announced/</guid>
        <description>Professor Weber has been acting dean since October of last year. He has previously held leading roles in the Department of Medicine, including Vice-Dean for Research and director of the Academic Health Science Centre (AHSC) – a collaboration between the college and different NHS trusts aiming to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Union bar supplier named</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-new-union-bar-supplier-named/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Frank Leggett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-new-union-bar-supplier-named/</guid>
        <description>Molson Coors – the current non-draft beer provider – has been chosen as the new draft beer supplier for the Imperial College Union bars, replacing Greene King.
The change of supplier will take effect on the 1st of August, after a five months&amp;rsquo; tender process for the position. Staropramen, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Secrets Facebook page shut down</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-imperial-secrets-facebook-page-shut-down/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Frank Leggett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-imperial-secrets-facebook-page-shut-down/</guid>
        <description>Imperial secrets, a popular Facebook page on which students could share secrets anonymously, was shut down last week.
The page, which had several thousand followers, has been under scrutiny for a large part of its existence: a meeting of Imperial College Union’s Community and Welfare Board earlier …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial 4th best university in UK; problems with student satisfaction continue</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-imperial-4th-best-university-in-uk-problems-with-student-satisfaction-continue/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Frank Leggett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-imperial-4th-best-university-in-uk-problems-with-student-satisfaction-continue/</guid>
        <description>The Complete University Guide (CUG) rankings, released last week, saw Imperial climb one spot to 4th best university in the country. The University of St. Andrews fell two places from the 2017 rankings, moving Imperial and the London School of Economics (LSE) up one place each. LSE has retained its …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union launches ethical investment survey</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-union-launches-ethical-investment-survey/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Frank Leggett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-union-launches-ethical-investment-survey/</guid>
        <description>The survey, launched online, has allowed respondents to voice their opinion on whether the Union should invest in industries considered ethically problematic such as pornography, fossil fuels, and the armament sector. The Union will invest its reserves and part of the Clubs, Societies and Projects …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Study finds higher education rife with sexual misconduct</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-06-study-finds-higher-education-rife-with-sexual-misconduct/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Frank Leggett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-06-study-finds-higher-education-rife-with-sexual-misconduct/</guid>
        <description>Over 40% of respondents to a survey recently carried out by the 1752 Group reported experiencing sexual misconduct by a member of higher education (HE) staff on at least one occasion.
The online survey, carried out by the National Union of Students (NUS) and the 1752 Group, which aims to end sexual …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College Union bar staff launch petition for London living wage </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-28-imperial-college-union-bar-staff-launch-petition-for-london-living-wage/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Frank Leggett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-28-imperial-college-union-bar-staff-launch-petition-for-london-living-wage/</guid>
        <description>A petition has been launched by members of Imperial College Union’s (ICU) bar staff asking them to increase the pay to the London Living Wage (LLW) .
The petition, launched last week on the site change.org has amassed close to 300 signatures at the time of the writing.
Felix has been told staff are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New strategy for sports at Imperial unveiled</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-new-strategy-for-sports-at-imperial-unveiled/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Frank Leggett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-new-strategy-for-sports-at-imperial-unveiled/</guid>
        <description>Sport Imperial and Imperial College Union have partnered to reshape sports and physical activity at Imperial College London.
The partnership aims to bring affordability, accessibility, and new opportunities for both student and staff bodies. It has put forward six objectives, including creating …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
