<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/felart/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/felart/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Arts in 2016 | a year in review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-arts-in-2016-a-year-in-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 15:06:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Arts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-arts-in-2016-a-year-in-review/</guid>
        <description> Ezra Kitson The Crucible&amp;rsquo; at Guildhall was my favourite show of the year. In the wake of everything that has happened in 2016 it’s quite difficult to be overly optimistic about the future but the Crucible reminded me of how mad people were in the 1950’s, and we managed to get through that. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A not-so shabby shocker
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-10-a-not-so-shabby-shocker/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 14:40:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Felix Arts,Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-10-a-not-so-shabby-shocker/</guid>
        <description>Puccini’s Tosca is well-known for being a melodramatic opera. After its premiere in 1900, it received mixed reviews from critics despite its popularity with the public - the musicologist Joseph Kerman famously dismissed it as “a shabby little shocker”.
The plot centres on Cavaradossi, a painter who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Government Inspector
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-the-government-inspector/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 04:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Arts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-the-government-inspector/</guid>
        <description>Jack Williams
Dramsoc Social Secretary
DramSoc’s winter play this year is Nikolai Gogol’s satirical comedy The Government Inspector. Banned by the tsarist government of Imperial Russia on its first publication, the play makes a mockery of the stupidity, greed and corruption of the officials of a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Artifacts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-the-artifacts/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 22:04:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Arts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-the-artifacts/</guid>
        <description>Each year, scientists from Imperial College and artists from the Royal College of Art join forces to create inspiring, innovative and interesting works of art under the scheme Artifact. Closet artist and Imperial student Meredith Thomas told Felix Arts all about it.
What is Artifact?
Artifact is a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don’t miss a treat!! IC Symphony Orchestra take you on a musical journey
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-dont-miss-a-treat-ic-symphony-orchestra-take-you-on-a-musical-journey/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 23:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Arts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-dont-miss-a-treat-ic-symphony-orchestra-take-you-on-a-musical-journey/</guid>
        <description>If you’ve never seen Imperial College Symphony Orchestra play, you’re missing out! Full of science-loving musicians, ICSO is Imperial’s flagship orchestra playing great music to the highest standards. After the success of playing to a sold out Cadogan Hall last year with the stunning BBC Young …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Top 10 Book Covers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-top-10-book-covers/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 21:47:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Arts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-top-10-book-covers/</guid>
        <description>Shirley Tucker
 The Bell Jar by Sylvia Plath featured a cover designed in 1966 by Shirley Tucker. Sylvia Plath’s only novel, published in the UK a month before her suicide, details the protagonist Esther Greenwood’s descent into clinical depression.
The bleak outlook is perfectly encapsulated in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Goalie’s Anxiety
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-the-goalies-anxiety/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 23:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Arts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-the-goalies-anxiety/</guid>
        <description>Peter Handke has been a very prolific artist during his lifetime, leaving behind several novels, plays and film scripts. He started his career working closely with the German literary avant-garde, which promoted works of post-war authors, unknown at the time, of the calibre of Günter Grass and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mitchell’s Cloud Atlas
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-mitchells-cloud-atlas/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 22:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Arts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-mitchells-cloud-atlas/</guid>
        <description>Cloud Atlas, to refresh your memory, is David Mitchell’s 2004 Booker short-listed novel whose film adaptation is due to release in the U.K early next year. The novel is, to put it mildly, a complex book, composed of six different narratives spanning time and space, from the 19th century South …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pedal powered comedy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-pedal-powered-comedy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 22:51:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Arts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-pedal-powered-comedy/</guid>
        <description>How do you deal with a heartbreak? Some people go and party it away. Others merge with their sofas until the tears dry out and some develop a freakish emotional attachment to a spinning bike…
That’s what happened to Clement, your Frenchspinning class teacher. I’m saying ‘your’ because the comedy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rumble in the jungle
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-rumble-in-the-jungle/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 03:07:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Arts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-rumble-in-the-jungle/</guid>
        <description>With an endless choice of world-renowned plays popping out every week in Central London, one might wonder why one need even look at the smaller theatres for entertainment. The answer, is that it is often only in off-the-beaten-track locations that you can find surprising little gems like the one …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flicks on bricks
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-flicks-on-bricks/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 20:57:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Arts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-flicks-on-bricks/</guid>
        <description>Last week from October 11th to 14th, the Bargehouse of Oxo Tower Wharf hosted the annual Moving Image fair, London’s only fair solely dedicated to moving image and contemporary video art. This meant four floors celebrating the video installations, projections and other forms of moving pictures of 35 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Not so tickled
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-not-so-tickled/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 11:30:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Arts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-not-so-tickled/</guid>
        <description>With most of the advertising targeting the Freshers, Monday’s Big Tickle comedy evening seemed to have slipped past the rest of the college unnoticed. Despite this, the predominantly fresher based audience gave the comics plenty to work with. Where else, but Imperial, would a debate over whether a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What the playwright heard
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-what-the-playwright-heard/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 22:19:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Arts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-what-the-playwright-heard/</guid>
        <description>With any absurd, wildly fantastic or outrageous anecdote about the world beyond our experiences, it is all too easy to dismiss it as an urban myth. The three men in their make-shift lounge dance between light-hearted, ludicrous and downright disturbingly macabre tales, and it doesn’t matter whether …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Made in SW11
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-14-made-in-sw11/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 11:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Arts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-14-made-in-sw11/</guid>
        <description>Rachel De-lahay has got it going on. Model, playwright, actress, joint winner of the Alfred Fagon award 2011 (which supports black playwrights) and her debut play The Westbridge currently showing at Sloane Square’s Royal Court Theatre.
Formerly called SW11 – the better name – The Westbridge delves …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Return of the Kings
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-14-the-return-of-the-kings/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 11:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Arts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-14-the-return-of-the-kings/</guid>
        <description>Here lies the end of an era – both on and off stage. Richard II as King of England and Michael Grandage as artistic director of the Donmar Warehouse. After almost a decade of ne’er erring productions, Grandage gives us Shakespeare’s Richard II. The stage has the hushed and sacrosanct air of a church …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cherries ripe for watching
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-cherries-ripe-for-watching/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 19:46:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Arts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-cherries-ripe-for-watching/</guid>
        <description>When I eventually managed to walk through the doors of the Olivier Theatre, blocked up with crowds, I turned my head to the stage and that enchanting stage setting took me to the beginning of the twentieth century straightaway. I could see a living room with wooden walls cosily enlightened with …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
