<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/lw408/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/lw408/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Senior Star Wars
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-senior-star-wars/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 18:17:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Wiles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-senior-star-wars/</guid>
        <description>It’s bad enough that there’s going to be another Star Wars film. It’s even worse that it’s going to be made by Disney. Worse still are the hints that some of the original cast will be returning to reprise their roles.
Rumours are flying around Hollywood that Carrie Fisher, Mark Hamill and Harrison …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The not-bad-you-should-probably-see-it Gatsby
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-the-not-bad-you-should-probably-see-it-gatsby/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 18:16:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Wiles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-the-not-bad-you-should-probably-see-it-gatsby/</guid>
        <description>You know how, more often than not, the trailer for a film shows all the film’s best bits and everyone is let down by the film? This is so not the case here. The Great Gatsby is everything the trailer promises, and more. It is bold, brash, glamorous and over-the-top in the trademark Baz Luhrmann way. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why won’t you just die?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-why-wont-you-just-die/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 01:28:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Wiles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-why-wont-you-just-die/</guid>
        <description>Well let’s face it – thechances of the fifth movie in ANY film franchise being spectacular were slim. But when Die Hard 4.0 (aka Live Free or Die Hard) was a bit rubbish, this one was bound to be equally shoddy. Which it was.
After the first three Die Hard films tied up the loose ends of a good …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>3.141592653589793238462643383279502884
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-3141592653589793238462643383279502884/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 23:01:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Wiles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-3141592653589793238462643383279502884/</guid>
        <description>For those of you who have read Yann Martel’s Booker prize-winning novel Life of Pi, you might have wondered, how on earth this soliloquy was going to be transformed into a half decent film. The majority of the novel is set in a small boat drifting around the ocean, and relates the thoughts of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Peter vs PETA
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-peter-vs-peta/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 23:09:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Wiles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-peter-vs-peta/</guid>
        <description>The Lord of the Rings and The Hobbit director Peter Jackson is currently at loggerheads with animal rights activist group PETA (People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals) over alleged animal cruelty during the filming of the Tolkien stories’ film franchise.
Jackson has vehemently denied claims …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Anthony’s Anti Academy Awards
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-anthonys-anti-academy-awards/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 23:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Wiles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-anthonys-anti-academy-awards/</guid>
        <description>Sir Anthony Hopkins, winner of the Academy Award for Best Actor for his portrayal of Hannibal Lector in The Silence of the Lambs, has labeled the Academy Awards system ‘disgusting’.
In a recent interview with The Huffington Post, Hopkins voiced his concerns over the sycophantic behaviour actors are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Disney buys Lucasfilm
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-disney-buys-lucasfilm/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 13:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Wiles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-disney-buys-lucasfilm/</guid>
        <description>Veteran film maker George Lucas has agreed to sell his company Lucasfilms – the company behind the entire Star Wars franchise – to Walt Disney, who will be making a seventh film in the series, to be released in 2015.
Lucasfilm, which is entirely owned by Lucas, will be added to Disney’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Madagascar 3 Review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-madagascar-3-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 13:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Wiles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-madagascar-3-review/</guid>
        <description>So the first one was good, and the second one was ok. But let’s face it, by the time the third film in a franchise turns up, nobody is expecting very much. But Madagascar 3 is surprisingly good – so good in fact that it currently holds the number two spot in the UK Box Office.
The dynamic quartet of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bond 23: The Skyfall of M
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-bond-23-the-skyfall-of-m/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 23:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Wiles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-bond-23-the-skyfall-of-m/</guid>
        <description>Practically every Bond film in the last 50 years has the same final promise before the credits roll: “James Bond will be back”. But that’s all we ever know – and the expectation surrounding this latest 007 endeavour was at an all-time high before its release last Friday. Sure – we knew it was Daniel …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Halloween Releases of 2012
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-new-halloween-releases-of-2012/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:32:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Wiles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-new-halloween-releases-of-2012/</guid>
        <description>Grave Encounters 2 - OUT NOW
Grave Encounters was a found-footage horror phenomenon that many people believed was just a movie. But in Grave Encounters 2, film student Alex Wright is out to prove the disbelievers wrong. Alex is as obsessed with the first film as the 20 million people who viewed its …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Emma Watson’s tasty wallflower
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-emma-watsons-tasty-wallflower/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 21:04:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Wiles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-emma-watsons-tasty-wallflower/</guid>
        <description>Adapted and directed by the author himself, Stephen Chbosky’s The Perks of Being a Wallflower is an enthusiastic, somewhat rushed, American teenage rite-of-passage story. Although a good premise and a best-selling novel, the film itself is distinctly over-full and does appear to have been put …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My chart reign will go on and on and on
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-my-chart-reign-will-go-on-and-on-and-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 18:29:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Wiles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-my-chart-reign-will-go-on-and-on-and-on/</guid>
        <description>Titanic 3D
Director James Cameron Screenwriter James Cameron Cast Leonardo DiCaprio, Kate Winslet
It’s been fifteen long years since James Cameron’s Titanic first graced our screens and, love it or hate it, you’ve got to admit – it’s become a totally iconic film. Even now, in the midst of a dramatic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Easter Special: Jesus in Cinema
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-easter-special-jesus-in-cinema/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 20:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Wiles,John G Park,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-easter-special-jesus-in-cinema/</guid>
        <description>The King of Kings (1927) – H. B. Warner The legendary Cecil B. DeMille’s last silent film, it does have its odd, completely original material (including its fairly creative opening in which Mary Magdalene, possessed by the Seven Deadly Sins, searches for her lover, Judah Iscariot), but he does …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Total mayhem and carnage... just your average night at Metric
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-total-mayhem-and-carnage-just-your-average-night-at-metric/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 22:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Wiles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-total-mayhem-and-carnage-just-your-average-night-at-metric/</guid>
        <description>Project X
Director Nima Nourizadeh Screenwriters Matt Drake, Michael Bacall Cast Thomas Mann, Oliver Cooper, Jonathan Daniel Brown
A distinctly unfunny teen-exploitation comedy about an epic all-night party that quickly collapses into anarchy, _Project X _also is a clever kind of clean page; viewers …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ten new releases to look out for over the Easter break
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-ten-new-releases-to-look-out-for-over-the-easter-break/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 21:47:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Wiles,John G Park,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-ten-new-releases-to-look-out-for-over-the-easter-break/</guid>
        <description>We Bought a Zoo (16 March)
Aimed at a large Christmas audience in the States, the significant delay in the U.K. release suggests the studio is banking on the warm, spring reception here in Europe. Which is just as well, because Cameron Crowe’s feel-good family drama involving lots of furry animals …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The return of the Muppet puppets
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-the-return-of-the-muppet-puppets/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 20:28:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Wiles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-the-return-of-the-muppet-puppets/</guid>
        <description>The Muppets
Director James Bobin Screenwriters Jason Segel, Nicholas Stoller, Jim Henson Cast Jason Segel, Amy Adams, Chris Cooper
They’re back! YES! The fantastic Muppets gang are back on the big screen with a whole new feature length movie for the first time in some years. Yes the story is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Harry Potter and the Deadly Woman
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-harry-potter-and-the-deadly-woman/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 21:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Wiles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-harry-potter-and-the-deadly-woman/</guid>
        <description>Director James Watkins Screenwriters Susan Hill (novel), Jane Goldman (screenplay) Cast Daniel Radcliffe, Ciarán Hinds, Janet McTeer
Anyone who has seen Susan Hill’s eery tale The Woman in Black on stage will know that the performance is terrifying. Even people who say they don’t get scared got …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Film talks to Aragorn
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-felix-film-talks-to-aragorn/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 23:53:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Wiles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-felix-film-talks-to-aragorn/</guid>
        <description>Last week, Felix Film was lucky enough to wangle a seat in a round-table interview with Viggo Mortensen – yes, an actual real actor – who played Freud quite brilliantly in A Dangerous Method. The interview took place at Freud’s old London house (which is now the quaint and interesting Freud Museum, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Witness the birth of psychoanalysis
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-witness-the-birth-of-psychoanalysis/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 23:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Wiles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-witness-the-birth-of-psychoanalysis/</guid>
        <description>A Dangerous Method
Director David Cronenberg Screenwriters Christopher Hampton (play), John Kerr (novel) Cast Viggo Mortensen, Michael Fassbender, Keira Knightley
A bit of an intense film, this one – a very starkly constructed look at a few strained relationships, most notably that of Carl Jung and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Silence is golden... so... shhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-silence-is-golden-so-shhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 22:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Wiles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-silence-is-golden-so-shhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh/</guid>
        <description> The Artist Director Michel Hazanavicius Screenwriter Michel Hazanavicius Cast Jean Dujardin, Bérénice Bejo
The French dream team of director/producer Michel Hazanavicius and actor Jean Dujardin are famous in France for their James Bond spoofs, the OSS 117 films. Now they venture into the States, to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Spielberg’s equine First World War
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-spielbergs-equine-first-world-war/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 20:29:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Wiles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-spielbergs-equine-first-world-war/</guid>
        <description>Director Steven Spielberg Screenwriters Lee Hall, Richard Curtis, Michael Morpurgo (play) Cast Jeremy Irvine, Emily Watson, Tom Hiddleston, David Thewlis, Peter Mullan
This is a true masterpiece. It’s certainly one of the most emotional films of recent times, with the last fifty minutes or so being …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cure for teen pregnancy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-cure-for-teen-pregnancy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 20:55:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Wiles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-cure-for-teen-pregnancy/</guid>
        <description>The Twilight Saga – Breaking Dawn Part 1
Director Bill Condon Screenwriters Melissa Rosenberg, Stephanie Meyers (novel) Cast Robert Pattinson, Kristen Stewart, Taylor Lautner
Thousands of hormonal Twihards queued for days for the much-anticipated arrival of The Twilight Saga: Breaking Dawn – Part 1; …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
