<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/alexander_koh/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/alexander_koh/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Which sector will prevail in the current market?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-which-sector-will-prevail-in-the-current-market/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Koh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-which-sector-will-prevail-in-the-current-market/</guid>
        <description>In an economically uncertain environment subject to policy-driven volatility, the underperformers would be high beta stocks such as the technology sector. The friction and tension surrounding the US-China trade war uncertainty has dampened the forecasted earnings of technology companies such as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Educational: Performing Absolute Evaluation</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-educational-performing-absolute-evaluation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Koh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-educational-performing-absolute-evaluation/</guid>
        <description>Investors are typically faced with the question of how much a stock (equity) is worth. To answer this question, there are two ways to value equities. The first method involves the use of ratios and comparison with other equities – relative valuation and the second method involves the use of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Insight into ETFs - The Future of Investing </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-an-insight-into-etfs-the-future-of-investing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Koh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-an-insight-into-etfs-the-future-of-investing/</guid>
        <description>Index funds refer to a mutual fund or Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) that track a specified basket of underlying securities (tradable financial assets). Moreover, ETFs are becoming an increasingly popular investment vehicle amongst both retail and institutional investors. More than 4,500 ETFs managed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bond Curve Yield Inversion </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-bond-curve-yield-inversion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Koh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-bond-curve-yield-inversion/</guid>
        <description>Yield curve inversions have traditionally been a foretelling sign of impending recessions. To explain the idea of a yield curve, one needs to understand what exactly a yield is. A yield to maturity, or simply bond yield has multiple interpretation, the simplest being – it is the return an investor …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
