<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Comment on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/comment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Comment on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/comment/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Why do we Pick and Choose when to Support People?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-20-why-pick-choose-support-people/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Damilola Toriola,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-20-why-pick-choose-support-people/</guid>
        <description>Recently there has been a lot of turmoil amongst social media users based on artists cancelling their concerts or wanting to abandon music all together because it damages their mental health. These artists have been receiving so much backlash simply because they want to put themselves first. Why do …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICBC Reflect on Mental Health and Spreading Awareness in the Rowing Community</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-icbc-reflect-mental-health-spreading-awareness-rowing-community/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-icbc-reflect-mental-health-spreading-awareness-rowing-community/</guid>
        <description>Mental health in sport is very often overlooked. Athletes are often perceived to be thick-skinned, resilient, and independent; looks can be deceiving. The thoughts, feelings, and emotions that navigate in that space between their ears are no different from that of any other person.
We are equally …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It is Not Corbyn that we Should be Blaming but Labour Centrists</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-not-corbyn-blame-labour-centrists/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-not-corbyn-blame-labour-centrists/</guid>
        <description>The Red Wall
The so-called ‘Red Wall’ includes many of the old Labour strongholds like Great Gimsby, Workington, that is famously being challenged by the Tories, and Don Valley. Many of these seats have non-local MPs who have been given a safe seat as a reward. Don Valley in Yorkshire, for example, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The End of a Decade: Italy</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-end-of-decade-italy/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Luca Rameli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-end-of-decade-italy/</guid>
        <description>The past decade has witnessed a proper political earthquake in Italian politics: what once was is no more. The political framework that has been in place since the nineties has fallen – the abrupt political changes that have occurred are similar to the previous largescale reshaping of the political …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your Union is Standing Firm</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-your-union-standing-firm/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-your-union-standing-firm/</guid>
        <description>There’s no doubt that this has been a tricky term for the Union. Our most senior member of staff is stepping down, the kitchens are closed, and student officers, in particular the deputy presidents, have had to work overtime to compensate for understaffing in the office.
Despite this, the Union is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>CONSUME! CONSUME! CONSUME! CONSUME! CONSUME! Then Die</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-consume-then-die/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-consume-then-die/</guid>
        <description>It’s the most wonderful time of the year… for the big fat cats to cash in on your appetite for greed and low self-esteem. Christmas is around the corner, and the capitalist gods have sent their finest to wring out every ounce of self-respect we have: Black Friday. Since its beginnings in mid-20th …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hong Kong: Home No More</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-hong-kong-home-no-more/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-hong-kong-home-no-more/</guid>
        <description>Hong Kong. An asphalt jungle lit by neon lights. The brutal trek up the Tiger’s Head and down towards the beaches of Discovery Bay. A mere cog in the global economy machinery. For me it was all that and more. But somehow six thousand miles away from the city I called home, I’ve now come to realise I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Will the UK be Voting On?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-what-will-uk-be-voting-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-what-will-uk-be-voting-on/</guid>
        <description>On December 12th, the British people will vote, but who and what are they voting for? Are they voting for thorough policies outlined in a manifesto or headline ideas performed on TV? Is it about the local candidate in their constituency or the celebrity like figure who leads that party?
This week, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Fourth Response on “Companies in China”</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-fourth-response-companies-in-china/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-fourth-response-companies-in-china/</guid>
        <description>This article forms part of a series of articles and responses, originating with Charles Titmuss&amp;rsquo; (2019 Comment Editor) article &amp;ldquo;Companies in China&amp;rdquo;.
It would appear that I have drawn the ire of two commentators due to articles that I wrote a couple of weeks ago. This is the last …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Further Response to the Article “Companies in China”</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-further-response-to-article-companies-in-china/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yuchu Liu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-further-response-to-article-companies-in-china/</guid>
        <description>This article forms part of a series of articles and responses originating with (2019-20) Comment Editor Charlie Titmuss&amp;rsquo; article &amp;ldquo;Companies in China&amp;rdquo;.
It was a great experience that my previous article was published on Felix without any discrimination, so I would like to express my …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Should be a Space for Rational Debate</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-felix-should-be-space-rational-debate/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jun Liu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-felix-should-be-space-rational-debate/</guid>
        <description>This article forms part of an ongoing series of articles and responses beginning with the (2019) Comment Editor, Charlie Titmuss&amp;rsquo;, article &amp;ldquo;Companies in China&amp;rdquo;.
Arguments usually help us explore new knowledge but quarrels often stop us from learning. The recent comments by Mr. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Political Pacts are Cheating the Electorate</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-political-pacts-cheating-electorate/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-political-pacts-cheating-electorate/</guid>
        <description>Since the election was announced a little over two weeks ago, there have been some big movements in the area of political pacts. With the Remain Alliance instigated between the Lib Dems, Greens and Plaid Cymru and the Brexit party making its own unilateral alliance, some voters find themselves …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title> You Either Die a Hero or you Live Long Enough to See Yourself Become the Villain</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-you-either-die-a-hero-or-live-long-enough-to-become-villain/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pedro Seifert,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-you-either-die-a-hero-or-live-long-enough-to-become-villain/</guid>
        <description>For those unfamiliar with this matter, Bolivia is a landlocked country in the western hemisphere. Called by many ‘the heart of South America’, due to its shape and geographical location, it is the poorest country in the region (by measure of its GDP per capita and its HDI). From the 16th century up …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Adiós, Evo</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-adios-evo/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nicolás Manrique,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-adios-evo/</guid>
        <description>More than anything else, the history of Latin America is a history of change. Its collection of revolutions, coups, elections, interventions and civil wars is long enough to keep even the most voracious historian busy, so it’s with an uneasy sense of déjà vu that Bolivia says goodbye to its …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NATO Needs Replacing</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-nato-needs-replacing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-nato-needs-replacing/</guid>
        <description>NATO was already creaking. Everyone could see it, from congressmen in the US tearing their hair out at Trump’s tweets to autocrats licking their lips. But no one wanted to say anything, because the emperor’s clothes are lovely until a child points out that he is naked. Macron is the allegorical …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Hidden Cost of Numbers</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-hidden-cost-numbers/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nicolás Manrique,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-hidden-cost-numbers/</guid>
        <description>Being someone who studies maths, it’s often assumed that I like nothing more than to think about numbers. In reality of course, studying maths is actually one the safest ways to be sure that you’ll never see one, and there’s a part of me which is grateful for this, for what initially might seem to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Unacceptable Situation in Xinjiang</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-unacceptable-situation-xinjiang/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Qyum Noor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-unacceptable-situation-xinjiang/</guid>
        <description>Felix published an article recently, highlighting how China exerts its economic muscle to manipulate the behaviour of companies and cajole them into turning a blind eye to many human rights abuses; in return, allowing businesses’ access to the large Chinese market, shamelessly forgoing ethics in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Response to “A Response to Companies in China”</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-08-11-a-response-to-a-response-to-companies-in-china/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-08-11-a-response-to-a-response-to-companies-in-china/</guid>
        <description>A couple of weeks ago, I wrote an article concerning Blizzard’s censorship of pro-Hong Kong protests entitled “Companies in China.” We have republished the article in question to provide context to this issue. Felix received a response which I recommend you look over before reading this, on the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Response to “Companies in China”</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-08-11-a-response-to-companies-in-china/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yuchu Liu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-08-11-a-response-to-companies-in-china/</guid>
        <description>By accident I noticed the article ‘Companies in China.’ As a Chinese international student at Imperial, the wording in this article is an insult, not only to me personally, but also to the whole Chinese community and our country. Imperial College should be a place where students from all over the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Companies in China</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-08-11-companies-in-china/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-08-11-companies-in-china/</guid>
        <description>For those of you that live on Instagram and have never met a cheeto-eating basement dweller, Blizzard are a gaming company that have developed some of the most popular titles over the last 20 years including Starcraft, Hearthstone and, of course, World of Warcraft. These games are popular all over …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fringe Parties: What are they good for?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-fringe-parties-what-are-they-good-for/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-fringe-parties-what-are-they-good-for/</guid>
        <description>The trigger has been pulled on what every political pundit is calling the most important general election of our generation. A choice between chaos with Johnson or a strong and stable Corbyn, or maybe it was the other way round? For many it is a choice between Brexit, championed by Boris Johnson, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>RE: “An opinion on the Hong Kong issue” – a Reality Check</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-08-11-response-to-an-opinion-on-Hong-Kong-a-reality-check/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-08-11-response-to-an-opinion-on-Hong-Kong-a-reality-check/</guid>
        <description>Have you ever read a piece of writing so factually inaccurate that you feel physically compelled to reply to it? That was the exact scenario in which I found myself after picking up a copy of Felix last Friday afternoon.
The article in the 1ST of November issue called ‘An opinion on the Hong Kong …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Opinion on the Hong Kong Issue</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-opinion-hong-kong-issue/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-opinion-hong-kong-issue/</guid>
        <description>The Hong Kong protests have been going on for 4 months now, with no end in sight. What started as a peaceful protest against the extradition bill has evolved (or devolved, depending on your perspective) into an often-violent movement against Beijing. Personally, I am both confused, amused and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Northern Ireland Abortion and Gay Rights</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-northern-ireland-abortion-gay-rights/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Wang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-northern-ireland-abortion-gay-rights/</guid>
        <description>Abortion was decriminalised in England, Wales and Scotland in 1967 and was made available through the NHS for free. Same-sex marriage was legalised in England &amp;amp; Wales in 2013 and 2014 in Scotland. Unfortunately, neither of these rights fully extend to Northern Ireland.
In July, the UK government …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I Hate Phones</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-I-hate-phones/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-I-hate-phones/</guid>
        <description>No, you can’t have my number. Why? Oh, that’s because I don’t have a phone. Yes, that does make me a better person than you. Thanks for noticing! I’ve actually been living life without a phone for six months now, and I’ve really felt the benefits.
It’s not because I’m scared that the Chinese …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Hong Kong Protests</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-hong-kong-protests/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrew Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-hong-kong-protests/</guid>
        <description>Protests in Hong Kong have been in the news for almost 4 months. Initially the protests were targeted to stop the extradition law to pass. I am sure that many are confused why a seemingly common extradition law caused full-scale riots and protests. The proposed extradition law included an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Prem de la Prem</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-prem-de-la-prem/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrew Melville,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-prem-de-la-prem/</guid>
        <description>As the wheels of top flight English football groan into action again after an arduous fortnight of international bullshit, let’s have a look at what we’ve actually missed. £35+ match prices, hours of advertisements, and the weekends games spread over 20 different streaming services. Us football fans …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BP Should Pay RSC More</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-bp-should-pay-rsc-more/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-bp-should-pay-rsc-more/</guid>
        <description>While activists might feel flushed with victory, they have damaged the funding sources of the RSC without offering a credible alternative.
I can only imagine that a sound like an airplane loo flushing went around the auditorium, there was so much indrawing of breath, after Richard Dawkins admitted …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Companies in China</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-companies-in-china/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-companies-in-china/</guid>
        <description>This article resulted in a series of follow-up articles and responses from the author and student respondents, which can be found in the Comment section.
For those of you that live on Instagram and have never met a cheeto-eating basement dweller, Blizzard are a gaming company that have developed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Extinction Rebellion</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-extinction-rebellion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dratsab Ypmurg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-extinction-rebellion/</guid>
        <description>Extinction rebellion (XR for short) has hit the streets of the UK and is being just as provocative as usual. Opinions of this current movement of concerned climate revolutionaries vary greatly, depending on who you are, and whether you are trying to get to work or not. The young, in general, are far …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We Should All Stop Fucking Swearing</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-we-should-all-stop-fucking-swearing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-we-should-all-stop-fucking-swearing/</guid>
        <description>We live in a society. One that swears too much. We are bombarded by expletives on the internet, in film, music, television, literature (and some sub-par “journalism” outlets). It has corrupted the youth and rooted itself deep into modern popular culture. Profanity has taken control of us and invaded …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We need an election</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-we-need-an-election/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-we-need-an-election/</guid>
        <description>There have been moments in world politics in the past four years where I have been surprised and perturbed by the result. Post-election hangovers are nearly always the best way to dull the immediate pain of being slapped in the face by certain events. At precisely 13:21 on Thursday 13th June, I read …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>No sympathy for Theresa May</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-no-sympathy-for-theresa-may/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-no-sympathy-for-theresa-may/</guid>
        <description>Let me start by stating very clearly: it is a privilege, not a right, to hold the most powerful job in the United Kingdom. This shouldn’t be a controversial statement, yet when Theresa May briefly broke down her veneer of stone-cold emotionlessness, the press immediately jumped onto it, making it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The UK’s hidden opioid crisis</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-the-uk-s-hidden-opioid-crisis/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-the-uk-s-hidden-opioid-crisis/</guid>
        <description>The phrase ‘opioid crisis’ has in the past had a Teflon-like quality about it, like ‘civil war’ or ‘theocracy’. These are terms used to describe distant news items. Fentanyl and oxycodone were intangible problems. However, studies by the Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development (OECD) …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PAARRY launch</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-paarry-launch/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Daniel Wigh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-paarry-launch/</guid>
        <description>Campaigners across the world have brought the issue of sexual misconduct into the spotlight in recent years and it has become apparent that it is a problem everywhere, including at Imperial. In an institutional culture report about Imperial from 2016, researchers found that: “Despite Imperial’s ‘no …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This week, we remember the dead</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-this-week-we-remember-the-dead/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-this-week-we-remember-the-dead/</guid>
        <description>Early Western explorers to China returned telling stories about a land of silk, jade and dragons. A whole artistic movement was birthed, Orientalism, that imagined the East – in particular China – as a semi-real land more out of story books than realism. The ruling Communist Party seems determined …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pointless, homophobic protests</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-pointless-homophobic-protests/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-pointless-homophobic-protests/</guid>
        <description>The introduction of the No Outsiders programme to schools in Birmingham has resulted in significant nationwide protests. The goal of the programme was to teach children about the protected characteristics in the Equalities Act 2010, including LGBT+ groups. Following its introduction, some parents …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Do you sometimes feel like you’re in China?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-do-you-sometimes-feel-like-you-re-in-china/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-do-you-sometimes-feel-like-you-re-in-china/</guid>
        <description>Do you sometimes feel like you’re in China? That’s what Suburban Express, a bus company based in Illinois, promises their customers will not feel when on their buses. The Urbana-Champaign campus of the University of Illinois (UIUC) has drawn a surging population of Chinese students to the area, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ideological purity and the Randos</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-ideological-purity-and-the-randos/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adam Kutnar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-ideological-purity-and-the-randos/</guid>
        <description>So another student, perhaps a coworker (or if you can imagine it, maybe even your university’s vice-provost of education) has shared some bigoted articles on their social media. They follow the twitter account of an organization that campaigns to take away support from trans children at school and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brexit: the end of internationalism</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-brexit-the-end-of-internationalism/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-brexit-the-end-of-internationalism/</guid>
        <description>I consider myself many things: a global citizen, a European citizen and a British citizen, in no particular order. Their ideals have always complimented each other but for the first time, they have started to clash. The onset of Brexit, as we rapidly approach the 29th of March, has thrown my whole …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Do we need Women’s Day?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-do-we-need-women-s-day/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aida Manzano-Kharman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-do-we-need-women-s-day/</guid>
        <description>Why do we need a day to celebrate women? In truth if you think about the concept of a day to celebrate women, it sounds almost absurd, women are so crucial to humankind that a one-day celebration doesn’t even come close to acknowledging how important women are. That’s one way of seeing it, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial pays working student late, again</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-imperial-pays-working-student-late-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-imperial-pays-working-student-late-again/</guid>
        <description>For the third time in six months, Imperial departments have failed to pay students who work for them on a part time basis on time. Students working on all day workshops around the pay date were informally told that they may have not be paid on time, and that it was their responsibility to follow it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grumpy Bastard’s Elections</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-grumpy-bastard-s-elections/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-grumpy-bastard-s-elections/</guid>
        <description>I’m unsure how many of you are aware of this but apparently voting in the student elections opens at 12 am today. A keen follower of student politics myself, I am excited to find out just who my representatives to the Union are going to be. Despite several years watching every single team of sabbs …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Anti-Vax movement</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-the-anti-vax-movement/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-the-anti-vax-movement/</guid>
        <description>Ethan Lindenberger is an American high-school senior who, on Tuesday, testified before the US Senate Committee on Health, Education, Labor and Pensions. He got himself vaccinated after asking on Reddit how to do so against the wishes of his anti-vax mother.
In his testimony, he attributed his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Imperial Bursary Scheme: a retrospective</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-the-imperial-bursary-scheme-a-retrospective/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhidian Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-the-imperial-bursary-scheme-a-retrospective/</guid>
        <description>Oh no, it’s another article about bursaries in Imperial! Though I can’t promise to be brief, I do promise that this is the last you’ll hear about it, from me, at least.
I’ll begin with the same preface given to every discussion of the bursary: genuine praise for the Imperial bursary scheme as a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is it #TimesUp for #MeToo?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-01-is-it-timesup-for-metoo/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-01-is-it-timesup-for-metoo/</guid>
        <description>It’s fair to say that the #MeToo movement has been the most significant social upheaval of recent times. Triggered by the much-publicised downfall of Harvey Weinstein, the tremendous outpouring of stories of both sexual assault and everyday sexism faced by women on a regular basis became a force too …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is Universal Basic Income the real solution to poverty?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-is-universal-basic-income-the-real-solution-to-poverty/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-is-universal-basic-income-the-real-solution-to-poverty/</guid>
        <description>Before I begin I should clarify some terms. The Finland experiment cannot truly be called an experiment in Universal Base Income. UBI is the idea that the government should give each of its citizens a ‘basic’ form of income. It has been picked up by both the left and the right with both the Green …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The long road to recovery</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-the-long-road-to-recovery/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-the-long-road-to-recovery/</guid>
        <description>This isn’t what I expected recovery to look like. For over ten years, I’ve battled with an eating disorder, and I’m starting to realise that recovery might not have an end to it. For now, it seems like it’s a dynamic process, with an equilibrium that shifts left or right depending on the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What to do with a man like Neeson?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-what-to-do-with-a-man-like-neeson/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-what-to-do-with-a-man-like-neeson/</guid>
        <description>Liam Neeson, whilst promoting his latest film, described a story of how a friend of his had been raped by a black man and how, following this, he wanted to kill a black man to avenge his friend. This is undeniably racist; he saw black men as indistinguishable and, therefore, killing any black man …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where is the line?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-where-is-the-line/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-where-is-the-line/</guid>
        <description>With only a week’s notice, College has told us they’re shutting the pub menu food service in h-bar. This is the latest in a long line of cuts: they’ve hiked up the fee at Ethos, they came after the SCR breakfast and the pool at St. Mary’s, and they’ve raised the price of food on campus and rent in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union Reform has only just begun – now we need you</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-union-reform-has-only-just-begun-now-we-need-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-union-reform-has-only-just-begun-now-we-need-you/</guid>
        <description>After a hefty debate about my paper, with many a discussion being had about if we need Union reform, when we need Union reform, why we need Union reform, and how we should do Union reform, the paper was passed, with an amendment limiting the scope of reform to democratic engagement; currently done …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Voluntourism: wasting time abroad</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-voluntourism-wasting-time-abroad/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sara Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-voluntourism-wasting-time-abroad/</guid>
        <description>Voluntourism, short for volunteer tourism, is when someone travels abroad and volunteers while on vacation, usually lasting a week or two. The glory days of voluntourism are slowly coming to an end. The reality that it does more harm than good in the long term is slowly dawning on people. Before we …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fashion is not a real thing</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-fashion-is-not-a-real-thing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-fashion-is-not-a-real-thing/</guid>
        <description>I deeply despise fashion. Whether it’s the pretentious designers selling a branded brick for a tonne of money, or the gormless idiots that buy it, everything in the fashion world is designed to piss me off. Apparently, however, it is one of the things many people at Imperial enjoy and have a serious …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why I’m proposing a complete restructure of the Union</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-why-i-m-proposing-a-complete-restructure-of-the-union/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-why-i-m-proposing-a-complete-restructure-of-the-union/</guid>
        <description>How much of a say do we really have in what the Union does? Whether introducing sweeping changes such as a whole new representation network (the Wellbeing Rep Network), implementing programmes like ICXP (Imperial Clubs Experience Project), tampering with election timetables (Leadership Elections …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A case study in Fake News</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-a-case-study-in-fake-news/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theodor Videnberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-a-case-study-in-fake-news/</guid>
        <description>A recent incident that was circulated on social media showed a confrontation between high schoolers, some of whom were wearing MAGA hats, a Native American man, and a group calling themselves Black Hebrew Israelites, in Washington D.C. In a snippet that was circulated later the smiling teenager …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Les Gilets Jaunes: protesters or extremists?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-les-gilets-jaunes-protesters-or-extremists/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xiu Xiuchen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-les-gilets-jaunes-protesters-or-extremists/</guid>
        <description>The yellow vest (gilets jaunes) movement began in November 2018 and was named after the high-vis jackets worn by motorists who started the movement. Although the gilets jaunes started by protesting against rising fuel taxes, the movement has become increasingly extreme with the manifestation of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Yemen: an unseen issue</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-yemen-an-unseen-issue/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stevie Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-yemen-an-unseen-issue/</guid>
        <description>The world has a problem. Absent from the front pages of our newspapers and digital screens is one of the largest humanitarian crises in modern history. Often referred to as “The Forgotten War”, Yemen has been caught in the middle of violent conflict between the Houthi forces – an anti-government …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Female Genital Mutilation: A Hidden Crisis</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-female-genital-mutilation-a-hidden-crisis/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-female-genital-mutilation-a-hidden-crisis/</guid>
        <description>Despite increased legal protections, FGM is still a significant issue that affects thousands of women and young girls in the UK.
What is Female Genital Mutilation(FGM)?
The World Health Organisation (WHO) defines Female Genital Mutilation (FGM) as ‘procedures that involve partial or total removal of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who should vote on what?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-who-should-vote-on-what/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-who-should-vote-on-what/</guid>
        <description>The Brexit vote has been in the zeitgeist for the past month as everything comes to a head. I humbly ask the reader to cast their minds back to that rosy day on the 23rd of June when the nation voted inconclusively for something to do with Europe. Although much attention has been paid to the way the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Meat-free Mondays: are they okay?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-meat-free-mondays-are-they-okay/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-meat-free-mondays-are-they-okay/</guid>
        <description>What possible change on campus this new year could spur so many people to respond with anger? What possible subject, requiring no effort on most anyone’s part could cause hordes to descend upon Imperial’s most popular social media platform at Imperial College Exposed to express their outrage? Of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The last domino to fall</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-the-last-domino-to-fall/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aida Manzano-Kharman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-the-last-domino-to-fall/</guid>
        <description>Amongst the seemingly ever rising far right movement in Europe, despite all the tumultuous events that have been occurring in Spain recently, the rise of an extreme right party was not something that Spanish and European citizens predicted as happening anytime soon. And yet nonetheless, Vox was the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Positive Peace</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-positive-peace/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fatima Ali,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-positive-peace/</guid>
        <description>Peace is something you give, not something you ask others to give you.” This is a particularly poignant quote shared by Hyppolite Ntigurirwa when describing the harrowing experiences of growing up in the middle of the Rwandan genocide. During the United Nations Peace Summit of Emerging Leaders 2018, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>And then what?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-and-then-what/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-and-then-what/</guid>
        <description>At some point, this Brexit nonsense must end. Reason, though seemingly in short supply nowadays, demands it. Any transition period will come to an end. Any backstop will be withdrawn from and a new norm for the country will arrive, however uneasily. The question is whether this new norm will arrive …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is mass immigration compatible with the idea of nationhood that nationalism requires?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-is-mass-immigration-compatible-with-the-idea-of-nationhood-that-nationalism-requires/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Auguste Rodin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-is-mass-immigration-compatible-with-the-idea-of-nationhood-that-nationalism-requires/</guid>
        <description>Perhaps to begin answering this question we should start by defining what really is nationalism. As with many other abstract concepts, what tends to happen is that different communities chose to define the concept in a way that suits their agenda, but in the simplest way of putting it, nationalism …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The grief of Brexit is nearly over</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-the-grief-of-brexit-is-nearly-over/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-the-grief-of-brexit-is-nearly-over/</guid>
        <description>There are five stages of grief: denial, anger, bargaining, depression and acceptance. We as a country have finally gotten near the end of our Brexit grief. First there was the denial that we as a country would ever vote for such a preposterous idea. Then there was anger as it became apparent our …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Remembering the Boxing Day Tsunami</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-remembering-the-boxing-day-tsunami/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laz Ranasinghe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-remembering-the-boxing-day-tsunami/</guid>
        <description>December has always been a time of deep reflection for me. As the lights erupt and the Christmas spirit envelops the nation, it truly is a special time of the year. However, it makes me value the importance of family and the sanctity of life for a very different reason.
On Boxing Day 2004, the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The End of the Union as We Know It</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-the-end-of-the-union-as-we-know-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lochlann Allison,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-the-end-of-the-union-as-we-know-it/</guid>
        <description>After a long day of uni, I return home to retire for the evening. I slump on my sofa and flick on the tv to a comedy channel for my daily intake of shits and giggles. The comedy channel I refer to is, obviously, BBC News. For the last two weeks, I have watched the comedy sketch, that is Her …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>US news is moving like constipated bowels</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-us-news-is-moving-like-constipated-bowels/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gritty,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-us-news-is-moving-like-constipated-bowels/</guid>
        <description>Hey folks, welcome back to another instalment of your favourite politics comment column. Remember that Felix can be your voice if you email us by Monday; having more lefty voices would be pretty swanky. This column is gonna be short; Charlie’s stealing my page. Sorry for the terseness.
RIP to a real …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Homelessness: a harsh reality</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-homelessness-a-harsh-reality/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ambreen Muhammed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-homelessness-a-harsh-reality/</guid>
        <description>The wind scratches your face, your mouth as dry as parchment, the bitter cold tormenting your every thought. Your bones moan in pain as you search frantically for shelter.under a tree, behind a dustbin, in a cardboard box, anything that will get you through the night. This is just a simplified …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Legitimate violence?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-legitimate-violence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-legitimate-violence/</guid>
        <description>Violence, or the threat of violence has been one of the governing factors of human interaction for as long as humans have been in existence, from the earliest social groups right through to the foundation of the modern state. In the modern day, violence and the threat of violence are the fundamental …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grumpy Bastard on Imperial Ethics</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-grumpy-bastard-on-imperial-ethics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-grumpy-bastard-on-imperial-ethics/</guid>
        <description>This week I’ve been unfortunate enough to be in the middle of Remembrance Day. In between the white and red poppy virtue signalling as hard as they possibly can. People are too busy trying to work out which wars are the right ones to remember and which ones should be ignored as immoral foreign …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is the haze craze kushing a tad too far?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-is-the-haze-craze-kushing-a-tad-too-far/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-is-the-haze-craze-kushing-a-tad-too-far/</guid>
        <description>Marijuana users all over rejoiced earlier this month when Canada became the first big Western democracy to legalize free use of cannabis. Canadians actually rejoiced so much that the country is now facing a weed shortage. It seems like the world is finally ready to move on from the question of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Paypal CEO replaced by 66,000 Guardian Readers</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-paypal-ceo-replaced-by-66-000-guardian-readers/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrew Melville,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-paypal-ceo-replaced-by-66-000-guardian-readers/</guid>
        <description>We work hard to achieve the right balance and to ensure that our decisions are values-driven and not political.” That was the press release churned out by Paypal’s PR team last Thursday, when they announced their decision to remove founder and former EDL leader Tommy Robinson’s (real name Stephen …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Christian Union on ACC</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-the-christian-union-on-acc/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Franz Tapia Chaca,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-the-christian-union-on-acc/</guid>
        <description>Are these biscuits free? May I take some?” – Imperial student at Halloween ACC.
“Yes and yes. They’re not there for you to just look at them!” – Imperial Christian Union.
“Jesus Christ!” – Imperial student.
Did you go to the Halloween ACC bar night on October 31st? If so, you may have seen a bright …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An ‘exploding’ political atmosphere</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-an-exploding-political-atmosphere/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-an-exploding-political-atmosphere/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday 24th October, news broke of suspicious packages containing explosives mailed to former President Barack Obama and former Secretary of State Hillary Clinton. Similar packages were quickly discovered, addressed to:
George Soros: billionaire investor and Democratic mega-donor
John Brennan: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>European museum of the year resting on its laurels</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-european-museum-of-the-year-resting-on-its-laurels/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-european-museum-of-the-year-resting-on-its-laurels/</guid>
        <description>In May of this year, the design museum, that resides a mere 15-minute walk away from our South Kensington campus, won the award for European museum of the year. Sat between a Byron burgers and the peacocks of Holland park, it became the 7th British museum to do so in the 41 years that the prize has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pittsburgh, a victimless crime?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-pittsburgh-a-victimless-crime/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Daniel Solomons,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-pittsburgh-a-victimless-crime/</guid>
        <description>The 27th of October 2018, will be a date tattooed on the hearts of every Jewish person around the world. 11 members of the Tree of Life synagogue, located in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, had their Saturday prayers cut tragically short. The details of the crime are gruesome, as with many mass shootings, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>White is the new red when it comes to poppies!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-white-is-the-new-red-when-it-comes-to-poppies/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-white-is-the-new-red-when-it-comes-to-poppies/</guid>
        <description>This year marks 100 years since the Armistice that ended the horrors of World War I. The war was big and affected many, and shortly after, people began using red poppies as symbols of remembrance. It was a way of honouring the men lost as well as reinforcing the idea that war could never happen …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The State of the Union</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-the-state-of-the-union/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-the-state-of-the-union/</guid>
        <description>A few weeks ago, I wrote a News article about a concerning image that emerged showing Jarlath O’Hara, the Managing Director of Imperial College London, pictured beside a man dressed in blackface. I was first made aware of the image on 27th September If I’m honest, my initial reaction to the picture …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is feminism still relevant?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-is-feminism-still-relevant/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-is-feminism-still-relevant/</guid>
        <description>At this point, you’re probably tired of hearing, seeing, listening to and arguing about feminism. I’m not too big of a fan of the word either so please don’t go ballistic just yet. Read on, try to keep an open mind, which I know is crazy hard, but how ’bout we try for just one sec?
Things are better …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s time for students at Imperial to have real opinions</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-it-s-time-for-students-at-imperial-to-have-real-opinions/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrew Melville,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-it-s-time-for-students-at-imperial-to-have-real-opinions/</guid>
        <description>Last week, Loughborough University announced they would be launching an investigation into two of its students, resulting in the immediate suspension of one. This was the University’s response to what it referred to as a “racist and misogynistic” post on the “Loughborough Towersposting” Facebook …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Revelling in the chaos of American politics</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-revelling-in-the-chaos-of-american-politics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-revelling-in-the-chaos-of-american-politics/</guid>
        <description>The midterms are nearly upon us, and this is no fun for anybody. And before you get excited about a possible radical change in the US federal government, take a dose of reality, bud. Shit slides slowly. But, with luck, shit will slide the right way.
Quick refresher for those of you not knowledgeable …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Should the Monarchy be Abolished?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-should-the-monarchy-be-abolished/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-should-the-monarchy-be-abolished/</guid>
        <description>What do Ellie Goulding, Ricky Martin and the Queen have in common? Other than the fact that they all used to be much more relevant 3 years, 20 years and 800 years ago respectively, they also all took part in the royal wedding celebrations over the weekend. Very much overshadowed by the spectacle of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Trust your Trustees?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-trust-your-trustees/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-trust-your-trustees/</guid>
        <description>One month, and one more record-breaking election, has already passed here at Imperial. Last week, new student reps were elected in every department, and though turnout figures are certainly worth celebrating, today I want to talk about what comes next.
Every day decisions are made in our name that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grumpy Bastard on the Royals</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-grumpy-bastard-on-the-royals/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-grumpy-bastard-on-the-royals/</guid>
        <description>Someone once told me that bad news come in threes. That person, like all people, was almost definitely wrong: there is no limit on the number of bad things that can happen at once. As an example, this week featured an announcement that the Brexit negotiations will be extended, that a Saudi …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kavanaugh: The aggressor or the victim?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-kavanaugh-the-aggressor-or-the-victim/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,Theodor Videnberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-kavanaugh-the-aggressor-or-the-victim/</guid>
        <description>The legal system works under the principle that one is innocent until proven guilty,
Three weeks ago Henry Eshbaugh wrote an article titled “Stuck in my Kava-craw” about US supreme court nominee Brett Kavanaugh. In the rather polemical piece he called Kavanaugh “non-human”, “a nympho who raped …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brexit just isn’t worth it.</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-15-brexit-just-isn-t-worth-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saym Hussein,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-15-brexit-just-isn-t-worth-it/</guid>
        <description>I am still angry. After over 2 years of politics surrounding Brexit, nothing good at all has happened. Our country is fractured, major issues with domestic policy haven’t been dealt with, and our government is a puppet of the far-right. It is about time that we come to terms with the fact that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>From dear Reader to dear Leader</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-15-from-dear-reader-to-dear-leader/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Gramsci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-15-from-dear-reader-to-dear-leader/</guid>
        <description>Salutations, fellow travellers! Bad news for regular followers of Grumpy Bastard’s column: they’ve had to take the week off to recover from a ruptured spleen, suffered supposedly due to the cumulative traumas of Freshers’ Week, the uncommonly pleasant weather, and the first advent calendars going on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Henry Hart accuses Sport Imperial of fraud</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-15-henry-hart-accuses-sport-imperial-of-fraud/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Hart,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-15-henry-hart-accuses-sport-imperial-of-fraud/</guid>
        <description>Fraud: Wrongful OR criminal deception intended to result in financial or personal gain. At least that’s the definition google gives me. It perfectly describes the situation that Sport Imperial has created with its new scheme to increase Ethos fees to £30 a year. Yes, I could hardly help but hear you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is Kanye West going south?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-15-is-kanye-west-going-south/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-15-is-kanye-west-going-south/</guid>
        <description>Never far from controversy, Kanye West (now wanting to be known as Ye), has hit headlines again, provoking a lot of reaction from the internet following his appearance on the 44th season premiere of Saturday Night Live last week. Ye performed his single “I love it” with Lil Pump, as they danced …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cull this rampant enthusiasm</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-cull-this-rampant-enthusiasm/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-cull-this-rampant-enthusiasm/</guid>
        <description>Welcome back to Imperial, I hope you’ve had a lovely summer and that you’re totally prepared for the year that lies ahead. However well prepared you think you are now, you definitely aren’t. There will come a time at some point this year when you experience that feeling as your brain exits through …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is misogyny a hate crime?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-is-misogyny-a-hate-crime/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dr. Yenushi Hirimuthugoda,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-is-misogyny-a-hate-crime/</guid>
        <description>Why are you getting so emotional? Stop being a drama queen! C’mon now, can’t you take a joke? Calm down! Why are you getting so worked up? That time of the month, eh? When are you getting married? When are you going to have children? Your biological clock is ticking! What do you mean, you don’t want …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Remodelling Conservation</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-remodelling-conservation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elisa Mogollon Perez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-remodelling-conservation/</guid>
        <description>In recent years, conservation has shifted towards increasingly sophisticated international policies that recognize the importance of equity and the rights of indigenous and local people. Despite this, communities within immediate proximity to biodiversity hotspots continue to suffer the most from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The bull climbs the stairs</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-the-bull-climbs-the-stairs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Hart,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-the-bull-climbs-the-stairs/</guid>
        <description>Stock markets rise and rise up until the point the bull jumps out of the window. US stock markets have been more expensive than now only twice in history: Black Tuesday of 1929, and the Dot Com bubble of 2000. Needless to say, both of those bubbles burst in spectacular fashion, and nothing helps to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why we need zoos</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-why-we-need-zoos/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maryna Voloshyna,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-why-we-need-zoos/</guid>
        <description>As more species become increasingly endangered and face steep decline, today’s zoos become the ark, a reservoir of the world’s valuable animals during the world-engulfing climatic warmth. As of 2018 the ZSL London and Whipsnade Zoos are a home to almost 23,000 animals across over 800 species.
Many …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Yemen: The big kids’ playground</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-yemen-the-big-kids-playground/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aida Manzano-Kharman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-yemen-the-big-kids-playground/</guid>
        <description>As of March 2018 the death toll in Yemen has surpassed 40,000 casualties. Save The Children reports that at least 50,000 children have died in 2017 alone, and to this day and counting the amount of displaced refugees is well over 2 million.
The civil war in Yemen has been raging on since 2015, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get Involved!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-get-involved/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-get-involved/</guid>
        <description>I’m sure you’ve heard this enough by now but, welcome! This is a difficult university to get into, and you’ve done tremendously well getting this far.
There are many benefits to studying at Imperial: it’s a rich, prestigious London university with a strong research culture and some of the world’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grumpy Bastard Welcomes you to Imperial</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-grumpy-bastard-welcomes-you-to-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grumpy Bastard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-grumpy-bastard-welcomes-you-to-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to Imperial College London. I hope you understand that when pronounced correctly, those words sound “you’re not smart anymore,” or whatever “you’re not smart anymore” is in the language of your choice. We are, after all a hugely diverse community of individuals from countries all over the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stuck in my Kava-craw</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-stuck-in-my-kava-craw/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-stuck-in-my-kava-craw/</guid>
        <description>Well, here’s a little Kavfefe that’s been dominating the US news cycle recently (anyone remember those kids in concentration camps? They’re still there for the record). Brett Kavanaugh, potential appointee to the Supreme Court of the United States, has had a rough few weeks. The media circus was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We Must Fight Inequality Using the State</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-we-must-fight-inequality-using-the-state/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-we-must-fight-inequality-using-the-state/</guid>
        <description>Governments and the state itself exist due to their ability to marshal large forces of people to achieve a common goal. The modern state was inexorable in its ability to extend its influence around the globe, to the point that where there are humans, there are now states to govern them. The nation …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
