<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ap1310/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ap1310/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The ‘hidden homeless’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-the-hidden-homeless/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 19:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anna Perman,Elizabeth Crouch,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-the-hidden-homeless/</guid>
        <description>A few weeks ago, many people were saddened to hear that Martin Milligan, who many knew as the man who sold the Big Issue in the South Kensington pedestrian tunnel, had passed away.
People flustered by the morning commute who would usually put their head down and stride past a homeless person, would …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Interview with Deputy President (Education) Alex Dahinten
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-interview-with-deputy-president-education-alex-dahinten/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 19:26:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anna Perman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-interview-with-deputy-president-education-alex-dahinten/</guid>
        <description>For other people who are thinking about running, what’s the one thing you wish you’d known before you started?
How many meetings you attend! There have been days, honestly, when I have sat in five or six meetings; I also have three-hour meetings once in a while. Most people come into the position …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The UK’s organ shortage kills 3 people every day...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-the-uks-organ-shortage-kills-3-people-every-day/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 18:41:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anna Perman,Katherine Bettany,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-the-uks-organ-shortage-kills-3-people-every-day/</guid>
        <description>Imagine. Something in your machinery has stopped working. Somewhere in your body, a vital organ, your kidneys, eyes, your heart, has malfunctioned. Your doctor says that the damage is irreversible and that you need a replacement.
For nearly 8,000 people in the UK currently waiting for an organ …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science doesn’t play by its own rules
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-science-doesnt-play-by-its-own-rules/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 21:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anna Perman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-science-doesnt-play-by-its-own-rules/</guid>
        <description>Happy 450th birthday Francis Bacon! In case you didn&amp;rsquo;t know, it ís thanks to him that you are studying here, and that science exists as it does. It was he who said that we should make observations and draw from them the physical laws which govern our planet. He also wrote that as scientific …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Classic Cinema
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-classic-cinema/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 20:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anna Perman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-classic-cinema/</guid>
        <description>Ever felt like your parents don’t understand you? Do they put pressure on you to achieve? Do they spoil you? Beat you? Or worse, ignore you? Everything is their fault. In fact, all adults just don’t understand kids, because ‘when you grow up, your heart dies’. Or so I’ve learnt from watching John …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is Stephen Fry right about women&#39;s sexuality?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-is-stephen-fry-right-about-womens-sexuality/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 21:41:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anna Perman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-is-stephen-fry-right-about-womens-sexuality/</guid>
        <description>Thou shalt not question Stephen Fry? Oh dear, I may as well go watch Hollyoaks and eat a Kit Kat. While we’re at it, the Beatles aren’t just a band – they are a way of life.
Stephen Fry, National Treasure™, has been quoted as saying women are uninterested in sex, except as the price for a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lord Browne points to higher fees
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-lord-browne-points-to-higher-fees/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 19:07:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,Alexander Karapetian,Anna Perman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-lord-browne-points-to-higher-fees/</guid>
        <description>Universities should be unlimited in charging fees to students, the Browne review of university funding has recommended. The influential review, released early this week, outlined various proposals and potential changes in higher education funding to the government, including lifting the current cap …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
