<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Science on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/science/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Science on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/science/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>70 Years of STEM Nobel Prizes &amp; Fields Medals</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-70-years-STEM-nobel-prizes-fields-medals/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Julia Dabrowska,Christine Parry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-70-years-STEM-nobel-prizes-fields-medals/</guid>
        <description>Below are 70 years worth of noteworthy awards in maths and science - but first, in recognition of our affiliated Imperial scientists, here’s a summary of our awardees &amp;amp; what they achieved:
1956: Cyril Norman Hinshelwood; Chemistry; for his research into the mechanism of chemical reactions
1958: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Seven Decades of Discovery</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-seven-decades-of-discovery/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Julia Dabrowska,Christine Parry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-seven-decades-of-discovery/</guid>
        <description>1949
Felix is launched, spawned from the University’s arts and culture magazine, Phoenix, after a need for news amongst the student community.
1950s
After WWII, the scientific community realised the full potential of its possibility and power, and feels an increased need to understand the social …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sir Geoffrey Wilkinson: Imperial’s Honoured Chemist and Recipient of the 1973 Nobel Prize in Chemistry</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-sir-geoffrey-wilkinson-imperials-honoured-chemist-recipient-1973-nobel-chemistry/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Arianne New,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-sir-geoffrey-wilkinson-imperials-honoured-chemist-recipient-1973-nobel-chemistry/</guid>
        <description>Any student who has been to the Chemistry Café would have seen the portrait of Sir Geoffrey Wilkinson at least once. Lying at the back of the café, with more pictures dotted throughout the building, and even his research paper framed right outside, he surely must be of importance. While most of us …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reimagined, Redesigned, and Revamped</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-reimagined-redesigned-revamped/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christine Parry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-reimagined-redesigned-revamped/</guid>
        <description>Earlier this month, the Science Museum unveiled their latest exhibition, ‘Medicine: the Wellcome Collection’, a gallery that, put simply, showcases the history of medicine, taking up 3000 square metres of space, spanning over 500 years of history right up to the present day, and presenting with a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Power of Bugs in Today’s Climate Crisis</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-power-bugs-todays-climate-crisis/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mery Shahin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-power-bugs-todays-climate-crisis/</guid>
        <description>From daily news features to public transport disruptions and political manifestos, climate change and all its consequences have finally become impossible to ignore. As temperatures rise, our relationship with nature will have to begrudgingly adjust. This adjustment will certainly involve the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Snap! Goes the Future…</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-snap-goes-future/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christine Parry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-snap-goes-future/</guid>
        <description>Have you ever played with one of those snap wristbands when you were younger?” Andres Arrieta asks. In the Engineering lab at Purdue University, Dr Arrieta and his team have designed a novel data sensor that uses a similar snap-change; from a curved shape that is under tension, to a flat structure …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Caterpillar, Butterfly, or Insect?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-caterpillar-butterly-insect/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christine Parry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-caterpillar-butterly-insect/</guid>
        <description>Forget that ‘animal, vegetable, mineral’ game you might have played as a kid on long car journeys, plants can do one better – they can tell exactly who is eating them.
It is not news that plants possess the ability to share information about what bird or beast is causing them damage, emitting a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>From the Lab to your Plate – the Science Behind Five Intriguing Foods</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-lab-to-plate-science-behind-five-intriguing-foods/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Julia Dabrowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-lab-to-plate-science-behind-five-intriguing-foods/</guid>
        <description>Most foods are simple - some ingredients grow on trees, bushes or in fields, others are taken from animals, and depending on their nutritional value, undergo some level of processing. But with the modern era comes change, and as science is increasingly being installed in the kitchen (food science is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In Summary: Nobel Prize 2019</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-in-summary-nobel-prize-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanziana Foia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-in-summary-nobel-prize-2019/</guid>
        <description>Physics
This year’s Nobel prize in Physics was awarded half to James Peebles (Princeton University) for work in physical cosmology and the other half jointly to Michel Mayor and Didier Queloz for the discovery of an exoplanet orbiting a solar-type star. Both have played an essential role in our …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Resistance is Futile: Why Antibiotic Overprescribing Remains a National and Global Problem</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-resistance-futile-why-antibiotic-overprescribing-remains-national-global-problem/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eyad Abuelgasim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-resistance-futile-why-antibiotic-overprescribing-remains-national-global-problem/</guid>
        <description>Antimicrobial resistance is a problem that we’ve known about for around 75 years now, with Alexander Fleming referring to it in his Nobel Prize speech way back in 1945. Since then the problem has become recognised internationally. It is estimated that around 700,000 people every year die from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oxygen: the generator of life</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-oxygen-the-generator-of-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-oxygen-the-generator-of-life/</guid>
        <description>When your peaceful summer nap is interrupted by the constant buzzing of a fly, do not think of it as the predetermined behaviour of a bothersome insect, but that of a many-times-removed cousin. Most animal phyla (the major groups under which the animal kingdom is divided, based originally in their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Psychedelics research at Imperial College enters a new phase  </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-psychedelics-research-at-imperial-college-enters-a-new-phase/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joe Sheppard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-psychedelics-research-at-imperial-college-enters-a-new-phase/</guid>
        <description>The second phase to be exact. This year the newly minted Centre for Psychedelic Research at Imperial College London began conducting a first-of-its-kind phase II clinical trial designed to test how effective the hallucinogenic compound psilocybin is at treating patients with major depressive …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The revival of measles</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-the-revival-of-measles/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Madeleine Openshaw,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-the-revival-of-measles/</guid>
        <description>When Max was 18, he woke up one morning feeling very unwell. “I just couldn’t get up,” he said, “I had been out the night before and my boyfriend at the time thought it was just a hangover, but his flatmate came in and said I looked truly awful.” Eventually, Max was taken in a taxi to Whitechapel …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Time to go to sleep</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-time-to-go-to-sleep/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yizhou Yu,Chiao Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-time-to-go-to-sleep/</guid>
        <description>During the day, our consciousness sails on the surface of an unfathomable, electrochemical sea into which it sinks every night when we sleep. How – and why – we lose consciousness, which some may argue is the most important part of the human experience, is still an unsolved mystery. With the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Xenon could be used to reduce traumatic brain damage, Imperial study finds</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-xenon-could-be-used-to-reduce-traumatic-brain-damage-imperial-study-finds/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanziana Foia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-xenon-could-be-used-to-reduce-traumatic-brain-damage-imperial-study-finds/</guid>
        <description>Traumatic Brain Injury (TBI) is the leading cause of death and disability for people aged under 45 in developed countries. The first ever life-long study in mice has found that head injury effects can be halted by xenon gas. Following TBI, xenon prevented the mice from early deaths, improved their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UK tour of Tim Peake’s Spacecraft attracts 1.3 million visitors</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-uk-tour-of-tim-peake-s-spacecraft-attracts-1-3-million-visitors/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanziana Foia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-uk-tour-of-tim-peake-s-spacecraft-attracts-1-3-million-visitors/</guid>
        <description>The Soyuz TMA-19M spacecraft carried Russian commander Yuri Malenchenko and US and UK flight engineers Tim Kopra and Tim Peake to the International Space Station (ISS) on 15 December 2015, and returned the same crew to Earth on 18 June 2016 (expeditions 46 and 47 to the ISS).
Soyuz TMA-19M is the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mycoprotein: a potential beneficial food for people with type 2 diabetes?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-mycoprotein-a-potential-beneficial-food-for-people-with-type-2-diabetes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anna Cherta-Murillo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-mycoprotein-a-potential-beneficial-food-for-people-with-type-2-diabetes/</guid>
        <description>If I were to ask you the first thing that comes to mind when you think of fungi, you would probably say mouldy walls, gone-off food, or athlete’s foot. The Fungi kingdom is often not viewed in a positive light. However, we owe a lot to fungi; they produce life-saving antibiotics, have allowed organ …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Air pollution in London: where are we now?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-air-pollution-in-london-where-are-we-now/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-air-pollution-in-london-where-are-we-now/</guid>
        <description>It is not an exaggeration to say that pollution is one of London’s biggest challenges for the foreseeable future. While it is true that the situation is not as concerning as 70 years ago, when the pea soup-like Great Smog killed 4000 people in less than a week, the current pollution cloud that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Seeing the light: Acting against actinic keratosis</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-seeing-the-light-acting-against-actinic-keratosis/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maya Kaushik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-seeing-the-light-acting-against-actinic-keratosis/</guid>
        <description>Easter weekend this year saw most of us out enjoying the sunshine, after digging through our cupboards to bring out our sunhats, sundresses, sunglasses and sun cream. While the first hot days of the year are always greatly appreciated, sun exposure can lead to several problems, both in the UK and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dinosaurs were thriving before asteroid strike that wiped them out</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-dinosaurs-were-thriving-before-asteroid-strike-that-wiped-them-out/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-dinosaurs-were-thriving-before-asteroid-strike-that-wiped-them-out/</guid>
        <description>A new analysis has posited that dinosaurs were unaffected by long-term climate changes and flourished before their sudden demise by asteroid strike.
Scientists largely agree that an asteroid impact, possibly coupled with intense volcanic activity, wiped out the dinosaurs at the end of the Cretaceous …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Explaining the Future book launched at UCL</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-explaining-the-future-book-launched-at-ucl/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rosie Dutt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-explaining-the-future-book-launched-at-ucl/</guid>
        <description>On Monday March 4th, Dr. Sunny Bains from the Department of Biochemical Engineering launched her new book Explaining the Future: How to Research, Analyze and Report on Emerging Technologies, published by Oxford University Press. The book – written for engineers, physical scientists, consultants, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New cholesterol-lowering drug could help patients unable to take statins</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-new-cholesterol-lowering-drug-could-help-patients-unable-to-take-statins/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-new-cholesterol-lowering-drug-could-help-patients-unable-to-take-statins/</guid>
        <description>A new class of oral cholesterol-lowering drug could help patients unable to take statins due to side effects.
The findings come from the largest study to date to test the effectiveness and safety of bempedoic acid, an oral medication - yet to be approved in Europe - which inhibits the body’s ability …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New hepatitis C cases down by almost 70% in HIV positive men in London</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-new-hepatitis-c-cases-down-by-almost-70-in-hiv-positive-men-in-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-new-hepatitis-c-cases-down-by-almost-70-in-hiv-positive-men-in-london/</guid>
        <description>New cases of hepatitis C amongst HIV positive men in London have fallen by nearly 70 per cent in recent years. The new analysis of data from three clinics in London found 256 men were diagnosed between 2013-2018. New infections peaked at 17 for every 1000 people studied in 2015 and fell to six by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>From single cells to multicellular organisms: witnessing  evolution</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-from-single-cells-to-multicellular-organisms-witnessing-evolution/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-from-single-cells-to-multicellular-organisms-witnessing-evolution/</guid>
        <description>Researchers from the George Institute of Technology and University of Montana have witnessed in real-time the development of single-cell algae into more complex multicellular organisms – and, astonishingly, the process took only 50 weeks, or just 750 generations. The only driving environmental …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Infectious diseases could be diagnosed with  smartphones in sub-Saharan Africa</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-infectious-diseases-could-be-diagnosed-with-smartphones-in-sub-saharan-africa/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-infectious-diseases-could-be-diagnosed-with-smartphones-in-sub-saharan-africa/</guid>
        <description>A new Imperial-led review has outlined how health workers could use existing phones to predict and curb the spread of infectious diseases.
The review was published in Nature, and involved researchers from Imperial, the Karolinska Institute, UCL, The University of KwaZulu-Natal, the Africa Health …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can machine learning predict ovarian cancer survival?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-can-machine-learning-predict-ovarian-cancer-survival/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-can-machine-learning-predict-ovarian-cancer-survival/</guid>
        <description>Researchers at Imperial College London and the University of Melbourne have created new machine learning software that can forecast the survival rates and response to treatments of patients with ovarian cancer.
The software has been able to predict the prognosis of patients with ovarian cancer …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lack of sleep is not necessarily fatal for flies</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-lack-of-sleep-is-not-necessarily-fatal-for-flies/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-lack-of-sleep-is-not-necessarily-fatal-for-flies/</guid>
        <description>Male flies kept awake do not die earlier than those allowed to sleep, leading researchers to question whether sleep is essential for staying alive. Whilst this study was in flies, the team speculate that if sleep is not essential for life in the same way food is, then it is possible that their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The return of British rockets</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-the-return-of-british-rockets/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Will Harradence,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-the-return-of-british-rockets/</guid>
        <description>In a dark and spacious room, with upbeat music accompanying a blue-lit bar, a crowd was gathering to await the latest product reveal from a hot British start-up. As the CEO took the stage, they were ushered to their seats, and a mass of cameras turned to face him. After an enthusiastic speech, he …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What next for Science in a No-Deal Brexit</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-what-next-for-science-in-a-no-deal-brexit/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eyad Abuelgasim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-what-next-for-science-in-a-no-deal-brexit/</guid>
        <description>On 14th June 2016, just over a week before the EU referendum, an open letter, signed by thirteen Vote Leave ministers, was published to calm the fears of British scientists, farmers and others who relied on European funds. It pledged: “If the public votes to leave on 23rd June, we will continue to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Facing the facts: Botulinum toxin in aesthetic medicine</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-facing-the-facts-botulinum-toxin-in-aesthetic-medicine/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maya Kaushik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-facing-the-facts-botulinum-toxin-in-aesthetic-medicine/</guid>
        <description>Pick up a glossy magazine to check out the latest gossip around your favourite Hollywood A-list celebrity, and you may notice that many of them have seemingly flawless faces, lacking the frown lines and crow’s feet that you might expect to see in someone of their age. Sometimes this is down to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mother’s smoking during pregnancy changes baby’s DNA</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-mother-s-smoking-during-pregnancy-changes-baby-s-dna/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eyad Abuelgasim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-mother-s-smoking-during-pregnancy-changes-baby-s-dna/</guid>
        <description>Smoking in pregnancy damages an unborn baby’s DNA – increasing its risk of smoking-related conditions in adulthood and a premature death, new research has found.
The study serves as a caution for mother smokers, more than half of whom continue during pregnancy, say scientists.
Mother’s smoking …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Getting under the skin: a new hope for cancer treatment</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-getting-under-the-skin-a-new-hope-for-cancer-treatment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maya Kaushik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-getting-under-the-skin-a-new-hope-for-cancer-treatment/</guid>
        <description>Cutaneous T-cell lymphoma (CTCL) is a rare cancer of the skin, which occurs when T cells, a type of white blood cell in the lymphatic system, grow out of control within the skin. This is often initially mistaken for other skin conditions like psoriasis, dermatitis or eczema, as it presents as red, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Poorest dying nearly ten years younger than the rich in “deeply worrying” trend for UK health</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-poorest-dying-nearly-ten-years-younger-than-the-rich-in-deeply-worrying-trend-for-uk-health/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-poorest-dying-nearly-ten-years-younger-than-the-rich-in-deeply-worrying-trend-for-uk-health/</guid>
        <description>The gap between the life expectancy of the richest and poorest sectors of society in England is increasing, according to new research from Imperial College London.
The study, which was published in the journal Lancet Public Health and funded by the Wellcome Trust, analysed Office for National …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Coffee? It’s in your genes!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-coffee-it-s-in-your-genes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paula Rowińska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-coffee-it-s-in-your-genes/</guid>
        <description>Bitter equals poisonous - at least according to our brain. There seems to exist only one exception from this evolutionary dislike for bitterness: coffee. Why many of us cannot even imagine a morning without a cup of espresso or latte, although its bitter taste should make our body issue a poison …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Cultural Brain Hypothesis</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-the-cultural-brain-hypothesis/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Photini Knoyle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-the-cultural-brain-hypothesis/</guid>
        <description>Generally speaking, larger brains* are more capable of storing and processing information and therefore achieve higher intelligence. Although this is a little simplistic (and does not factor in the degree of neuronal connectivity - where “smarter” brains are also more intra-connected), human brains …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Detective Inspector Dog – Mission: Malaria</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-detective-inspector-dog-mission-malaria/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Photini Knoyle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-detective-inspector-dog-mission-malaria/</guid>
        <description>Dogs are often considered to be man’s best friend. This relationship has persisted for millennia, with our canine pals taking roles such as bomb detection agents, sheep herders, nannies and of course, companions. The role of dogs in global health includes the early detection of many human diseases, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fear is in the Air</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-fear-is-in-the-air/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paula Rowińska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-fear-is-in-the-air/</guid>
        <description>How old should one be to watch Harry Potter? What about The Hunger Games? Or Transformers? So far, age ratings for movies depended on subjective opinions.
However, researchers at the Max Planck Institute for Chemistry in Mainz suggested that we could base the age classification on the isoprene …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bombs dropped during WWII had effects even at the “edge of space”</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-bombs-dropped-during-wwii-had-effects-even-at-the-edge-of-space/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie Jones,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-bombs-dropped-during-wwii-had-effects-even-at-the-edge-of-space/</guid>
        <description>World War II is widely known to be the most devastating and deadly war in the history of mankind. However, the study of its impacts beyond Earth is very recent and could play a major role in improving modern technologies. In a study published last month, professor of astrophysics Chris Scott and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Store Glacier: storing water?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-store-glacier-storing-water/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Photini Knoyle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-store-glacier-storing-water/</guid>
        <description>By now, many of us are aware of the 5th Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC) report, which has attracted a storm of media attention since its publication last month. The report considers the environmental consequences of many possible climatic scenarios. These consequences include global …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Trolley Problem: What Would You Choose?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-the-trolley-problem-what-would-you-choose/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paula Rowińska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-the-trolley-problem-what-would-you-choose/</guid>
        <description>Researchers from the MIT Media Lab’s Scalable Cooperation group have surveyed over 2 million citizens from over 200 countries about morally difficult decisions that autonomous vehicles might have to make. Participants played ‘Moral Machine’, an online game designed by the researchers. In a series of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pick and Choose</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-pick-and-choose/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paula Rowińska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-pick-and-choose/</guid>
        <description>Neuroscientists from Johns Hopkins University studied how our brains help us make spontaneous food choices at buffets, in restaurants or in front of our own fridge. The research on rats helped them identify a brain region that could be responsible for our food decisions, according to the paper in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Birth of words</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-birth-of-words/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paula Rowińska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-birth-of-words/</guid>
        <description>A team of linguists and geographers from the Centre for Corpus Research at the University of Birmingham traced the geographical roots of emerging words in American English. Among 8.9 billion words used in 980 million Tweets posted in the US they identified 54 new words, which were rare in October …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dark cores (not a new Ben and Jerry’s™ flavour)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-dark-cores-not-a-new-ben-and-jerry-s-flavour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Photini Knoyle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-dark-cores-not-a-new-ben-and-jerry-s-flavour/</guid>
        <description>In day to day life we all encounter people who consistently exhibit morally questionable behaviour. Psychologists describe these individuals as possessing one or more “dark” traits. Previous studies have shown that these traits relate to one another - but do they share a common denominator … a “dark …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can’t Stop, Won’t Stop: Science on why we can’t stop eating</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-can-t-stop-won-t-stop-science-on-why-we-can-t-stop-eating/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-can-t-stop-won-t-stop-science-on-why-we-can-t-stop-eating/</guid>
        <description>I lied to myself again: “I will just have one more,” as I engulfed the whole bag of crisps. Interestingly, this gluttonous behaviour can be explained by science, so we are not to be blamed entirely.
In the brain, there are two main types of neurones that impact our appetite in the hypothalamus: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICESat-2, NASA’s new satellite to measure the melting of ice</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-icesat-2-nasa-s-new-satellite-to-measure-the-melting-of-ice/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie Jones,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-icesat-2-nasa-s-new-satellite-to-measure-the-melting-of-ice/</guid>
        <description>On Saturday the 15th of September, NASA launched their newest laser, the ICESat-2, which stands for “Ice, Cloud and land Elevation Satellite”. In orbit 500 km above our heads, the satellite’s main mission is to measure the alarming evolution of ice melting in the poles.
Since 2009 and the end of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Moths at Midnight</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-moths-at-midnight/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Photini Knoyle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-moths-at-midnight/</guid>
        <description>We all know that pollination is an invaluable process, critical for both the maintenance of ecosystems and continued agricultural production. With growing pressure on agriculture to sustain the inflating human population, the role of pollinators is becoming increasingly important. In spite of global …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nobel Season: A Summary of the Prizes for 2018</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-nobel-season-a-summary-of-the-prizes-for-2018/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Rowlands,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-nobel-season-a-summary-of-the-prizes-for-2018/</guid>
        <description>Last week was Nobel Prize season, and whilst it’s not quite as glamorous as the Oscars, it comes with a lot of prestige and a chance to go down in history. These yearly prizes are awarded to those who make significant contributions in several categories outlined in the will of Alfred Nobel, with the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2018 Nobel Prize in Medicine: the fight against cancer</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-2018-nobel-prize-in-medicine-the-fight-against-cancer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paula Rowińska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-2018-nobel-prize-in-medicine-the-fight-against-cancer/</guid>
        <description>The 2018 Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine went to James P. Allison and Tasuku Honjo for the “discovery of cancer therapy by inhibition of negative immune regulation.”
Be it bacteria, virus or cancer cell, no foreign molecule can expect a warm welcome to our body. T-cells, a type of white blood …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bacteria in poop: the key to losing weight?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-bacteria-in-poop-the-key-to-losing-weight/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-bacteria-in-poop-the-key-to-losing-weight/</guid>
        <description>Summer is officially over and, temporarily, we don’t need our summer bodies. However, losing weight is not just about looking nice on sandy beaches; obesity is one of the key risk factors that causes cardiovascular disease and other chronic diseases.
Obesity is a multi-facet condition: genetics, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Prime time</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-prime-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paula Rowińska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-prime-time/</guid>
        <description>Had you recently visited the maths department, you would have felt like during the World Cup: students and researchers engaged in heated discussions while watching a 45-minute-long video. Only instead of a football game, we followed a lecture broadcast from Heidelberg in Germany.
On Monday 24th …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Zombie cells</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-zombie-cells/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Rowlands,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-zombie-cells/</guid>
        <description>The zombies are here, except turns out it’s on a cellular scale, so stop boarding up your windows and pick up that microscope! In new research from Dr Baker at the Mayo Clinic, scientists found that removing senescent cells, also known as ‘zombie’ cells, reduced symptoms associated with age related …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Does reciting the Ten Commandments reduce cheating behaviour?  </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-does-reciting-the-ten-commandments-reduce-cheating-behaviour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-does-reciting-the-ten-commandments-reduce-cheating-behaviour/</guid>
        <description>Farewell summer, and welcome to a new academic year! On the bright side, Halloween and Christmas are upon us, and you get to catch up with all your friends. On the downside, however, is the university-associated stress: coursework, presentations and examinations. Even for the post-graduates amongst …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Take a deep breath: Biologics are set to change the global treatment of severe asthma</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-take-a-deep-breath-biologics-are-set-to-change-the-global-treatment-of-severe-asthma/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maya Kaushik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-take-a-deep-breath-biologics-are-set-to-change-the-global-treatment-of-severe-asthma/</guid>
        <description>Imagine being a young woman, who is told that the drug you are prescribed by your doctor is going to cause you to gain weight, and have uncontrollable mood swings. Or perhaps, a young man who is aware that your medication may cause cataracts in your eyes, changes to the shape of your face, or your …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We were born to be lazy</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-we-were-born-to-be-lazy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paula Rowińska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-we-were-born-to-be-lazy/</guid>
        <description>Researchers from the Brain Behaviour Laboratory designed an experiment to understand why the couch attracts us so much more than a good workout. The group led by Matthieu Boisgontier discovered that the human brain might innately prefer the lack of physical activity.
The human kind would not have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cancer and the immune system – friend or foe?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-cancer-and-the-immune-system-friend-or-foe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Roser Gonzalez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-cancer-and-the-immune-system-friend-or-foe/</guid>
        <description>Why is cancer so difficult to beat, you might be wondering. The main problem with cancer is that it arises from our own cells. We are all unique and special, but so are our tumors, which makes it difficult to deal with them at a population level. Unfortunately, the same drug might not have the same …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with Conservation: how we can all help</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-connect-with-conservation-how-we-can-all-help/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-connect-with-conservation-how-we-can-all-help/</guid>
        <description>Over the past few months, I have been updating you all with a number of conservation stories, both optimistic, and less so. Now, to wrap things up, I thought it would be a good idea to give you all a few ideas on how you can make a few small changes to your daily routine to help save the planet. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Could platypus milk help beat antibiotic resistance?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-could-platypus-milk-help-beat-antibiotic-resistance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie Jones,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-could-platypus-milk-help-beat-antibiotic-resistance/</guid>
        <description>In 2014, the World Health Organisation warned the international community of the threat of antibiotic resistance. Due to an excessive use of antibiotics – mostly fed to food-producing animals – bacteria are able to develop resistance, which they then transmit to the next generation of bugs, who can …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Drop in cancer risk five years after quitting smoking</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-drop-in-cancer-risk-five-years-after-quitting-smoking/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Diego F. Nájera,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-drop-in-cancer-risk-five-years-after-quitting-smoking/</guid>
        <description>A new analysis of the Framingham Heart Study, conducted by a team of researchers led by Hilary Tindle MD, MPH at the Vanderbilt University Medical Centre, has revealed encouraging findings for both current and former smokers.
Findings from the Study – which is supported by the National Heart, Lung, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First new stereoisomer type in 50 years, claim chemists</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-first-new-stereoisomer-type-in-50-years-claim-chemists/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-first-new-stereoisomer-type-in-50-years-claim-chemists/</guid>
        <description>Chemists at both Shanghai University and the University of Sydney have announced the discovery of the first new kind of molecular stereoisomer in half a century. For those who have never heard of this term, stereoisomers are molecules that share the same molecular formula (i.e. contain the same …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial CDT Science festival: Science and Ethics</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-imperial-cdt-science-festival-science-and-ethics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riccardo Moriconi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-imperial-cdt-science-festival-science-and-ethics/</guid>
        <description>The synergy between Science and Ethics is pervasive in our society. Scientific advances and technological developments are shaping the future of our life, and society as a whole. Imperial will be holding their annual CDT Science Festival, which this year aims to explore and understand how scientific …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The dawning of the age of synthetic biology</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-the-dawning-of-the-age-of-synthetic-biology/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Varshit Dusad,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-the-dawning-of-the-age-of-synthetic-biology/</guid>
        <description>Would you like to have a vegan hamburger? Are you concerned with the deteriorating environment? Are you a biology geek eager to explain why biology is cool? The answer to such wide-ranging questions is synthetic biology.
What is synthetic biology? Formally, it is the interdisciplinary science of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Want to eat more healthily? Try putting on some ambient music</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-want-to-eat-more-healthily-try-putting-on-some-ambient-music/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-want-to-eat-more-healthily-try-putting-on-some-ambient-music/</guid>
        <description>When choosing our food, our conscious self is never in full control – I always let my cravings get the best of me. For instance, when I am sad I eat ice-cream; when I smell a pizza, I will instantly want to eat one. But have you ever considered how our hearing can impact on food choices?
In London, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why we struggle to live up to our ideals</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-why-we-struggle-to-live-up-to-our-ideals/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maria Balaet,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-why-we-struggle-to-live-up-to-our-ideals/</guid>
        <description>A recent study from Dr. Shai Davidai and Professor Thomas Gilovich at Cornell University shows our prominent regrets arise from ‘the ideal road not taken’ – our inability to fulfil our ideal-self aspirations. Additionally, results from six studies indicate 76% of people report not meeting their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bringing in a new era of healthcare data</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-bringing-in-a-new-era-of-healthcare-data/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Varshit Dusad,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-bringing-in-a-new-era-of-healthcare-data/</guid>
        <description>GDPR is in full effect, and technology companies are sweating to work out the appropriate strategy to comply with new regulations governing digital data. However, amidst this data frenzy around our web footprint, a new conversation around a different kind of data is taking place: healthcare data! …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Charles Dickens – was he the original science communicator?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-charles-dickens-was-he-the-original-science-communicator/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rosie Dutt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-charles-dickens-was-he-the-original-science-communicator/</guid>
        <description>When you hear of Charles Dickens, you most likely instantly think of classic works of literature, such as A Christmas Carol, Oliver Twist, or Great Expectations. However, seldom does one hear he was a man of science – let alone an early science communicator! Indeed, George Henry Lewes, a prominent …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with Conservation: cat-astrophe</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-connect-with-conservation-cat-astrophe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-connect-with-conservation-cat-astrophe/</guid>
        <description>One of the more surprising invasive species, now found across the world thanks to mankind, is the domestic cat! Whether these moggies are pets left to roam free, or have established themselves as feral population, both cause unimaginable damage to various species around the globe. Domestic cats have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Exam stress? Time to cure your fear of spiders</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-exam-stress-time-to-cure-your-fear-of-spiders/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Rowlands,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-exam-stress-time-to-cure-your-fear-of-spiders/</guid>
        <description>Is the end of term getting you all stressed out? The latest research suggests now may also be the perfect time to tackle that fear of spiders…yes, you heard right – spiders! A new study from Professor Oliver Wolf at Ruhr-University Bochum has shown stress can increase extinction learning, which …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Puppy science: Why they are so cute? </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-puppy-science-why-they-are-so-cute/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-puppy-science-why-they-are-so-cute/</guid>
        <description>I don’t know about all of you reading this, but I am crazy about puppies! However, have you ever wondered why they look so incredibly adorable, especially at a young age?
According to a recent collaborative study between the US and the Netherlands, puppies have evolved to be cute because their life …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with Conservation: insect apocalypse</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-connect-with-conservation-insect-apocalypse/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-connect-with-conservation-insect-apocalypse/</guid>
        <description>Remember back to the days of your childhood when you would go on long drives to see family, or to visit the coast on a warm bank holiday. Like me, you may have been observant enough to recognise that car windscreens are devilishly good at catching insects. Fortunately, this was picked up by the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mercury spacecraft BepiColombo makes its landing at the Science Museum</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-mercury-spacecraft-bepicolombo-makes-its-landing-at-the-science-museum/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rosie Dutt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-mercury-spacecraft-bepicolombo-makes-its-landing-at-the-science-museum/</guid>
        <description>The unknown. It is a concept almost every individual fears in one form or another; one that many question, but few have the ability to really explore. On May 16th, the Science Museum had the privilege of unveiling a full-size structural thermal model of BepiColombo, the first European spacecraft to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stressed Mother, Stressed Child?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-stressed-mother-stressed-child/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-stressed-mother-stressed-child/</guid>
        <description>Before any of us were born, the only way we could get information from outside was via the senses of our mother. In terms of evolution, it would be greatly beneficial if we could respond to the external stimulation our mother’s sensed, since it would increase our chances of survival. This process of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with Conservation: Malta bird massacre</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-connect-with-conservation-malta-bird-massacre/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-connect-with-conservation-malta-bird-massacre/</guid>
        <description>If there is one group of birds you have probably noticed declining in the British countryside over the past few years, it is the songbirds. Songbirds are a large group of birds, which, as their name suggests, like to sing, filling the landscapes they inhabit with the beautiful sound of bird songs. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Getting down with the kids</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-getting-down-with-the-kids/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Varshit Dusad,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-getting-down-with-the-kids/</guid>
        <description>Who doesn’t love chocolate? While you and I might enjoy its taste freely, there are 80,000 children each year who are unable to do so. The reason: they suffer from type 1 diabetes, which manifests itself at an early age. Unlike type 2 diabetes, which comes into effect at an old age, due to the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mobile phones make you hyper-social, not anti-social!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-mobile-phones-make-you-hyper-social-not-anti-social/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rosie Dutt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-mobile-phones-make-you-hyper-social-not-anti-social/</guid>
        <description>As we grow older, we begin to adopt a routine. This commences from the earliest of ages – from when we learn to brush our teeth in the morning, to sleeping at a particular time at night. With the advent of modern technology, checking our phones has also become embedded in our everyday lives.
Many …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Solar cells absorb 20% more light with nanoscale coating</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-solar-cells-absorb-20-more-light-with-nanoscale-coating/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lara Bailey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-solar-cells-absorb-20-more-light-with-nanoscale-coating/</guid>
        <description>Researchers at the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) have developed a nanoscale coating for solar cells. These are made of thousands of glass beads of sulphur dioxide, each no larger than one-hundredth of the width of a human hair.
The coating creates an optical ‘whispering …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with Conservation – Information Conservation Technology</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-connect-with-conservation-information-conservation-technology/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-connect-with-conservation-information-conservation-technology/</guid>
        <description>It is becoming increasingly clear that technology is advancing at such a rate that tasks that once took conservationists weeks or months have been cut down to a number of days. This includes the use of equipment such as camera traps, drones, and custom-built prototypes that are project specific. If, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science at the gym: the molecular basis of metabolism</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-science-at-the-gym-the-molecular-basis-of-metabolism/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-science-at-the-gym-the-molecular-basis-of-metabolism/</guid>
        <description>Exercise is good for you, we all know that. You don’t need to read an article on it – or do you? I guess the main question is, do you know how to exercise effectively?
The standard answer about the effects of exercising is that it trains heart muscles to become stronger, enabling it to pump …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Searching for a match: could you be Kaiya’s stem cell donor?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-searching-for-a-match-could-you-be-kaiya-s-stem-cell-donor/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-searching-for-a-match-could-you-be-kaiya-s-stem-cell-donor/</guid>
        <description>When the parents of five-year-old Kaiya took her to the doctors following some bruising, they weren’t expecting to hear anything out of the ordinary. Instead, they returned home with the news that their daughter had leukaemia.
Kaiya, who was diagnosed a little over six weeks ago, is one of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with conservation: Snake Fungal Disease</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-connect-with-conservation-snake-fungal-disease/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-connect-with-conservation-snake-fungal-disease/</guid>
        <description>In recent years, we have seen a spike in the number of fungal diseases infecting wildlife, causing population declines. This includes the chytrid fungus in amphibians and white-nose syndrome in bats. Recently, a new fungus has been discovered in the US, which so far seems to exclusively infect …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>EU moves to ban neonicotinoids</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-eu-moves-to-ban-neonicotinoids/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sam S Welch,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-eu-moves-to-ban-neonicotinoids/</guid>
        <description>On Friday 27th April, member states of the EU moved to support the ban of outdoor agricultural uses of three important neonicotinoid pesticides, due to concerns surrounding their harmful effects on bees and other pollinators. This decision followed the European Food Safety Authority’s (EFSA) …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Happening today –100 years of Feynman</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-happening-today-100-years-of-feynman/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanziana Foia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-happening-today-100-years-of-feynman/</guid>
        <description>Richard Feynman, born on the 11th of May 1918 in New York, is one of the greatest physicists and science communicators of all times. He is best known for his work in the field of quantum electrodynamics and for his ingenious way of representing complex mathematics through simplified diagrams. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Looking after your mental health in exam season</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-looking-after-your-mental-health-in-exam-season/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-looking-after-your-mental-health-in-exam-season/</guid>
        <description>Exam season is perceived as dark and full of danger. It is highly likely that you are feeling anxious, and living off energy drinks in the library – or perhaps you are one of the post-docs that survived exams since you have the time to read this! Nevertheless, this article still concerns you: maybe …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with conservation – the scandal of Sudan</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-connect-with-conservation-the-scandal-of-sudan/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-connect-with-conservation-the-scandal-of-sudan/</guid>
        <description>Some of you may have recently read that the last male northern white rhinoceros, called Sudan, was put down due to age-related ailments. The northern white rhinoceros is a a now functionally-extinct subspecies of the white rhinoceros, with only two females remaining. This day was imminent – with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How do we mend the rift between science and art?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-how-do-we-mend-the-rift-between-science-and-art/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-how-do-we-mend-the-rift-between-science-and-art/</guid>
        <description>I am slightly ashamed to admit that after four years at Imperial, I had yet to attend a single conference. However, in the spirit of trying new things and expanding my horizons, I agreed to accompany my friend to Aesop’s Arts in Health Conference and Showcase. This neophiliac mentality was what …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lab-grown heart  used for drug safety testing</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-lab-grown-heart-used-for-drug-safety-testing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-lab-grown-heart-used-for-drug-safety-testing/</guid>
        <description>Currently, drug safety testing has to be initially conducted on animals, before trials in humans begin. While animal models have proven to be useful, in some respects, they do not wholly mimic human reactions. One of my lecturers’ favourite examples is thalidomide – a mild sleeping tablet that was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let’s talk about sex(ual health)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-let-s-talk-about-sex-ual-health/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nada Mohamed-Ali,Harumi Quezada Yamamoto,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-let-s-talk-about-sex-ual-health/</guid>
        <description>They say your years at university are some of the best of your life. That the lessons you will learn and the experiences you will gain will be paramount in forming who you are as a person. However, it does not always feel that way. For many of us the transition from the shelter of our homes to the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science and eternity – perspectives on immortality</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-science-and-eternity-perspectives-on-immortality/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maria Balaet,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-science-and-eternity-perspectives-on-immortality/</guid>
        <description>One of the most recent hot topics in the field of science and technology centres around Netcome – a private company who have set out to preserve human brains post-mortem, such that, one day, following technological advancements, they would be able to “recreate your mind”. Nectome bases their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flagship species – putting the con in conservation</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-flagship-species-putting-the-con-in-conservation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-flagship-species-putting-the-con-in-conservation/</guid>
        <description>For those unaware of what a flagship species is: it is a species selected by a conservation organisation, such as the World Wide Fund (WWF), to act as an icon or symbol for a defined issue or environmental problem. This being said, you are all probably thinking of one of the best-known flagship …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Quickening: Why you need that kick</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-quickening-why-you-need-that-kick/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-quickening-why-you-need-that-kick/</guid>
        <description>I am not a mother myself, but I imagine having a tiny human kicking and moving around in your womb can feel quite uncomfortable. At some point, you may, out of frustration, wonder: why do they move around so much?! A research group co-led by Paula Murphy from Trinity College Dublin has been able to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The dangers of vaping</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-the-dangers-of-vaping/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ignatius-Roy Hillcoat-Nalletamby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-the-dangers-of-vaping/</guid>
        <description>E-cigarettes, often advertised as an aid for smoking cessation, may actually encourage young adults to take up smoking, new research suggests.
E-cigarettes are growing in popularity, both in the US and UK, with vaping shops opening on every other street corner. E-cigarettes provide the same smoking …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Galaxies far, far away: The problem of the spinning stars</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-22-galaxies-far-far-away-the-problem-of-the-spinning-stars/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maya Kaushik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-22-galaxies-far-far-away-the-problem-of-the-spinning-stars/</guid>
        <description>Princess Leia was a feminist icon of the 1980s that many of us grew up with. When Carrie Fisher passed away just over a year ago, social media and the news were filled with people mourning her death. Two days before, however, on Christmas Day in 2016, Vera Rubin quietly passed away in the USA. Rubin …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Behind the scenes of London’s snowy adventure </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-behind-the-scenes-of-london-s-snowy-adventure/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rachel Ong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-behind-the-scenes-of-london-s-snowy-adventure/</guid>
        <description>With the weather seeming to be on the verge of spring, it seems hard to believe that just a couple of weeks ago London had experienced some of the most severe snow days in years. Air temperatures dropped to a 27-year low, and – much to everyone’s bother – signal failures and track problems disrupted …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with Conservation – LEGO goes green</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-connect-with-conservation-lego-goes-green/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-connect-with-conservation-lego-goes-green/</guid>
        <description>It may be a surprise – for those who remember treading on rogue LEGO pieces in the dark – to hear the company is going green by producing plant-based plastics! Known as LEGO Botanical Elements, they will start to enter playsets later on this year, with the first pieces to be replaced including …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I can show you the world: How gene therapy brightens the future for eye diseases</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-i-can-show-you-the-world-how-gene-therapy-brightens-the-future-for-eye-diseases/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-i-can-show-you-the-world-how-gene-therapy-brightens-the-future-for-eye-diseases/</guid>
        <description>You may have your mother’s eyes, or your father’s nose, as genetics plays a significant role in determining physical traits such as height and eye colour. But genes can also determine other things: diseases! Cystic fibrosis is an example of a disease that has a genetic basis, meaning that the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ready player one – how games are fuelling ‘citizen science’</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-ready-player-one-how-games-are-fuelling-citizen-science/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Varshit Dusad,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-ready-player-one-how-games-are-fuelling-citizen-science/</guid>
        <description>If you were told that the next solution to one of our endearing medical and scientific challenges may be coming from a bunch of computer gamers around the world, your immediate reaction will be one of disbelief. Though it sounds surprising, a computer game called FoldIt has been a beneficial tool in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Connect with conservation – A lonely frog</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-connect-with-conservation-a-lonely-frog/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Steve Allain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-connect-with-conservation-a-lonely-frog/</guid>
        <description>Just in times for Valentine’s Day, a Sehuencas water frog named Romeo had an online dating profile setup to search for love. This sort of thing isn’t usually newsworthy, except for the fact Romeo has been dubbed ‘the world’s loneliest frog’. He is the only known individual of his species, and the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>From Jaws to jaws: the impact of shark-fin soup</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-from-jaws-to-jaws-the-impact-of-shark-fin-soup/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Olly Dove,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-from-jaws-to-jaws-the-impact-of-shark-fin-soup/</guid>
        <description>Over forty years ago, a film was released into cinemas that would forever haunt those swimming in the open sea. But the main star of Jaws, the infamous great white shark, sadly has more to fear from humans than we do from them. While we may think of sharks preying upon us, in this case it is humans …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grantham lecture: a topical discussion with a distinguished speaker</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-grantham-lecture-a-topical-discussion-with-a-distinguished-speaker/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kenza Tazi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-grantham-lecture-a-topical-discussion-with-a-distinguished-speaker/</guid>
        <description>Following the established tradition of his predecessors, His Serene Highness Prince Albert II came to Imperial to promote ocean conservation. The principality of Monaco is known to have led many expeditions under the leadership of Prince Albert I, the current prince’s grandfather, and Jacques-Yves …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In light of dark matter: oldest stars lead to detection</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-in-light-of-dark-matter-oldest-stars-lead-to-detection/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-in-light-of-dark-matter-oldest-stars-lead-to-detection/</guid>
        <description>Recent research conducted in Arizona State University suggests that we have the “first direct proof” that dark matter exists, as a team of astronomers analysed absorption lines from the oldest stars in the universe. Dark matter is an invisible stockpile of mass that we estimate to make up about 27% …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Words and genes</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-words-and-genes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-words-and-genes/</guid>
        <description>Language and genetics do not usually go hand in hand in human history. Languages are, if anything, an instrument for domination – the epitome of international prestige as well as commercial and political supremacy. As the scholar of Yiddish Max Weinreich once said: “a language is a dialect with an …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
