<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/xc3313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/xc3313/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Krav Maga – A fearsome addition to IC’s martial arts roster
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-13-krav-maga-a-fearsome-addition-to-ics-martial-arts-roster/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2015 15:21:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xuan Chen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-13-krav-maga-a-fearsome-addition-to-ics-martial-arts-roster/</guid>
        <description>For anyone unfamiliar with Krav Maga, the short summary is this; it’s a brutally effective modern self-defence system invented by the Israeli military halfway through the 20th century.
What hopes to become one of Imperial’s newest societies offered a free taster session one rainy Sunday to gauge the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Getting close to Cowley
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-getting-close-to-cowley/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 23:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xuan Chen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-getting-close-to-cowley/</guid>
        <description>Professor Steven Cowley is the CEO of the United Kingdom Atomic Energy Authority and a part-time professor in plasma physics here at Imperial College. But that’s not what catches the attention of an entire cohort of physics undergraduates every year – it’s his lectures, where his charisma and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Behold, the UK’s finest collegiate a cappella groups
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-30-behold-the-uks-finest-collegiate-a-cappella-groups/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 00:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xuan Chen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-30-behold-the-uks-finest-collegiate-a-cappella-groups/</guid>
        <description>Last weekend Imperial College played host to the vivacious, nerve-wracking, and outrageously outstanding International Championship of Collegiate A Cappella (ICCA) UK Semifinal competition: a massive undertaking attracting the best unaccompanied singing groups in the world.Nine of the UK’s best …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s go hyper
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-lets-go-hyper/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 00:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xuan Chen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-lets-go-hyper/</guid>
        <description>The biannual gathering of dedicated Japanese markets and exhibitors took place two weekends ago, and managed an exhibition which was a verifiable smorgasbord of Japanese culture.
Exhibitions like these are a clarion call for like-minded small and medium business owners to come together in one place …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Commercialisation in creative technology
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-commercialisation-in-creative-technology/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 12:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xuan Chen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-commercialisation-in-creative-technology/</guid>
        <description>The release of the iPad in the UK in the early summer of 2010 was a watershed moment which forever changed the way we interact with application technology. It was only a matter of time before a number of social entrepreneurs decided to weave the creative talent together in the form of conventions, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Comic Convention you’d be crazy to miss but even crazier to attend
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-the-comic-convention-youd-be-crazy-to-miss-but-even-crazier-to-attend/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 19:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xuan Chen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-the-comic-convention-youd-be-crazy-to-miss-but-even-crazier-to-attend/</guid>
        <description>Why would someone with no knowledge of any anime, comic books, and video games attend an event aimed at bringing these people together? Curiosity, that’s why.
The MCM London Comic Convention starts much earlier than I anticipated; costumed attendees with bright hair and elaborate costumes board the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
