<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jc5412/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jc5412/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Science, what’s good?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-science-whats-good/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 11:52:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jane Courtnell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-science-whats-good/</guid>
        <description>Mechanical heartbreak fix
Mechanically patching up a ‘broken’ heart may soon be possible thanks to Tal Dvir and Ron Feiner. They have integrated electronics with living tissues to produce the “cyborg heart patch”. The patch acts like an organ, but is powered by a machine, regulating heart …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who really killed the Ichthyosaur?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-who-really-killed-the-ichthyosaur/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 11:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jane Courtnell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-who-really-killed-the-ichthyosaur/</guid>
        <description>Meteorites and volcanic eruptions; large events as such are generally considered to have led to the dinosaurs’ demise. However, their legacy is not simple – they lived, big rock collides with the Earth, they died. The Ichthyosaur, otherwise known as the ‘fish lizard’, bewildered scientists with its …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science, what’s good?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-science-whats-good/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 11:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jane Courtnell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-science-whats-good/</guid>
        <description>Speeding up Evolution
Humans are once again appointed felon in the Ecological community. Zoologists Rudman and Schluter documented reverse speciation in the British Columbia Lakes, particularly Enos Lake on Vancouver Island. Introduction of Crayfish species was found to cause the extinction of two …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The elusive green business model
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-the-elusive-green-business-model/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 12:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jane Courtnell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-the-elusive-green-business-model/</guid>
        <description>Business sustainability as a concept came about in the early 70s, with controversial publications such as The Limits to Growth, addressing environmental and social consequences of economic growth. Since the ‘green business’ model began to establish its domain, little attention was paid to the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lonely wail might indicate new species
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-lonely-wail-might-indicate-new-species/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 14:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jane Courtnell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-lonely-wail-might-indicate-new-species/</guid>
        <description>How many species do you think exist on planet earth? 100 thousand, one million, ten million? Recent estimations have induced a species count of 8.7 million. More than 1000 years would be needed to catalogue such a vast number. It’s really a question of ‘where do we start?’
From the depths of the icy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Money is green? Bank of England in awe
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-money-is-green-bank-of-england-in-awe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 11:40:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jane Courtnell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-money-is-green-bank-of-england-in-awe/</guid>
        <description>Reports dooming the Earth as we know it are not novel concepts. For all the much needed scaremongering in the media, climate change as a threat sits on a pedestal. It’s a threat that respects no boundaries, operating across all borders. However it’s only recently that the financial repercussions of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What’s your angle? Willows and biofuels
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-20-whats-your-angle-willows-and-biofuels/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2015 00:49:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jane Courtnell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-20-whats-your-angle-willows-and-biofuels/</guid>
        <description>The true scale of climate change and its impacts on our planet has escalated in the last 50 years. Scientific advancement has been at the forefront in efforts to achieve a more stable climatic future. Biofuel development symbolises a significant movement towards this future. However, growing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fossil discovery sheds light on human origins
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-13-fossil-discovery-sheds-light-on-human-origins/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 00:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jane Courtnell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-13-fossil-discovery-sheds-light-on-human-origins/</guid>
        <description>Humans still have an unmistakable tie to our ape origins. The question is, how did we get from such a beginning to our where we are now? The fossil record provides a fragmented view of human evolution. From this record, the time of split between the Homo genus and Australopithecus genus remains …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You are what you eat – but where does it come from?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-9-you-are-what-you-eat-but-where-does-it-come-from/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 19:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jane Courtnell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-9-you-are-what-you-eat-but-where-does-it-come-from/</guid>
        <description>Fertile Crescent of Western Asia provides the earliest evidence so far of agricultural development; dated to have occurred in this region around 11,000 years ago. This behaviour originated independently at several locations and spread globally.
In the last 50 years, following the “green revolution”, …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
