<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/eoy05/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/eoy05/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Tackling Cystic Fibrosis
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-tackling-cystic-fibrosis/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 23:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edward Yoxall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-tackling-cystic-fibrosis/</guid>
        <description>In June this year, the Cystic Fibrosis Gene Therapy Consortium started a ground breaking new trial looking at the effects of regularly dosing sufferers with gene therapy. Ned Yoxall speaks to Dr Jane Davies, the clinical lead investigator in London, to find out more.
Ned Yoxall: Thanks so much for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Becoming Ironman: Part 2
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-becoming-ironman-part-2/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:03:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edward Yoxall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-becoming-ironman-part-2/</guid>
        <description>On race morning I got out of bed just after 4 and gorged myself on porridge and muesli. It’s an odd feeling waking up so early knowing that you’re going to spend an entire day exercising. Almost all of it will be uncomfortable (as in you’d kind of like to do something else instead) and a good chunk …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Preparing for winter by becoming an Ironman
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-preparing-for-winter-by-becoming-an-ironman/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 13:30:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edward Yoxall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-preparing-for-winter-by-becoming-an-ironman/</guid>
        <description>Just before Christmas I decided to take up a “challenge” to raise money for the Cystic Fibrosis Trust. My little cousin, who suffers from the disease, had been going through a rough patch. I wanted to do something that would attract sponsorship, so I plumped for Ironman Wales. What I did know was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Library doors: a refutation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-library-doors-a-refutation/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 20:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edward Yoxall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-library-doors-a-refutation/</guid>
        <description>In training for long distance things, you have to train for quite a long time. Whether I’m in the pool, on the bike, or on a run I usually get some ‘quality’ time with my own thoughts. What follows is the result of this time alone…
Recently in Felix, Laurence de Lussy Kubisa wrote a remarkable …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Awkward conversations
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-awkward-conversations/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 23:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edward Yoxall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-awkward-conversations/</guid>
        <description>Now I’m not really one to feel self-conscious. If we’re being brutally honest here, I actually quite like getting attention – a hangover from my Mum never looking at how high I was going. Recent experience, however, has taught me that I have boundaries – lines that should not, under any …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why you should give me your money
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-why-you-should-give-me-your-money/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 23:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edward Yoxall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-why-you-should-give-me-your-money/</guid>
        <description>I’m going to lay my cards out on the table straight away. I will spend the next six months begging you for money. This is the raison d’etre of this column. Amusing you (or more likely myself) would be a nice perk on the side – a bit like dental insurance.
Given that you are all, no doubt, very …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
