<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/tr511/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/tr511/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Campaigning is hard work...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-19-campaigning-is-hard-work/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 23:52:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abigail E de Bruin,Benjamin Howitt,Tom Rivlin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-19-campaigning-is-hard-work/</guid>
        <description>Tom Rivlin: Deputy President (Clubs and Societies) candidate, 2015
Let’s get one thing out of the way first: yes, I did just lose in the Big Elections. Yes, I am extremely bitter about this. Yes, you can read the whole article as just a sore loser whining about losing sorely if you want.
That said I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Adventure Time saved Cartoon Network
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-how-adventure-time-saved-cartoon-network/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 23:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Rivlin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-how-adventure-time-saved-cartoon-network/</guid>
        <description> It’s safe to say that Adventure Time (AT), the hit eleven-minute cartoon about Jake the dog, Finn the human, and their crazy adventures, has been a huge success for its studio/host channel, Cartoon Network (CN). Now in its sixth season, the show has amassed a huge audience of children providing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Reddit made it okay to hate women
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-how-reddit-made-it-okay-to-hate-women/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 18:26:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Rivlin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-how-reddit-made-it-okay-to-hate-women/</guid>
        <description>Last week I wrote in Felix about ‘GamerGate’, a loosely defined movement nominally about “ethics in video game journalism”. In the article I outlined how really the movement is about harassing women online.
But GamerGate wasn’t created when some developer was accused of sleeping around: it’s the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>GamerGate: not about ethics in journalism
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-gamergate-not-about-ethics-in-journalism/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 01:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Rivlin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-gamergate-not-about-ethics-in-journalism/</guid>
        <description>Anyone with an interest in feminism, social media, video games or nerd culture in general has probably heard this term over the past few months: GamerGate. What exactly is it? Why is it so awful? To get to the bottom of this we need to take a long, ugly look at gaming culture…
The short version of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cartoon Corner – Teen Titans Go!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-20-cartoon-corner-teen-titans-go/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 21:48:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Rivlin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-20-cartoon-corner-teen-titans-go/</guid>
        <description>Fandoms can be weird places sometimes. Let me explain&amp;hellip;
_Teen Titans _was a superhero cartoon (‘capeshit’, as my flatmates call it) that ran for five seasons from 2003, based on the long-running DC comic book of the same name. It was fairly popular, with above average writing and characters …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where the hell did this come from?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-where-the-hell-did-this-come-from/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 22:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Rivlin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-where-the-hell-did-this-come-from/</guid>
        <description>Dan Harmon’s beloved sitcom _Community _has long been known to fans as a ‘genre’ show smuggled onto our screens under the disguise of a regular comedy about a community college. In Adult Swim cartoon Rick and Morty, co-creator Dan Harmon has done the opposite – he’s managed to smuggle an earnest, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Twitch Plays Pokémon: Alive and Kicking
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-twitch-plays-pokmon-alive-and-kicking/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 20:42:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Rivlin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-twitch-plays-pokmon-alive-and-kicking/</guid>
        <description>Remember that thing that everyone cared about for one week in February? To a future historian it’ll look like a weird mind virus infected everyone for exactly a week and then disappeared. Let’s talk about it again!
If you missed it, in February a programmer created a channel on Twitch (a game …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Singularity Sky
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-singularity-sky/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 03:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Rivlin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-singularity-sky/</guid>
        <description>It’s hard to decide whether Singularity Sky is hard or soft sci-fi. Inherent to the setting of the book is faster-than-light (FTL) travel and an omnipotent, post-singularity AI. However that stuff is all really just a backdrop to incredibly nerdy (and delightful) discussions of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cartoon Corner: Adventure Time
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-cartoon-corner-adventure-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 16:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Rivlin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-cartoon-corner-adventure-time/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to Cartoon Corner, the new weekly column where we explore the wonderful world of animation! (Not anime. We have a separate club for that.) Each week I’ll be doing either a review of a currently airing show, or a retrospective on something more nostalgic. So, word counts are tight here, let’s …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
