<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sm5810/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sm5810/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s like it’s 2009 all over again
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-its-like-its-2009-all-over-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 14:58:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-its-like-its-2009-all-over-again/</guid>
        <description>It may have been just five years ago, but 2009 seems like the distant past. I was still in sixth form, and, more importantly for the context of this review, I had fully immersed myself in the wide world of music. The landfill indie of my teenage years had been put to one side, and I was making the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS albums you may have missed!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-ams-albums-you-may-have-missed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 01:28:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-ams-albums-you-may-have-missed/</guid>
        <description>St. Vincent - St. Vincent
St. Vincent released her first album, Marry Me, back in 2007. It was pretty good. 2009 saw Actor released, and that was really good. 2011’s Strange Mercy was absolutely spectacular. A stunningly well crafted art pop record, it reamins one of the best things released this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gig Review: Seahaven
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-gig-review-seahaven/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 01:24:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-gig-review-seahaven/</guid>
        <description>Birthday’s in Dalston is about as hipster as venues come. It’s in Dalston for a start. Upstairs there’s a burger joint that serves food on trays, but to be fair, does do a mean sweet potato burger and some extraodinary cheesy chips, oh, those cheesy chips… The stage is in the basement, and it’s a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cloud Nothings - Here and Nowhere Else
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-cloud-nothings-here-and-nowhere-else/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 05:46:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-cloud-nothings-here-and-nowhere-else/</guid>
        <description>It has been an unusual journey for Dylan Baldi, the man behind Cleveland based Cloud Nothings. He was signed as a one-man band and released his first two albums, Turned On and the self-titled Cloud Nothings, were recorded as such. They were full of lo-fi noise pop at its most frantic and fun, with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Raving on About Mogwai Going to Shit
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-raving-on-about-mogwai-going-to-shit/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 04:37:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-raving-on-about-mogwai-going-to-shit/</guid>
        <description>Rave is not a word I would ever have associated with the music of Mogwai. As people, it makes a bit more sense. They has always been a certain distance between them and the more pretentious attitudes most post-rock bands employ. On a Mogwai album, you won’t find made-up languages (I’m looking at you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Deer Tick (but no Lyme Disease)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-deer-tick-but-no-lyme-disease/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 04:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-deer-tick-but-no-lyme-disease/</guid>
        <description>I have managed to catch Providence based alt-country act Deer Tick a couple of times at festivals before. I allegedly first caught them back in 2010, although the performance was unmemorable to the point where I actually have no memory of the set. Of course, this could well not be indicative of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I Break Horses Break No New Ground
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-i-break-horses-break-no-new-ground/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:07:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-i-break-horses-break-no-new-ground/</guid>
        <description>Swedish act I Break Horses released their debut album, Hearts, back in 2011. Full of fuzzy a, processed beats and dreamy vocals I remember being fairly impressed when I first listened to it, but by no means blown away. I then caught them at a festival in the summer of 2012 and was completely blown …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Black Metal and a Crywank
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-black-metal-and-a-crywank/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Forrest Seiwald,Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-black-metal-and-a-crywank/</guid>
        <description>When I asked Stuart if he wanted to come to Crywank with me, he was understandably confused. Thankfully, I was able to quickly able to correct any misunderstandings and on Monday night we headed to see Crywank, performing with Caïna, Old Skin, and Ithaca at Power Lunches.
Crywank is an acoustic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tara Jane O’Neil - Where Shine New Lights
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-tara-jane-oneil-where-shine-new-lights/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 03:53:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-tara-jane-oneil-where-shine-new-lights/</guid>
        <description>Tara Jane O’Neil is a multi-talented musician based out of Portland, Oregon. At the age of 19 she was already playing bass for art punk band Rodan. She then went about forming Retsin, a folky indie duo and The Sonora Pine, a more experimental post-rock type band. Since then there has been a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Thrill-Ver Mount Zion
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-a-thrill-ver-mount-zion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 03:52:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-a-thrill-ver-mount-zion/</guid>
        <description>It’s difficult for any side project to ever be judged in comparison to anything but their parent band, and when that band is Godspeed You! Black Emperor, it is probably never going to go well for you. Starting as A Silver Mt. Zion in 1999, Thee Silver Mt. Zion Memorial Orchestra are onto their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS album of the week: Government Plates
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-ams-album-of-the-week-government-plates/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 22:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-ams-album-of-the-week-government-plates/</guid>
        <description>Death Grips rose to prominence with the 2011 mixtape Exmilitary. This still stands to this day as one of my favourite hip-hop records. It’s raw, filled with crushing industrial beats and has, in MC Ride, a very unique rapping style. 2012 saw two more albums: The Money Store and NO LOVE DEEP WEB, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Emserine – Dalmak
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-emserine-dalmak/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 22:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-emserine-dalmak/</guid>
        <description>Esmerine are one of the more loosely-related Godspeed You! Black Emperor side projects. It features Bruce Cawdron, the drummer from GY!BE (he also plays in Set Fire to Flames), alongside cellist Beckie Foon, who plays with both Set Fire to Flames, HRSTA and A Silver Mt. Zion (all other Godspeed side …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sixteen Fantastic Bands and It’s About Time!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-sixteen-fantastic-bands-and-its-about-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 16:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Forrest Seiwald,Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-sixteen-fantastic-bands-and-its-about-time/</guid>
        <description>Last Saturday saw the Bussey Building in Peckham play host to About Time #2. A day festival chocked full of the best in UK emo, screamo and noise rock is tough to say no to, so we headed down to check out some bands. The two stages were staggered so you could see everything, and we did our best. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS album of the week: The Albatross
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-ams-album-of-the-week-the-albatross/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 18:08:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-ams-album-of-the-week-the-albatross/</guid>
        <description>Foxing released an EP last year called Old Songs. I did not care for it. It was everything post-rock-tinged emo shouldn’t be. The three songs were overthought and overstretched, but worst of all, they were really dull. It was an emo band trying to be a post-rock band with little success. Since then …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS album of the week: Reflektor
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-ams-album-of-the-week-reflektor/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 09:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-ams-album-of-the-week-reflektor/</guid>
        <description>Despite it being over ten years since AF first burnt music onto a CD to hand out at a small local gig in their Montreal neighbourhood, they are still teenagers – full of fire, angst, beauty and surprising lyricism. They have been almost alone in crafting albums which have a lot to say without …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dealing Conversation a Falco-n Punch
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-dealing-conversation-a-falco-n-punch/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 09:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-dealing-conversation-a-falco-n-punch/</guid>
        <description>Future of the Left released their latest album, How to Stop Your Brain in an Accident, last week and they are currently touring the UK, visiting London on the 13th. Stuart Masson caught up with lead singer and guitarist Andrew ‘Falco’ Falkous.
For starters, can you give a quick description of Future …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Album Review: Deaf Havana
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-album-review-deaf-havana/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 09:37:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-album-review-deaf-havana/</guid>
        <description>Deaf Havana’s early single Friends Like These ends with the repeated line “Nothing gets worse than growing old”. This show made me realise they’re not wrong (maybe grammatically, but, you know…). Surrounded by teenagers having the time of their young lives, I came to the startling realisation that I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Arcade Fire: REFLEKTOR
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-arcade-fire-reflektor/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 00:39:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-arcade-fire-reflektor/</guid>
        <description>rcade Fire release their new album on October 28th. Reflektor was announced in a reply to a single fan on twitter, it’s been preceded with a viral campaign inspired by Haitian veve drawings (me neither) and a single credited to a fictional band called The Reflektors. The hipster darlings are doing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS album of the week: Bitter Rivals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-ams-album-of-the-week-bitter-rivals/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 00:37:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-ams-album-of-the-week-bitter-rivals/</guid>
        <description>First, some honesty, I chose to review this album because I expected it to be really bad. The hype died years ago for Sleigh Bells, and I’ve yet to find a positive review of this one. I fancied tearing this apart in the written press, because that is what makes me feel big. I’m disappointed on all …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chillin’ in fanboy heaven
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-20-chillin-in-fanboy-heaven/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 01:50:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-20-chillin-in-fanboy-heaven/</guid>
        <description>The Mountain Goats are probably my favourite musical artist. From the early years of just John Darnielle with a guitar and a tape recorder right through to the current three piece iteration, I am an embarrassingly large fanboy. So, a few months back, when they announced they were playing at the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>No Age: An Object (Live)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-no-age-an-object-live/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 00:40:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-no-age-an-object-live/</guid>
        <description>No Age descended on North London last week to showcase their new album, “An Object”. The LA two piece were originally scheduled to play at Koko but the gig was downsized to the school hall-esque Dome in Tufnell Park. This is definitely a band on the way down. The new album, unlike its predecessors, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS album of the week 23
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-ams-album-of-the-week-23/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 22:49:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-ams-album-of-the-week-23/</guid>
        <description>The World Is a Beautiful Place &amp;amp; I Am No Longer Afraid to Die are an emo band. To some people, admitting to liking emo is somethingto be shared only in hushed tones to well trusted close friends. However, I’ve spent long enough in the emo closet, I’m coming out. Emo is the best. Some of you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS Album of the Week 19
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-ams-album-of-the-week-19/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 14:49:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-ams-album-of-the-week-19/</guid>
        <description>The National are a band who have transcended modern music trends. They first came to prominence with the glut of “post-punk revival” indie bands in the mid-2000s. That scene died years ago, but The National rose from the ashes, and have continued to rise and rise. Their last album, High Violet, saw …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS Album of the Week 13
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-ams-album-of-the-week-13/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 01:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-ams-album-of-the-week-13/</guid>
        <description>Veronica Falls released their self titled debut album back in 2011 to a smattering of applause from the indie pop scene. Adding shoegaze elements and some great little indie guitar riffs to the basic Camera Obscura template made for a very listenable and funalbum. It never really clicked for me …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS album of the week 10
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-ams-album-of-the-week-10/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 00:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-ams-album-of-the-week-10/</guid>
        <description>Local Natives have never been groundbreaking. They stood out not because they were doing something different to their peers, but because they were doing it quite well. Their second album, Hummingbird, does not break the trend. It wears its influences on its sleeve and they’re pretty much the same as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS Album of the Week 9
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-ams-album-of-the-week-9/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 00:52:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-ams-album-of-the-week-9/</guid>
        <description>Yo La Tengo are not the sort of band you can pigeonhole. Their albums are a mishmash of genres from across the alternative rock spectrum and beyond. Their latest effort, Fade, is slightly less of a mixed bag. All of the standard sounds are here, but they don’t get their own tracks any more. There …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS Album of the Week 8
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-ams-album-of-the-week-8/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 22:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-ams-album-of-the-week-8/</guid>
        <description>Big Boi, or the other guy in OutKast, has always been a bit lost in the shadow of Andre 3000. Andre was the crazy experimentalist and Big Boi was just a really good rapper. Big Boi’s excellent debut solo album, Sir Lucious Left Foot, blurred that idea a little. There were big pop hits as well as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>St. Vincent woos Shepherd’s Bush
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-st-vincent-woos-shepherds-bush/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 23:10:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-st-vincent-woos-shepherds-bush/</guid>
        <description>I am 110% in love with Annie Clark, of St. Vincent. That means I could backtrack 10% and still be completely in love with her. The woman knows her way around a guitar and what more do you need? The live tone is sensational, probably the best I’ve ever heard, and it suits her manic little riffs …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The best of Heaven
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-the-best-of-heaven/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 21:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stuart Masson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-the-best-of-heaven/</guid>
        <description>EMA stands for Erika M. Anderson, but she performs with a full band. Her debut album Past Life Martyred Saints has been gathering positive reviews from across the music press spectrum, and for good reason. The live performance is something else, though. The whole gig switches between haunting …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
