<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/al4915/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/al4915/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Can dessert be good for you?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-can-dessert-be-good-for-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 14:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-can-dessert-be-good-for-you/</guid>
        <description>Today’s port of call is a French poires au chocolat clafoutis. In other words, what I made last Sunday. As a food and science writer I find tremendous reconciliation in the overlap between food, psychology, and science. I thought it would, or could, be relevant to extend my habitual weekend kitchen …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fear Food, Fear Death
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-fear-food-fear-death/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 13:33:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-fear-food-fear-death/</guid>
        <description>Last week I was at a posh restaurant, because pretending to have money with mediocre savings is this new and dangerous trend I have undertaken. Dessert being my ultimate weakness, I made a big deal out of the pre-dessert and dessert. Meringuelets shrouded in freeze-dried raspberries, swimming …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ending the Cycle of Junk
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-ending-the-cycle-of-junk/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 14:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-ending-the-cycle-of-junk/</guid>
        <description>As I type, I’m eating a thin slice of Japanese soufflé cheesecake I made yesterday. But the pleasure I took in eating it triggered a glitch of annoyance. I realised such fine nuances of taste and texture are easily overlooked in today’s world where easy access to and high abundance of high-energy, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is meat really manly?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-is-meat-really-manly/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 16:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-is-meat-really-manly/</guid>
        <description>I guess I’ll start with a controversial, but factual statement: Men don’t live as long as women do. Now, would you believe that this and so many other gendered beliefs affect our health habits, including the foods we choose to eat? An article in The Washington Post piqued my interest lately, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Clean eating | The dirty truth
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-clean-eating-the-dirty-truth/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 16:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-clean-eating-the-dirty-truth/</guid>
        <description>Sweet potato brownies, smoothie bowls, tofu cheesecake, courgette noodles. Call it, name it, it’s all out there. The crowned diet gurus so charismatically persuade you to convert to these superior versions. God forbid refined sugar. No dairy. No gluten. Capri-Sonne? What’s that? I don’t hate these …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fish from the Med, good for the head?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-fish-from-the-med-good-for-the-head/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-fish-from-the-med-good-for-the-head/</guid>
        <description>Think back to the last time you dipped sourdough into balsamic, mixed with a gleaming pool of olive oil. Extra virgin, please. As the world of nutrition science continues to shift our perceptions between food ideals, a new study has come to light featuring the sunny, olive oil lifestyle. The paper, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Does this look burnt?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-does-this-look-burnt/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 12:08:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,Alexandra Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-does-this-look-burnt/</guid>
        <description>The perennial question. You notice that slightly-too-blackened edge of your fried chicken thigh during a friend’s thanksgiving dinner, and hesitate just a little, but eat it anyway because nothing can take that peri-peri pleasure away from you. I guess it’s common knowledge that burnt foods can be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The (alphas) and omegas of food
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-the-alphas-and-omegas-of-food/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 14:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-the-alphas-and-omegas-of-food/</guid>
        <description>I hereby appeal to everyone: pick up a copy of Michael Pollan’s In Defence of Food this week. It truly drives home how food is being treated in this nutrition-crazed world, with people’s sad attempts to reduce it to health components. Most forget that food in itself is more significant than this. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>To be or not to be vegan?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-to-be-or-not-to-be-vegan/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 12:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-to-be-or-not-to-be-vegan/</guid>
        <description>Let the flags fly and wars rage. Veganism is probably one of the most contentious topics of our time. Though I am not fully vegan due to personal reasons, I joined VegSoc because, after watching documentaries like Cowspiracy and Food Matters, anyone would be hard-pressed to lay off meat slightly. I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pale vs. Kale
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-pale-vs-kale/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 15:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-pale-vs-kale/</guid>
        <description>Something we are constantly told when it comes to food is to ‘eat the rainbow’. Densely packed nutrients bind to colour pigments, hence why colourful veggies are thought of as bright bundles of nourishment. Most white or pale foods are overlooked, with many lacking fibre and nutrients. However, a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Getting Oily: The science of cooking
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-14-getting-oily-the-science-of-cooking/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 11:25:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Selin Olenik,Alexandra Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-14-getting-oily-the-science-of-cooking/</guid>
        <description>The latest branch of research is all about oil, specifically the daily occurrence of heating up some olive oil in a pan, something most of us don’t even think about.
So you’re in the kitchen, searing that fatty, gorgeous pink salmon, when your friend starts a convenient Facetime session. Next thing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is vaginal yoghurt the future?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-is-vaginal-yoghurt-the-future/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 09:10:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-is-vaginal-yoghurt-the-future/</guid>
        <description>If you haven’t already, I implore you all to read The Diet Myth by Tim Spector, the acclaimed work by professor of genetic epidemiology and consultant physician (sadly at a rival university here in London). It finely elucidates all the factors which play gargantuan roles in the way we react to and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Creamy heavenly probiotic goodness
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-creamy-heavenly-probiotic-goodness/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 09:11:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-creamy-heavenly-probiotic-goodness/</guid>
        <description>I was perusing ‘What to Eat’ by the fabulous nutrition professor Marion Nestle, and was particularly intrigued by her short piece elucidating all the hoo-ha around yoghurt. Say the word ‘yoghurt’ just once and you’re more likely than not to get a ho-hum reaction. Is it a health food? Breakfast? …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Seven minutes of hell
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-seven-minutes-of-hell/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 09:05:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-seven-minutes-of-hell/</guid>
        <description>With exams drawing near, many think setting aside time for a dedicated workout is simply not worth it. The mere idea of walking to Ethos makes you die a little inside. Long-drawn lectures and revision means the treadmill is off the agenda on weekdays, so you settle for that walk to the library, the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is it time for a move to frozen foods?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-is-it-time-for-a-move-to-frozen-foods/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 09:56:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-is-it-time-for-a-move-to-frozen-foods/</guid>
        <description>Breakfast this morning got me thinking. It merely involved microwaving frozen bread prior to making French toast, but the nonchalant routine reminded me to extol the virtues of frozen food, something I think many of us tend to overlook.
Sadly, the modern consumer is inclined to look down on frozen …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s not all about the D
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-its-not-all-about-the-d/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 11:48:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-its-not-all-about-the-d/</guid>
        <description>Some of us go pretty far when it comes to maintaining vigilance with our diets. We pinch our noses as we down that tablespoon of cod liver oil, chuck mounds of spinach into Tesco’s spinach ricotta tortellini, because obviously just the latter doesn’t quite fulfil our magnesium requirements, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are there really different sugars?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-are-there-really-different-sugars/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 11:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-are-there-really-different-sugars/</guid>
        <description>Cane sugar, honey, raw turbinado, coconut sugar, agave syrup. Many nutrition experts sitting on their high horses all wax lyrical over these glistening labels, eager to proclaim the nutritional properties of each. These are the same people who are religious avocado-toast eaters and green-juice …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The neurobiology of Anorexia
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-the-neurobiology-of-anorexia/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 11:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-the-neurobiology-of-anorexia/</guid>
        <description>It’s amazing how science can be so fiercely intertwined with a topic as contentious as dieting. The relationship between the two became evident when I attended the past weekend’s most anticipated brainy event – the London Students’ Neuroscience Conference 2016. It heralded a most intriguing …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
