<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/gda07/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/gda07/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The End of a Media Empire
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-8-5-the-end-of-a-media-empire/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 13:29:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gilead Amit,Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-8-5-the-end-of-a-media-empire/</guid>
        <description>Events of the past few weeks have shone a new light on how our media has been operated as a monopoly, with one arguably great but unquestionably evil man at its apex. With the disintegration of his empire, the question now facing all of us is how can the media change its ways of operating and still …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Glimpses of the past – the Imperial Institute
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-22-glimpses-of-the-past-the-imperial-institute/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2011 12:23:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,Gilead Amit,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-22-glimpses-of-the-past-the-imperial-institute/</guid>
        <description>When construction began on the grand Imperial Institute in 1887, fears were already being expressed that it would turn into a wasteful white elephant. Barely a year later, in fact, Thomas Henry Huxley had already pronounced the monumental project ‘a failure’. But when Rector Sir Patrick Linstead …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>MTSoc&#39;s &#34;We Will Rock You&#34; - rehearsed and performed within 27 hours
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-7-mtsocs-we-will-rock-you-rehearsed-and-performed-within-27-hours/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 16:56:47 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gilead Amit,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-7-mtsocs-we-will-rock-you-rehearsed-and-performed-within-27-hours/</guid>
        <description>______________________
19:38 All right. It&amp;rsquo;s been 24 hours of constant rehearsals, and not-so-constant liveblogging. I&amp;rsquo;ve expended nearly 6,000 words in an attempt to convey the awesomeness of this cast, and I don&amp;rsquo;t think 60,000 could do them justice. I don&amp;rsquo;t have much more …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Losing proportion
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-losing-proportion/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2010 21:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gilead Amit,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-losing-proportion/</guid>
        <description>Towards the end of my second year at Imperial, I was approached by the chair of what was then the Atheist and Agnostic Society with a view to becoming his successor as official Union Antichrist. Owing to a number of other commitments that would have made Beelzebub blanch, I regretfully declined. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Battle of Ideas comes to South Kensington
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-battle-of-ideas-comes-to-south-kensington/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 19:13:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gilead Amit,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-battle-of-ideas-comes-to-south-kensington/</guid>
        <description>If I can start by being totally honest, I hadn’t heard of the ‘Battle of Ideas’ before I found out you were coming to the Royal College of Art this year. What would you like people to know before they come along?
When we set it up 6 years ago, we wanted to suggest that there was not an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>If you read nothing else this week...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-8-if-you-read-nothing-else-this-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 06:33:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gilead Amit,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-8-if-you-read-nothing-else-this-week/</guid>
        <description>Gosh. Cripes. Blimey. What a responsibility. I have just been asked by the delightful new Arts editor to inaugurate this column by writing a short, pithy piece on my favourite book. Publicity whore that I am, I couldnít bring myself to refuse.
But, though gratified to have been offered this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Scientists rally to fight funding cuts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-7-scientists-rally-to-fight-funding-cuts/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 22:31:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gilead Amit,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-7-scientists-rally-to-fight-funding-cuts/</guid>
        <description>On Saturday the 9th of October, over 2,000 scientists and science supporters will rally at Westminster to protect the future of British science. Their aim is to make the government reconsider any spending cuts to be made in the fields of research and development, cuts that scientists fear could …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Enough damn advice already!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-1-enough-damn-advice-already/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 22:40:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gilead Amit,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-1-enough-damn-advice-already/</guid>
        <description>Before you get any further, I feel you should know that writing these things isn’t as easy as it looks. That’s partly because you don’t actually see us writing them, but mainly because, unlike columnists at the Guardian who write for everybody who counts, and those at the Sun who write for everybody …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Icemen Cometh
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-27-the-icemen-cometh/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2010 17:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gilead Amit,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-27-the-icemen-cometh/</guid>
        <description>When I was younger, and had time on my hands and nothing better to do, I frequently fell ill. Nothing particularly debilitating or life-threatening, you understand, only regular healthy doses of the common cold or flu. Influenza, as they say, and out flew my health. It is possibly one of the best …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The abuse of sympathy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-the-abuse-of-sympathy/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 17:09:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gilead Amit,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-the-abuse-of-sympathy/</guid>
        <description>This has been a busy week on campus. Imperial Christian Union have been hosting their free thinking week, and the Palestinian Society have organised a Gaza awareness week. And being a conscientious, participating member of the Union, I&amp;rsquo;ve tried to get involved with all these conflicting …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Underwriting as a hobby
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-22-underwriting-as-a-hobby/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 13:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gilead Amit,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-22-underwriting-as-a-hobby/</guid>
        <description>Can&amp;rsquo;t I put it off for a few hours longer?
No, I&amp;rsquo;ve wasted enough time already. Right – time to sit down and finally batter out this week&amp;rsquo;s comment piece. Maybe I should just clean the living room again? Some more dust may have accumulated under the sofa in the two minutes since I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Moderates must make their voices heard
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-14-moderates-must-make-their-voices-heard/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 17:46:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gilead Amit,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-14-moderates-must-make-their-voices-heard/</guid>
        <description>It’s good to see that all of you have safely made it back to college. Whether by plane, train, sleigh or snowplough, or thanks to having hitched a ride on the back of a frisky reindeer, you’ve finally made it back to the warm embracing arms of college. Some of you have had to fight snow and ice, …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
