<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ko409/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ko409/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Evidence for sexism in the Union?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-evidence-for-sexism-in-the-union/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 22:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Osborne,Marissa Lewis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-evidence-for-sexism-in-the-union/</guid>
        <description>Inequality irritates me, particularly as it is so prevalent within our society. Women are oppressed on many different levels; here at Imperial the most recent evidence for this is the refusal by the NCC (New Clubs Committee) of a Gender Equality Society. The reasoning of the Union is as follows: we …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Protesting at Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-protesting-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 21:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Osborne,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-protesting-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>What protests have you been to recently?
The last protests I went to were some of the student cuts protests last year. The student cuts protests were genuinely intimidating so I haven’t attended recently.
Why do you feel the need to protest?
I feel it is another way to express your opinion in a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Amateur serpents and super amorists
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-18-amateur-serpents-and-super-amorists/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 08:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Osborne,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-18-amateur-serpents-and-super-amorists/</guid>
        <description>I was apprehensive when I heard that, because the budget would not allow for period costume, this production was to be a contemporary version of the opera. That is not to say I know anything about opera, but for me part of its appeal is the historic context and atmosphere that it exudes. However, I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Somebody killed the show
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-somebody-killed-the-show/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 20:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Osborne,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-somebody-killed-the-show/</guid>
        <description>Sitting down in a dingy backroom of a pub in Camden, it seemed that we the audience were to play a more crucial role in this Hitchcock parody than previously anticipated. I turned to my ‘Partner in Crime’ and wryly noted that there were 13 members of the audience, indeed an unlucky number for the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>If you read nothing else this week...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-if-you-read-nothing-else-this-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 19:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Osborne,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-if-you-read-nothing-else-this-week/</guid>
        <description>Looking for a thought provoking but comfortable and easy read? Look no further. A book which should not be rejected for having pi in the title. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there&amp;rsquo;s nary a mention of the ratio of a circle to its diameter between its covers.
Life of Pi follows the unusual adventures of …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
