<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/gib13/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/gib13/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Real change comes from real action
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-real-change-comes-from-real-action/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 16:22:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Giacomo I Boscaini-Gilroy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-real-change-comes-from-real-action/</guid>
        <description>Oh, you went on Saturday’s march? You must have the moral high ground now. You 100% changed the world by walking around with a sign. Here’s a reality check: the only way to influence the nation is through government. You didn’t make any tangible change, you sent a letter of complaint: &amp;lsquo;Hi, I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Millennials are all that can save us in this post-truth world
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-the-millennials-are-all-that-can-save-us-in-this-post-truth-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 15:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Giacomo I Boscaini-Gilroy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-the-millennials-are-all-that-can-save-us-in-this-post-truth-world/</guid>
        <description>As a year, 2016 really pissed me off. I remember when 2008 ended. I remember people saying that it would be consigned to history as the year of the Great Recession. My call is that 2016 will be seen as the year of the fuck-up. The future looks uncertain and shaky. No one planned for political …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Corbyn finally said something and I’m not impressed
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-corbyn-finally-said-something-and-im-not-impressed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Giacomo I Boscaini-Gilroy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-corbyn-finally-said-something-and-im-not-impressed/</guid>
        <description>News flash; Jeremy Corbyn emerged from his ferret hole in North London and made a speech! He must have read my article about how he needed to get his act together and talk positively about immigration. As if I were felix’s de facto Labour immigration policy correspondent, I have returned to give a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Labour must lead a positive debate on immigration
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-21-labour-must-lead-a-positive-debate-on-immigration/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 12:28:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aishwarya Pattar,Giacomo I Boscaini-Gilroy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-21-labour-must-lead-a-positive-debate-on-immigration/</guid>
        <description>Imperial’s success depends on a culture of open-mindedness that has attracted academics and students to come from abroad, and means people from different cultures, but with similar interests, can exchange ideas. Immigration has allowed this university to thrive, so why is it that in Britain today it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The NUS doesn’t represent Jewish students
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-the-nus-doesnt-represent-jewish-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:19:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Giacomo I Boscaini-Gilroy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-the-nus-doesnt-represent-jewish-students/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday 20th April, the NUS voted in Malia Bouattia as the first female black Muslim president. It is great that at a time when Islamophobia is increasing and London mayoral candidate Sadiq Khan is pettily attacked over past acquaintances, the largest student body stands together with it’s …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
