<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/chunyuanhii/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/chunyuanhii/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Asian invasion</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-asian-invasion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chun Yuan Hii,Adrian Lua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-asian-invasion/</guid>
        <description>Felix Food has been sharing simple and quick recipes for the past few issues, and that’s great! Hopefully they’ve helped you to survive the term in some ways. But don’t you occasionally imagine yourself cooking a Michelin-starred dish, unleashing your inner chef, and it no longer mattering if you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Have a sweet tooth? We sure do...</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-have-a-sweet-tooth-we-sure-do/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chun Yuan Hii,Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-have-a-sweet-tooth-we-sure-do/</guid>
        <description>Admit it, we all need our sugary boost sometimes (though this might be heavily frowned upon by my friend who wrote on healthy eating last week&amp;hellip;) Maybe it’s just me, but occasionally, after a nine-to-five day full of labs and lectures, you just want to have something warm, sweet, and – most …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grub’s up! Felix Food’s guide to campus food</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-grub-s-up-felix-food-s-guide-to-campus-food/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Davage,Chun Yuan Hii,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-grub-s-up-felix-food-s-guide-to-campus-food/</guid>
        <description>1. JCR
The canteen with blue tables has a standard deli selling fancy baguettes and a canteen with all the normal lunch grub (boxed sandwiches, crisps, etc.).
Pieminster sells gourmet pie and mash. A little pricey but sometimes they do discounts so look out for those. They offer a range of gravy, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Tis the season... again</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27--tis-the-season-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chun Yuan Hii,Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27--tis-the-season-again/</guid>
        <description>I’ll bet my lunch that you have already seen those shop-fronts decorated in orangey strips, the vampire Frappucino adverts outside Starbucks, your friends marking ‘Interested’ on Halloween-themed Facebook events, and those tacky, plasticky, not-even-scary masks lining the aisles of Tesco. Well okay, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Foodie’s Guide to South Kensington</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-foodie-s-guide-to-south-kensington/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chun Yuan Hii,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-foodie-s-guide-to-south-kensington/</guid>
        <description>With Freshers’ week going on in full swing, there’s bound to be a moment when you’re a little bit too weak to go near the stove and dish out your perfectly organised, healthy and affordable meal plans. Or maybe you just need somewhere to go with your new friends without becoming financially …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
