<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ezrakitson14/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ezrakitson14/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Manwatching | Want Women Really Want
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-25-manwatching-want-women-really-want/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 12:03:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ezra Kitson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-25-manwatching-want-women-really-want/</guid>
        <description>Manwatching offers an insight to the heterosexual world of sex from a female point of view. The show consists of a roughly sixty minute monologue, which explores several aspects of sex including masturbation, sexual fantasies and consent. The prose is raw, explicit and dynamically written. In every …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Puppets answer everything you wanted to know about sex but were too afraid to ask
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-19-puppets-answer-everything-you-wanted-to-know-about-sex-but-were-too-afraid-to-ask/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 15:07:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ezra Kitson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-19-puppets-answer-everything-you-wanted-to-know-about-sex-but-were-too-afraid-to-ask/</guid>
        <description>Sex and Puppets is reimagining the way we think and talk about sex and relationships. A production by the puppet company Wondering Hands uses a series of witty sketches, devised in collaboration with puppeteer Alicia Britt that are based on real life experiences as told by members of the public in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Everything you wanted to know about sex but were too afraid to ask, from puppets
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-19-everything-you-wanted-to-know-about-sex-but-were-too-afraid-to-ask-from-puppets/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 13:12:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ezra Kitson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-19-everything-you-wanted-to-know-about-sex-but-were-too-afraid-to-ask-from-puppets/</guid>
        <description>‘Sex and Puppets’ is reimagining the way we talk about sex. The show devised by the puppet company Wondering Hands uses a series of witty sketches - composed from verbatim transcripts of real life experiences - to explore different aspects of sex.
It is directed by Edie Edmundson, who I interviewed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ballet Black – A rough cut gem
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-7-ballet-black-a-rough-cut-gem/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 15:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ezra Kitson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-7-ballet-black-a-rough-cut-gem/</guid>
        <description>Ballet Black’s triple bill at the Barbican consisted of three works, which covered an eclectic range of compositions and dances. The first work, House of Dreams, was a non-narrative work consisting of three pas de deux and a finale to a diverse selection of compositions by Debussy. The compositions …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Richard III | An exploration of a monster
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-richard-iii-an-exploration-of-a-monster/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 22:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ezra Kitson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-richard-iii-an-exploration-of-a-monster/</guid>
        <description>Thomas Ostermeier’s production of Richard III is a celebration of the wicked, the tragic, and the profane. The play is on tour from Schaubühne Berlin and is performed entirely in German with English surtitles on the stage.
Not only is this a departure from the original Shakespeare in terms of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Arts Interviews | Edie Edmundson
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-arts-interviews-edie-edmundson/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 15:59:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ezra Kitson,Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-arts-interviews-edie-edmundson/</guid>
        <description>The Little Matchgirl is a show populated by people and puppets, of which the eponymous character, masterfully operated by Edie Edmundson, is one. Our writer, Ezra Kitson, was fortunate enough to speak with her after the performance.
Edmundson was drawn to puppetry by a National Theatre production of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Little Matchgirl and Other Happier Tales
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-the-little-matchgirl-and-other-happier-tales/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 15:57:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ezra Kitson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-the-little-matchgirl-and-other-happier-tales/</guid>
        <description>Emma Rice has encapsulated the spirit of the season in the Sam Wanamaker Playhouse’s Christmas production of The Little Matchgirl and Other Happier Tales, and it’s not as jubilant as you might expect. The artistic director has baked together several of Hans Christian Anderson’s tales to create a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Great Expectations | A worthy adaptation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-great-expectations-a-worthy-adaptation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 15:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ezra Kitson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-great-expectations-a-worthy-adaptation/</guid>
        <description>The advice of Mr Jaggers is &amp;ldquo;Take nothing on its looks; take everything on evidence. There’s no better rule.&amp;rdquo; It is keenly observed by Christian Burgess who delivers a no frills production of Great Expectations superbly carried by convincing performances and slick directing.
Great …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Nest overeggs performances to give an uneven show
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-14-the-nest-overeggs-performances-to-give-an-uneven-show/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 14:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ezra Kitson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-14-the-nest-overeggs-performances-to-give-an-uneven-show/</guid>
        <description>Having just read We Need to Talk About Kevin I seated myself in the packed Young Vic theatre with considerable foreboding. All I knew of The Nest, Franz Xaver Kroetz’ parable with an ecological warning, was that it involved a great tragedy becoming two young parents. I quickly realised that my …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Pacifist’s Guide to the War on Cancer
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-a-pacifists-guide-to-the-war-on-cancer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 14:25:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,Ezra Kitson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-a-pacifists-guide-to-the-war-on-cancer/</guid>
        <description>Bryony Kimmings’ latest project might be her most ambitious. A Pacifist’s Guide to the War on Cancer is a poignant portrayal of life alongside cancer, experienced through the naïve eyes of a mother whose baby boy is diagnosed. This sombre premise is transformed with all Kimmings’ charm and …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
