<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jeg07/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jeg07/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Festive science facts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-12-festive-science-facts/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2010 13:55:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Goldsack,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-12-festive-science-facts/</guid>
        <description>Roasts:
One of the better aspects of Christmas is the food. A juicy roast is a must, and the process of roasting sets off many chemical reactions that few other methods can match.
Whatever meat you choose, it is the muscle tissue that you will be dying to tuck into. Muscle tissue normally consists …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Barley disease sequenced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-12-barley-disease-sequenced/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2010 13:50:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Goldsack,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-12-barley-disease-sequenced/</guid>
        <description>Researchers from the beleaguered Department of Life Sciences at Imperial College have sequenced the genome of a major fungal disease that affects cereal crops including barley. This breakthrough could advance our understanding of the evolution of plant diseases. The research suggests that parasites …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New anti-psychotic drugs in pipeline
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-new-anti-psychotic-drugs-in-pipeline/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2010 20:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Goldsack,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-new-anti-psychotic-drugs-in-pipeline/</guid>
        <description>Schizophrenia could be caused by abnormal levels of neurotransmitters dopamine and glutamate, according to new research carried out at Imperial College London.
Researchers found evidence that glutamate-releasing cells in the hippocampus influence the activity of dopamine-releasing cells, which in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Light and death for hospital superbugs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-light-and-death-for-hospital-superbugs/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2010 20:06:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Goldsack,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-light-and-death-for-hospital-superbugs/</guid>
        <description>A new technology that uses light beams to kill bacteria could be used in hospitals to stop the spread of MRSA and other antibiotic resistant bugs, say scientists from the University of Strathclyde.
The technology, known as HINS light, uses visible light wavelengths to excite molecules within …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Blade Runner!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-blade-runner/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 21:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Goldsack,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-blade-runner/</guid>
        <description>On BBC iPlayer until midnight tomorrow (Saturday 13th), is the best film you can see for free this weekend. Starring Harrison Ford as Deckard, the policeman tasked with hunting down a group of escaped androids, banned from earth due to their threat to humanity. The visual palette of this film is an …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
