<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/tom_alston/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/tom_alston/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Has MiFID II demolished the research industry?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-has-mifid-ii-demolished-the-research-industry/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-has-mifid-ii-demolished-the-research-industry/</guid>
        <description>At the beginning of last year MiFID II was introduced to make the financial industry more transparent. One key aspect of this is the move from bundled to unbundled products brokerage firms provide. Previously, a fund manager buying a security through a broker would pay a hefty commission. This would …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are Uber’s bankers getting cold feet? </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-are-uber-s-bankers-getting-cold-feet/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-are-uber-s-bankers-getting-cold-feet/</guid>
        <description>The ride haling app has lowered its expectations from a rumoured IPO valuation of around $100 billion to between $80-90 billion. This would still be the largest public offering from Silicon Valley since Facebook, with the company pitching an initial price range of $44 to $55, even as many other …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Educational: Monetary and Fiscal Policy </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-01-educational-monetary-and-fiscal-policy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-01-educational-monetary-and-fiscal-policy/</guid>
        <description>Monetary and Fiscal Policy are the two most widely used tools governments and central banks use to control a nation’s economy. You may have read in FT about how the Federal Reserve, the US Central Bank has become “dovish”, due to its overly “hawkish” stance last year due to Trump’s fiscal policy. In …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What are derivatives and how are they used? </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-what-are-derivatives-and-how-are-they-used/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-what-are-derivatives-and-how-are-they-used/</guid>
        <description>Warren Buffet has described them as “financial weapons of mass destruction”. Robert Kiyosaki said that the subprime Morgage Backed Security (MBS) disaster was a result of them “exploding in financial institutions such as AIG and Lehman Brothers”. So, what exactly are derivatives?
A derivative is a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sovereign debt: a tale of two dilemma’s</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-sovereign-debt-a-tale-of-two-dilemma-s/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-sovereign-debt-a-tale-of-two-dilemma-s/</guid>
        <description>At the beginning of the month, Beth Hammack, a senior Goldman Sachs banker and chair of the government advisory group know as the Treasury Bond Advisory Committee sent a letter to Steven Mnuchin, Treasury Secretary, warning that according to TBAC calculations, America will need to sell $12 trillion …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Will the dollar determine markets in 2019?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-will-the-dollar-determine-markets-in-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-will-the-dollar-determine-markets-in-2019/</guid>
        <description>After a volatile end to 2018, investors are now looking at what the new year can bring. Despite rising 7% against a broad basket of currencies in 2018, many now deem the dollar overvalued. Drawing parallels from both physics and Forex trading, it is well known that whatever goes up must eventually …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Scandals raises questions over Goldman Conduct</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-scandals-raises-questions-over-goldman-conduct/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-scandals-raises-questions-over-goldman-conduct/</guid>
        <description>Back in 2010, Goldman Sachs was sued by the US Securities and Exchange Commission over allegations that it had misled clients over the mortgage backed securities it had sold. Internal Goldman emails surfaced showing how arrogant self-interest bankers had left their clients out in the cold to save …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tech sell-off leads to market slump</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-tech-sell-off-leads-to-market-slump/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-tech-sell-off-leads-to-market-slump/</guid>
        <description>Turbulence in the global financial markets, particularly in the technology sector, saw equity sell offs, oil prices tumble, and dollar swings this week as concerns over the global economy intensified as investors fear growing trade tensions and weak corporate earnings. FAANG stocks, which had …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Crude oil enters bear market</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-crude-oil-enters-bear-market/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-crude-oil-enters-bear-market/</guid>
        <description>US crude oil prices entered a bear market [defined as a 20% drop from a recent high] on Thursday as concerns of tight global supplies eased. This follows Washington allowing eight countries to continue buying Iranian crude, softening the blow of new international sanctions on the nation. In addition …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ESG investing, is it really worth it?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-esg-investing-is-it-really-worth-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-esg-investing-is-it-really-worth-it/</guid>
        <description>Global Warming. Corruption. War. Poverty. These are all problems every human on the face of the earth must deal with, and it is something everyone should be tackling. The financial industry has decided to combat these problems with Environmental, Social and Governance (ESG) Investing. It is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Investment banks relish in hawkish environment</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-investment-banks-relish-in-hawkish-environment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-investment-banks-relish-in-hawkish-environment/</guid>
        <description>It is a well-known fact that when interest rates are hiked, investment banks increase their profitability due to their massive cash holdings. Increasing the interest rates directly increases the yield on the cash it holds, and the proceeds go directly into the income statement. Furthermore, interest …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rising Fed rates puts pressure on markets</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-rising-fed-rates-puts-pressure-on-markets/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-rising-fed-rates-puts-pressure-on-markets/</guid>
        <description>Since the fiscal stimulus of tax cuts that the Trump administration has implemented this year, the US economy on the surface has been doing great. It has notched a 4.1% annualized growth rate for Q2, which is considerably faster than the 2% growth rate that has been standard since 2001. Then in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Rise of Private Equity</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-the-rise-of-private-equity/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-the-rise-of-private-equity/</guid>
        <description>Before the financial crisis, private equity investors followed closely the “buyout” manual pioneered by Henry Kravis and George Roberts when they founded the firm KKR in the 1970’s. Essentially, they would acquire companies whole, then they would cut costs and load them with low interest rate debt. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Commercial Cannabis: Bitcoin Bubble?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-commercial-cannabis-bitcoin-bubble/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-commercial-cannabis-bitcoin-bubble/</guid>
        <description>On Tuesday 18th September, the US Drug Enforcement Agency gave the Canadian cannabis producer Tilray permission to export its cannabis to the United States for medical research. The next day Tilray Inc. shares were halted five times from trading in less than one hour as the market neared its close. …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
