<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ar3310/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ar3310/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Movember Centre of Excellence opens in London
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-movember-centre-of-excellence-opens-in-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 22:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-movember-centre-of-excellence-opens-in-london/</guid>
        <description>Earlier this year Imperial College London, in collaboration with the Institute of Cancer Research and University College London, launched The London Movember Centre of Excellence. The new centre has been created to redefine and personalise the care given to men with prostate cancer and was funded by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What’s happened to the Aldwych Group?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-whats-happened-to-the-aldwych-group/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 10:59:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-whats-happened-to-the-aldwych-group/</guid>
        <description>[Tabloid Special]
As a group of representatives of the Student’s Unions and Associations of the Russell Group, you would expect them to be doing, well something. With an empty website and empty promises of meeting at least 6 times a year, rumours have been spreading amongst the twittersphere that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Elections begin at Imperial College Union
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-elections-begin-at-imperial-college-union/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 04:35:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-elections-begin-at-imperial-college-union/</guid>
        <description>The Big Elections for 2014 have started this week at Imperial College. Campaigning started on Monday 3rd March and will continue through till the 14th March and voting opens next week on Friday 7th March and will last one week.
According to the ICU website, over 459 candidates are running. So even …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Key IRA suspect of the Hyde Park bombings walks free on a police ‘blunder’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-28-key-ira-suspect-of-the-hyde-park-bombings-walks-free-on-a-police-blunder/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 07:12:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-28-key-ira-suspect-of-the-hyde-park-bombings-walks-free-on-a-police-blunder/</guid>
        <description>John Downey, 62, was a main suspect for the murder of four soldiers by the IRA (Provisional Irish Republican Army) and has now been let free due to a police error that gave him effective immunity.
The Hyde Park and Regent Park bombings occurred in 1982 and resulted in the deaths of 11 military …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Badly dressed intruder escorted from Tizard hall
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-24-badly-dressed-intruder-escorted-from-tizard-hall/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 23:31:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-24-badly-dressed-intruder-escorted-from-tizard-hall/</guid>
        <description>A mysterious stranger was caught wandering Tizard last Sunday. The man was described as tall with dark skin and badly dressed. He was wearing a red jacket and was noted to be carrying a Bible and had an American accent.
The intruder was escorted from the premises by hall security and the Tizard …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Prince Harry Visits Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-18-prince-harry-visits-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 20:34:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-18-prince-harry-visits-imperial/</guid>
        <description>The Royal British Legion Centre for Blast Injury Studies (CBIS) officially opened at Imperial College today (Oct 17). The CBIS held its second networking event in the Royal School of Mines and invited HRH Prince Harry to unveil the centre.
The CBIS is a charitably funded research centre between the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fisher Halls are Fishy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-3-fisher-halls-are-fishy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2013 23:08:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,Benjamin Fernando,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-3-fisher-halls-are-fishy/</guid>
        <description>Much of last year’s #AgainstActon campaign focused on the impending closure of Evelyn Gardens’ Fisher Hall. The huge campaign lasted months but the plans to create the halls were continued. In 2011, the college announced that the Fisher Hall was no longer required. This was due to the completion of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Global biomedical hub to be built in London
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-global-biomedical-hub-to-be-built-in-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 23:10:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-global-biomedical-hub-to-be-built-in-london/</guid>
        <description>A £650 million medical research centre is under construction in London. Funded by the Medical Research Council, Cancer Research UK, the Welcome Trust as well as Imperial College London, University College London and King’s College London. The Francis Crick Institute will be based in King Cross next …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union awards announced 2013
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-union-awards-announced-2013/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 23:06:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-union-awards-announced-2013/</guid>
        <description>The Imperial College Union Awards Ceremony was held yesterday (Thursday June 13). The Awards Committee chose the winners and Union Council unanimously upheld the decision.
Union Fellowship with Distinction was awarded to Nathaniel Bottrell, a long-time trustee, and Stephen Richardson, Deputy Rector …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Business School appoint new Dean
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-9-business-school-appoint-new-dean/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 11:39:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-9-business-school-appoint-new-dean/</guid>
        <description>Professor G. ‘Anand’ Anandalingam has been named the new Dean of Imperial College Business School and Professor of Management Science. He replaces Professor Dorothy Griffiths OBE who has been Head since February 2012.
He currently holds the position as the Dean of the Robert H. Smith School of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Medics stage protest over BUCS decision
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-14-medics-stage-protest-over-bucs-decision/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 23:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-14-medics-stage-protest-over-bucs-decision/</guid>
        <description>The British Universities &amp;amp; Colleges Sport (BUCS) acts as the national governing body for higher education sport in the UK. They have decided that a single educational institution should not be able to compete as two separate teams. This means that the current system where Imperial College (IC) …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A&amp;E department closures announced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-ae-department-closures-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 00:09:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-ae-department-closures-announced/</guid>
        <description>The hope that the Charing Cross A&amp;amp;E department was to be saved has been overturned after the official meeting was held on February 19. This comes after speculation that the A&amp;amp;E department was going to remain open as a smaller A&amp;amp;E.
Andy Slaughter, Hammersmith and Fulham Labour MP, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Charing Cross A&amp;E Department saved
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-charing-cross-ae-department-saved/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 21:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-charing-cross-ae-department-saved/</guid>
        <description>Plans to close the Accident and Emergency department of Charing Cross Hospital have been scrapped in a last minute decision. The original plan to downgrade Charing Cross Hospital has been changed so that the hospital will still have a 24&amp;frasl;7 emergency service for those who make their own way to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>International PG applications down
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-international-pg-applications-down/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2013 01:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-international-pg-applications-down/</guid>
        <description>The number of Non-EU postgraduate applicants has fallen for the first time in 16 years. In previous years the numbers had risen annually by an average of more than 10%. Figures released by the Higher Education Statistical Agency (Hesa) shows a 1% drop fuelling ideas that the government’s immigration …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Employers don’t want you they want Warwick – says survey
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-17-employers-dont-want-you-they-want-warwick-says-survey/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 23:47:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-17-employers-dont-want-you-they-want-warwick-says-survey/</guid>
        <description>A recent study by High Flier Research claims that the top 100 graduate employers focussing on finding graduate recruits on a small number of universities. A list oftwenty universities targeted found Warwick University at the top and Imperial at 12th place.
The majority of graduate employers …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Charing Cross and Hammersmith hospital A&amp;E departments to close
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-charing-cross-and-hammersmith-hospital-ae-departments-to-close/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 22:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-charing-cross-and-hammersmith-hospital-ae-departments-to-close/</guid>
        <description>Charing Cross and Hammersmith A&amp;amp;E departments are going to be closed.
Following a public consultation last year, the decision was made concerning the future of the Hammersmith and Fulham borough hospitals. Charing Cross Hospital will now become a local hospital and Hammersmith Hospital will be a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Female students recruited to be escorts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-female-students-recruited-to-be-escorts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 00:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-female-students-recruited-to-be-escorts/</guid>
        <description>The Independent has uncovered that female students are being offered up to £15,000 a year to pay for their university fees in return for having sex with a stranger. A website called SponsorAScholar.co.uk proclaimed that they have set 1,400 women between the ages of 17-24 with wealthy businessmen …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial teams on top
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-imperial-teams-on-top/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 21:43:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-imperial-teams-on-top/</guid>
        <description>83 technology students from 15 different Universities participated in J.P Morgan’s first ever Tech Coding Challenge. 17 teams competed in this Hackathon-style event that took place in the headquarters of J.P. Morgan in Canary Wharf. Their coding skills were put to the test as they used technology to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Middle East protest in Kensington
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-middle-east-protest-in-kensington/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 22:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-middle-east-protest-in-kensington/</guid>
        <description>Last Thursday, High Street Kensington found itself overwhelmed with protestors. At 5:30pm, crowds gathered to protest against the violence in the Middle East.
Imperial students were amongst these protestors, campaigning with members of the public. Protestors could be found carrying signs, chanting …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>More Grants, Less Money
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-more-grants-less-money/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 20:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-more-grants-less-money/</guid>
        <description>Imperial has received the highest amount of research council’s money out of all the institutions in the UK.
Imperial has received £76.7 million in 2011-2012, the most out of all the institutions that applied. However, this is a fall of 19% when compared to last year’s total of £94.5 million.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial has highest international fees
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-8-imperial-has-highest-international-fees/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2012 23:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Proctor,Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-8-imperial-has-highest-international-fees/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College has been found to charge the most for their International student tuition fees out of the Russell group universities. The data shows that Imperial’s international students who do clinical medicine are charged a massive £39,150.
International fees are broken down into bands. Band 1 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial open up about animal research
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-imperial-open-up-about-animal-research/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 22:18:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-imperial-open-up-about-animal-research/</guid>
        <description>Animal testing has always been a very controversial topic amongst people. A lot of research is conducted at Imperial and sometimes this may involve the use of animals. The currently policy on the Use of Animals in Research states that “animals may only be used in research programmes where their use …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Skyfall from Beit
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-a-skyfall-from-beit/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 01:38:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-a-skyfall-from-beit/</guid>
        <description>As a lot of you must know, because it would almost have been impossible to miss for even the keenest attendee of the Library, the new James Bond movie Skyfall premiered at the Royal Albert Hall on Tuesday night. Prince Consort Road was partially closed off and access was restricted around the area. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Up with The Times
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-up-with-the-times/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:53:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-up-with-the-times/</guid>
        <description>Overall Rankings
The Times
Imperial College London has come in 4th in the league table. This is the same place as last year but a rank below from in 2011, where we came 3rd. Imperial have come above London rival University College London (UCL), which came in 7th place.
The Sunday Times
Imperial came …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Babar Ahmad extradited
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-babar-ahmad-extradited/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 20:19:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-babar-ahmad-extradited/</guid>
        <description>Babar Ahmad has been extradited to the United States after the High Court refused to review his case. Last month, the European Court of Human Rights (ECHR) gave its final approval for the extradition. At a federal district court hearing in New Haven, Connecticut, Babar Ahmad pleaded not guilty and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Possible A&amp;E changes
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-possible-ae-changes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 15:52:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-possible-ae-changes/</guid>
        <description>Plans have been made to close the Accident and Emergency departments of both Charing Cross and Hammersmith hospitals. Instead, Chelsea and Westminster Hospital will be made the main A&amp;amp;E department for the area and will be expanded to handle the extra patients from the borough. Other hospitals …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Central Library for 24 hour opening over Summer
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-1-central-library-for-24-hour-opening-over-summer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2012 12:04:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-1-central-library-for-24-hour-opening-over-summer/</guid>
        <description>For the first time in Imperial College history, the Central Library will continue its 24-hour opening times throughout the summer holidays. Imperial College has decided to keep its library door open to students who wish to use the library, starting from 30 June through until 30 September.
In …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>General meeting date announced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-general-meeting-date-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 06:01:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-general-meeting-date-announced/</guid>
        <description>Following on from his comment article published on 2 March, Union President Scott Heath has confirmed a date for the General Meeting. The meeting will be held on Wednesday 6 June in SAF Lecture Theatre G34.
The General Meeting is an open forum that can be attended by any union member. With a usual …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Court approves Babar Ahmad extradition to United States
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-court-approves-babar-ahmad-extradition-to-united-states/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 18:55:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-court-approves-babar-ahmad-extradition-to-united-states/</guid>
        <description>Babar Ahmad is a British Citizen and former student and staff member of Imperial College London who has been detained in prison for eight years under anti-terrorist legislation without a trial in the UK. He has been battling against extradition to the US but on 10 April the European Court of Human …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial take on BP Grand Final
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-imperial-take-on-bp-grand-final/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 21:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-imperial-take-on-bp-grand-final/</guid>
        <description>Following the Regional Semi-Finals last month, two teams from Imperial College have made it to the BP Ultimate Field Trip Grand Final. The Grand Final will take place in the Royal Institute on 8 May. Imperial teams make up two of the three teams competing to win the prize of a 6-8 week internship in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Break-in at Beit Hall
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-9-break-in-at-beit-hall/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 01:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-9-break-in-at-beit-hall/</guid>
        <description>Student residence Beit Hall was disrupted on Wednesday 29 February following a series of thefts that took place during a fire alarm. Following the alarm, which began at 1am and lasted for 45 minutes, students who left their doors open during the commotion returned to find items such as cash, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Neeson leads a lacklustre pack
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-4-neeson-leads-a-lacklustre-pack/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2012 17:28:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-4-neeson-leads-a-lacklustre-pack/</guid>
        <description>The Grey
Director Joe Carnahan Screenwriters Joe Carnahan, Ian MacKenzie Jeffers Cast Liam Neeson, Frank Grillo, Dermot Mulroney, Dallas Roberts, Joe Anderson
If you like dogs, don’t watch this ﬁlm.
Based in Alaska, a typical plane crash results in seven men surviving. Why do guys always survive …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial storm BP semi-finals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-imperial-storm-bp-semi-finals/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 00:34:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-imperial-storm-bp-semi-finals/</guid>
        <description>The BP Ultimate Field Trip semi-finalists have been revealed, and include nine Imperial students. They will compete in the regional semi-final that will take place towards the end of February for the prize of a 6-8 week internship in Trinidad and Tobago in the Gulf of Mexico.
The three teams were …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chinese Ambassador visits Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-27-chinese-ambassador-visits-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 00:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-27-chinese-ambassador-visits-imperial/</guid>
        <description>The Chinese Ambassador to the UK visited Imperial College last week to discover more about Imperial and also gave a lecture on the role of innovation as the path to success in twenty first century China. Xiaoming Liu has been the Ambassador for China since 2009 and took the time to talk to Chinese …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial West masterplan unveiled
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-imperial-west-masterplan-unveiled/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 22:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-imperial-west-masterplan-unveiled/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London has submitted a planning application for the second phase of the development of a new postgraduate campus at Wood Lane, with the project aiming to include the construction of a 34-storey residential tower block.
Imperial purchased the Wood Lane site from the BBC in September …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UK extradition laws to be reformed
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-uk-extradition-laws-to-be-reformed/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 20:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-uk-extradition-laws-to-be-reformed/</guid>
        <description>A parliamentary debate on extradition took place on Monday 5 December where it was concluded that there should be further calls for a public inquiry into the Crown Prosecution Service (CPS). The debate came as a result of an e-petition to put Babar Ahmad on trial in the UK securing over 141,000 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Babar Ahmad petition leads to debate
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-babar-ahmad-petition-leads-to-debate/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 21:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-babar-ahmad-petition-leads-to-debate/</guid>
        <description>An online petition calling for ex-Imperial College staff member Babar Ahmad to be put on trial in the United Kingdom reached 141,000 signatures by its closing date of November 11, passing the requirement of 100,000 for a discussion in Parliament. This has led to a parliamentary debate being held …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The History of Legalisation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-the-history-of-legalisation/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 22:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-the-history-of-legalisation/</guid>
        <description>Originally made illegal in this country in 1928 as part of a international drive to rid the world of opium and other such nasties, the legal status of weed in the Britain depends on where it is classified under the 1971 Misuse of Drugs Act. Up until the early part of the last decade, that was Class …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Babar Ahmad ‘should face trial in the UK’, says sister
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-babar-ahmad-should-face-trial-in-the-uk-says-sister/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 21:14:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,Navid Nabijou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-babar-ahmad-should-face-trial-in-the-uk-says-sister/</guid>
        <description>With less than a month before the online petition concerning Babar Ahmad closes, his sister Amna spoke to Felix about her brother’s experience. For the past seven years, Babar Ahmad has been in prison fighting extradition to the United States. The current petition, launched two months ago, calls on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why didn&#39;t we riot?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-9-30-why-didnt-we-riot/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2011 10:28:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-9-30-why-didnt-we-riot/</guid>
        <description>I’m young. I’m a student. I’ve grown up with today’s British Culture and I am a part of ‘Today’s Generation’. So why didn’t you see me running around London setting fire to furniture stores and stealing carpets? Oh that’s right, because I’m not a complete and utter idiot.
What started out as a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students warned about campus pervert
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-students-warned-about-campus-pervert/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 18:55:24 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-students-warned-about-campus-pervert/</guid>
        <description>On Saturday 18th June, during the Summer Ball, an at around 3pm in the Central Library, a female Imperial student, who has asked to remain anonymous, was followed into the 2nd floor toilets by another person who then attempted to take pictures of her by sliding their mobile phone underneath the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Election winners announced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-election-winners-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 20:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-election-winners-announced/</guid>
        <description>The Imperial College Union Sabbatical and Student Trustee election results were released last Monday at Council. RCSU President Scott Heath beat closest contender Danish Khan in the third stage of the voting process by 1983 to 1593 votes to be elected Union president. Heath said in a statement that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Candidates begin campaigning
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-candidates-begin-campaigning/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 20:46:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,Maciej Matuszewski,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-candidates-begin-campaigning/</guid>
        <description>With Sabbatical Elections right around the corner, the candidates for the different positions are getting geared up for a fierce week of campaigning for the voting period that starts next week.
In yesterday’s initial election meeting, the terms of campaigning were set with the different …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sherfield NatWest to close in May
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-sherfield-natwest-to-close-in-may/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 19:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-sherfield-natwest-to-close-in-may/</guid>
        <description>The Sherfield branch of NatWest is due to close in May after the bank decided not to renew its lease. The closure will leave only one bank on campus, Santander, and there are concerns that international students will be badly hit by the loss of the student expertise at the branch.
By Wednesday it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Summer Ball
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-the-summer-ball/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 19:21:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-the-summer-ball/</guid>
        <description>End of year summer exams, nobody likes them. It is the best way to ruin the best season of the year and everyone dreads them. But now there&amp;rsquo;s something epic to look forward to, because this year, not only is there an end of year summer ball, but there&amp;rsquo;s a whole day of live performances …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>SELKIRK RULES! ...and regulations
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-selkirk-rules-and-regulations/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 19:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-selkirk-rules-and-regulations/</guid>
        <description>After several recent incidents in Selkirk Halls – mainly involving alcohol – the Wardens have decided to implement a series of rules regarding ‘gatherings’ and noise levels late at night. These regulations request that students inform the wardens about gatherings so that they can be ‘approved’ and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Increasing obstacles for prospective students
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-increasing-obstacles-for-prospective-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 18:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-increasing-obstacles-for-prospective-students/</guid>
        <description>Recent figures published by UCAS in their Final End of Year Figures for 2010 has shown a decrease of 0.1% in accepted applicants in the UK compared to 2009, but this doesn’t really come as a surprise after all the over-hyped news of university cuts and how 200,000 students had missed out on places …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Does Imperial have a drinking problem?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-does-imperial-have-a-drinking-problem/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 21:11:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,Aemun Reza,Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-does-imperial-have-a-drinking-problem/</guid>
        <description>Following the controversial exposure of the drunken antics of Imperial medical students at the Reynolds Bar earlier this month, action has been taken to clamp down on the excessive drinking of “a minority of students”. However, as Felix found this week, many students have shrugged off concerns about …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
