<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jmw216/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jmw216/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Strike threat as College rejects plea to protect pensions</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-strike-threat-as-college-rejects-plea-to-protect-pensions/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-strike-threat-as-college-rejects-plea-to-protect-pensions/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College has rejected a request from the University and College Union (UCU) to commit to effectively capping employees’ pension contributions at 8%, despite warnings that the move could trigger strikes later this year and in 2020.
Last month, the College – along with most other universities …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tuition cuts a “shallow gesture” claims Labour minister</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-tuition-cuts-a-shallow-gesture-claims-labour-minister/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-tuition-cuts-a-shallow-gesture-claims-labour-minister/</guid>
        <description>Tuition fees should be slashed and repaid with less interest over a longer period of time before being written off, according to an independent report published last week. The report also recommends the reintroduction of maintenance grants.
The Augar report, commissioned in February 2018 as part of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College to publish results of latest staff consultation regarding pension schemes </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-imperial-college-to-publish-results-of-latest-staff-consultation-regarding-pension-schemes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-imperial-college-to-publish-results-of-latest-staff-consultation-regarding-pension-schemes/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College will next week publish the results of the latest staff consultation regarding changes to their pension schemes.
This latest phase in the long-running dispute that saw countrywide strikes last year adds a third option to the 2018 valuation of the Universities Superannuation Scheme. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Staff consulted over pensions in bid to avoid &#34;undeniable threat to jobs&#34;</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-staff-consulted-over-pensions-in-bid-to-avoid-undeniable-threat-to-jobs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-staff-consulted-over-pensions-in-bid-to-avoid-undeniable-threat-to-jobs/</guid>
        <description>Lecturers are once again being consulted about the future of their pensions as universities prepare for a planned increase in employer and employee contributions that is set to come into force later this year.
With the 2017 valuation of the Universities Superannuation Scheme (USS) concluded, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Times hosts &#34;Designer Babies&#34; debate at Imperial</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-01-the-times-hosts-designer-babies-debate-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-01-the-times-hosts-designer-babies-debate-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Imperial’s partnership with The Times and The Sunday Times continued this week with a discussion of ‘designer babies’. Tom Whipple, science editor of The Times and chair of the event was joined on the panel by IVF pioneer Lord (Robert) Winston, Dr Güneş Taylor from the Francis Crick Institute, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pension deficit down but doubts remain</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-pension-deficit-down-but-doubts-remain/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-pension-deficit-down-but-doubts-remain/</guid>
        <description>The university pension deficit has more than halved since 2017, according to a report released last week. A phased increase in employee contributions is due to begin in April. The news coincides with the beginning of a consultation to determine how much financial risk universities are willing to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s pay protected as debts double</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-president-s-pay-protected-as-debts-double/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-president-s-pay-protected-as-debts-double/</guid>
        <description>Imperial President Alice Gast has been named as one of the highest paid university heads in the country. The disclosure came shortly before it was revealed that Imperial has more than doubled its borrowing, giving it the largest debt of any British university.
Professor Gast receives a salary of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial joins forces with The Times to cultivate &#34;shared interests&#34;</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-imperial-joins-forces-with-the-times-to-cultivate-shared-interests/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-imperial-joins-forces-with-the-times-to-cultivate-shared-interests/</guid>
        <description>A partnership between Imperial and The Times and The Sunday Times was officially launched this week.
The “What the hell is going on?” event marked the start of a year-long collaboration, which will feature joint events to “advance shared interests in the future of science and culture”.
Tuesday …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Augar review: what does the future hold for tuition fees?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-augar-review-what-does-the-future-hold-for-tuition-fees/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-augar-review-what-does-the-future-hold-for-tuition-fees/</guid>
        <description>Tuition fees could be cut to £6,500 per year as part of the latest government review into higher education. The government is also urging shorter degrees to keep overall costs down.
The year-long Augar review will examine whether or not the current funding situation provides good value for money for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College declares support for increased pension contributions to settle long-running dispute</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-college-declares-support-for-increased-pension-contributions-to-settle-long-running-dispute/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-college-declares-support-for-increased-pension-contributions-to-settle-long-running-dispute/</guid>
        <description>Imperial has stated it is willing to increase its pension contributions as a consultation over a long-running dispute closes.
Proposed changes to the University Superannuation Scheme (USS) – the pension plan to which most lecturers in the UK belong – sparked strikes earlier this year. The suggested …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Felix News round-up: some highlights from a year of news around campus</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-the-felix-news-round-up-some-highlights-from-a-year-of-news-around-campus/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-the-felix-news-round-up-some-highlights-from-a-year-of-news-around-campus/</guid>
        <description>This year Felix has been reporting on a wide range of news stories, from the UCU strikes hitting campuses across the UK, to the College removing cooked breakfasts from the SCR. Here&amp;rsquo;s our round-up of a year in news:
SCR remove cooked breakfast as campus services are cut
At the end of July last …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>TEF round three: the reckoning</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-tef-round-three-the-reckoning/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-tef-round-three-the-reckoning/</guid>
        <description>Results are in for the third year of the Teaching Excellence Framework (TEF), which has undergone significant changes following the year two consultation. Imperial’s gold rating (awarded in June 2017) still stands, though it may not be directly comparable with institutions that received gold in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial staff pay falling by 1.1% per year in real terms</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-imperial-staff-pay-falling-by-1-1-per-year-in-real-terms/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-imperial-staff-pay-falling-by-1-1-per-year-in-real-terms/</guid>
        <description>Wages of Imperial employees are decreasing in real terms despite many staff working longer each week than is permitted by government regulations.
College spending on staff as a proportion of total expenditure has fallen from 55.2% in 2011&amp;frasl;12 to 52.8% in 2016&amp;frasl;17. Pay at Imperial has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial emitted more CO­2­ than any other university in the UK last year</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-imperial-emitted-more-co-2-than-any-other-university-in-the-uk-last-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-imperial-emitted-more-co-2-than-any-other-university-in-the-uk-last-year/</guid>
        <description>The level of carbon dioxide emitted by Imperial is higher than that of any other higher education provider in the UK. The College is also one of the worst-perfroming institutions for energy consumption and wastewater.
Imperial was responsible for almost 75.8 million kg of CO2 released in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Success for Imperial graduates in last week&#39;s local elections</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-success-for-imperial-graduates-in-last-week-s-local-elections/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-success-for-imperial-graduates-in-last-week-s-local-elections/</guid>
        <description>Three Imperial graduates have taken seats on London councils in this month’s local elections.
Sina Lari and Leo Cassarani – both of whom stood as Labour Party candidates – won seats in the wards of Golborne and Swiss Cottage respectively. Zain Abbas also won a seat in Canbury Ward, which is part of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Strikes come to an end, as UCU rejects UUK deal</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-strikes-come-to-an-end-as-ucu-rejects-uuk-deal/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-strikes-come-to-an-end-as-ucu-rejects-uuk-deal/</guid>
        <description>The four weeks of strikes that have hit campus end today, a few days after a deal to resolve the pensions dispute was rejected. The agreement would have seen members of the University and College Union (UCU) make larger pension contributions while the current scheme is phased out.
The proposal, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>TEF: The government strikes back</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-tef-the-government-strikes-back/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-tef-the-government-strikes-back/</guid>
        <description>Degree courses are to be rated on teaching quality in an extension of the Teaching Excellence Framework (TEF). In addition to rating each university as a whole, individual subjects will now be categorised as gold, silver, or bronze.
The ten week consultation launched earlier this week by the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial senior pay among highest of Russell Group</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-imperial-senior-pay-among-highest-of-russell-group/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-imperial-senior-pay-among-highest-of-russell-group/</guid>
        <description>Imperial spends more on the salaries of senior staff than any other Russell Group university, a Felix analysis has found. Vice-chancellor pay at Imperial is also near the top of the list.
Data obtained by Felix reveals that in 2017 Imperial spent £5.6 million on ‘key management’ personnel (KMP) – a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Max Mosley-owned trust funding Imperial lab</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-05-max-mosley-owned-trust-funding-imperial-lab/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-05-max-mosley-owned-trust-funding-imperial-lab/</guid>
        <description>Imperial’s Centre for Neuropsychopharmacology is partly funded by a family trust owned by former Formula One boss Max Mosley.
The Alexander Mosley Charitable Trust was set up in memory of Mosley’s son, who died of a suspected drug overdose in 2009. Since then, the trust has donated at least £600,000 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial most unequal university in England; Union Council rejects motion for Social Mobility Officer</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-imperial-most-unequal-university-in-england-union-council-rejects-motion-for-social-mobility-officer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-imperial-most-unequal-university-in-england-union-council-rejects-motion-for-social-mobility-officer/</guid>
        <description>Imperial has the largest gap between numbers of students from affluent areas and students from disadvantaged neighbourhoods. This makes Imperial the most unequal university in England in terms of socioeconomic status.
Data from university admissions body UCAS reveals, that for 70 out of 132 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Leaking library closes recently re-opened area</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-leaking-library-closes-recently-re-opened-area/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-leaking-library-closes-recently-re-opened-area/</guid>
        <description>A water leak has closed part of Central Library. The stairs connecting floors 4 and 5 were closed off on Monday and, at time of writing, remain inaccessible.
The news was announced by the library’s Twitter account on Monday morning. Despite the disruption, floor 5 remained open and accessible via …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oxford Student Union continues NSS boycott</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-oxford-student-union-continues-nss-boycott/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-oxford-student-union-continues-nss-boycott/</guid>
        <description>Oxford Student Union (OSU) has voted to boycott the National Student Survey (NSS) as part of its protest against “the increasing marketisation of our education system”.
The OSU resolved to continue its boycott of the NSS until controversial reforms to the higher education sector are withdrawn. These …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Staff set to strike over planned pension pot changes as universities claim they can&#39;t afford to pay in </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-staff-set-to-strike-over-planned-pension-pot-changes-as-universities-claim-they-can-t-afford-to-pay-in/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-staff-set-to-strike-over-planned-pension-pot-changes-as-universities-claim-they-can-t-afford-to-pay-in/</guid>
        <description>Dozens of universities could be disrupted by strike action in a row over pensions.
Members of the University and College Union (UCU) voted in favour of industrial action; 88% backed a strike and 93% supported lesser action, such as refusing to reschedule classes or providing cover for colleagues. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New mathematics partnership gives hope to post-Brexit research</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-new-mathematics-partnership-gives-hope-to-post-brexit-research/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-new-mathematics-partnership-gives-hope-to-post-brexit-research/</guid>
        <description>Imperial has partnered with a French research agency to open a maths lab, which will promote collaboration between the UK and France as Britain enters a post-Brexit world.
The International Joint Research Unit (UMI – unité mixte internationale) is the first research collaboration between the UK and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial physicist recognised in Blavatnik Awards for young scientists</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-imperial-physicist-recognised-in-blavatnik-awards-for-young-scientists/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-imperial-physicist-recognised-in-blavatnik-awards-for-young-scientists/</guid>
        <description>An Imperial physicist has become one of the first people from the UK to win the Blavatnik Awards, which recognise outstanding young scientists under the age of 42.
Dr Claudia de Rham was awarded the Finalist title in the Awards’ Physical Sciences &amp;amp; Engineering category, in the first year the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Physics students sent email, reminding them to &#34;conduct yourself sensibly&#34;</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-physics-students-sent-email-reminding-them-to-conduct-yourself-sensibly/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-physics-students-sent-email-reminding-them-to-conduct-yourself-sensibly/</guid>
        <description>The physics department has warned students to be “mindful of your behaviour and conversations” in a “gentle reminder” to promote respect and courtesy.
An email sent at the beginning of this term told students that the department is “committed to promoting an environment where everyone is treated …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Vice-chancellor of Bath University asked to leave immediately amid ongoing pay row</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-vice-chancellor-of-bath-university-asked-to-leave-immediately-amid-ongoing-pay-row/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-vice-chancellor-of-bath-university-asked-to-leave-immediately-amid-ongoing-pay-row/</guid>
        <description>The vice-chancellor of Bath University is facing pressure to leave immediately following a controversy over high pay.
Dame Glynis Breakwell made £471,000 in the year up to April 2017, and had received thousands of pounds in benefits in kind, when she announced her retirement last November. She …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jo Johnson out as universities minister in cabinet reshuffle</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-jo-johnson-out-as-universities-minister-in-cabinet-reshuffle/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-jo-johnson-out-as-universities-minister-in-cabinet-reshuffle/</guid>
        <description>A new universities minister has been named in Theresa May’s cabinet reshuffle. Former prisons minister Sam Gyimah takes over from Jo Johnson, who has been moved to the Department for Transport (DfT). Johnson has faced pressure in recent weeks over the appointment of Toby Young to the board of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Theresa, what’s good? Our round up of the best (and worst) of what happened this year in politics</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-theresa-what-s-good-our-round-up-of-the-best-and-worst-of-what-happened-this-year-in-politics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-theresa-what-s-good-our-round-up-of-the-best-and-worst-of-what-happened-this-year-in-politics/</guid>
        <description>For most of humankind, 2017 has been an awful year for politics. For satirists and political commentators, it has been an absolute gift. Here are some of the best bits.
“Easiest [negotiations] in history” – Liam Fox, international trade secretary (Brexit)
Nine months have passed since Article 50 was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bath vice-chancellor steps down amid pay debate</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-bath-vice-chancellor-steps-down-amid-pay-debate/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-bath-vice-chancellor-steps-down-amid-pay-debate/</guid>
        <description>The vice-chancellor of Bath University will step down at the end of the academic year following concerns over her pay, but will continue to collect her salary until 2019.
Dame Glynis Breakwell is the highest-paid vice-chancellor in the country, earning £468,000 a year, compared to a sector average …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>EU Imperial staff leaving following Brexit decision</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-eu-imperial-staff-leaving-following-brexit-decision/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-eu-imperial-staff-leaving-following-brexit-decision/</guid>
        <description>Imperial staff from the EU have begun leaving following last year’s Brexit referendum.
Speaking to the Evening Standard, Imperial president Alice Gast said she was “very concerned” about the uncertainties surrounding Brexit negotiations, which have caused some Imperial staff who had moved to the UK …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New laws introduced to regulate drones</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-new-laws-introduced-to-regulate-drones/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-new-laws-introduced-to-regulate-drones/</guid>
        <description>A crackdown on drones will come into force next year following repeated near misses with aircraft.
The draft Drone Bill, due to be published in spring, will require drone operators to register a flight plan via an app, which will determine if the drone can be used “safely and legally”. Police will …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial praised for its approach to cheating</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-imperial-praised-for-its-approach-to-cheating/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-imperial-praised-for-its-approach-to-cheating/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London has been praised for its approach to cheating, amid rising concerns of plagiarism.
Writing for the Times Higher Education, barrister and Imperial alumnus Dr Daniel Sokol lamented the low standard of proof required to convict students of cheating. A guide by the Quality …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students support TEF but fear medal system will have negative impact on graduate prospects</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-students-support-tef-but-fear-medal-system-will-have-negative-impact-on-graduate-prospects/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-students-support-tef-but-fear-medal-system-will-have-negative-impact-on-graduate-prospects/</guid>
        <description>Students largely agree with the principle of the Teaching Excellence Framework (TEF) but are less convinced about the way it is currently implemented, according to a survey commissioned by a consortium of student unions, including Imperial College Union.
The Teaching excellence: the student …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Metric crowds prompt fear of serious harm</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-metric-crowds-prompt-fear-of-serious-harm/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-metric-crowds-prompt-fear-of-serious-harm/</guid>
        <description>Safety concerns have been raised in relation to the number of people attending Metric at peak times. Students have reported annoyance over a lack of crowd control and properly trained staff, particularly at special events and ACC nights. The Union, however, disputes claims that Metric is unsafe.
A …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Charity Week event cancelled after speaker accused of rape</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-imperial-charity-week-event-cancelled-after-speaker-accused-of-rape/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-imperial-charity-week-event-cancelled-after-speaker-accused-of-rape/</guid>
        <description>A lecture hosted as part of Imperial College’s charity week has been postponed after the speaker was accused of rape.
Oxford Professor Tariq Ramadan was billed to appear in a talk entitled ‘What could the future hold for Islam in Europe?’ on Monday, 24th of October. However, it was indefinitely …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pro-Kurdish protesters gather outside Iraqi Embassy</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-pro-kurdish-protesters-gather-outside-iraqi-embassy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-pro-kurdish-protesters-gather-outside-iraqi-embassy/</guid>
        <description>Protesters gathered outside the Iraqi embassy on Queen’s Gate earlier this week in reaction to Iraq’s seizure of the city of Kirkuk from Kurdish forces who had occupied it for the past three years.
Last Monday, 18th October, a group of demonstrators took to the speech, carrying Kurdish flags and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union launches survey of College’s Campus Services</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-union-launches-survey-of-college-s-campus-services/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-union-launches-survey-of-college-s-campus-services/</guid>
        <description>A survey of campus services has been launched by Imperial College Union following “significant changes” to Imperial’s catering and dining facilities. The move comes more than two months after the College’s Campus Services implemented changes without consulting staff or students. The changes are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Enquiries continue into Exhibition Road car crash</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-14-enquiries-continue-into-exhibition-road-car-crash/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-14-enquiries-continue-into-exhibition-road-car-crash/</guid>
        <description>Enquiries continue into the road traffic collision on Exhibition Road on Saturday, 7th of October. A 47-year-old man arrested at the scene on suspicion of dangerous driving was released under investigation the following day.
Eleven people were injured when a black Toyota Prius minicab mounted the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tories introduce plans for tuition fee freeze</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-tories-introduce-plans-for-tuition-fee-freeze/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-tories-introduce-plans-for-tuition-fee-freeze/</guid>
        <description>Theresa May has announced that tuition fees will be frozen at a maximum of £9,250 a year until 2019. The government will also raise the threshold at which loans must be paid back to £25,000. Announced at the Conservative party conference in Manchester, the pledges are part of an £11 billion drive to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial overtakes Durham to claim fourth place in this year’s Good University Guide</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-imperial-overtakes-durham-to-claim-fourth-place-in-this-year-s-good-university-guide/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-imperial-overtakes-durham-to-claim-fourth-place-in-this-year-s-good-university-guide/</guid>
        <description>mperial has been ranked fourth in The Times and Sunday Times Good University Guide 2018. This sees the College rise one place after overtaking Durham.
An analysis published by Imperial cites improvements in teaching quality and student experience as the main reasons for its rise in the rankings. Out …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Waiting for Godot has its definitive homecoming at the Arts Theatre
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-12-waiting-for-godot-has-its-definitive-homecoming-at-the-arts-theatre/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 09:25:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-12-waiting-for-godot-has-its-definitive-homecoming-at-the-arts-theatre/</guid>
        <description>Billed as its “definitive homecoming” Samuel Beckett’s tragicomedy Waiting for Godot returns to the Arts Theatre after the first English-language production premiered there in 1955.
Nick Devlin and Patrick O’Donnell are delightfully childish and mercurial as vagabonds Didi and Gogo, who seem to love …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nutt talks at Psychedelics Studies Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-nutt-talks-at-psychedelics-studies-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:50:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-nutt-talks-at-psychedelics-studies-imperial/</guid>
        <description>The psychedelic renaissance is here. Psychedelic Studies Imperial launched their venture last Wednesday with a mind-expanding talk by Professor David Nutt.
Despite initially being told that psychedelics was too niche a subject to form a society around, the PSI has sprung into life with the aim of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Party candidates come to Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-party-candidates-come-to-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:50:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-party-candidates-come-to-imperial/</guid>
        <description>A hustings of local parliamentary candidates was held yesterday in Blackett which saw Victoria Borwick (Conservatives), Cllr Alan De’Ath (Labour), Bridget Fox (LibDems), Richard Braine (UKIP), and finally Bill Cashmore (Green), engaging in a debate on Education, Public Health and Brexit.
Borwick, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Atomic funding pours into Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-atomic-funding-pours-into-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:49:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-atomic-funding-pours-into-imperial/</guid>
        <description>The Atomic Weapons Establishment (AWE) has long been responsible for the UK’s nuclear deterrence programme. In addition to providing the nuclear warheads for each of the Vanguard submarines that make up Trident, the AWE contributes significant amounts to the coffers of Imperial.
Imperial is one of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Physics flops in league tables
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-physics-flops-in-league-tables/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 12:28:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-physics-flops-in-league-tables/</guid>
        <description>Imperial is regularly declared one of the best universities in the world. The latest Guardian university league tables reaffirms this, placing us in joint 6th place overall. Imperial ranked top in Earth and Marine Sciences, Civil Engineering, Electronic and Electrical Engineering, and Engineering …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Migrant students gain financial aid
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-19-migrant-students-gain-financial-aid/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 14:58:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-19-migrant-students-gain-financial-aid/</guid>
        <description>An interesting paper at this week’s Union Council meeting addressed the issues faced by asylum-seekers and migrants trying to access higher education in London.
To study at a UK university, asylum-seekers and migrants with Discretionary Leave to Remain (DLR) or Limited Leave to Remain (LLR) must pay …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fossil fuel divestment finally on the table
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-19-fossil-fuel-divestment-finally-on-the-table/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 14:57:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-19-fossil-fuel-divestment-finally-on-the-table/</guid>
        <description>Following the resurrection of the Imperial divestment campaign, a paper brought to this week’s Union Council meeting set out proposals for the future of fossil fuels at Imperial.
The Divest Imperial Council Paper recognises that the majority of currently available fossil fuels must not be used if we …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lost Gem Rediscovered | The Wipers Times
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-lost-gem-rediscovered-the-wipers-times/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 16:19:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-lost-gem-rediscovered-the-wipers-times/</guid>
        <description>They are just a gang of back-chat comedians deliberately undermining morale with this impertinent, unpatriotic rag.” So goes Lieutenant Colonel Howfield’s complaint about The Wipers Times, a satirical trench newspaper brought to life in the Arts Theatre thanks to Ian Hislop and Nick Newman.
James …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your new sabbs are here
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-your-new-sabbs-are-here/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 13:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-your-new-sabbs-are-here/</guid>
        <description>Following a 36.79% turnout (down a bit from last year but still the third-highest in the country according to the Union website), elections are finally over and winners have been announced. As previously reported, out of the 21 candidates standing for sabbatical positions, only 13 were ever serious …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Higher Education faces depression epidemic
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-higher-education-faces-depression-epidemic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 13:23:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-higher-education-faces-depression-epidemic/</guid>
        <description>Recent years show an alarming trend amongst students. Rising rates of mental illness show little sign of slowing. In the past ten years, suicide rates have almost doubled. In York, up to 50% of ambulance call-outs to the university were for self-harm or suicide attempts. This is a far from localised …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Greens speak up for suspended students
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-greens-speak-up-for-suspended-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 13:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-greens-speak-up-for-suspended-students/</guid>
        <description>Last week we reported on the suspension and arrests of several students from King’s College London following their involvement in a campaign to persuade KCL to divest from fossil fuels. Since then, several members of the Green Party have written to King’s to show their support for the students. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fuck Valentine’s Day | Asexual and aromantic
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-fuck-valentines-day-asexual-and-aromantic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 14:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-fuck-valentines-day-asexual-and-aromantic/</guid>
        <description>The first two weeks in February are an infernal nightmare of constant bombardment with advertisements for jewellery, chocolates, and lingerie – all for that ‘special someone’. People in relationships presumably don’t mind. Single people complain incessantly about it. For aromantics however, …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
