<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/oa1612/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/oa1612/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Engineering the Hyperloop prototype
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-engineering-the-hyperloop-prototype/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 14:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Osama Awara,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-engineering-the-hyperloop-prototype/</guid>
        <description>It was in 2012 that the restless entrepreneur Elon Musk first announced his idea for a high speed transport system – the Hyperloop. Described by the magnate as ‘a cross between a Concorde, a railgun and an air hockey-table,’ this next-generation train system aims to transport people at speeds of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The art of war for faceless people
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-the-art-of-war-for-faceless-people/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 18:09:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Osama Awara,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-the-art-of-war-for-faceless-people/</guid>
        <description>The previous few weeks have seen a surge in cyber warfare like no other. From the Sony Pictures hacking over The Interview – a satire film depicting the assassination attempt of Kim Jong-Un, to the ISIS hacking of US Central Command Twitter account. The hacktivist group Anonymous have vowed to take …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Microsoft hope 3 is the magic number
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-microsoft-hope-3-is-the-magic-number/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 22:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Osama Awara,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-microsoft-hope-3-is-the-magic-number/</guid>
        <description>The third generation of Windows tablets, or Lablets as I like to call them, have been released by Microsoft. They claim that the Surface Pro 3 is not only a tablet, but a laptop as well, potentially replacing both of those devices in your home. After owning one for several weeks, I can honestly back …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Future of Social Media
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-future-of-social-media/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 03:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Osama Awara,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-future-of-social-media/</guid>
        <description>When you hear the term social media, what comes to mind? Facebook? Twitter? Or perhaps even that embarrassing video you were tagged in by your friends last night. Of the modern age of technology, social media has perhaps had the most profound effect on our lives, reaching out with its addictive grip …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Future of Social Media
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-19-future-of-social-media/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 21:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Osama Awara,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-19-future-of-social-media/</guid>
        <description>When you hear the term social media what comes to mind? Facebook? Twitter? Or perhaps even that embarrassing video you were tagged in by your friends last night. Of the modern age of technology, social media has perhaps had the most profound effect on our lives, reaching out with its addictive grip …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Consumer Electronics Show
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-consumer-electronics-show/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 04:24:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Osama Awara,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-consumer-electronics-show/</guid>
        <description>The Consumer Electronics Show (CES) is an annual technology and consumer products show held every January in Las Vegas. Being the global stage that attracts next generation innovations and electronics, CES is the largest of its kind, showcasing over 3000 exhibitors from computer hardware …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tech for X-Mas
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-tech-for-x-mas/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 16:23:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Osama Awara,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-tech-for-x-mas/</guid>
        <description> Samsung KN55S9C OLED TV If you’ve ever thought that HD pictures were not enough, fear no more, the Samsung OLED TV that uses organic self-emitting pixels would blow your mind away this Christmas giving you the best quality, surpassing even the best LCD TVs. This TV doesn’t come cheap, expect to be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>5 Things Consoles are killing
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-27-5-things-consoles-are-killing/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 16:09:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Osama Awara,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-27-5-things-consoles-are-killing/</guid>
        <description> Many Potential PC Gamers The great thing about consoles is their price relative to gaming PC rigs. With the Xbox One currently at £430 and the PS4 standing at £80 less, it’s no wonder so many gamers flock to consoles instead. With the same amount of ‘console money’ you’d only manage to buy a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Ultimate Luxury Tech List
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-13-the-ultimate-luxury-tech-list/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2013 22:57:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Osama Awara,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-13-the-ultimate-luxury-tech-list/</guid>
        <description> Alienware laptops: If you ever imagined what a laptop in the future might look like, just take a look at these gaming laptops; the must-have gadget for any hard-core gamer. When you compare the specs of the Alienware to your average PC world or Curry’s laptops, it is light-years ahead. Carrying the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>10 things the internet has slaughtered
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-30-10-things-the-internet-has-slaughtered/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 16:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Osama Awara,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-30-10-things-the-internet-has-slaughtered/</guid>
        <description> 1. Movie Stores Long gone are the days of popping in to your local Blockbusters and buying that VHS tape or DVD that had you sorted for the night. With the boom of wireless internet from your Ming Dynasty era dial-up connection, streaming movies/shows online has never been quicker or easier. With …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cyber black market is no more
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-cyber-black-market-is-no-more/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 00:59:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Osama Awara,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-cyber-black-market-is-no-more/</guid>
        <description>Known and loved by its many users and advocates as the Silk Road Marketplace, this underground website dubbed as the ‘amazon.com’ and ‘e-bay’ of illegal drugs has officially been shut down by the FBI. Seizing what is believed to be $3.6 million dollars in bitcoins, a small fraction of their $80 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NSA: Peeling the skin off TOR users
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-16-nsa-peeling-the-skin-off-tor-users/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 14:00:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Osama Awara,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-16-nsa-peeling-the-skin-off-tor-users/</guid>
        <description>The NSA known for its privacy breaching of internet users across the globe has been found ‘peeling’ the encryption that Tor provides for its users’ information sent online, in order to gain access to sensitive information. Tor is a piece of software, ironically funded by the US government, which …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>3-D Printers take off!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-3-d-printers-take-off/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 19:38:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Osama Awara,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-3-d-printers-take-off/</guid>
        <description>Launching a rocket into space is in itself a tricky business; well after all it is rocket science! Being able to repair one or a space station for that matter is a different ball game altogether. NASA has plans to launch their very own 3-D printer by next year, and for those of you who aren’t …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
