<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/abhijaysood/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/abhijaysood/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>ICBC Reflect on Mental Health and Spreading Awareness in the Rowing Community</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-icbc-reflect-mental-health-spreading-awareness-rowing-community/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-icbc-reflect-mental-health-spreading-awareness-rowing-community/</guid>
        <description>Mental health in sport is very often overlooked. Athletes are often perceived to be thick-skinned, resilient, and independent; looks can be deceiving. The thoughts, feelings, and emotions that navigate in that space between their ears are no different from that of any other person.
We are equally …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your Union is Standing Firm</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-your-union-standing-firm/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-your-union-standing-firm/</guid>
        <description>There’s no doubt that this has been a tricky term for the Union. Our most senior member of staff is stepping down, the kitchens are closed, and student officers, in particular the deputy presidents, have had to work overtime to compensate for understaffing in the office.
Despite this, the Union is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“If you dare to struggle, you dare to win...”</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-dare-to-struggle-dare-to-win/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-dare-to-struggle-dare-to-win/</guid>
        <description>Before dawn on December 4th, 1969, Fred Hampton was murdered in his bed. He was killed in a police raid with the assent of local law enforcement, the state government’s prosecutor’s office, and the FBI. He was 21 years old.
Hampton was a member of the Black Panther Party. Established in 1966, the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where is the line?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-where-is-the-line/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-where-is-the-line/</guid>
        <description>With only a week’s notice, College has told us they’re shutting the pub menu food service in h-bar. This is the latest in a long line of cuts: they’ve hiked up the fee at Ethos, they came after the SCR breakfast and the pool at St. Mary’s, and they’ve raised the price of food on campus and rent in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Trust your Trustees?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-trust-your-trustees/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-trust-your-trustees/</guid>
        <description>One month, and one more record-breaking election, has already passed here at Imperial. Last week, new student reps were elected in every department, and though turnout figures are certainly worth celebrating, today I want to talk about what comes next.
Every day decisions are made in our name that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get Involved!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-get-involved/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-get-involved/</guid>
        <description>I’m sure you’ve heard this enough by now but, welcome! This is a difficult university to get into, and you’ve done tremendously well getting this far.
There are many benefits to studying at Imperial: it’s a rich, prestigious London university with a strong research culture and some of the world’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Changing times...</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-changing-times/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-changing-times/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College isn’t the place it used to be. The student body is becoming less inward focussed, less tolerant of poor decision making on the part of the university, and less dismissive of things beyond the four walls of their degrees. We have a way to go yet, but the culture at our university is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students need to support the strikes – here’s what you can do to help</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-students-need-to-support-the-strikes-here-s-what-you-can-do-to-help/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lloyd T James,Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-students-need-to-support-the-strikes-here-s-what-you-can-do-to-help/</guid>
        <description>After two months of failed negotiations, with university management proposing huge cuts to pensions, university staff will be taking the only action available to them: striking. The staff walkout will begin next Thursday, February 22nd, and will escalate over a four-week period.
You might be worried …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Politics takes on the Autumn Budget</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-felix-politics-takes-on-the-autumn-budget/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-felix-politics-takes-on-the-autumn-budget/</guid>
        <description>This Wednesday, the Autumn Budget was delivered by the Chancellor of the Exchequer, Philip Hammond. It entails details about government spending and borrowing, and related policies, in advance of the next financial year. This sort of thing sounds horrendously dull, but it’s important to appreciate …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tuition fees are completely nonsensical: it’s time we scrapped them, for good</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-tuition-fees-are-completely-nonsensical-it-s-time-we-scrapped-them-for-good/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-tuition-fees-are-completely-nonsensical-it-s-time-we-scrapped-them-for-good/</guid>
        <description>There is no more obvious hot-button issue for UK students at the moment than tuition fees. Their trebling in the past few years was met with a wave of student anger, and Labour’s position at the last election – abolishing fees, though not cancelling past debt – doubtless helped them curry favour …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why I’m voting Labour
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-why-im-voting-labour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 14:16:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-why-im-voting-labour/</guid>
        <description>Soft on security, denying the deficit, and incapable of addressing concerns over immigration. These sound like the sort of accusations the Conservatives levelled at the last Labour government not too long ago, and yet after seven years in government, these are all areas in which the Conservative …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
