<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/markaduol/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/markaduol/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Film’s guide to the Oscars – who will win, who should win, and who’ve been left out in the cold</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-felix-film-s-guide-to-the-oscars-who-will-win-who-should-win-and-who-ve-been-left-out-in-the-cold/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Ashley Luckyram,Mark Aduol,Mikhail Demtchenko,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-felix-film-s-guide-to-the-oscars-who-will-win-who-should-win-and-who-ve-been-left-out-in-the-cold/</guid>
        <description>Oscars season is upon as! And, as is traditional, Felix are here to give you a rundown of what will win on the night, as well as what should win, and who didn&amp;rsquo;t even get a nomination:
 Best Picture
 It’s been a complicated awards season. Call Me by Your Name started out in the lead when it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Diversity at the Oscars – how far have we come?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-diversity-at-the-oscars-how-far-have-we-come/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark Aduol,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-diversity-at-the-oscars-how-far-have-we-come/</guid>
        <description>Before 1962, Hollywood didn’t make many films about race. This made some moviegoers unhappy. So, they put down their popcorn, picked up their picket signs and marched over to Hollywood Boulevard demanding that film studio executives increase the racial diversity of characters in their films. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mudbound – A sweeping epic that plays out like an intricate character study </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-mudbound-a-sweeping-epic-that-plays-out-like-an-intricate-character-study/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark Aduol,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-mudbound-a-sweeping-epic-that-plays-out-like-an-intricate-character-study/</guid>
        <description>Look out at the world and you’ll notice all the things that set you apart from everyone else; the characteristics that make you – and everyone else – unique and different. Mudbound however, is a reminder of what we all share – the human struggle to take control of our lives and make something out of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First They Killed My Father: Angelina Jolie’s first directorial triumph</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-first-they-killed-my-father-angelina-jolie-s-first-directorial-triumph/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark Aduol,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-first-they-killed-my-father-angelina-jolie-s-first-directorial-triumph/</guid>
        <description>First They Killed My Father, subtitled A Daughter of Cambodia Remembers, tells the story of Cambodian author Loung Ung and her battle to stay alive under the brutal regime of the Khmer Rouge. Most films that deal with war often tend to hover around a particular incident during the conflict. Whether …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Film’s Summer 2017 cinema round-up</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-felix-film-s-summer-2017-cinema-round-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark Aduol,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-felix-film-s-summer-2017-cinema-round-up/</guid>
        <description>Depending on who you are, the summer movie season was either a blessing or a disaster. For film studio executives, it was unquestionably dismal. There was little comfort in watching each new release miss its box office targets. On Labour Day Weekend – the long summer weekend in the United States …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
