<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ko407/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ko407/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The decline of British bee power
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-25-the-decline-of-british-bee-power/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 18:42:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Oakes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-25-the-decline-of-british-bee-power/</guid>
        <description>Pesticides may be the bees knees when it comes to protecting crops, but researchers from the UK and France have shown that exposure to one common pesticide leads to a dramatic loss to the number of queen bees, and another pesticide affects foragers’ ability to find their way back to the hive. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s raining methane
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-its-raining-methane/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 21:56:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Oakes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-its-raining-methane/</guid>
        <description>Scientists have developed the most advanced model yet of the weather system on Titan, one of Saturn’s moons and the only place in the solar system other than Earth that harbours lakes.
Instead of water, Titan’s lakes are filled with methane, a molecule made of one carbon atom and four hydrogen ones. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let it snow, let it snow...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-let-it-snow-let-it-snow/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 20:38:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Oakes,Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-let-it-snow-let-it-snow/</guid>
        <description>Snowflakes start out life as small particles of dust in a high up cloud. Water freezes around the dust particles, forming tiny ice crystals. At first, the ice crystals grow slowly, developing flat sides known as facets. At this stage they are hexagonal prisms, with eight sides or facets – two shaped …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dreaming of another world
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-dreaming-of-another-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 19:35:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Oakes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-dreaming-of-another-world/</guid>
        <description>Have you ever woken up the day after a night out and mentally recoiled in horror as you remember embarrassing things that you said or did under the influence of alcohol? Well, researchers at the University of California, Berkeley, have discovered a way to take the edge off those painful memories — …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Neutrinos still faster-than-light?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-neutrinos-still-faster-than-light/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 20:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Oakes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-neutrinos-still-faster-than-light/</guid>
        <description>In September, physicists working on the Opera experiment announced that they had observed some subatomic particles called neutrinos travelling faster than the speed of light. The neutrinos in question undertook a journey from CERN in Geneva, through the Earth, and finally ended up at the Gran Sasso …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Women in Science
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-4-women-in-science/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 09:38:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Oakes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-4-women-in-science/</guid>
        <description>In his Commemoration Day address this year, the Rector, Sir Keith O’Nions, recalled a conversation he had with an alumnus of Imperial. The alumnus, who graduated in 1966, told him that in her time here only 180 of the 3500 students were women. Sir Keith told those of us gathered at the Royal Albert …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Aboriginal Australian genome sequenced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-aboriginal-australian-genome-sequenced/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 09:54:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Oakes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-aboriginal-australian-genome-sequenced/</guid>
        <description>An 100-year-old lock of hair has helped scientists to unravel the movements of early humans on their journey to Australia. Scientists have obtained a genomic sequence from the hair, donated in the early 20th century by a man who was an Aboriginal Australian.
The genome reveals that, while we knew …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Distant stardust found
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-distant-stardust-found/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 09:31:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Oakes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-distant-stardust-found/</guid>
        <description>In early October this year, there were 687 confirmed discoveries of planets outside our solar system. This number is growing almost daily and as it increases we can begin to dig deeper into the details of these planets, known as exoplanets because of their “extrasolar” nature, and explore their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>While you were away...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-9-30-while-you-were-away/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2011 11:02:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Oakes,Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-9-30-while-you-were-away/</guid>
        <description>While you’ve been busy travelling the world, waiting for term to start, the staff at Imperial have been pushing the boundaries of human knowledge. The keen students amongst you may be aware of what headlines Imperial has been making over the last few months. But for those of you whose New Scientist …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Collaborations clash at Tevatron
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-collaborations-clash-at-tevatron/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 20:04:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Oakes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-collaborations-clash-at-tevatron/</guid>
        <description>Earlier this year, the Collider Detector at Fermilab (CDF) collaboration tentatively put forward new results suggesting that they had observed a new, unpredicted particle. A month later they published more results that seemed to reinforce the earlier data. But last week the DZero collaboration, also …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Electron sends scientists round in circles
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-electron-sends-scientists-round-in-circles/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 19:16:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Oakes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-electron-sends-scientists-round-in-circles/</guid>
        <description>Electrons are almost perfect spheres, new research published in Nature this week has reported. Scientists here at Imperial have made the most accurate measurement yet of the size of an electron, and discovered that it is only 0.000000000000000000000000001 cm away from being perfectly round. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Scientific foundations of Tōhoku quake
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-scientific-foundations-of-thoku-quake/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 20:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thea Cunningham,Charles Harvey,Kelly Oakes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-scientific-foundations-of-thoku-quake/</guid>
        <description>Like all large earthquakes, the Japanese quake occurred in what is known as a subduction zone. In these zones – which are common in the Pacific – large slabs of solid rock called tectonic plates move towards each other. When they collide, the less dense plate will ride over the denser plate, which …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Floods, fireballs and chaos?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-floods-fireballs-and-chaos/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 19:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Oakes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-floods-fireballs-and-chaos/</guid>
        <description>Of the four billion species that have existed on the Earth, only 1% are still around today. Many of these forgotten creatures became extinct gradually, slowly making way for new ones to evolve and take their place. However, sometimes the rate of extinction can increase so much that more than three …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Probing the depths
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-probing-the-depths/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 16:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Oakes,Charles Harvey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-probing-the-depths/</guid>
        <description>Ever since man has been able to think of clichés, he has dreamed of heading to the stars. The staff and students at Imperial College London are no exception, and have been involved in numerous missions to explore our solar system. Here, we take a look at just some of the missions Imperial is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Black holes cut down to size
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-black-holes-cut-down-to-size/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 20:12:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Oakes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-black-holes-cut-down-to-size/</guid>
        <description>You might not be able to tell from wherever you are reading this, but black holes in the distant universe just shrunk down to as little as a tenth of their previous size. This is not some cosmic disappearing act; a new analysis of supermassive black holes at the centres of active galactic nuclei has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The state of academic blogging at Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-the-state-of-academic-blogging-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 20:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Oakes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-the-state-of-academic-blogging-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Imperial&amp;rsquo;s David Robertson might be up for a Bloggie, but what about the rest of us? It might not be something you&amp;rsquo;ve thought about, but science blogging is an activity that could be worth considering. And with funding tighter than ever, it might be time to start fleshing out that CV and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In a galaxy far, far away...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-in-a-galaxy-far-far-away/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 19:59:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Oakes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-in-a-galaxy-far-far-away/</guid>
        <description>There haven’t always been stars and galaxies in the universe, and the time when they began to form — known as the reionisation epoch — is the subject of much interest in astrophysics. A paper published in Nature last week details a discovery that could tell us more about this mysterious time.
In the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Superfast genome sequencing on a chip
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-superfast-genome-sequencing-on-a-chip/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 18:50:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Oakes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-superfast-genome-sequencing-on-a-chip/</guid>
        <description>The first step on a path that could lead to the sequencing of an entire genome in minutes has been developed by chemists at Imperial College London. A paper describing the prototype technology was published last month in the journal Nano Letters.
This innovation also means sequencing will become …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Huge leap forward in quantum computing
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-huge-leap-forward-in-quantum-computing/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 20:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Oakes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-huge-leap-forward-in-quantum-computing/</guid>
        <description>Do you think you could make sense of this sentence if every fourth word was missing? How about trying to hold a conversation when you can only hear three quarters of what the other person is saying? Cutting out a fraction of the information being transferred in a given situation may make life …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
