<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/oh106/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/oh106/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Avoid haemorrhoids... and make magazines
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-avoid-haemorrhoids-and-make-magazines/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 21:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Omar Hafeez-Bore,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-avoid-haemorrhoids-and-make-magazines/</guid>
        <description>I had a health scare the other day. In an otherwise innocuous tutorial about job applications, a renowned doctor casually joked that we shouldn’t spend too long on the toilet for fear of haemorrhoids. Everyone laughed. I froze.
Woah woah woah, hang on a sec (I said in my head) – has this been …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The future of gaming...?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-the-future-of-gaming/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 21:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Cook,Omar Hafeez-Bore,Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-the-future-of-gaming/</guid>
        <description>Interested in how gaming got to where it is today? See our companion article here!
Michael Cook
It’s hard to look at where we came from and try to assess where we might be in even a few years time. How impossible something like OnLive might have seemed before the Internet was even a possibility …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gaming through the ages: ‘When this baby reaches 88 miles per hour...’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-gaming-through-the-ages-when-this-baby-reaches-88-miles-per-hour/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 20:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Omar Hafeez-Bore,Michael Cook,Simon Worthington,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-gaming-through-the-ages-when-this-baby-reaches-88-miles-per-hour/</guid>
        <description>Interested in what our writers think of the future of gaming? See the companion article here!
Felix Issue 500 (1978) - Michael Cook
It’s June 1978, and Felix is celebrating its 500th issue being printed. Meanwhile, on the other side of the world, Japanese arcades are playing host to a videogame that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gaming in Reverse - Final Fantasy IX
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-gaming-in-reverse-final-fantasy-ix/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 10:26:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Omar Hafeez-Bore,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-gaming-in-reverse-final-fantasy-ix/</guid>
        <description>See last week&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Gaming in Reverse&amp;rsquo; here!
Welcome to Gaming in Reverse, where every week we use The Power of Writing to reverse time on a game series or remake. We’re flipping history to pretend the newest games are the oldest games! Can we prove that older is actually sometimes …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What does it matter what I learnt here?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-14-what-does-it-matter-what-i-learnt-here/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 00:15:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Omar Hafeez-Bore,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-14-what-does-it-matter-what-i-learnt-here/</guid>
        <description>It’s my 6th year here and my brain has been permanently disfigured, forever transformed by all that Science. It’s my 6th year of student discounts. My 6th year of Tuna-pasta dinners. My 6th year of pretending that I know stuff, and my 6th year of exam-period all-nighters because I don’t.
It’ll also …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gaming in reverse - Quake
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-gaming-in-reverse-quake/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 22:31:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Omar Hafeez-Bore,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-gaming-in-reverse-quake/</guid>
        <description>So here’s my plan, to get my own back on the remakes. By actually going back. As in, back-WARDS in time! Yes, I’m going to use the power of artistic licence to reverse time, and see what pixelated gems of gaming goodness have been lost along the way.
What has pushed me to this drastic plan of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Try Chopstix
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-12-try-chopstix/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 16:14:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Omar Hafeez-Bore,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-12-try-chopstix/</guid>
        <description>Be honest now. You love this exam period. It’s the ultimate trump card, a super-charged get-out-of-anything free excuse accepted by everyone. Exercise? Can’t, exams. Important favours? Can’t, exams. Washing? Can’t, exams.
But the best guilty self-persuasion is a culinary one. Spending time cooking …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are video games a waste of time?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-are-video-games-a-waste-of-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 19:05:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Omar Hafeez-Bore,Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-are-video-games-a-waste-of-time/</guid>
        <description>I guess so – Laurence Pope
This was always going to be a difficult piece to write, since the answer to the above question could be summed up succinctly in a single syllable – yes. Unfortunately, my editor isn’t particularly happy with one word articles, so I suppose I’d better make something out of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>From the Midlands back to Mirpur
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-18-from-the-midlands-back-to-mirpur/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 06:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kahfeel Hussain,Omar Hafeez-Bore,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-18-from-the-midlands-back-to-mirpur/</guid>
        <description>_Read part one &amp;ldquo;From Mirpur to the Midlands&amp;rdquo; _
People grow roots slowly; it happens unseen, and unknown. Certainly they were hidden from the Mirpuri men who came here 40 years ago, intending to spend some years working and sending money back from the verdant land of Valaid, of England. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Nandos Health Service
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-the-nandos-health-service/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 20:46:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Omar Hafeez-Bore,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-the-nandos-health-service/</guid>
        <description>Everyone seems to love Nandos. This makes actually writing about the place a health hazard, so violent would the backlash be from a negative piece. On the potential-trouble gauge used by Felix writers it is only topped by ‘Doing a Review of the Rector’s Face’. The situation for me is even more …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>From Mirpur to the Midlands
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-from-mirpur-to-the-midlands/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 19:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Omar Hafeez-Bore,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-from-mirpur-to-the-midlands/</guid>
        <description>For an international student from Pakistan, London is an explosion of new experiences. People form queues, food is bland, the police actually care (but families hardly seem to), dogs are walked, old men jog, commuters are silent, ‘smiling shop staff’ are rarely as described, and under the ground men …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s the Eye of the Tiger... but I don’t need it
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-its-the-eye-of-the-tiger-but-i-dont-need-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 20:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Omar Hafeez-Bore,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-its-the-eye-of-the-tiger-but-i-dont-need-it/</guid>
        <description>Is Survivor’s 80s classic ‘Eye of the Tiger’ the sweatiest song of all time? Whilst Elvis can take credit for millions of broken teenage hearts, and Barry White for millions of unplanned children, Survivor can take pride in being responsible for a sea of sweat lost by inspired gym-goers since Rocky …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Too much of Lara Croft’s bum!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-too-much-of-lara-crofts-bum/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 20:27:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Omar Hafeez-Bore,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-too-much-of-lara-crofts-bum/</guid>
        <description>Now I don’t usually start off by focusing on Lara Croft’s buttocks (who does?), but I’ve seen an awful lot of them lately and feel the need to confess why: I changed the controls I used in Tomb Raider Anniversary. And now I’m worried, because somehow I changed everything else too.
Hear me out: I did …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cut-price foods make me happy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-cut-price-foods-make-me-happy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 21:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Omar Hafeez-Bore,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-cut-price-foods-make-me-happy/</guid>
        <description>Christmas has now come and gone, hopefully fulfilling its promise as a time of goodwill to all people. According to A Christmas Carol, it is a time when rich people should have been kind and generous to the poor as, statistically at least; many of them are people too!
But social contact and friendly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>See life in a fresh gamma value
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-see-life-in-a-fresh-gamma-value/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 20:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Omar Hafeez-Bore,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-see-life-in-a-fresh-gamma-value/</guid>
        <description>Power: I’m not used to it. My last laptop was not a gaming powerhouse; it struggled to run even modest stuff smoothly. Like Solitaire, say. Or Word.
But like all electronic machines it eventually developed human emotions, and in a desperate act of self-gratification managed to tempt some local thug …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>VVVVVVictorious!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-26-vvvvvvictorious/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2010 14:56:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Omar Hafeez-Bore,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-26-vvvvvvictorious/</guid>
        <description>Am I the most successful person ever? Winston Churchill described success as “going from failure to failure without losing enthusiasm”. Well, I did that.
I did not give up dousing the flames of Fire Leo. I cried and cried until I could laugh in the face of Ninja Gaiden’s final boss. I can play …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Anyone up for a Snog? It’s juicy, saucy... it’s yoghurt.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-anyone-up-for-a-snog-its-juicy-saucy-its-yoghurt/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 21:23:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Omar Hafeez-Bore,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-anyone-up-for-a-snog-its-juicy-saucy-its-yoghurt/</guid>
        <description>Frozen yoghurt is a tasty cold treat, and London has caught the cold. It’s going round. If it was a warmer foodstuff they’d say it was spreading like wildfire. Instead, it’s spreading more like the Starbucks and Subways that now punctuate every high street. This is an ice-age moment after years of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial students make their last ‘Panto’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-imperial-students-make-their-last-panto/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 19:20:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Omar Hafeez-Bore,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-imperial-students-make-their-last-panto/</guid>
        <description>Over the last couple of years I have had the pleasure of putting on three little known, but well received, performances of what was codenamed ‘Panto’. In two weeks time we’ll stage the final Panto Show, laying the series to rest once and for all.
“Oh no you won’t!”
Oh yes, I will. Just one more, …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
