<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/felfood/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/felfood/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Chip(olatas) Off The Ol’ Block
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-17-chipolatas-off-the-ol-block/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 18:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Food,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-17-chipolatas-off-the-ol-block/</guid>
        <description>This Valentine’s Day, Felix pays homage to our own population with a closer look at the food that has become one of our running jokes/characteristics&amp;hellip;at our expense. Well if you can’t beat them, join them! And in true Hugh Fearnley-Whittingstall’s Three Good Things style - or well, thinly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Emergency hangover cures
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-emergency-hangover-cures/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 15:39:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Y K Chung,Felix Food,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-emergency-hangover-cures/</guid>
        <description> Need something quick? Beans on toast with a twist The classic beans on toast is an awesome hangover cure. Not only do the beans contain high protein, it also releases energy slowly, so you feel better for the day! If you want to increase your appetite at the same time, why not add a can of tinned …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Epic(ly broke) Meal Time - Instant Ramen
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-epicly-broke-meal-time-instant-ramen/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 23:25:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Food,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-epicly-broke-meal-time-instant-ramen/</guid>
        <description>This week – we get broke from eating out all the time during exams. SQUAWK being domestic gods or goddesses, we’re tired. And skint. We don’t got “YouTube money” to blow on real food like Harley and that lot – we need cash for the post-exam booze. So we buy cheap like SQUAWK instant ramen and pimp …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>VegSoc do Sushi
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-vegsoc-do-sushi/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 03:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Food,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-vegsoc-do-sushi/</guid>
        <description>Think vegetarian food is boring? Think again! VegSoc, Imperial’s Vegetarian Society was created five years ago to celebrate how amazing and diverse vegetarian cooking can be. We have regular events and always aim to do something unique, exciting and internationally inspired from hands-on vegan sushi …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flapjacks, pasta and meatballs in 1!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-flapjacks-pasta-and-meatballs-in-1/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 14:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Food,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-flapjacks-pasta-and-meatballs-in-1/</guid>
        <description> When you see me, you would probably guess that I like eating. And you couldn’t be more right! I was lucky enough that my food was cooked for me for most of my life. So when I was finally let loose in the kitchen, I have been going bonkers. Here is some of my favourite recipes that I have made. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Zombie Apocalypse Now
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-zombie-apocalypse-now/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 22:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Food,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-zombie-apocalypse-now/</guid>
        <description>When I first heard about the TV show The Walking Dead from my friends I couldn’t understand their immense excitement about it. On the question “what is it about?” I got the answer “the world is taken over by zombies and a few people are trying to survive”. Well, that didn’t do it for me. I mean, it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Trick or treat recipe - chocolate spiders
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-trick-or-treat-recipe-chocolate-spiders/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 02:52:24 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Food,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-trick-or-treat-recipe-chocolate-spiders/</guid>
        <description>Want to make some treats this year for Halloween? Try your hand at these frightfully delicious chocolate-covered peanut butter spiders. Your friends and family will be screaming with delight after they take their first bite.
Ingredients (for 50 spiders):
2 cups smooth peanut butter
1&amp;frasl;2 cup of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What to do with all that pumpkin post-Halloween
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-what-to-do-with-all-that-pumpkin-post-halloween/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 02:51:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Food,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-what-to-do-with-all-that-pumpkin-post-halloween/</guid>
        <description>Pumpkin Soup
Extremely easy and delicious! (Even if you don’t like pumpkin!)
Ingredients:
1 medium onion
1 leek
1 pumpkin (preferably onion squash) 2 tbsp olive oil
Salt and pepperto taste
Chopped chillies
Peel the pumpkin and chop it in small cubes. Chop the onion and leeks. Heat the olive oil in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The White Horse
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-the-white-horse/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:44:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Food,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-the-white-horse/</guid>
        <description>In the northern corner of Parson’s Green stands the long established Fulham favourite, The White Horse, known for its unpretentious seasonal menus, extensive drinks selection and reasonable prices. Its location makes this restaurant perfect for the large proportion of Imperial Students who live in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London Restaurant Festival showcases culinary diversity
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-london-restaurant-festival-showcases-culinary-diversity/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 13:08:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Food,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-london-restaurant-festival-showcases-culinary-diversity/</guid>
        <description>London Restaurant Festival celebrates the Capital’s restaurants and their diversity. For two weeks (October 3-17) visitors will be able to try things they wouldn’t otherwise, tickle their tasting pallet and taste extraordinary food prepared by all kinds of chefs experiencing the ultimate dining …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
