<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ls411/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ls411/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Totally shambolic policing tactics
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-totally-shambolic-policing-tactics/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 23:58:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Luke Sheldon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-totally-shambolic-policing-tactics/</guid>
        <description>As the first students paying £9,000 fees have started this term the fight against fees and cuts to education hit the streets again this Wednesday. Whilst the last National Union of Students (NUS) march two years ago saw the destruction of Tory HQ on Millbank, the fire that ignited from this and saw …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The world is warming quicker than we thought
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-the-world-is-warming-quicker-than-we-thought/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 21:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Luke Sheldon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-the-world-is-warming-quicker-than-we-thought/</guid>
        <description>Climate change is expected to be more severe than previously thought as the climate models, which record the greatest warming, are found to be more accurate according to a new study.
Scientists from the National Centre for Atmospheric Research in the US used observations of Tropical humidity in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Head-to-head: Welfare - Are the Coalition reforms fair?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-head-to-head-welfare-are-the-coalition-reforms-fair/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:19:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Luke Sheldon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-head-to-head-welfare-are-the-coalition-reforms-fair/</guid>
        <description>Yes
GH
For those of you fortunate enough to have read my last two forays into these hallowed pages, you will perhaps be aware that my articles have a certain propensity (apparently) of aligning themselves with the minority view: that, some might claim, of the so-called “1 percent”. This week, after …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Post exams party against austerity
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-post-exams-party-against-austerity/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 06:27:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Luke Sheldon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-post-exams-party-against-austerity/</guid>
        <description>The first twelve months of austerity saw Tory HQ get smashed up and students taking to the streets in their thousands against rising tuition fees. Town halls were occupied as the budgets detailing the severity of the cuts were passed, half a million people marched in London and hundreds of tax …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Student protests: one year on
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-student-protests-one-year-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 21:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Luke Sheldon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-student-protests-one-year-on/</guid>
        <description>On the student march last term, as 10,000 people protesting against the government’s Higher Education white paper trundled through a path laid out by 4,000 riot police, a chant rose up: “Lets go back to Millbank, Na-Na-Na-Na, Hey!” But what is the student movement now?
Is it merely nostalgia for a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Volunteering at Tesco
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-volunteering-at-tesco/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 21:08:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Luke Sheldon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-volunteering-at-tesco/</guid>
        <description>Work experience is something most of us did at school. It was unpaid, but it was two weeks long and we did not do the work of paid staff. Invariably we shadowed workers and got a chance to carry out a few of the tasks. This is far from the “work experience” the government have been championing this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Apathy leads to better group decisions
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-apathy-leads-to-better-group-decisions/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 22:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Luke Sheldon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-apathy-leads-to-better-group-decisions/</guid>
        <description>Every four or five years we go along to a ballot box, tick our preferred political party and defer all other decisions to the group that gains power. Most people probably believe this is the best way of running things. We may not even have much to say about education, economics or war, so how could …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Total policing” not like total football
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-total-policing-not-like-total-football/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 21:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Luke Sheldon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-total-policing-not-like-total-football/</guid>
        <description>After 12 hours of protest, beginning at 7 in the morning at Liverpool Street, the idea of protesters as lazy hippies has simply dissolved. They believe the mantra that the early anarchist gets the worm. We saw electricians, librarians, teachers, council workers and children line the pickets and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why I’m striking
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-why-im-striking/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 21:39:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Luke Sheldon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-why-im-striking/</guid>
        <description>“I will be striking on N30. It’s absolutely outrageous cutting pensions. I do feel ambivalent; to forfeit a wadge of money, when my wage is very low does worry me greatly, however, what they are doing is obscene. It is outrageous pensions are not protected, they’re not fantastic anyway. You work the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>November 30th: day of action
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-november-30th-day-of-action/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 21:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Luke Sheldon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-november-30th-day-of-action/</guid>
        <description>You may have heard news headlines describing the biggest strike in generations happening on 30th November, but perhaps thought little of it. What has striking got to do with students? Especially striking over pensions. Pensions seem ages away, we’re only just dealing with our students loans! The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Extreme weather set to increase
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-extreme-weather-set-to-increase/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 21:11:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Luke Sheldon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-extreme-weather-set-to-increase/</guid>
        <description>Last week the IPCC released the executive summary to their special report on extreme events and disasters that will be published in full in February next year. The review looked at extreme events in two ways, first considering how they have changed over the last 50 years and then looking at how …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Car Sick: Why we need to reclaim our streets
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-car-sick-why-we-need-to-reclaim-our-streets/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 21:37:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Luke Sheldon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-car-sick-why-we-need-to-reclaim-our-streets/</guid>
        <description>Our streets are currently being occupied by aggressive, murderous, polluting inhabitants: cars. They are effectively environmental squatters. Unfortunately, whereas the criminalisation of squatting, which was voted through the Commons the other week, will throw thousands of the most vulnerable in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Doth the lady protest too much?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-doth-the-lady-protest-too-much/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 20:24:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Luke Sheldon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-doth-the-lady-protest-too-much/</guid>
        <description>It’s that time of year again. The placards will be waved and students will rapidly get bored of chanting, “No ifs. No buts. No education cuts.” Two student demonstrations are planned for November, with the first happening on the Wednesday just gone. However, this year, the fight is against the rapid …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Privatisation of Universities
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-the-privatisation-of-universities/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 20:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Luke Sheldon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-the-privatisation-of-universities/</guid>
        <description>Even though neither of the two parties in power mentioned drastic transformation of our higher education system in their manifestos the white paper published this summer, ‘Higher Education: Putting students at the Heart of the System’, proposes this. The raising of tuition fees, which also held no …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dale Farm: a traveller&#39;s tale
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-dale-farm-a-travellers-tale/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 23:46:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Luke Sheldon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-dale-farm-a-travellers-tale/</guid>
        <description>Last week, the decade of legal battles over half of the traveller site at Dale Farm culminated into a physical one. Tony Balls, the Tory leader of Basildon council, has defended this eviction on the grounds of “fairness” – that the law must apply to everyone – which has been backed by his party’s …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
