<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/theofarah13/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/theofarah13/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>We are all Hadiza</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-we-are-all-hadiza/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theo Farah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-we-are-all-hadiza/</guid>
        <description>In the days following the successful appeal by the General Medical Council (GMC) to have Dr Hadiza Bawa-Garba struck off the medical register, meaning she is not able to return to practice for at least five years, a crowd-funding campaign has raised over £200, 000 to fund further legal counsel for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We’re all a bunch of boozy drug addicts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-were-all-a-bunch-of-boozy-drug-addicts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:34:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theo Farah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-were-all-a-bunch-of-boozy-drug-addicts/</guid>
        <description>Every single one of us has as some point been lectured about the dangers of cocaine, Adderall, and heroin. Take them once and it might not be long before you’re finding an excuse to take them again. Regardless of whether it’s the oh-so-good high or a few too many nights out one week, you can easily …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The National Wedding Show is decadent and depraved
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-the-national-wedding-show-is-decadent-and-depraved/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 17:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theo Farah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-the-national-wedding-show-is-decadent-and-depraved/</guid>
        <description>As I walked along Hammersmith Road to the convention centre, Kensington Olympia, a faltering bundle of nerves, I scanned my brain for excuses not to enter the palatial structure. Fortified by a cocktail of stimulants, I still felt lacking in brass for my foray behind enemy lines. Twenty-one and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tycho at Electric Brixton
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-tycho-at-electric-brixton/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 15:39:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theo Farah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-tycho-at-electric-brixton/</guid>
        <description>The venue’s facade was bright and fairly minimalist, with white walls and a simple entrance. Inside, we were surprised to hear techno pumping out of the solid sound system in front of us. I looked around, noting the royal blue walls decorated by gold baroque detailing; the interior felt both modern …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London’s new music scene
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-londons-new-music-scene/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 15:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theo Farah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-londons-new-music-scene/</guid>
        <description>Part of the allure of moving to London for music lovers is the incredible access to up and coming artists. Many times while living here, I’ve high-fived myself for gaining hipster points after discovering artists who’ve yet to break into the charts. Vanity aside, the ease with which Londoners can …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Musicians against Trump
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-musicians-against-trump/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 17:04:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theo Farah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-musicians-against-trump/</guid>
        <description>As the world reacts to Trump’s Muslim ban, amidst huge protests held across the globe, condemnation from the music industry has been rife.
Nicki Minaj, Bette Midler, and DJ Khaled are three of the many musicians to take to twitter to oppose Trump’s most controversial executive order so far, while …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Denial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-denial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 16:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Theo Farah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-denial/</guid>
        <description>In a political climate increasingly described with the neologism ‘post-factual’, director Mick Jackson’s latest film Denial is sharply relevant. Centering around the libel case of British Holocaust-denier David Irving against American historian Deborah Lipstadt – a case that was often referred to as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Silence
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-silence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Theo Farah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-silence/</guid>
        <description>Following on from the messy hedonism of The Wolf of Wall Street – a three hour orgy of casual violence, over-sexualisation, and easy profanity – it is clear that Martin Scorsese is searching for a kind of ‘mea culpa’ with Silence, a mix of asceticism, endurance, and proselytism. It’s a hard pill to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Time for a fresh approach to club drugs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-time-for-a-fresh-approach-to-club-drugs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 14:48:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theo Farah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-time-for-a-fresh-approach-to-club-drugs/</guid>
        <description>Last week it was announced that fabric would be reopening “soon”, along with an extensive new licensing agreement. Particularly salient for students in London is the new block on under 19s from entering on club nights and the lifetime bans for those found with drugs on them or attempting to purchase …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I, Olga Hepnarová
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-i-olga-hepnarov/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 14:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Theo Farah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-i-olga-hepnarov/</guid>
        <description>T he directorial debut from Czech directors Petr Kazda and Tomás Weinreb – I, Olga Hepnarová – takes its title from a line in the manifesto left behind by the last woman to be executed in Czechoslovakia. In 1973, at the age of 22, Hepnarová ran over a group of people with a truck, killing eight, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>fabric to reopen under strict drug control
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-fabric-to-reopen-under-strict-drug-control/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 13:19:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theo Farah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-fabric-to-reopen-under-strict-drug-control/</guid>
        <description>The iconic Farringdon nightclub, fabric, has announced it will reopen its doors, following a hearing at Highbury Corner Magistrate’s Court on Monday, the 21st of November. The club was closed in September after two 18-year-olds tragically died of drug-related causes at the venue this Summer. An …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where to get your post-fabric fix
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-where-to-get-your-post-fabric-fix/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 18:36:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theo Farah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-where-to-get-your-post-fabric-fix/</guid>
        <description> Corsica Studios Ranked an impressive 2nd on Resident Advisor’s list of top London clubs, it boasts impressive soundsystems and a friendly vibe,
conveniently situated only a couple of minutes walk from Elephant and Castle station. Run as a not-for-profit, it is an enterprise in sustaining arts and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix meets | Formation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-7-felix-meets-formation/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 17:37:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theo Farah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-7-felix-meets-formation/</guid>
        <description>felix catches up with Formation while they’re on tour with Jagwar Ma. Another notch on their belt after playing Glastonbury, Field Day and having their song Pleasure chosen for the FIFA 17 soundtrack. In the room are front-man Will Ritson, his twin brother Matt (synths), Jonny Tams (bass) and Kai …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Into the Inferno
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-into-the-inferno/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 15:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,Theo Farah,En Lai,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-into-the-inferno/</guid>
        <description>Violent. Destructive.Catastrophic. These may be the words you think of when encountering the word volcano. Werner Herzog, one of the world’s most influential directors, together with volcanologist Clive Oppenheimer, take you on a trip to the heart of the earth, with the question: are volcanoes all …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
