<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ff712/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ff712/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The Felix News round-up: some highlights from a year of news around campus</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-the-felix-news-round-up-some-highlights-from-a-year-of-news-around-campus/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-the-felix-news-round-up-some-highlights-from-a-year-of-news-around-campus/</guid>
        <description>This year Felix has been reporting on a wide range of news stories, from the UCU strikes hitting campuses across the UK, to the College removing cooked breakfasts from the SCR. Here&amp;rsquo;s our round-up of a year in news:
SCR remove cooked breakfast as campus services are cut
At the end of July last …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Art on the Underground: contemporary tube maps, iconic designs, and giant egg invaders…</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-15-art-on-the-underground-contemporary-tube-maps-iconic-designs-and-giant-egg-invaders/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-15-art-on-the-underground-contemporary-tube-maps-iconic-designs-and-giant-egg-invaders/</guid>
        <description>Regular users of Gloucester Road tube station may have noticed a rather surreal visitor cropping up last week. The disused rail platform, lying opposite the District and Circle line platforms, has been occupied by a dizzying array of eggs: eggs coming out of shower heads; eggs cracked open by nails; …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Death of Cardiff lecturer highlights teaching workload </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-death-of-cardiff-lecturer-highlights-teaching-workload/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-death-of-cardiff-lecturer-highlights-teaching-workload/</guid>
        <description>A lecturer at Cardiff University who fell to his death had been struggling with an increasing workload, an inquest heard last week.
Dr Malcolm Anderson, who was a lecturer in accounting at Cardiff University’s Business School, as well as a personal tutor, fell to his death on the morning of the 19th …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix recommends – reading for summer days</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-15-felix-recommends-reading-for-summer-days/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-15-felix-recommends-reading-for-summer-days/</guid>
        <description>Mrs Dalloway by Virginia Woolf
Virginia Woolf’s most well-known work crackles with a vibrant energy and zest. Set on a ‘Wednesday in mid-June’, it remains one of the best portrayals of London in the early summer, full of the vibrant optimism that characterises long days in the city. Taking place …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix recommends: top picks for a summer of culture</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-15-felix-recommends-top-picks-for-a-summer-of-culture/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-15-felix-recommends-top-picks-for-a-summer-of-culture/</guid>
        <description>There’s a strange paradox within the London cultural scene: as soon as summer hits, with the days growing longer, and the evenings stretching out before us to the horizon, theatres and galleries begin to close shop, using the summer months to prepare their new seasons. It’s unfortunate, since July …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>God save the Childqueen</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-god-save-the-childqueen/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-god-save-the-childqueen/</guid>
        <description>There is a double pleasure in discovering the music of LA psychedelic-soul artist Kadhja Bonet. There is, first of all, the joy to be found in the music: warm and inviting, completely drenched in a sticky sense of pleasant nostalgia, the songs seem to have been beamed to us directly from the 1970s. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Iliac Crest – An unsettling tale of disappearance and mystery</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-15-the-iliac-crest-an-unsettling-tale-of-disappearance-and-mystery/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-15-the-iliac-crest-an-unsettling-tale-of-disappearance-and-mystery/</guid>
        <description>In literature, disappearance tends to be a primarily active phenomenon, with individuals making the choice to leave their family and friends behind. While it is not necessarily a consensual act – ‘disappear’ implies people are left behind, who are often searching for the missing individual – the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The cinema of Japanese master Hirokazu Kore-eda</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-the-cinema-of-japanese-master-hirokazu-kore-eda/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-the-cinema-of-japanese-master-hirokazu-kore-eda/</guid>
        <description>This year’s Cannes Film Festival, which closed last month, saw a timely focus on the issues of sexual harassment that have dominated the film industry press over the last year. The discussion reached a shocking conclusion when actor Asia Argento made a speech during the closing ceremony, accusing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UCU calls on withheld salaries to fund bursaries</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-ucu-calls-on-withheld-salaries-to-fund-bursaries/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-ucu-calls-on-withheld-salaries-to-fund-bursaries/</guid>
        <description>The Imperial College London branch of the Universities and College Union (UCU) has called on senior management to make withheld salaries available to students who faced a cut in their student bursaries. In an email sent to Louise Lindsay, Director of Human Resources and Organisational Change, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What you need to do before you leave Imperial</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-what-you-need-to-do-before-you-leave-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Alice Davage,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-what-you-need-to-do-before-you-leave-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Watch a premiere
Ever noticed those bright spotlights encircling the night sky over campus? No, they are not signalling an alien invasion. The police are not scouring campus for a wanted criminal either. Although, both of these things would certainly liven up exam season. They are in fact a sign …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Universities withholding millions from staff involved in UCU strike</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-universities-withholding-millions-from-staff-involved-in-ucu-strike/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-universities-withholding-millions-from-staff-involved-in-ucu-strike/</guid>
        <description>Russell Group universities have withheld over £8 million in salaries from staff members who participated in this year’s strikes, with further deductions planned for the near future. A series of Freedom of Information requests to Russell Group universities revealed those whose staff took part in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can there be art after warfare?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-can-there-be-art-after-warfare/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-can-there-be-art-after-warfare/</guid>
        <description>Aftermath, the title of the Tate Britain’s new exhibition, which looks at art produced in Europe after World War One, was originally an agricultural term. It described the growth of grass and other plants that followed a harvest – the sweeping away of the old creating a space in which the new could …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Clash of Cultures – Mindy Lee</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-clash-of-cultures-mindy-lee/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-clash-of-cultures-mindy-lee/</guid>
        <description>When I listen back to the recording of my conversation with Mindy Lee, artist and curator of Imperial’s Blyth Gallery, there’s the faint sound of piano music tinkling along in the background. Mindy’s office is located in the Blyth Centre, surrounded by music practice rooms, from which the sound of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Disoriental – A multi-generational study of identity</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-disoriental-a-multi-generational-study-of-identity/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-disoriental-a-multi-generational-study-of-identity/</guid>
        <description>The father of a friend of mine has a story about growing up between cultures. Born in England to a Greek-Cypriot family, he lived in London until he was a few years old, before going to Cyprus for about six months. Surrounded by family members, all chattering away in Greek, the English he had …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>François Ozon’s sexual thriller fails to ignite</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-fran-ois-ozon-s-sexual-thriller-fails-to-ignite/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-fran-ois-ozon-s-sexual-thriller-fails-to-ignite/</guid>
        <description>With Amant Double, there is the sense that French director François Ozon is returning to where he is most comfortable: sexual psychodrama. While Ozon’s filmography has some notable exceptions – the high-camp comedy Potiche among them – he seems to be most at home when straddling the line between …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Men&#39;s Rugby Club suspended after footage of team exposing themselves in public emerges</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-men-s-rugby-club-suspended-after-footage-of-team-exposing-themselves-in-public-emerges/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-men-s-rugby-club-suspended-after-footage-of-team-exposing-themselves-in-public-emerges/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Men’s Rugby Club (ICURFC) have been suspended after evidence emerged showing the team exposing themselves in public.
Students were caught showing their genitals in front of the Cenotaph, climbing naked into the fountains in Trafalgar Square, and making jokes about Mexicans and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Natalie Prass returns bigger, bolder, and hella funkier</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-natalie-prass-returns-bigger-bolder-and-hella-funkier/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-natalie-prass-returns-bigger-bolder-and-hella-funkier/</guid>
        <description>Along with a worsening of the environmental crisis, the increasing shamelessness of neo-Nazis, and a potentially precipitous plunge into nuclear armageddon, we can blame Donald Trump for another problem: the long wait for The Future and the Past, the follow up to Virginian songwriter and Matthew E. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>That Summer: The revenge of Grey Gardens</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-that-summer-the-revenge-of-grey-gardens/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-that-summer-the-revenge-of-grey-gardens/</guid>
        <description>In terms of Great American Mysteries, the story of the Beales ranks up there with Lindbergh’s baby or the Black Dahlia. Why and how, exactly, did ‘Big Edie’ and ‘Little Edie’ Beale, the mother-daughter duo, lock themselves inside their decrepit mansion in the East Hamptons for decades, slowly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The age of Oneohtrix Point Never has finally touched down</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-the-age-of-oneohtrix-point-never-has-finally-touched-down/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-the-age-of-oneohtrix-point-never-has-finally-touched-down/</guid>
        <description>In their 1997 book The Fourth Turning, historians and authors William Strauss and Neil Howe put forward their theory that all of human history could be tracked as an infinite cycle of four ages, as regular and predictable as clockwork. An ‘awakening’ would be followed by an ‘unravelling’, then a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial President&#39;s expenses bill among highest of entire Russell Group</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-imperial-president-s-expenses-bill-among-highest-of-entire-russell-group/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-imperial-president-s-expenses-bill-among-highest-of-entire-russell-group/</guid>
        <description>Professor Alice Gast, President of Imperial College London, last year had one of the largest expense claims of any Russell Group head, Felix can reveal.
Data obtained from Freedom of Information requests show Professor Gast last year claimed nearly £44,000 in expenses, mainly for travel abroad.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Food taste test: instant ramen flavours</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-felix-food-taste-test-instant-ramen-flavours/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-felix-food-taste-test-instant-ramen-flavours/</guid>
        <description>There is, fairly or unfairly, perhaps no meal more closely associated with the student experience than instant ramen. Different universities may have their own iconic foodstuffs, but the ubiquity of instant noodles seems to cut across time and space. At the most basic level, instant noodles appeal …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial subjects fall in Guardian League Table, as Cambridge retains top position</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-imperial-subjects-fall-in-guardian-league-table-as-cambridge-retains-top-position/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-imperial-subjects-fall-in-guardian-league-table-as-cambridge-retains-top-position/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London has dropped one place in the Guardian League Tables, with a number of individual subjects dropping sharply in the rankings.
Overall, Imperial was ranked seventh in the country, between Bath (which placed 6th) and Warwick (which placed 8th). Cambridge, Oxford, and St Andrews …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Breadwinner fails to win our heart</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-the-breadwinner-fails-to-win-our-heart/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-the-breadwinner-fails-to-win-our-heart/</guid>
        <description>The Breadwinner, Nora Twomey’s follow-up to her breakout film The Secret of Kells, opens with a scene we are to take as paradigmatic of life in Afghanistan at the turn of the 21st century: a one-legged man, who fought in the Soviet-Afghan war, hawks a red dress his daughter has never had the chance …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The revision soundtrack you wish you had this year</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-the-revision-soundtrack-you-wish-you-had-this-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Henry Eshbaugh,Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-the-revision-soundtrack-you-wish-you-had-this-year/</guid>
        <description>Right in time for the end of exam season, the usual suspects rec some LPs that you should’ve been listening to all along. Sucks you don’t have a time machine, or you could’ve had that many more hours of pleasant revision coasting emotionally on the bangin’ tunes we tell you to like. Well, there’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Theory of Bastards: the short distance between man and animal</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-theory-of-bastards-the-short-distance-between-man-and-animal/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-theory-of-bastards-the-short-distance-between-man-and-animal/</guid>
        <description>There is something slightly off-putting about our simian cousins – those gorillas, chimpanzees, and bonobos who seem so human-like and yet also so distant from us. We know that many such species behave in ways similar to humans – they exhibit complex social behaviour, are self-aware, and are able to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union elections close, with some positions unfilled</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-union-elections-close-with-some-positions-unfilled/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-union-elections-close-with-some-positions-unfilled/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Union last week closed voting in their Summer Elections.
Students had the opportunity to vote in the third set of Union elections this academic year from noon, Tuesday 29th May – a significantly shorter voting timeframe than the last set of elections, which saw voting open for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Artists at Work – the original selfies</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-artists-at-work-the-original-selfies/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-artists-at-work-the-original-selfies/</guid>
        <description>Artists at Work, the title of the small collection of drawings currently on display at the Courtauld Gallery, is appropriate in more ways than one. While curators Deanna Petterbridge and Anita Viola Sganzerla undoubtedly chose the name to reflect the content of the drawings – artists leaning close …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Courtney Barnett trades barbs for guitars</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-courtney-barnett-trades-barbs-for-guitars/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-courtney-barnett-trades-barbs-for-guitars/</guid>
        <description>On first listen, Tell Me How You Really Feel, the long-anticipated new album from Australian slacker-rock queen Courtney Barnett couldn’t seem more different from her breakthrough Sometimes I Sit and Think, and Sometimes I Just Sit. ‘Hopefulessness’, the opening track, is a guitar-led dirge, with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nailed It!, Netflix, and the death of modern TV</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-nailed-it-netflix-and-the-death-of-modern-tv/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-nailed-it-netflix-and-the-death-of-modern-tv/</guid>
        <description>In 1978, the author and activist Jerry Mander released a book entitled Four Arguments for the Elimination of Television. Mander, who had worked in the advertising world for 15 years before turning his attention more fully to activism, argued television was not a neutral technology, but rather …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On Chesil Beach: A strained drama that loses it in the last act</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-on-chesil-beach-a-strained-drama-that-loses-it-in-the-last-act/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-on-chesil-beach-a-strained-drama-that-loses-it-in-the-last-act/</guid>
        <description>On Chesil Beach has perhaps the longest sex scene I’ve ever seen in my history of cinema-going. We encounter newly-weds Florence (Saoirse Ronan) and Edward (Billy Howle) right at the beginning of Dominic Cooke’s film, and – shortly after sitting through the post-wedding dinner from hotel hell – they …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Philip Roth: Mourning the loss of an American literary giant</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-philip-roth-mourning-the-loss-of-an-american-literary-giant/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-philip-roth-mourning-the-loss-of-an-american-literary-giant/</guid>
        <description>You’re looking, as you begin, for what’s going to resist you. You’re looking for trouble. Sometimes in the beginning uncertainty arises not because the writing is difficult, but because it isn’t difficult enough.”
These words were spoken by the late American author Philip Roth, who died earlier this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pure Hollywood: a long-anticipated UK debut proves to be worth the wait</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-pure-hollywood-a-long-anticipated-uk-debut-proves-to-be-worth-the-wait/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-pure-hollywood-a-long-anticipated-uk-debut-proves-to-be-worth-the-wait/</guid>
        <description>California, despite its associations in popular culture with dreaming and love and soul, can be an inhospitable place; the beauty of the sunshine that gives the state its nickname is tempered by its power – to dessicate, oppress, and crack open, like asphalt rutted open by an eternal summer. In her …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Under Pressure: Counselling Service hit by increased student demand</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-under-pressure-counselling-service-hit-by-increased-student-demand/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-under-pressure-counselling-service-hit-by-increased-student-demand/</guid>
        <description>Towards the end of the last academic year, while experiencing a number of difficulties, Claire* finally picked up the courage to go and see Imperial’s Counselling Service. After waiting a few weeks for an initial assessment, she went along to the counsellor&amp;rsquo;s office at her appointed time, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Break in at Beit Hall</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-break-in-at-beit-hall/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-break-in-at-beit-hall/</guid>
        <description>An intruder was arrested earlier this week after attempting to enter unlocked rooms in Beit Hall. On Tuesday evening the individual, who was trying to gain access to rooms within the hall, was spotted by a student, who contacted the on-site security team. The police were then phoned, who arrested …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Changes to appeals and complaints process</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-changes-to-appeals-and-complaints-process/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-changes-to-appeals-and-complaints-process/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London has put in place changes to their policies on academic appeals and student complaints, aimed to make the process clearer and easier.
The changes, which came into effect earlier this week, included separating out arithmetical mark checks from the usual appeals process, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mistaken Identity – how should the left move forward from identity politics?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-mistaken-identity-how-should-the-left-move-forward-from-identity-politics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-mistaken-identity-how-should-the-left-move-forward-from-identity-politics/</guid>
        <description>In June 2015, an interview conducted by KXLY, a small news outlet located in the city of Spokane, Washington, sparked heated debate across the world. For the first eight minutes, Jeff Humphrey, the interviewer, speaks to Rachel Dolezal, president of the local NAACP chapter, about hate crimes she’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Searching for a match: could you be Kaiya’s stem cell donor?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-searching-for-a-match-could-you-be-kaiya-s-stem-cell-donor/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-searching-for-a-match-could-you-be-kaiya-s-stem-cell-donor/</guid>
        <description>When the parents of five-year-old Kaiya took her to the doctors following some bruising, they weren’t expecting to hear anything out of the ordinary. Instead, they returned home with the news that their daughter had leukaemia.
Kaiya, who was diagnosed a little over six weeks ago, is one of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Student Academic Choice Award winners revealed</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-student-academic-choice-award-winners-revealed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-student-academic-choice-award-winners-revealed/</guid>
        <description>The Student Academic Choice Awards (SACAs) took place earlier this week, with eight staff from across a number of departments going home with awards.
The awards ceremony, organised by Imperial College Union, took place on Monday evening. 48 staff from across the College were nominated by students …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial among most international universities in the world</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-imperial-among-most-international-universities-in-the-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-imperial-among-most-international-universities-in-the-world/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London has one of the highest proportions of international students of European universities, according to new data.
An analysis by Times Higher Education found Imperial was the seventh most international university in the world, with 55.4% of the student body coming from overseas. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial needs to do more for sustainability and climate change, report argues</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-imperial-needs-to-do-more-for-sustainability-and-climate-change-report-argues/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-imperial-needs-to-do-more-for-sustainability-and-climate-change-report-argues/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London needs to do more for sustainability and the environment in order to keep up with fellow universities, according to a new report released last week.
Greening Imperial, an initiative to “understand and improve how Imperial College London implements sustainability and action on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Clash of Cultures: Giskin Day</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-clash-of-cultures-giskin-day/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-clash-of-cultures-giskin-day/</guid>
        <description>When I enter Giskin Day’s office, past the main entrance of the Centre for Languages, Culture, and Communication, on the third floor of Sherfield, it has been overrun with an array of padlocked backpacks. They’re being stored there in preparation of the Imperial Festival, which ran the weekend after …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lean on Pete: Transmissions from the Interior West</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-lean-on-pete-transmissions-from-the-interior-west/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-lean-on-pete-transmissions-from-the-interior-west/</guid>
        <description>What is a Western? While everybody might know a film is a Western when they watch it, the actual definition is – as with any attempt to define cultural movements – difficult to pin down, squirming and wriggling away like a slippery eel. The American Film Institute has defined the Western as films …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London rated best city for international university students</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-london-rated-best-city-for-international-university-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-london-rated-best-city-for-international-university-students/</guid>
        <description>London has been ranked the best city for university students, beating out Tokyo and Melbourne for the top spot.
This is the first year London has topped the rankings, which are organised by the higher education company QS. London came third in the rankings last year, being beaten by Montreal and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial 4th best university in UK; problems with student satisfaction continue</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-imperial-4th-best-university-in-uk-problems-with-student-satisfaction-continue/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Frank Leggett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-imperial-4th-best-university-in-uk-problems-with-student-satisfaction-continue/</guid>
        <description>The Complete University Guide (CUG) rankings, released last week, saw Imperial climb one spot to 4th best university in the country. The University of St. Andrews fell two places from the 2017 rankings, moving Imperial and the London School of Economics (LSE) up one place each. LSE has retained its …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grid of Points – A ambient meditation on silence and absence</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-grid-of-points-a-ambient-meditation-on-silence-and-absence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-grid-of-points-a-ambient-meditation-on-silence-and-absence/</guid>
        <description>Liz Harris, the woman behind the ambient outfit Grouper, whose latest release Grid of Points dropped last week, lives in Astoria. It’s a small town located on the very northernmost edge of Oregon, on a strip of land that abuts the Columbia river as it bleeds into the wide Pacific. To look at images …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Joe Hill-Gibbins takes us on a tour of hell</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-joe-hill-gibbins-takes-us-on-a-tour-of-hell/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-joe-hill-gibbins-takes-us-on-a-tour-of-hell/</guid>
        <description>The National Theatre’s production of Absolute Hell, Rodney King’s jet-black dramedy set in Soho after the Second World War, begins by attempting to prove Jean-Paul Sartre’s adage that ‘hell is other people’. The entire cast – 28 people strong – line themselves up along the front of the Lyttelton …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Professor&#39;s arrest in Iran confirmed</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-professor-s-arrest-in-iran-confirmed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-professor-s-arrest-in-iran-confirmed/</guid>
        <description>Professor Abbas Edalat, from Imperial College London’s Department of Computing, has been detained in Iran, the Iranian government has confirmed.
The news of Professor Edalat’s arrest, which was first reported by the Centre for Human Rights in Iran (CHRI), a US-based non-profit, was confirmed by the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students raise concerns over Central Library toilets</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-students-raise-concerns-over-central-library-toilets/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-students-raise-concerns-over-central-library-toilets/</guid>
        <description>A number of students have recently raised concerns over the cleanliness and upkeep of the toilet facilities at Imperial.
Several students this week spoke to Felix over the state of the bathrooms around campus, particularly those in Central Library. Students reported having to use bathrooms with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Devil’s Dance – dancing on the border between imagination and reality</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-the-devil-s-dance-dancing-on-the-border-between-imagination-and-reality/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-the-devil-s-dance-dancing-on-the-border-between-imagination-and-reality/</guid>
        <description>The death of Islam Karimov, the dictatorial leader of Uzbekistan, nearly two years ago, dropped the country into a quagmire of uncertainty. The leader, who had held power for 27 years, was widely criticised for his use of torture, crackdown on press freedoms, and a 2005 massacre in which around 400 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The photographer as painter, sculptor, artist</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-the-photographer-as-painter-sculptor-artist/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-the-photographer-as-painter-sculptor-artist/</guid>
        <description>From the dawn of the age of the camera, photography as an artistic medium has been consistently set apart from the tradition of fine art. Henry Fox Talbot, one of the fathers of the photographic process, wrote in the mid-19th century that photographic plates “are impressed by the agence of Light …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Universities minister promises to crack-down on no-platforming with first interventions in 30 years</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-universities-minister-promises-to-crack-down-on-no-platforming-with-first-interventions-in-30-years/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-universities-minister-promises-to-crack-down-on-no-platforming-with-first-interventions-in-30-years/</guid>
        <description>Universities Minister Sam Gyimah this week promised to crack down on the “institutional hostility” of safe-space and no-platform policies, with the first government interventions on the issue in 30 years. At a closed-door free speech summit chaired by Gyimah on Thursday 3rd May, the minister called …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Russell Group gender pay gap nearly twice national average</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-russell-group-gender-pay-gap-nearly-twice-national-average/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-russell-group-gender-pay-gap-nearly-twice-national-average/</guid>
        <description>Data released last month show the Russell Group has a gender pay gap nearly twice that of the national average.
Across the 24 universities making up the Russell Group, the median gender pay gap was 16.7%, slightly larger than the average for higher education institutions (HEIs) as a whole, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A tale of two women</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-a-tale-of-two-women/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-a-tale-of-two-women/</guid>
        <description>Filmgoers looking for stories of complex women struggling to succeed in a man’s world, which simultaneously serve as an exploration and critique of a particular cultural moment are this week, surprisingly, spoiled for choice. Funny Cow (Dir: Adrian Shergold) and Let the Sunshine In (Dir: Claire …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial computing professor detained in Iran</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-imperial-computing-professor-detained-in-iran/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-imperial-computing-professor-detained-in-iran/</guid>
        <description>A professor from Imperial College London is believed to have been detained in Iran last week.
Professor Abbas Edalat, who is based at Imperial’s Department of Computing, was arrested by Iran’s Revolutionary Guards on the 15th April, according to a human rights group.
The Centre for Human Rights in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>QTR Restaurant to close through summer term</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-qtr-restaurant-to-close-through-summer-term/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-qtr-restaurant-to-close-through-summer-term/</guid>
        <description>The Queen’s Tower Rooms Restaurant will be closed throughout the entire summer term, Imperial College London has announced, as the space is to be used as a venue for examinations.
The move, which comes following a trial in January, will see the outlet – which is usually open for lunch on weekdays …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UCU call off further strike action, as debates around tuition fee refunds continue</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-ucu-call-off-further-strike-action-as-debates-around-tuition-fee-refunds-continue/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-ucu-call-off-further-strike-action-as-debates-around-tuition-fee-refunds-continue/</guid>
        <description>Members of the University and College Union (UCU) earlier this month voted to accept proposals from Universities UK (UUK), cancelling strike action scheduled for later this term.
In a ballot, whose results were revealed on the 13th April, 64% of members voted to accept the pensions offer from UUK, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grantham Institute launch art prize with Royal College of Art</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-grantham-institute-launch-art-prize-with-royal-college-of-art/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-grantham-institute-launch-art-prize-with-royal-college-of-art/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London’s Grantham Institute has launched an art competition as part of their 10th anniversary celebrations.
The Grantham Art Prize, which is being run in collaboration with the Department of Fine Art at the Royal College of Art (RCA), will provide up to six artists or groups £700 to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix recommends the perfect TV for exam season</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-felix-recommends-the-perfect-tv-for-exam-season/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-felix-recommends-the-perfect-tv-for-exam-season/</guid>
        <description>You know the feeling. You’re approaching your eighth solid hour in Central Library, trying to do something that comes remotely close to revision, but can feel your concentration dwindling away with each passing moment. It’s time for a break, but what to do? The lining of your stomach can’t handle …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Poor weather doesn&#39;t dampen spirits at postgraduate graduation ceremony</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-poor-weather-doesn-t-dampen-spirits-at-postgraduate-graduation-ceremony/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-poor-weather-doesn-t-dampen-spirits-at-postgraduate-graduation-ceremony/</guid>
        <description>Over 3,500 graduands made their way across the stage of the Royal Albert Hall this Wednesday to receive their degrees during the postgraduate graduation ceremony.
Students who had completed masters and doctorates made their way to the South Kensington campus from more than 60 countries, with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial gender pay gap shows men dominating top positions</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-26-imperial-gender-pay-gap-shows-men-dominating-top-positions/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-26-imperial-gender-pay-gap-shows-men-dominating-top-positions/</guid>
        <description>Newly-released data on the gender pay gap show women working Imperial College London earn, on average, 9.4% less per hour than male staff.
The data, which were released last Friday, show men dominating the highest paying jobs at Imperial. Furthermore, men are more likely to be granted bonus pay, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Council paper raised over cheating concerns in Leadership Elections</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-26-council-paper-raised-over-cheating-concerns-in-leadership-elections/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-26-council-paper-raised-over-cheating-concerns-in-leadership-elections/</guid>
        <description>Union Council last week passed a paper calling on clarification of election rules and establishment of an appeals process for complaints, following concerns over cheating in this year’s Leadership Elections.
The paper was proposed by Kelvin Zhang, a first year computing student, and seconded by a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Professor Robert Winston lecture sees low turnout amid strike action</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-22-professor-robert-winston-lecture-sees-low-turnout-amid-strike-action/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-22-professor-robert-winston-lecture-sees-low-turnout-amid-strike-action/</guid>
        <description>An Imperial lecture hosted by Professor Robert Winston last week saw a low turnout amid a boycott by striking staff members.
The lecture, entitled “Is there still a place for old-fashioned medicine?” took place on Thursday 15th March, in the penultimate day of industrial action from members of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix investigates sexism at Imperial</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-felix-investigates-sexism-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 12:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-felix-investigates-sexism-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>A Felix survey on sexism at Imperial College London has revealed a number of concerns over the treatment of female students and staff across multiple areas.
The survey, which ran for six weeks, gathered about 300 responses from students, alumni, and staff. Around two-thirds of respondents identified …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Strikes set to hit exam period if talks over pensions aren&#39;t resolved</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-strikes-set-to-hit-exam-period-if-talks-over-pensions-aren-t-resolved/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-strikes-set-to-hit-exam-period-if-talks-over-pensions-aren-t-resolved/</guid>
        <description>University College Union (UCU) has sanctioned another 14 days of strike action during exam and assessment periods if the current dispute with Universities UK (UUK) is not resolved. The news comes as the third week of strike action comes to an end, with academic and support staff across the country …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Audit on feedback times shows wide ranges between departments</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-audit-on-feedback-times-shows-wide-ranges-between-departments/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-audit-on-feedback-times-shows-wide-ranges-between-departments/</guid>
        <description>An audit of first year assessments from last term, organised by Imperial College Union (ICU), has found a large range in how promptly departments provide feedback.
While nearly 90% of assessed feedback last term was returned within the recommended ten working day time-frame, there was a wide range …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial to continue to operate cashless-only system at six outlets, despite negative feedback</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-imperial-to-continue-to-operate-cashless-only-system-at-six-outlets-despite-negative-feedback/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-imperial-to-continue-to-operate-cashless-only-system-at-six-outlets-despite-negative-feedback/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London will continue to use cashless payment across eight of its catering outlets, despite overall negative feedback on the changes.
In a survey carried out between December 2017 and February 2018, 88% of students and staff who responded were not in favour of expanding to a fully …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Provost named as Prof. Ian Walmsley</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-new-provost-named-as-prof-ian-walmsley/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-new-provost-named-as-prof-ian-walmsley/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London have appointed Professor Ian Walmsley FRS as the new Provost.
Professor Walmsley joins Imperial from the University of Oxford, where he is the Hooke Professor of Experimental Physics and the current Pro-Vice-Chancellor (Research and Innovation).
Professor Walmsley graduated …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Princes Garden Hackspace to close this week</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-princes-garden-hackspace-to-close-this-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-princes-garden-hackspace-to-close-this-week/</guid>
        <description>The Hackspace at 10 Princes Gardens will shut this Monday, following “departmental changes”.
The Hackspace, which is mainly used by students to produce prototypes, will close on Monday 12th March. Imperial College Advanced Hackspace (ICAH), who operate the space, say the change is the result of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Student Academic Choice Awards shortlist revealed</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-student-academic-choice-awards-shortlist-revealed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-student-academic-choice-awards-shortlist-revealed/</guid>
        <description>The shortlist for this year’s Student Academic Choice Awards (SACAs) has been revealed.
48 staff from across a number of departments are shortlisted for eight awards, including Best Teaching for Undergraduates, Best Support Staff, and Best Supervision. This year 935 staff members were nominated, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students complain over library temperatures</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-students-complain-over-library-temperatures/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-students-complain-over-library-temperatures/</guid>
        <description>Students have been reporting excessively high temperatures at Central Library over the past week. Throughout last weekend, and the beginning of this week, students have been reporting excessively high temperatures, despite the new climate control systems that were installed last year.
In a series of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students raise concerns over organisation of this year&#39;s Leadership Elections</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-students-raise-concerns-over-organisation-of-this-year-s-leadership-elections/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-students-raise-concerns-over-organisation-of-this-year-s-leadership-elections/</guid>
        <description>A number of students have criticised Imperial College Union (ICU) for poor planning and execution of this year’s Leadership Elections, which finish today.
Students have highlighted problems with communication, organisation, and enforcement of campaign rules. During the past week, a number of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Oscars 2018: predictable results, predictable protests, predictable jokes, predictable disappointment</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-the-oscars-2018-predictable-results-predictable-protests-predictable-jokes-predictable-disappointment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-the-oscars-2018-predictable-results-predictable-protests-predictable-jokes-predictable-disappointment/</guid>
        <description>In the early hours of the morning, UK time, another year in the film industry came to a close, as Jimmy Kimmel closed out the 90th Academy Awards. The winners headed off to the after party, cleaners began sweeping the theatre floor of discarded acceptance speeches and candy wrappers, and film …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Winners of Leadership Elections revealed</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-winners-of-leadership-elections-revealed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-winners-of-leadership-elections-revealed/</guid>
        <description>The winners of this year’s Imperial College Union (ICU) Leadership Elections have been revealed.
The Officer Trustee team for next academic year will consist of Robert Tomkies as Union President, James Medler as Deputy President (Clubs &amp;amp; Societies) (DPCS), Alejandro Luy as Deputy President …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial&#39;s property holdings revealed</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-05-imperial-s-property-holdings-revealed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-05-imperial-s-property-holdings-revealed/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London’s property holdings are among the most extensive of London universities and include a significant amount of student accommodation. Through data obtained from freedom of information requests, as well as publicly available records and statements, Felix has found Imperial has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Film’s guide to the Oscars – who will win, who should win, and who’ve been left out in the cold</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-felix-film-s-guide-to-the-oscars-who-will-win-who-should-win-and-who-ve-been-left-out-in-the-cold/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Ashley Luckyram,Mark Aduol,Mikhail Demtchenko,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-felix-film-s-guide-to-the-oscars-who-will-win-who-should-win-and-who-ve-been-left-out-in-the-cold/</guid>
        <description>Oscars season is upon as! And, as is traditional, Felix are here to give you a rundown of what will win on the night, as well as what should win, and who didn&amp;rsquo;t even get a nomination:
 Best Picture
 It’s been a complicated awards season. Call Me by Your Name started out in the lead when it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First five days of strikes end with Imperial calling for review of UUK changes</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-05-first-five-days-of-strikes-end-with-imperial-calling-for-review-of-uuk-changes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-05-first-five-days-of-strikes-end-with-imperial-calling-for-review-of-uuk-changes/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London senior management have called on Universities UK to reevaluate their proposed changes to the Universities Superannuation Scheme (USS), amid concerns over data and analysis.
In an email sent out to staff on Tuesday afternoon, Professor Alice Gast, President, and Professor …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>VarsityFest delayed due to poor weather</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-05-varsityfest-delayed-due-to-poor-weather/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-05-varsityfest-delayed-due-to-poor-weather/</guid>
        <description>This year’s VarsityFest has been postponed, following heavy snow and cold weather. In an update, Imperial College Union (ICU) told students: “Due to adverse weather VarsityFest from this Saturday 3 March is postponed.” Club captains are scheduled to receive emails about contingency plans, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial confirm students will not be examined on content missed due to strikes</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-26-imperial-confirm-students-will-not-be-examined-on-content-missed-due-to-strikes/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-26-imperial-confirm-students-will-not-be-examined-on-content-missed-due-to-strikes/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London have confirmed students will not be examined on material missed as a result of the ongoing strikes by the University and College Union (UCU).
In an email sent out on Friday to all students, Professor James Stirling, Provost, and Professor Simone Buitendijk, Vice-Provost …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Strikes hit Imperial over pensions dispute</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-23-strikes-hit-imperial-over-pensions-dispute/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-23-strikes-hit-imperial-over-pensions-dispute/</guid>
        <description>This week saw lectures and tutorials cancelled, as university staff across the UK began their walkout over pension pay.
Members of the University and College Union (UCU) across 64 higher education institutions went on strike of Thursday and Friday of this week. It marks the first two days of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Baftas 2018: A predictable awards ceremony that leaves the road to the Oscars clear</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-baftas-2018-a-predictable-awards-ceremony-that-leaves-the-road-to-the-oscars-clear/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-baftas-2018-a-predictable-awards-ceremony-that-leaves-the-road-to-the-oscars-clear/</guid>
        <description>Even for those at Imperial who aren’t particularly interested in film, the presence of the 2018 Baftas was difficult to miss. For one thing, the evening was hosted at the Royal Albert Hall, allowing some students and staff the chance to engage in some star-spotting (insert pun about Blackett astro …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Changes to graduation seating put in place</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-23-changes-to-graduation-seating-put-in-place/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-23-changes-to-graduation-seating-put-in-place/</guid>
        <description>Guests of students attending graduation ceremonies at Imperial College London may have to sit apart, under a new ticketing system put in place.
This year the responsibility of the ticketing and seating allocation will be taken over from College by the Royal Albert Hall. The College told Felix: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Elections error accidentally reveals manifestos early</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-23-elections-error-accidentally-reveals-manifestos-early/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-23-elections-error-accidentally-reveals-manifestos-early/</guid>
        <description>An error in Imperial College Union’s elections webpage meant submitted manifestos were available to view for nearly two weeks.
An incorrect setting in the eVoting database meant a discontinued set of manifesto display pages, which had been removed in 2016, were accidentally reactivated. The result …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Guillermo del Toro shows us the shape of his dreams in this fantasy romance</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-guillermo-del-toro-shows-us-the-shape-of-his-dreams-in-this-fantasy-romance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-guillermo-del-toro-shows-us-the-shape-of-his-dreams-in-this-fantasy-romance/</guid>
        <description>&amp;ldquo;Disobedience is one of the strongest signals of your conscience of what is right and what is wrong” said Guillermo del Toro when promoting his masterpiece Pan’s Labyrinth, “when you disobey in an intelligent way, you disobey in a natural way, it turns out to be more beneficial than blind …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lady Bird: Love and cinema in Sacramento</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-lady-bird-love-and-cinema-in-sacramento/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-lady-bird-love-and-cinema-in-sacramento/</guid>
        <description>Don’t you think maybe they are the same thing? Love and attention?”
Christine “Lady Bird” McPherson (Saoirse Ronan) is in her last year of high school, at a catholic institution in the city of Sacramento, California. Her dream, like innumerable other teens across the states of America, is to get as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Strike action affects exams</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-23-strike-action-affects-exams/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-23-strike-action-affects-exams/</guid>
        <description>Strike action by the University and College Union (UCU) could impact summer examinations if disputes over pensions are not resolved, with a number of UK universities stating they will alter their assessments to reflect loss of teaching.
Cambridge, York, and University College London (UCL) were among …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Theresa May announces tuition fee review</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-23-theresa-may-announces-tuition-fee-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-23-theresa-may-announces-tuition-fee-review/</guid>
        <description>Theresa May announced her planned review of post-18 education in a speech in Derby earlier this week.
Speaking at Derby College on Monday 19th February, May outlined her plans for the future of higher education, specifically potential changes to how courses at higher education institutions would be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union hit by breach to database</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-23-union-hit-by-breach-to-database/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-23-union-hit-by-breach-to-database/</guid>
        <description>A number of members of Imperial College Union (ICU) have had their personal data extracted from a Union database.
The breach, which occurred on the 8th of February 2018, affected 267 past and current members of Imperial College Union, who had a limited amount of personal data accessed. These data …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial academic believed to have been detained in Iran</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-imperial-academic-believed-to-have-been-detained-in-iran/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-imperial-academic-believed-to-have-been-detained-in-iran/</guid>
        <description>An Imperial academic is believed to have been detailed in Iran for 72 hours last weekend.
Dr Kaveh Madani, a Reader at the Centre for Environmental Policy, was made Deputy Head of Iran’s Department of Environment last year. There was confusion over his whereabouts throughout last weekend, following …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College Union to support strikes</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-imperial-college-union-to-support-strikes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-imperial-college-union-to-support-strikes/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Union (ICU) Council this week voted to support the upcoming strike action being taken by the University and College Union (UCU) over changes to the pension scheme.
In a secret ballot, 76% of Council members in attendance voted to pass a paper that called on “elected representatives …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial psychotherapy services to be potentially cut</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-imperial-psychotherapy-services-to-be-potentially-cut/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-imperial-psychotherapy-services-to-be-potentially-cut/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Health Centre (ICHC) is set to lose funding for psychotherapy services later this year under new NHS plans.
Under current proposals from the NHS Central London Clinical Commissioning Group, the body responsible for commissioning health services, primary care centres across …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Loveless: Andrey Zvyagintsev gets under the skin of modern Russia</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-loveless-andrey-zvyagintsev-gets-under-the-skin-of-modern-russia/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-loveless-andrey-zvyagintsev-gets-under-the-skin-of-modern-russia/</guid>
        <description>Andrey Zvyagintsev’s Loveless, his follow up to his 2014 Leviathan, features one of the most haunting images I’ve encountered in cinema: Shenya (Maryana Spivak) and Boris (Aleksey Rozin), a middle-class couple in the throes of an ugly divorce, argue about what they should do with their son Alexey …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Russell Group respond to Office for Students proposals on fines</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-russell-group-respond-to-office-for-students-proposals-on-fines/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-russell-group-respond-to-office-for-students-proposals-on-fines/</guid>
        <description>The Russell Group has responded to the Office for Students’ (OfS) proposals to place financial penalties on universities that breach registration conditions.
The Russell Group – a group of 24 universities in the UK, including Imperial College London, who are ‘committed to maintaining the very best …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>SACAs see record-breaking number of nominations</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-sacas-see-record-breaking-number-of-nominations/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-sacas-see-record-breaking-number-of-nominations/</guid>
        <description>This year’s Student Academic Choice Awards (SACAs) have received the highest number of nominations since their inception.
Imperial College Union, who organise the SACAs, received 1868 nominations for the awards, across a range of areas. The previous highest number of nominations was 831, which was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union apologise after calling Disabilities Officer &#39;Disabled Officer&#39;</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-union-apologise-after-calling-disabilities-officer-disabled-officer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-union-apologise-after-calling-disabilities-officer-disabled-officer/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Union has apologised after referring to the Disabilities Officer as the ‘Disabled Officer’ in some of the Leadership Elections 2018 promotional material.
The mistake occurred across the booklet outlining the positions students could run for, adverts in Issue 1684 of Felix, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union to put new petition in place for members</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-union-to-put-new-petition-in-place-for-members/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-union-to-put-new-petition-in-place-for-members/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Union will start looking into creating an online petition system, following the success of a paper at this week’s Union Council meeting.
The paper, which was proposed by Ansh Bhatnagar, Undergraduate Ordinary Member for the Faculty of Natural Sciences, was raised following a number …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sabb-otage: Nick Burstow, Deputy President (Education)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-12-sabb-otage-nick-burstow-deputy-president-education/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-12-sabb-otage-nick-burstow-deputy-president-education/</guid>
        <description>Nick Burstow, Deputy President (Education), has now been in his role for six months. We thought it was time to look at what he&amp;rsquo;d been up to, and which of his manifesto promises he&amp;rsquo;d managed to keep. Burstow is responsible for representing Imperial students when it comes to their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial among bottom of Russell Group in accepting state school applicants</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-imperial-among-bottom-of-russell-group-in-accepting-state-school-applicants/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-imperial-among-bottom-of-russell-group-in-accepting-state-school-applicants/</guid>
        <description>New data show Imperial is among the worst-performing universities in the UK in terms of admission of state school applicants.
Data released by the Higher Education Statistics Agency (HESA), the official agency for collection of quantitative information about higher education in the UK, showed that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cashless trial extended to end of February</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-cashless-trial-extended-to-end-of-february/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-cashless-trial-extended-to-end-of-february/</guid>
        <description>The cashless trial at eight of Imperial College London’s outlets has been extended for a second time, until the end of February.
The trial, which originally began at the beginning of December across four outlets, was continued through January, when it was expanded to eight outlets. The trial will …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Masterplan for White City revealed</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-masterplan-for-white-city-revealed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-masterplan-for-white-city-revealed/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London last week revealed their masterplan for the southern section of their new campus in White City.
The site, which is located south of the Westway, next to Wood Lane and the White City underground station, is the second aspect of Imperial White City – the new campus, which …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Portrait of Professor Tom Kibble unveiled</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-portrait-of-professor-tom-kibble-unveiled/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-portrait-of-professor-tom-kibble-unveiled/</guid>
        <description>A portrait of Professor Sir Tom Kibble, former Emeritus Professor of Theoretical Physics at Imperial College London, was unveiled earlier this week.
The portrait, which was painted by Tess Barnes, was revealed by Professor Kibble’s three children, in a ceremony on Monday. Professor Peter Higgs, who …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
