<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sport on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/sport/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sport on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/sport/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>ICHC Ladies 2s Reach the Top of their League</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-ichc-ladies-2s-reach-top-of-league/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chloe Jeremy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-ichc-ladies-2s-reach-top-of-league/</guid>
        <description>It has been a term of change for the ICHC L2s. The previous few seasons saw a lot of defeat, with moments of greatness and unbeatable team spirit, but just not many actual goals. Something had to change, and so October brought the hotly debated creation of the L3s, led by the blindingly optimistic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICHC: An Ode to Monday Night Training</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-ichc-ode-monday-night-training/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chloe Jeremy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-ichc-ode-monday-night-training/</guid>
        <description>It is 4:40 pm and I haven’t got as much work done as I’d hoped today. Why? A Marble Olympics YouTube hole, mental and emotional fatigue… TikTok? It doesn’t really matter. I log out of my hard-earned library computer and begin to pack up. Another student has noticed me stir and now hovers near my …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College Men’s Rugby take on Movember and Mental Health</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-imperial-college-mens-rugby-take-movember-mental-health/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Draper-Barr,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-imperial-college-mens-rugby-take-movember-mental-health/</guid>
        <description>This November, you may have been wondering why a male housemate had grown a moustache that looked more like a cappuccino stain than facial hair or why those loud blokes in ties in the union bar on a Wednesday were somehow looking more handsome than usual. It was because across Imperial and the UK, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Octopush battle it out in Oxford</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-imperial-octopush-battle-out-oxford/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Slater,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-imperial-octopush-battle-out-oxford/</guid>
        <description>On Saturday 30th November, the Octopush team (also known as Underwater Hockey or UWH) played their first competition of the year at the University of Oxford.
For the few people reading this who don’t already know, Octopush is a game created in 1954 by scuba divers to help them let off some steam …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In the Wake of Tragedy</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-wake-of-tragedy-icbc-members-alumni-sail-ocean-raise-mental-health-awareness/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bazil Saiq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-wake-of-tragedy-icbc-members-alumni-sail-ocean-raise-mental-health-awareness/</guid>
        <description>This article continues from a predecessor, &amp;ldquo;ICBC reflect on mental health and spreading awareness in the rowing community&amp;rdquo;.
A separate campaign, Race4René, in memory of René, was set up in 2018 with some of René’s closest friends and family, aiming to sail across the Atlantic with the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sports Editor’s Experience of the Relationship Between Sport and Mental Health</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-sports-editors-experience-of-relationship-sport-mental-health/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imraj Singh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-sports-editors-experience-of-relationship-sport-mental-health/</guid>
        <description>For Felix’s 70th Anniversary we’ve asked sports clubs for content on mental health in sport. I am happy to see that Imperial athletes, alongside their sport AND studies, run a range of campaigns spreading mental health awareness. Additionally, some teams have taken steps to promote welfare by having …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Heartache for Hertfordshire</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-29-11-heartache-hertfordshire/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Toby Daniels,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-29-11-heartache-hertfordshire/</guid>
        <description>With the squeals and whimpers of the Canterbury ‘players’ still fresh on our minds, we headed back to fortress Harlington to kick off our cup run. Today’s victims were familiar faces, they’d received a gentle 26-7 spanking a mere 5 weeks ago, an experience they were clearly unsatisfied with. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICXCAC Success at the Brighton 10k</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-ICXCAC-success-at-Brighton-10k/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Minty Hampden-Martin,Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-ICXCAC-success-at-Brighton-10k/</guid>
        <description>On Sunday 17th November, a rowdy group of 56 of Imperial’s finest specimens woke up in the wee hours to catch their 6:36 train from London Bridge. While most would cringe at the idea of such an early wakke-up on their rest day, the ICXCAC runners all rose to the challenge and (nearly all) made it on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Triathlon triumph at BUCS Duathlon</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-imperial-triathlon-triumph-bucs-duathlon/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>David Ho,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-imperial-triathlon-triumph-bucs-duathlon/</guid>
        <description>Sunday 24th November was one of those days where the world seemed to be set against the Imperial College triathlon team as they prepared for their first British Universities championships: in duathlon, a multisport event comprised of a run, followed by a cycle, then another run to finish.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Carnage in Canterbury</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-carnage-canterbury/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Faf De Klerk,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-carnage-canterbury/</guid>
        <description>In wake of Canterbury pipping the Imperial Mens 2nd team to the post last week, the 1s headed out with vengeance and hunger in their hearts. The type of vengeance felt when you twig on to the fact your flatmate has been knowingly using your milk without the common decency of asking. We were going …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Sailing Cosy up at Oxford Magnum</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-imperial-sailing-cosy-up-oxford-magnum/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anita Plumley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-imperial-sailing-cosy-up-oxford-magnum/</guid>
        <description>Last weekend Imperial Sailing sent their first team to Farmoor Reservoir for the annual, invite-only Oxford Magnum. The weekend really started on the Friday evening, when most of the team (cough Eve cough) made their way to the Commodore’s house for a last-minute R&amp;amp;T (Raclette and Theory) sesh. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>National Synchronized Swimming Masters Championships</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-national-synchronised-swimming-masters-championships/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Monica Fiorevanti,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-national-synchronised-swimming-masters-championships/</guid>
        <description>What a wonderful experience today was, Saturday 16th November 2019. Coming back from the national’s competition , the feeling that is in my heart is happiness! Before I even begin to describe my first synchronised swimming competition with Imperial College London, I would like to thank a few people …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICTri Take on Hillingdon Duathlon</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-ictri-take-on-hillingdon-duathlon/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emma Claxton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-ictri-take-on-hillingdon-duathlon/</guid>
        <description>On a crisp November morning, when all should have been asleep and enjoying a Sunday morning lie-in, 15 brave Imperial triathletes decided to brave the cold weather and race at the Hillingdon Duathlon. The skies had cleared from the Saturday’s rain to leave us all with brilliant race conditions: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Immortals’ Second Game of the Season</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-imperial-immortals-second-game-season/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sebastiano Zane,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-imperial-immortals-second-game-season/</guid>
        <description>Result: Imperial Immortals 0 - 48 Queen Mary&amp;rsquo;s Vipers
After the week one game against the Falcons, the game against Queen Mary’s Vipers on Sunday was the Immortals’ second chance to get a win this season. As it was the day before Remembrance Day, both teams lined up on the side-line and took …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICHC: Men’s 4s get underway in arduous season</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-ICHC-mens-4s-get-underway-in-arduous-season/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>John Hunter,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-ICHC-mens-4s-get-underway-in-arduous-season/</guid>
        <description>In their debut appearance in the Felix, ICHC Men’s 4s made the brave and treacherous journey out to the ‘Fortress’ Harlington to play 2 year rivals, New Bucks University. After a narrow win in last season’s league, tensions ran high before the match. Captain Ethan Houchen was overheard saying ‘This …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICXCAC go to Snowdonia for their Annual Trail Pilgrimage</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-ICXCAC-go-to-Snowdonia-for-annual-trail-pilgrimage/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-ICXCAC-go-to-Snowdonia-for-annual-trail-pilgrimage/</guid>
        <description>Many clubs and societies have their own traditions that they cherish: for some, a varsity match that they usually win, others have a sunny picnic by the beach, some have a WILD social; for Cross-Country and Athletics, the first weekend of November holds a special place in the heart of most regulars: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Immortals’ first game of the season</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-imperial-immortals-first-game-of-season/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sebastiano Zane,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-imperial-immortals-first-game-of-season/</guid>
        <description>Having trained hard for 5 weeks, the 30-men strong Immortals squad were up bright and early at 9 am on Sunday for the long coach journey to the home of the Kent Falcons. The Falcons are a big rival to the team, so this was a great chance to set a strong start to the season.
The game started off …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial on top of London Once Again!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-Imperial-on-top-of-London-once-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Hart,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-Imperial-on-top-of-London-once-again/</guid>
        <description>Going into Mitcham, the second cross country fixture of the season, Imperial were engaged in a battle to be the top club in London with none other than St. Mary’s University, Twickenham. Mary’s, the University of Mo Farah and a National Lottery funded British Athletics Program, was going to be a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Many Medals for IC Triathlon at Relay Duathlon</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-many-medals-for-ic-triathlon-at-relay-duathlon/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>David Ho,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-many-medals-for-ic-triathlon-at-relay-duathlon/</guid>
        <description>This Sunday showed an impressive performance from 24 of Imperial’s multisport athletes at the Olympic Velopark, in the London Universities Relay Duathlon - the first race of the year. In teams of three they would compete against Kings and UCL, with each member completing a two-mile run, a six-mile …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bike the UK for MS visit Imperial</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-bike-uk-ms-visit-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laura Bosomworth,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-bike-uk-ms-visit-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Next summer, Bike the UK for MS cyclists will be hitting the road once again as they pedal to raise funds and awareness for Multiple Sclerosis.
The charity, founded by University of Bath student James Whateley, started in 2014 following his experience of cycling across America as a 19 year old and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Members of ICXCAC Return to Parliament, and they Mean Business</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-members-icxcac-return-parliament-mean-business/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-members-icxcac-return-parliament-mean-business/</guid>
        <description>Leaves are turning brown, leaves are fallilng down, weather turns chilly and the the fields are getting muddy - it’s time for some Cross-Country.
Last year, Imperial’s Cross-Country teams absolutely dominated the field, winning the Women’s league with the Men’s team coming in second place behind the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Triathlon, Cake, Karaoke and the Many Punctures that Broke us All Together</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-triathlon-cake-karaoke-many-punctures-broke-us-all-together/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emma Claxton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-triathlon-cake-karaoke-many-punctures-broke-us-all-together/</guid>
        <description>Three weeks into the new term and guess who was already fed up of work and wanting to get away for the weekend? Why, 15 of Imperial’s finest and freshest triathletes, that’s who. On Friday 19th October, we packed our bikes (remembering to remove our pedals, don’t want any scratches!) and made the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Eliud Kipchoge Ran a Sub-2h Marathon</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-18-10-how-eliud-kipchoge-ran-sub-2h-marathon/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Hart,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-18-10-how-eliud-kipchoge-ran-sub-2h-marathon/</guid>
        <description>Sub-2 has happened, and it still hasn’t sunk in completely. Yes, the conditions were VERY optimised and it is not record eligible, and we’ll get to that later, but the enormity of such an effort is almost unbelievable. Prior to this time last year, only one man had run under 2:03 in a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC Rugby 1st, 2nd, and 3rd Teams Share Triple Victory</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-18-10-IC-rugby-reports/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sean Nakai,Simon Thornton,Matt Takle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-18-10-IC-rugby-reports/</guid>
        <description>IC rugby 1st team smash KCL
Result: KCL 1st XV 7 - 19 Imperial 1st XV
The 1st XV campaign of 2019 started with an away game to KCL. The crisp weather seemed to reflect the nerves amongst the freshers, while the autumnal sunshine mirrored the excitement within the team. The first 10 minutes saw …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC Fishing Society Finds Affordable Fishing in London</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-ic-fishing-society-finds-affordable-fishing-London/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imraj Singh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-ic-fishing-society-finds-affordable-fishing-London/</guid>
        <description>Okay now you’ve taken the bait. There is no Imperial fishing society, but I do recommend starting a society if enough of you are interested. Also I am gill-ty of not technically fishing in London, it was Epping, but Central line does go there! Affordability is also questionable, £40 for a full day …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICXCAC: A Tale of Two Summer Tours</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-icxcac-tale-two-summer-tours/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-icxcac-tale-two-summer-tours/</guid>
        <description>After a very successful year which saw the Women’s A team winning the London Universities Cross-Country League, the Women’s B team coming 3rd and the Men’s A coming in 2nd place and athletes performing extremely well individually at BUCS, the Cross-Country and Athletics Club hit the mountains twice …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Finish Mile(s) Ahead</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-imperial-finish-mile-s-ahead/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-imperial-finish-mile-s-ahead/</guid>
        <description>Just one day after their triumph at the Battle of Battersea, as previously reported by Felix, Imperial’s top athletes headed off to one of the iconic parts of London for the Westminster Mile, a legacy event from the 2012 Olympic Games.
Starting on the Mall facing towards Horse Guards Parade, the one …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Battle of Battersea</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-battle-of-battersea/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mihai Vanea,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-battle-of-battersea/</guid>
        <description>Saturday 25th May will be remembered as the day when the athletes of Imperial College came together one last time to compete in the LUCA Outdoors series, in the same fanatic spirit that has defined this club in the past few years and made it the LUCA Club of the Year.
One of the first events was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Need for Speed at BUCS Outdoor Athletics Champs</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-need-for-speed-at-bucs-outdoor-athletics-champs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-need-for-speed-at-bucs-outdoor-athletics-champs/</guid>
        <description>Over the Early May bank holiday weekend whilst students across the nation were locked indoors studying hard for exams, the country’s finest student athletes gathered at Bedford’s premium track for an ultimate athletics showdown.
The weekend began with heats on Saturday, with former-Club Captain Alex …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial stay on track in LUCA Athletics League</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-imperial-stay-on-track-in-luca-athletics-league/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-imperial-stay-on-track-in-luca-athletics-league/</guid>
        <description>A badly scheduled athletics calendar meant the second meet in the London Universities and Colleges Athletics (LUCA) Outdoors League fell on 20th April - Easter Saturday.
Expectations of a severely depleted squad failed to materialise, however, with 9 stoic athletes still keen to compete at the Lee …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC Taekwondo Victorious Spring Championships</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-ic-taekwondo-victorious-spring-championships/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sojin Park,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-ic-taekwondo-victorious-spring-championships/</guid>
        <description>Twenty members from Imperial College Taekwondo (ICUTKD) travelled to Worcester from 16th to 17th March for Spring Championships, the final competition by British Student Taekwondo Federation (BSTF). Students entered the individual and team poomsae and sparring for both World Taekwondo (WT) and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICXCAC bring home second place from Poznań</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-icxcac-bring-home-second-place-from-pozna/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie Jones,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-icxcac-bring-home-second-place-from-pozna/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Cross Country and Athletics team won a superb silver trophy at the Economic Five Race in Poznań, Poland, on Sunday 7th April, adding to their 2019 collection of successes.
On Friday 5th April, 12 of their finest runners took an early plane to Poznań, one of Poland’s major cities. At …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Triathlon does Duathlon</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-triathlon-does-duathlon/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark Pollock,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-triathlon-does-duathlon/</guid>
        <description>Another weekend, another duathlon for IC Triathlon. This time we ventured outside of London to the Bedford Autodrome; a racing circuit for cars built on an old airfield. The Bedford Autodrome duathlon is a unique one in the Triathlon race calendar, as it is the only national competition that we take …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Surprise success for Imperial at the Teddy Hall Relays </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-surprise-success-for-imperial-at-the-teddy-hall-relays/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Hart,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-surprise-success-for-imperial-at-the-teddy-hall-relays/</guid>
        <description>In the aftermath of the successful 2019 edition of ICXCAC’s Hyde Park Relays, a merry band of Imperial runners headed out to Oxford for the ‘away’ fixture: Oxford’s Teddy Halls Relays. With runners wearily boarding the convenient Oxford Tube at Notting Hill or Shepherd’s Bush, the banter slowly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC Dance Club: Best Victory in 2 Decades</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-ic-dance-club-best-victory-in-2-decades/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alistair McMurray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-ic-dance-club-best-victory-in-2-decades/</guid>
        <description>I was ~3 months old when Imperial last won Best A Team at Blackpool. Now I am 237 months old and Imperial has at last done it again, vanquishing the titans of Cambridge.
It all started on a sunny Friday afternoon when 62 dancers embarked on a long, slow coach ride to the home of Ballroom. With …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Immortals emerge victorious from trip to Canterbury and dodge relegation</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-immortals-emerge-victorious-from-trip-to-canterbury-and-dodge-relegation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Daniel Grumberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-immortals-emerge-victorious-from-trip-to-canterbury-and-dodge-relegation/</guid>
        <description>Canterbury Chargers 14 - 18 Imperial Immortals
The Immortals just played their last match of the season, and what a thriller it was! We travelled to the Chargers’ home grounds in Canterbury to battle it out. The maths was simple: win and stay on in Div 1 or lose and potentially face relegation. This …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College Conquers Closely Contested Championship</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-imperial-college-conquers-closely-contested-championship/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark Pollock,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-imperial-college-conquers-closely-contested-championship/</guid>
        <description>Imperial returns to the Velopark in Stratford, London for the inaugural London Universities Duathlon Championships.
Pre-race prep included: gawking at the competition’s incredibly expensive bikes; going to the toilet and putting on a trisuit in the wrong order; debating over the optimum bike racking …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial make their mark at BUCS Indoors Athletics</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-imperial-make-their-mark-at-bucs-indoors-athletics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Mitchell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-imperial-make-their-mark-at-bucs-indoors-athletics/</guid>
        <description>Between the 15th and 17th of February, a team of Imperial’s finest athletes set off for BUCS Indoors in Sheffield.
This is the first big event of the athletics calendar and is attended by the best university athletes from across the country. It provides a great chance for athletes to gain experience …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s in the Baggs! Imperial lift silverware after final race in the London Universities Cross Country League</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-it-s-in-the-baggs-imperial-lift-silverware-after-final-race-in-the-london-universities-cross-country-league/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-it-s-in-the-baggs-imperial-lift-silverware-after-final-race-in-the-london-universities-cross-country-league/</guid>
        <description>It was a glorious Wednesday afternoon in the middle of February - the hottest winter day on record - which was no surprise to many of Imperial’s cross country runners who knew this competition had been hotting up for some time.
The final fixture in the London Universities and Colleges Cross Country …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>After a summer of nearly’s, Football has finally come home...</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-after-a-summer-of-nearly-s-football-has-finally-come-home/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Hughes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-after-a-summer-of-nearly-s-football-has-finally-come-home/</guid>
        <description>Following a run of excellent league results, RSM Football went into the big one in high spirits. It had been 14 years of pain since their last varsity victory, although on the back of a draw and narrow loss in the past two years, there were whisperings that this could be the year.
The first half was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BOTTLE MATCH Badminton</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-bottle-match-badminton/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Annie Mao,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-bottle-match-badminton/</guid>
        <description>After the ‘true’ CSM badminton team (in which only 2 out of 6 players were miners (GEOGRAPHERS)) won the trophy last year, this year, CSM surprisingly bothered to send their actual team (of course, a NO-MINER team) to London. However, neither waking up at 5.30am nor a 6-hour drive demolished their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BOTTLE MATCH Netball</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-bottle-match-netball/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Friar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-bottle-match-netball/</guid>
        <description>This year’s netball Bottle Match proved to be a tough one. With CSM winning the coin toss, they took the first centre and the game began.
It soon became apparent that the CSM team had found last year’s scoreline a bit close for comfort, considering that they have held the netball trophy since …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BOTTLE MATCH Squash</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-bottle-match-squash/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charlie Braham,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-bottle-match-squash/</guid>
        <description>With no feature in last year’s bottle, squash returned with noise, and lots of it. Ethos witnessed an atmosphere rivalling sporting cathedral, with quality squash played in a great competitive spirit.
RSM took an early lead thanks to 4th string George Meddings who won 3&amp;frasl;0, but were levelled …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BOTTLE MATCH Women&#39;s Hockey</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-bottle-match-women-s-hockey/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bethany Grant,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-bottle-match-women-s-hockey/</guid>
        <description>Sunny weather greeted the Women’s hockey team at Harlington as we took first push back,. The RSM supporters had no competition with CSM for being the loudest.
We had a strong start from the attack, with majority possession for the first 15 minutes of the game. Unfortunately we had a lull where CSM …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lacrosse secures the W!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-lacrosse-secures-the-w/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Kwong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-lacrosse-secures-the-w/</guid>
        <description>Feeling the pressure of being the first team to play on the Saturday of Bottle Match, tensions were high but the raucous support on the side lines (great banners and chants all round) quickly calmed the nerves before the game began. The RSM supporters had witnessed unfortunate losses the day before …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Parries, pancakes and parties in Paris</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-https-f001-backblazeb2-com-file-felixonline-2018-felix-issues-issue-1716-1716-sports-paris-2019-2-jpg/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carolina Colagrossi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-https-f001-backblazeb2-com-file-felixonline-2018-felix-issues-issue-1716-1716-sports-paris-2019-2-jpg/</guid>
        <description>Every year in Paris, the Challenge X-Systra – a student run fencing competition organized by the École Polytechnique – hosts students from all over Europe. Those who love the sport don’t shy away from a three hour train, and so, this year went eighteen Imperial College Fencing Club members to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Royal School of Mines bring back the bottle</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-royal-school-of-mines-bring-back-the-bottle/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>George Morgan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-royal-school-of-mines-bring-back-the-bottle/</guid>
        <description>Following last year’s away loss to CSM, the stage was set for the RSM rugby boys to put in a huge performance. With the glorious sunshine in the hands of RSM, the team looked strong from the off.
RSM kicked off well while CSM were being dazzled by the Harlington sun. A knock-on from kick off allowed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Self-eliminations and shiny silver for IC Fencing </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-self-eliminations-and-shiny-silver-for-ic-fencing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ben Fry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-self-eliminations-and-shiny-silver-for-ic-fencing/</guid>
        <description>Valentine’s Day: 22 fencers, 6 competitions, 4 Imperial self-eliminations, 3 days, and 1 silver medal!
On the evening of Valentine’s, while most people were with loved ones, 9 fencers set off to Sheffield to show their love of fencing. They were attending BUCS Individuals where university fencers …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC American Football: Immortals Charge to a 40-0 win</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-ic-american-football-immortals-charge-to-a-40-0-win/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Daniel Grumberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-ic-american-football-immortals-charge-to-a-40-0-win/</guid>
        <description>With the end of the season insight, we are in the middle of a two-part relegation battle. The battle is against the Canterbury Christ Church Chargers a team who, like us, have sustained a losing record throughout the season. Due to the league timetabling, our matches against them are the final two …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Squash: Mad dog and Imperial men</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-imperial-squash-mad-dog-and-imperial-men/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Seigo Masuda,David Newman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-imperial-squash-mad-dog-and-imperial-men/</guid>
        <description>Continuing on from the success of the Roehampton Uni Cup, Imperial College Squash Men’s 1st Team travelled up to Birmingham last weekend (9th &amp;amp; 10th of February) to compete in the BUCS Premier Division play-off where the top 8 universities around the country gather to decide their placings for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Taekwondo’s Winter Championships spirit unbeatable</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-taekwondo-s-winter-championships-spirit-unbeatable/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sojin Park,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-taekwondo-s-winter-championships-spirit-unbeatable/</guid>
        <description>Twenty members of Imperial College Taekwondo (ICUTKD) travelled to Nottingham for the Winter Championships held by the British Student Taekwondo Federation (BSTF). Returning home are 21 medals: ten bronze, seven silver and four gold across all disciplinaries. There has been an overall improvement in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hyde Park Relays returns with aplomb</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-hyde-park-relays-returns-with-aplomb/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Hart,Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-hyde-park-relays-returns-with-aplomb/</guid>
        <description>On Saturday 9th February, the much anticipated 70th annual edition of the Hyde Park Relays, hosted by Imperial College Cross Country and Athletics, smashed onto the scene.
With over 80 teams and nearly 500 participants, it was once again a roaring success for the club.
This event holds a special …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC Squash: It was a Roller! (coaster weekend)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-ic-squash-it-was-a-roller-coaster-weekend/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>David Newman,Seigo Masuda,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-ic-squash-it-was-a-roller-coaster-weekend/</guid>
        <description>The Roehampton University Cup attracts the best university teams in the country, each of them competing for the prize of a year’s membership at Roehampton and their names on the prestigious trophy.
Imperial’s 1st team, who were also defending champions, had a tough draw during the group stage with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Sailing invades Warwick and takes on the Turtle </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-imperial-sailing-invades-warwick-and-takes-on-the-turtle/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marta Nunes De Abreu,Anita Plumley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-imperial-sailing-invades-warwick-and-takes-on-the-turtle/</guid>
        <description>The weekend started earlier for some members of Imperial Sailing, as they left the lecture theatres, packed up their sailing bags and drove up to Warwick on the Friday night. The specially appointed driver (Toby) was trusted with towing two of the club’s boats that Warwick Sailing Club had borrowed, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Super Bowl LIII: GOAT defeats Rams</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-super-bowl-liii-goat-defeats-rams/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imraj Singh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-super-bowl-liii-goat-defeats-rams/</guid>
        <description>New England Patriots 13 - 3 Los Angeles Rams
Field general Tom Brady marches down the field throwing short bullets and long bombs. Precise, calculated, commanding and highly efficient. Ain’t no mercy for the weak.
This is the demi-god quarterback of yesteryear who overcame the largest point deficit …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wat-er Race!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-wat-er-race/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alix Vermeulen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-wat-er-race/</guid>
        <description>On Saturday 2nd February, at 5:45am, 50 brave ICXC runners boarded the coach, ready to set off and compete in the BUCS Cross-Country Championships hosted by the University of Exeter.
At 6:06am, a not-so-brave ICXC over-sleeper arrived and the club was finally able to depart.
After another 3 solid …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Cross Country on verge of greatness with one race left in the LUCA XC League</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-imperial-cross-country-on-verge-of-greatness-with-one-race-left-in-the-luca-xc-league/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-imperial-cross-country-on-verge-of-greatness-with-one-race-left-in-the-luca-xc-league/</guid>
        <description>As dawn broke on Alexandra Palace, the birds began to sing and the mud glistened brightly in the morning sun.
The day was set to be a cold one, with a gentle dew hovering over the freshly watered grass, and patches of bog forming after the recent rain.
Meanwhile, away from the tranquility, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get your running shoes on, it’s the Hyde Park Relays!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-get-your-running-shoes-on-it-s-the-hyde-park-relays/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Hart,Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-get-your-running-shoes-on-it-s-the-hyde-park-relays/</guid>
        <description>The Hyde Park Relays are the largest annual student relays in the UK and have seen over 500 competitors take to the paths of the iconic Hyde Park in Central London every year since 1949 to complete 5km laps in men’s or mixed teams of 6 and women’s teams of 4. This year’s edition is set to be even …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Promising signs for ICXCAC as they begin 2019 with a successful training weekend</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-promising-signs-for-icxcac-as-they-begin-2019-with-a-successful-training-weekend/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-promising-signs-for-icxcac-as-they-begin-2019-with-a-successful-training-weekend/</guid>
        <description>ICXCAC’s runners returned from the Christmas break in dire need of a training weekend, and 2019’s winter tour destination was Church Stretton – a quaint town just outside Shropshire’s county town of Shrewsbury.
During the late Victorian period the small town was known as “Little Switzerland” and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Couch-to-5k: From Couch Potatoes to Runner Beans</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-couch-to-5k-from-couch-potatoes-to-runner-beans/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Karyshma Gill,Noemie David-Rogeat,Charlotte Barratt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-couch-to-5k-from-couch-potatoes-to-runner-beans/</guid>
        <description>You know how some people start the academic year determined to do their best?
We, the couch potatoes, decided to trade Netflix for ICXCAC and running shoes.
We know what you’re thinking: why would perfectly sane people give up the TV for running? At first, that was us as well.
Who in their right …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Immortals Stumble at Home against Kent Falcons</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-immortals-stumble-at-home-against-kent-falcons/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Daniel Grumberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-immortals-stumble-at-home-against-kent-falcons/</guid>
        <description>With a lot of new recruits and some veterans returning for a final season, the team looked entirely different for our rematch against the Falcons.
We were hoping for a much more contested game this time around at our home grounds.
This time around we weren’t suffering from missing minibuses or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cross country gives indoors athletics a try</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-cross-country-gives-indoors-athletics-a-try/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-cross-country-gives-indoors-athletics-a-try/</guid>
        <description>This week Cross Country &amp;amp; Athletics ditched muddy hills to tackle some faster terrain - an indoor athletics track.
The state-of-the-art Lee Valley Athletics Centre is situated amidst a desolate wasteland in the far reaches of north London. After meeting at Beit Quad to collect some of the famous …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College Water Polo Make History For Both</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-imperial-college-water-polo-make-history-for-both/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ramon Fernandez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-imperial-college-water-polo-make-history-for-both/</guid>
        <description>A couple of weeks ago, the water polo boys hopped on the ‘banter’ bus and headed to Bristol’s pool.
It not only has a reputation for being very yellow, but also for being the field of battle for a water polo team that has always ranked in the top 5 in the UK.
In fact, Imperial’s Men’s team had never …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Taekwondo returns successful in first of three national student Competitions</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-imperial-taekwondo-returns-successful-in-first-of-three-national-student-competitions/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sojin Park,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-imperial-taekwondo-returns-successful-in-first-of-three-national-student-competitions/</guid>
        <description>Sunday 18th November saw 14 members of Imperial College Union Taekwondo (ICUTKD) competing in the nationwide Autumn Championships and London University Sports League (LUSL) in East London.
The team brought back three gold, three silver and seven bronze medals.
ICUTKD travelled as a team from Notting …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Men’s and Women’s Teams</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-men-s-and-women-s-teams/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laura Bevis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-men-s-and-women-s-teams/</guid>
        <description>After a sickening 30-3 defeat in the away game that left them shaking (literally), the IC girls skipped merrily along to High Barnet with little expectation from Saturday’s game other than to have a nice time and not get as destroyed as last time they played the Bristol women.
After a quick warm-up …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Triathlon gives BUCS Duathlon a ‘tri’</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-triathlon-gives-bucs-duathlon-a-tri/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Amy Devila,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-triathlon-gives-bucs-duathlon-a-tri/</guid>
        <description>Sunrise came. The sun was finally shining, giving relief to a week of grim weather.
It was BUCS duathlon.
The biggest race in the duathlon calendar.
A season finale.
The challenge? A 2 mile run, followed by a 10 mile bike, and then another 2 mile run.
Nice.
With an air of excitement, the team …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>From Brighton With Love</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-from-brighton-with-love/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mihai Vanea,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-from-brighton-with-love/</guid>
        <description>Last Sunday 18th November, Imperial’s keenest and finest runners went on an adventurous trip to one of the most hotly anticipated events in the autumn term running calendar.
It was long, it was girthy, it was fast, and it was flat. Yes, you guessed it, it was the Brighton 10k.
With only a few hours …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Immortals Fight Back Against QMUL Vipers</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-immortals-fight-back-against-qmul-vipers/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Daniel Grumberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-immortals-fight-back-against-qmul-vipers/</guid>
        <description>For the first time this season we faced a new opponent, the Queen Mary Vipers. Our squad was much improved from last week, due to an addition of new recruits, and the return of our starting running back Jonas “Vegan Bull” Eschenfelder, coming back from a hand injury.
With the Queen Mary grounds …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC Triathlon take on the Hillingdon Duathlon</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-ic-triathlon-take-on-the-hillingdon-duathlon/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark Pollock,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-ic-triathlon-take-on-the-hillingdon-duathlon/</guid>
        <description>The Hillingdon Duathlon is one of the favourite events in the Triathlon calendar, not only is it a nearby, beginner-friendly, closed circuit duathlon – but you also get a mug for entering. Win win. The race consists of 2-mile run, 10-mile bike and then another 1-mile run. The men’s race was an hour …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICXC regain Bannister Cup in final LXCL of 2018</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-icxc-regain-bannister-cup-in-final-lxcl-of-2018/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-icxc-regain-bannister-cup-in-final-lxcl-of-2018/</guid>
        <description>Last Wednesday, 14th November, just two weeks after Mitcham Common’s sunny race, London’s sturdy athletes took out their spikes once more to compete in this term’s (and 2018’s) final LUCA Cross-Country League race, the much-anticipated Wimbledon Common.
With laps being longer than average at 4.7km, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Sailing takes on the Wet Dream</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-imperial-sailing-takes-on-the-wet-dream/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anita Plumley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-imperial-sailing-takes-on-the-wet-dream/</guid>
        <description>On Friday 26th October, most of the 2nd and 3rd Imperial sailing teams met at Victoria Coach Station to make our way to compete at the Wet Dream in Reading. Stragglers were forced to take the train, which ultimately proved to be much faster (but less fun) than the coach. We entertained ourselves on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>There and Back Again: A Trail Runner’s Tale from Northern Wales</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-there-and-back-again-a-trail-runner-s-tale-from-northern-wales/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-there-and-back-again-a-trail-runner-s-tale-from-northern-wales/</guid>
        <description>It seems we at ICXCAC just can’t get enough of soggy weather, lack of central heating, and world-renowned banter. And so, on Friday 2nd November, 15 of London’s finest and rowdiest decided to travel to Imperial’s infamous St Mary’s Mountain Hut in Rhyd-Ddu, Northern Wales, the international hub for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UEA Pirates Away</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-uea-pirates-away/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Daniel Grumberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-uea-pirates-away/</guid>
        <description>After last week’s bruising defeat, we were eager to get back on the field in order to provide our rookies some much-needed experience. As always, the veterans looked forward to playing at Harlington Sports Ground, lovingly nicknamed “The Fortress” after our undefeated run at home two years ago. We …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cross-Country Makes Gains at Mitcham Common</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-09-cross-country-makes-gains-at-mitcham-common/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-09-cross-country-makes-gains-at-mitcham-common/</guid>
        <description>Just two weeks after the first cross-country race of the London University’s XC League at Parliament Hill, the rowdy Imperial runners woke up on Halloween to find the sun shining and their calendars showing the highlight of their upcoming day: a lovely race at Mitcham Common.
The course is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICSWP sink, swim and win on Southampton tour</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-09-icswp-sink-swim-and-win-on-southampton-tour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ryan Clarke,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-09-icswp-sink-swim-and-win-on-southampton-tour/</guid>
        <description>They say that all roads lead to Rome, but it seems the M3 leads to Southampton: famous for pretty much nothing, other than being the departing location of the Titanic before it sank. And so it was, that 19 members of swim-polo undertook this pilgrimage with the aim of sinking the Southampton Water …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Wolverines Women make history at inaugural fixture</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-09-imperial-wolverines-women-make-history-at-inaugural-fixture/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Leo Haigh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-09-imperial-wolverines-women-make-history-at-inaugural-fixture/</guid>
        <description>On Sunday, Imperial Wolverines made history at the University South Open with several remarkable achievements.
The newly formed Women’s 1st team made their inaugural appearance at a competitive fixture, the Men’s 1st team accomplished 2nd place amongst fierce competition and, for the first time, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ultimate frisbee: Disc doctors’ october digest</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-ultimate-frisbee-disc-doctors-october-digest/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imperial discDoctors,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-ultimate-frisbee-disc-doctors-october-digest/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College’s Ultimate Team, disc Doctors, had a busy October full of tournaments and socials. Just in the first month of term we sent beginner teams to 3 different tournaments across England in: London, Brighton, and Norwich. In addition, one of the tournaments, “Skyde Park” was hosted by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICURFC 2nd XV’s winning streak lives on</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-icurfc-2nd-xv-s-winning-streak-lives-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gustave RDB,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-icurfc-2nd-xv-s-winning-streak-lives-on/</guid>
        <description>Imperial 2nd XV 20 - 7 UCL 3rd XV
On Wednesday, freshers discovered the pleasure of taking public transport to Fortress Harlington for our second game of the season. It was nice to see that the other team actually showed up on time after the 40-minute game last week. After a quick but intense and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICURFC 3rd XV’s fresher Ridge builds up an appetite</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-icurfc-3rd-xv-s-fresher-ridge-builds-up-an-appetite/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Will Cox,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-icurfc-3rd-xv-s-fresher-ridge-builds-up-an-appetite/</guid>
        <description>Imperial 3rd XV 59 - 27 UWL 1st XV
Wednesday was a big day for the 3s in several aspects. After a tough loss the previous week, some changes to the squad, and only a few substitutes, it was integral that everyone plays to their best form.
On arrival at Fortress Harlington, we eyed up the eager …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cross Country Runs for Parliament (Hill)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-cross-country-runs-for-parliament-hill/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Hart,Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-cross-country-runs-for-parliament-hill/</guid>
        <description>The first few weeks of October always seem to have surprisingly good weather to put the new freshers at ease, but eventually the first day of rain comes.
For years, engineers and scientists have been trying to refine the Navier-Stokes equations enough to be able to predict weather accurately. One …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cycling reach new heights at BUCS Hill Climb</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-cycling-reach-new-heights-at-bucs-hill-climb/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imperial Cycling Club,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-cycling-reach-new-heights-at-bucs-hill-climb/</guid>
        <description>The bikes had been stripped; bottle cages removed, handlebar tape gone, batteries only half charged, and we’d been surviving off sparkling water and lettuce for the last three days. The universal sign of an upcoming hill climb.
The BUCS Hill Climb, held this year on the infamous Mam Tor in the Peak …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College Lawn Tennis Club heads to Nice for summer tour!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-imperial-college-lawn-tennis-club-heads-to-nice-for-summer-tour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Arnaud Legrand,Bartu Ackaba,Diego Vargas Ortiz,Philip Mogul,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-imperial-college-lawn-tennis-club-heads-to-nice-for-summer-tour/</guid>
        <description>This summer we set out to Nice, France, for our summer tour. Aiming to experience clay-court tennis (a surface we never get to play on in London) we took this opportunity to spend some time together after a successful season.
The excitement to play on the top-quality clay courts in Nice was clear as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICURFC 2nd XV:  All hail King Thornton, Lord of the 3s</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-icurfc-2nd-xv-all-hail-king-thornton-lord-of-the-3s/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simon Thornton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-icurfc-2nd-xv-all-hail-king-thornton-lord-of-the-3s/</guid>
        <description>Arriving with a squad of 19 to Regent’s park, and conditions looking ideal for a game of running rugby, the stage was set for what promised to be a tough first game against a rather unknown SOAS 1st XV.
As SOAS went through phases following kick off, Imperial’s defence was proving difficult to break …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICURFC 2nd XV:  Welcome back Sylvia</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-icurfc-2nd-xv-welcome-back-sylvia/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Daniel Kirrane,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-icurfc-2nd-xv-welcome-back-sylvia/</guid>
        <description>The first game of the 2XV’s season was a home match against Queen Mary’s, a side who last season were 2 leagues above us. Due to this theoretical gulf in quality, the Queen Mary’s side decided to turn up 45 minutes late, leaving little time for a warm up. Little did they know that this 2XV side were …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Dominates Duathlon with VeloPark Victories</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-imperial-dominates-duathlon-with-velopark-victories/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark Pollock,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-imperial-dominates-duathlon-with-velopark-victories/</guid>
        <description>The morning started with an alarm sounding at 6:30AM – not a particularly cruel time for a triathlete, but for many students it was a relaxed Sunday morning lie-in. Undeterred by the rain and forecast thunderstorms, they made their way over to the Velopark in Stratford. Travelling on the tube with a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>F1 season review: post Japanese Grand Prix</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-f1-season-review-post-japanese-grand-prix/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-f1-season-review-post-japanese-grand-prix/</guid>
        <description>Following the Japanese Grand Prix Vettel’s chances of winning the 2018 F1 Championship have diminished to barely more than a dream. Following a season in which both Hamilton and Vettel have been closely matched throughout this is a bitter pill to swallow for Ferrari.
Following the first 10 races …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UEFA Nations League: explained</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-uefa-nations-league-explained/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-uefa-nations-league-explained/</guid>
        <description>This week the Premier League takes a break and the second round of fixtures in the all-new UEFA Nations League are taking place, but what even is the Nations League?
News stories circulated back before the first fixture that England gaffer Gareth Southgate had tried to explain the new competition …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ultimate frisbee fly out to Italy for an international beach tournament</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-ultimate-frisbee-fly-out-to-italy-for-an-international-beach-tournament/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>May Kyaw,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-ultimate-frisbee-fly-out-to-italy-for-an-international-beach-tournament/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Ultimate’s Disc Doctors recently participated in an international beach tournament, BURLA, from September 20th to September 23rd in Viareggio, Italy. The aim of attending BURLA was to allow our university team to participate in beach ultimate, which is not implemented during the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College Sailing Club travels to the Mediterranean</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-imperial-college-sailing-club-travels-to-the-mediterranean/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nilani Chandradeva,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-imperial-college-sailing-club-travels-to-the-mediterranean/</guid>
        <description>On the 30th of June, 12 members of the Imperial College Sailing Club met at Gatwick’s Wetherspoons before beginning the voyage to Corfu, Greece.
Upon a late night arrival at the marina, they carb loaded with the infamous Greek dish, gyros, and headed into town to join their training partners from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cross Country &amp; Athletics’ Welsh Adventure</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-cross-country-athletics-welsh-adventure/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-cross-country-athletics-welsh-adventure/</guid>
        <description>*wettest
Imperial’s Cross Country &amp;amp; Athletics Club became the largest sports club at Imperial last year, and to celebrate both the end of a fantastic season and the start of another the club travelled to the north coast of Wales for their summer tour in the second week of September.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get involved with sport at Imperial!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-get-involved-with-sport-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imraj Singh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-get-involved-with-sport-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Sport has been for myself, and many of my friends, an integral part of university life. Being at university can be stressful not only because of academic pressure, but also because of moving away from home, dealing with finances, making new friends and stresses from home, as well as being pushed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Baseball rank 8th in the Country</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-imperial-baseball-rank-8th-in-the-country/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonathan Cheung,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-imperial-baseball-rank-8th-in-the-country/</guid>
        <description>On the last Saturday of the term, the Imperial Falcons descended to Farnham Park for the National University Baseball Championships. The inconvenient date of the event meant many club members could not attend the tournament. Thankfully, we were able to field a full team due to Abrar Masud joining …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>WTF is Ultimate Frisbee? </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-wtf-is-ultimate-frisbee/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imraj Singh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-wtf-is-ultimate-frisbee/</guid>
        <description>Ultimate Frisbee, also known by cool kids as just ‘Ultimate’, is a relatively new sport, having only been developed in the late 1960s by a few students in New Jersey. Since its inception, the sport has exploded in popularity; from flinging cookie tin lids in a play-ground to being recognized by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICXCAC – regicide on the athletics track</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-icxcac-regicide-on-the-athletics-track/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max Thorp,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-icxcac-regicide-on-the-athletics-track/</guid>
        <description>Over the past month, Imperial Cross Country and Athletics Club have been fighting exam doom and gloom with record-breaking achievements. It all began at BUCS Outdoors in Bedford with one of their largest ever teams ready to challenge some of the best athletes in the country. Over the three-day …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial dodgeball: Championship teams battle it out in the final tournament of the year</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-imperial-dodgeball-championship-teams-battle-it-out-in-the-final-tournament-of-the-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lochlann Allison,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-imperial-dodgeball-championship-teams-battle-it-out-in-the-final-tournament-of-the-year/</guid>
        <description>Last Sunday, Imperial Wolverines ventured one last time out of the comforts of London into the wilderness of the north for the final university dodgeball fixture of the year: the University Championship. Teams from far and wide dropped their revision books and grabbed their balls to take part at the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>WTF is Futsal? Felix sport’s guide to little known high-velocity, quick-paced, team-orientated Spanish sport</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-wtf-is-futsal-felix-sport-s-guide-to-little-known-high-velocity-quick-paced-team-orientated-spanish-sport/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imraj Singh,Harry Lanz,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-wtf-is-futsal-felix-sport-s-guide-to-little-known-high-velocity-quick-paced-team-orientated-spanish-sport/</guid>
        <description>Futsal is a bit of a rogue sport: one of the rare beauties with a cult following. Relatively unknown in the UK, it has larger audiences in Argentina, Brazil, Spain, and Portugal – countries which have spawned some of the best football players in the world. That is no coincidence. The likes of Pelé, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LUCA Outdoors Championships II – revenge of ICXCAC</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-luca-outdoors-championships-ii-revenge-of-icxcac/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Mitchell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-luca-outdoors-championships-ii-revenge-of-icxcac/</guid>
        <description>LUCA outdoors – take two. Taking place at Lee Valley stadium on 28th April, this was an incredible event for ICXCAC and turned out to be our most successful ever athletics meet, in large part due to the enormous number of athletes that signed up to be part of the action.
The day began with a bang, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICXCAC head to the LUCA outdoors competition</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-icxcac-head-to-the-luca-outdoors-competition/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Mitchell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-icxcac-head-to-the-luca-outdoors-competition/</guid>
        <description>The sun was shining, and despite the early start for many, the ICXCAC team was smiling. Why? It was time for the LUCA (London Universities and Colleges Athletics) outdoors athletics series, beginning at Parliament Hill athletics track. On 15th April, the first meeting kicked off, with competitors …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cracking open a cold run with the boys</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-cracking-open-a-cold-run-with-the-boys/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Maynard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-cracking-open-a-cold-run-with-the-boys/</guid>
        <description>Last month, with the ‘mini-beast from the East’ spreading its frosty tendrils over the North Sea, the Met Office issued amber warnings for wind, ice, and snow across much of the UK. The same time, a detachment of hardy (foolish?) ICXCAC trail runners left London with their sights set on a very long …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fencing Men’s Second Team finish a triumphant year</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-fencing-men-s-second-team-finish-a-triumphant-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jake Reynolds,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-fencing-men-s-second-team-finish-a-triumphant-year/</guid>
        <description>In terms of BUCS points scored, fencing remains the most successful club at Imperial, and it has been an especially incredible season for the Men’s Second team. Remaining undefeated throughout our fourteen matches has led to promotion to a tier one league; a level never before reached by the team. …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
