<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/bcmaile/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/bcmaile/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>A beginner’s guide to public sex
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-a-beginners-guide-to-public-sex/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 17:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>B. C. Maile,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-a-beginners-guide-to-public-sex/</guid>
        <description>So, since this is the last issue before the Spring break, and as people customarily tend to travel during breaks, this article is going to be about taking advantage of opportunities to have sex in unusual locations. Of course, I’m not referring to France (their love of cheese is not unusual – just …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Self love
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-self-love/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 14:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>B. C. Maile,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-self-love/</guid>
        <description> Toys for girls If you’re a girl and you’ve never tried a sex toy, that’s absolutely fine. It’s your body and you should do with it as you please. I do feel, however, that if you weren’t aware of the existence of sex toys, you should probably know about them. There are a wide range of dildos and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Enter the kink | BDSM 101
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-enter-the-kink-bdsm-101/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 16:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>B. C. Maile,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-enter-the-kink-bdsm-101/</guid>
        <description> Following the election theme, today I’m going to talk about relinquishing control of yourself to someone who you deem trustworthy enough not to cause permanent damage to your well-being. Welcome to BDSM 101.
There’s been a fair bit of press around BDSM since the release of those Fifty Shades of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Enter the kink | Looning
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-enter-the-kink-looning/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 15:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>B. C. Maile,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-enter-the-kink-looning/</guid>
        <description>Dan got into the shower, washing himself. Holly said she would clear up the mess they had made after the pump-to-pop in the sleeping bag. He still couldn&amp;rsquo;t believe what Holly did for his birthday. They had had a few sessions with balloons before but nothing like this. Last time they had a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A gay and a lesbian walk into a bar...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-a-gay-and-a-lesbian-walk-into-a-bar/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 14:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>B. C. Maile,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-a-gay-and-a-lesbian-walk-into-a-bar/</guid>
        <description> This week, I met with B.R Coli, a female queer friend, to talk about sex. We wanted to shed some light on the general ins and outs and common misconceptions surrounding gay sex, as well as learn a bit about each other’s sex lives and see what common ground we have, and what’s different between man …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I heard you like... food?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-i-heard-you-like-food/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 18:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,B. C. Maile,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-i-heard-you-like-food/</guid>
        <description> Have you ever found yourself aroused by the thought of having a cream pie pushed into your face or cracking eggs over someone’s chest? Of course you have. Well, you’re not alone. This fringe phenomenon is called ‘Wet and Messy Fetishism’, often abbreviated to WAM or simply called sploshing. Fans of …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
