<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ss9011/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ss9011/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The Magical World of RPGs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-6-the-magical-world-of-rpgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 16:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanchit Sharma,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-6-the-magical-world-of-rpgs/</guid>
        <description>RPG is an arguably misleading term, which stands for “Role-Playing Game”. The reason I say it is arguably misleading is that there are very few games, both tabletop and otherwise, in which the player does not take on a role. Yet the term roleplaying game nevertheless has a very precise definition. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dance Dance Revolution: Kung Fu style
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-dance-dance-revolution-kung-fu-style/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 19:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanchit Sharma,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-dance-dance-revolution-kung-fu-style/</guid>
        <description>Kickbeat describes itself as “an innovative rhythm game with a kung fu theme, featuring fully 3D characters and high-energy music!” Which sounds pretty good. The reality is not quite as good as it seems at first.
In essence, Kickbeat is a classic four-button rhythm game – at the right time you press …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Always the Story, Sometimes the Choices, Mostly Monsters
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-always-the-story-sometimes-the-choices-mostly-monsters/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 01:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanchit Sharma,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-always-the-story-sometimes-the-choices-mostly-monsters/</guid>
        <description>Always Sometimes Monsters is an indie game by Vagabond Dog and Devolver Digital. The first time you load it up, you’ll see a tiny (560x454) window with the game logo and 3 buttons – New Game, Credits, and Quit. Yeah, no options. This is a pretty simple game. You can adjust the window by pressing F6 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Android Humble Bundle
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-30-android-humble-bundle/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 15:37:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanchit Sharma,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-30-android-humble-bundle/</guid>
        <description> The Humble Bundle with Android #7 is currently on sale. For those of you who don&amp;rsquo;t know what this is, the Humble Bundle is a sale in which a set of games are available for whatever price you choose. It started off as an indie game only bundle, but since then it has expanded and even THQ has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oil, oil everywhere...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-oil-oil-everywhere/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 22:47:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanchit Sharma,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-oil-oil-everywhere/</guid>
        <description>“Huh. Maxed out on oil again.” – Me, when playing Oil Rush. Oil Rush is an interesting take on the real time strategy genre. It is a naval strategy game that takes place in the future, where nuclear war has melted the polar ice caps leaving little habitable land on the planet. As such, many people …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to Esther island!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-welcome-to-esther-island/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 22:37:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanchit Sharma,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-welcome-to-esther-island/</guid>
        <description>&amp;ldquo;Dear Esther. The morning after I was washed ashore, salt in my ears, sand in my mouth and the waves always at my ankles, I felt as though everything had conspired to this one last shipwreck. I remembered nothing but water, stones in my belly and my shoes threatening to drag me underwater to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An otherworldly tutor
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-5-an-otherworldly-tutor/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 12:57:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanchit Sharma,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-5-an-otherworldly-tutor/</guid>
        <description>Ever wanted to build a boring wasteland of a planet into a thriving world? Or control giants that can influence the planet on a large scale? “Dammit, ocean giant, I said one space to the left!” Okay, command giants; they’re a bit imprecise. “Come back forest giant, I need you over here!” The silly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bringing ink to a gunfight
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-29-bringing-ink-to-a-gunfight/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 16:12:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanchit Sharma,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-29-bringing-ink-to-a-gunfight/</guid>
        <description>&amp;ldquo;Hey. You. Don’t you hear the bell? We need to get out of here, and fast. I’m here to help you. Rule number one: Don’t get me killed. Wait, where’s your sword? Stick to the darkness until you find it. Good thing you were out cold, looks like they don’t know you’re alive. Let’s keep it that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Electro-Swing at KOKO
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-electro-swing-at-koko/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 03:37:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanchit Sharma,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-electro-swing-at-koko/</guid>
        <description>November 21st, was an important day for British fans of the electro-swing band Caravan Palace. They held their first ever concert in the UK – which took place not too far from Imperial College, in the Camden KOKO venue.
Caravan Palace started off in France with three members – Vial, Payen, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Free vs. open source: why you should care
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-free-vs-open-source-why-you-should-care/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 21:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanchit Sharma,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-free-vs-open-source-why-you-should-care/</guid>
        <description>I recently had the opportunity to attend a talk by Richard Stallman, founder of the Free Software Foundation, and a strong Free software advocate. He spoke on Free software, and the rights of us all as users of software, and in the process he brought something to my attention.
A term is being …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
