<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/fergusjohnson/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/fergusjohnson/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Finish Mile(s) Ahead</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-imperial-finish-mile-s-ahead/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-imperial-finish-mile-s-ahead/</guid>
        <description>Just one day after their triumph at the Battle of Battersea, as previously reported by Felix, Imperial’s top athletes headed off to one of the iconic parts of London for the Westminster Mile, a legacy event from the 2012 Olympic Games.
Starting on the Mall facing towards Horse Guards Parade, the one …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Need for Speed at BUCS Outdoor Athletics Champs</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-need-for-speed-at-bucs-outdoor-athletics-champs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-need-for-speed-at-bucs-outdoor-athletics-champs/</guid>
        <description>Over the Early May bank holiday weekend whilst students across the nation were locked indoors studying hard for exams, the country’s finest student athletes gathered at Bedford’s premium track for an ultimate athletics showdown.
The weekend began with heats on Saturday, with former-Club Captain Alex …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial stay on track in LUCA Athletics League</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-imperial-stay-on-track-in-luca-athletics-league/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-imperial-stay-on-track-in-luca-athletics-league/</guid>
        <description>A badly scheduled athletics calendar meant the second meet in the London Universities and Colleges Athletics (LUCA) Outdoors League fell on 20th April - Easter Saturday.
Expectations of a severely depleted squad failed to materialise, however, with 9 stoic athletes still keen to compete at the Lee …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s in the Baggs! Imperial lift silverware after final race in the London Universities Cross Country League</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-it-s-in-the-baggs-imperial-lift-silverware-after-final-race-in-the-london-universities-cross-country-league/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-it-s-in-the-baggs-imperial-lift-silverware-after-final-race-in-the-london-universities-cross-country-league/</guid>
        <description>It was a glorious Wednesday afternoon in the middle of February - the hottest winter day on record - which was no surprise to many of Imperial’s cross country runners who knew this competition had been hotting up for some time.
The final fixture in the London Universities and Colleges Cross Country …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Cross Country on verge of greatness with one race left in the LUCA XC League</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-imperial-cross-country-on-verge-of-greatness-with-one-race-left-in-the-luca-xc-league/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-imperial-cross-country-on-verge-of-greatness-with-one-race-left-in-the-luca-xc-league/</guid>
        <description>As dawn broke on Alexandra Palace, the birds began to sing and the mud glistened brightly in the morning sun.
The day was set to be a cold one, with a gentle dew hovering over the freshly watered grass, and patches of bog forming after the recent rain.
Meanwhile, away from the tranquility, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Promising signs for ICXCAC as they begin 2019 with a successful training weekend</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-promising-signs-for-icxcac-as-they-begin-2019-with-a-successful-training-weekend/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-promising-signs-for-icxcac-as-they-begin-2019-with-a-successful-training-weekend/</guid>
        <description>ICXCAC’s runners returned from the Christmas break in dire need of a training weekend, and 2019’s winter tour destination was Church Stretton – a quaint town just outside Shropshire’s county town of Shrewsbury.
During the late Victorian period the small town was known as “Little Switzerland” and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cross country gives indoors athletics a try</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-cross-country-gives-indoors-athletics-a-try/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-cross-country-gives-indoors-athletics-a-try/</guid>
        <description>This week Cross Country &amp;amp; Athletics ditched muddy hills to tackle some faster terrain - an indoor athletics track.
The state-of-the-art Lee Valley Athletics Centre is situated amidst a desolate wasteland in the far reaches of north London. After meeting at Beit Quad to collect some of the famous …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICXC regain Bannister Cup in final LXCL of 2018</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-icxc-regain-bannister-cup-in-final-lxcl-of-2018/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-icxc-regain-bannister-cup-in-final-lxcl-of-2018/</guid>
        <description>Last Wednesday, 14th November, just two weeks after Mitcham Common’s sunny race, London’s sturdy athletes took out their spikes once more to compete in this term’s (and 2018’s) final LUCA Cross-Country League race, the much-anticipated Wimbledon Common.
With laps being longer than average at 4.7km, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cross Country Runs for Parliament (Hill)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-cross-country-runs-for-parliament-hill/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Hart,Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-cross-country-runs-for-parliament-hill/</guid>
        <description>The first few weeks of October always seem to have surprisingly good weather to put the new freshers at ease, but eventually the first day of rain comes.
For years, engineers and scientists have been trying to refine the Navier-Stokes equations enough to be able to predict weather accurately. One …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UEFA Nations League: explained</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-uefa-nations-league-explained/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-uefa-nations-league-explained/</guid>
        <description>This week the Premier League takes a break and the second round of fixtures in the all-new UEFA Nations League are taking place, but what even is the Nations League?
News stories circulated back before the first fixture that England gaffer Gareth Southgate had tried to explain the new competition …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cross Country &amp; Athletics’ Welsh Adventure</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-cross-country-athletics-welsh-adventure/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-cross-country-athletics-welsh-adventure/</guid>
        <description>*wettest
Imperial’s Cross Country &amp;amp; Athletics Club became the largest sports club at Imperial last year, and to celebrate both the end of a fantastic season and the start of another the club travelled to the north coast of Wales for their summer tour in the second week of September.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICXCAC – overtakes and underpasses</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-icxcac-overtakes-and-underpasses/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-icxcac-overtakes-and-underpasses/</guid>
        <description>Sunday 11th March saw the intrepid ICXCAC runners head to the desolate wasteland of Milton Keynes for its annual festival of running. With the majority of the team choosing to tackle the half-marathon distance, and a couple opting for the more manageable 10K, they all met at the reasonably early …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC Cross Country and Athletics go on a Winter DorchesTour</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-ic-cross-country-and-athletics-go-on-a-winter-dorchestour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-ic-cross-country-and-athletics-go-on-a-winter-dorchestour/</guid>
        <description>It’s January again, and to offset the misery of the darkest mornings of the year Imperial’s Cross Country and Athletics Club once again had cunningly planned a weekend escape from the bustling capital to somewhere slightly quieter. Last year saw a minibus-load make the trek up North to Newcastle; …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brighton-wards and upwards for ICXCAC</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-brighton-wards-and-upwards-for-icxcac/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-brighton-wards-and-upwards-for-icxcac/</guid>
        <description>Sunday 19th November was the date of Imperial College Cross Country &amp;amp; Athletics Club’s first road race of the year: the Brighton 10k.
With a meeting time of 6am at London Bridge Station, by the early hours 50 students were already rising groggily from their beds, eyes blearily checking their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICXCAC Trail Team summit Mount Snowdon</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-icxcac-trail-team-summit-mount-snowdon/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-icxcac-trail-team-summit-mount-snowdon/</guid>
        <description>With first term now in full-swing, and some of ICXCAC’s athletes getting bored of endless laps of Hyde Park, trail captain Henry had organised a timely trail running tour to the notorious Imperial-owned St. Mary’s Mountain Hut in the deepest, darkest corner of Snowdonia National Park.
Having failed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mud, sweat, and beers: the Cross-Country racing season begins at Parliament Hill</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-mud-sweat-and-beers-the-cross-country-racing-season-begins-at-parliament-hill/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-mud-sweat-and-beers-the-cross-country-racing-season-begins-at-parliament-hill/</guid>
        <description>It was a dreary Wednesday afternoon, and a crowd of chilly-looking runners were gathering in Beit Quad, sporting distinctive navy and red vests rather than the gowns and mortarboards donned by a large proportion of the graduating students around campus. That could only mean one thing: it must be the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cross Country and Athletics reach dizzying heights in the Pyrenees</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-cross-country-and-athletics-reach-dizzying-heights-in-the-pyrenees/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-cross-country-and-athletics-reach-dizzying-heights-in-the-pyrenees/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday 23rd August Imperial College’s Cross Country and Athletics team began to make their journey to their international summer tour. Their destination was Font-Romeu – 1800m above sea-level in the Pyrenees and a 2.5 hour 1€ bus journey from the airport in Perpignan. Upon arrival, it was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Keeping Track of Imperial’s Cross Country &amp; Athletics Club
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-keeping-track-of-imperials-cross-country-athletics-club/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:42:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-keeping-track-of-imperials-cross-country-athletics-club/</guid>
        <description>Saturday the 27th of May saw the final event in the London Universities and Colleges Athletics (LUCA) outdoors championship take place. The series of three athletics meets between the London universities had previously visited St. Mary’s and Woodford athletics tracks, and the destination for the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
