<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ra2410/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ra2410/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Supersonic Festival Preview
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-2-supersonic-festival-preview/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 12:49:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-2-supersonic-festival-preview/</guid>
        <description> Birmingham’s Supersonic Festival is undoubtedly an institution in British experimental music. I was lucky enough to attend their last festival in 2012, and found it to be a postively life-changing experience, which featured a great mix of obscure and impressive new discoveries to more established …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Henriksen’s Cosmic Creation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-henriksens-cosmic-creation/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 16:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-henriksens-cosmic-creation/</guid>
        <description>This week, I’ve set out on a factfinding mission to discover whether the latest effort by Arve Henriksen, entitled Cosmic Creation, lives up to its grandiose title. Despite the obvious spoiler of my review, I can tell you that my conclusion was that it does indeed live up to the title. Aside from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Review: Bohren &amp; der Club of Gore
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-review-bohren-der-club-of-gore/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 03:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-review-bohren-der-club-of-gore/</guid>
        <description>After more than twenty years of plugging away with a familiar sound, one that combines jazz, drone, doom and many other genres into an agonisingly slow rhythm, Bohren &amp;amp; der Club of Gore released an album earlier this month which does little to change this sound.
Their classic sound has been …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Pelican Brief
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-the-pelican-brief/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:08:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-the-pelican-brief/</guid>
        <description>Following the release of their latest effort, _Forever Becoming _(the rather excellent, if a little mystifying artwork is shown on the right) , an album that is instantly distinguishable as Pelican, while still breaking new ground, I had the chance to talk to Pelican’s two guitarists, founder member …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chris Forsyth – Solar Motel Review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-chris-forsyth-solar-motel-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 18:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-chris-forsyth-solar-motel-review/</guid>
        <description>Chris Forsyth is an American psych rock guitarist much admired by myself for his dabblings in drone and general guitar badass-ery. In my review of his previous full length, Kenzo Deluxe, I noted that Forsyth was essentially returning the guitar to some past glory, shedding it of the threadbare …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Embarrassments or Riches?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-embarrassments-or-riches/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 09:57:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-embarrassments-or-riches/</guid>
        <description>Sergio Sorrentino &amp;amp; Machinefabriek Vignettes
Autodidactic Dutch graphic artist – turned sound artist Machinefabriek recently added to his prolofic 2013 output with this effort, a collaboration with Sergio Sorrentino, an Italian avante-garde guitarist considered to be one of the best modern …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Immersed in Fanboy Heaven
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-immersed-in-fanboy-heaven/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 09:33:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-immersed-in-fanboy-heaven/</guid>
        <description>n my less pretentious teenage years I was a big fan of all things metal. I gradually, however, found myself gravitating away from the more pedestrian areas of the genre, such as Slayer, who employed a classic thrash sound that influenced many. It became clear to me that the genre had moved way …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oneohtrix Point Hecker
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-oneohtrix-point-hecker/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 00:29:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-oneohtrix-point-hecker/</guid>
        <description>Tim Hecker and Oneohtrix Point Never are two of the most successful ambient musicians of recent times. Tim Hecker is widely famed for his immersive live performance, where he plays to an audience on a pitch black stage in a pitch black venue, putting all of the audience’s attention on the music and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Album: Chalk White Nights
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-8-21-album-chalk-white-nights/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2013 07:05:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-8-21-album-chalk-white-nights/</guid>
        <description>Stranger By Starlight is a collaboration between Eugene Robinson of legendary experimental rock band Oxbow and Anthony Saggers, the man behind projects such as Stray Ghost. The name alone summarises the sort of unsettling ambience to the music, along with an album title which I can only hope is a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This Week At Oto: Rushford &amp; Talia
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-this-week-at-oto-rushford-talia/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 23:02:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-this-week-at-oto-rushford-talia/</guid>
        <description>Between a live date in Oto as a duo and another in a large ensemble with Oren Ambarchi, I was able to grab an interview with Australian musucians James Rushford and Joe Talia. Aside from my aiming for an inside scoop about the night’s rendition of ‘Knots’ (from Ambarchi’s Audience Of One), we …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Album Review: Palms
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-6-album-review-palms/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 19:48:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-6-album-review-palms/</guid>
        <description>Released on Mike Patton’s Ipecac label, Palms sees 3 members of Isis join Chino Moreno of Deftones fame, making an album whose sound is somewhere between the two. Where Aaron Turner’s inscrutable vocals on esoteric, often philosophical topics (Panopticon) or abstract concept albums (Oceanic) gave …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cassette Culture: RRR Records
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-28-cassette-culture-rrr-records/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2013 14:42:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-28-cassette-culture-rrr-records/</guid>
        <description>After hearing about RRR records through their Recycled series, I discovered a contribution to the development and proliferation of noise music that goes far beyond a series of tapes which brings together some of noise’s most important artists. Based in Lowell, Massachusetts, RRR has the distinction …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Melvins: Live Review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-melvins-live-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 22:21:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-melvins-live-review/</guid>
        <description>The Melvins have long since become an institution, one of the most influential bands in modern rock. In recent years however, they have not simply been resting on the laurels of their classic albums, but exploring new territory and breaking new ground. Their album as Melvins Lite, a stripped down …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dentistry: make an appointment soon
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-dentistry-make-an-appointment-soon/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 14:43:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-dentistry-make-an-appointment-soon/</guid>
        <description>I recently got in touch with Cian Walker and Patrick Fennelly of Irish band Dentistry. Their debut last year released on Forwind Records made quite an impression on me and I got a chance to discuss their approach to making music.
Riaz Agahi: I read somewhere that Dentistry started as a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Roots of Hacker Farm
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-roots-of-hacker-farm/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 21:38:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-roots-of-hacker-farm/</guid>
        <description>Ahead of the Hacker Farm exclusive on IC Radio next week, I spoke to them about their influences, motivations and what’s coming up next. Kek W ably walked me through the HF ethos.
Punk Bucket
We’ve all known one another since the Punk Era – we grew up during that period, so Punk as well as Glam, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cold Cuts of Noise
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-cold-cuts-of-noise/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 01:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-cold-cuts-of-noise/</guid>
        <description>Merzbow is widely regarded as the biggest name in noise music; the man’s been blistering eardrums in over 350 recordings since 1979. Like most of the experimental music world, in addition to copious solo albums, there are copious collaborations, often live.
This album, mastered by James Plotkin, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Album review: Maranata - Royal Hex
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-album-review-maranata-royal-hex/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 13:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-album-review-maranata-royal-hex/</guid>
        <description>Free-noise duo Maranata have collaborated with some big figures in the experimental scene including Maja S.K Ratkje and C.Spencer Yeh. On this effort, released on a 175 cassette run (remember that, it’s important), they collaborate with Sayaka Himeno, Sakaya Himeno of Japanese all girl trio …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fear in a Handful of Dust
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-fear-in-a-handful-of-dust/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 22:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-fear-in-a-handful-of-dust/</guid>
        <description>There is a scene in Fitzgerald’s novel The Great Gatsby, where he describes a valley of ashes, a wasteland in suburban New York, full of dirt, decay, ash, and poverty. If such a place had a soundtrack, it would probably be Hacker Farm. Such is the intimidating, disconcerting nature of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Neurosis in conversation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-neurosis-in-conversation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 03:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-neurosis-in-conversation/</guid>
        <description>One of the most influential bands out there, progressive sludge outfit Neurosis have left their mark on the metal scene and anyone who’s seen their live performance. After seeing an impressive show of theirs at ATP,I was able to speak to Scott Kelly of Neurosis about Neurosis’ decision to remove …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ATP Xmas Special
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-atp-xmas-special/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 22:56:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-atp-xmas-special/</guid>
        <description>ATP in many ways can be seen as an embodiment of alternative music, often attended by those who know their music, it never fails to provide a selection of the finest alternative music out there, sweeping a wide range of musical genres in every line up. This quality is coupled with a spirit of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Education in Guitar
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-23-an-education-in-guitar/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2012 00:19:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-23-an-education-in-guitar/</guid>
        <description>Ever since I first discovered his music, Chris Forsyth has been one of my favourite musicians. A psych rock guitarist, he proved himself worthy to support Grouper due to his use of drone and a thirst for experimentalism, but he elegantly balanced this with some more conventional use of the guitar …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Supersonic Festival 2012
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-supersonic-festival-2012/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 03:14:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-supersonic-festival-2012/</guid>
        <description>The 10th Supersonic Festival was held in the Custard Factory in Birmingham. Since the line-up was announced some months ago, I had been excited about attending. The slogan on a lot of the commemorative t-shirts was ‘celebrating 10 years of adventurous music.’ My experiences ranged from the obscure …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>O. Ambarchi: an introduction
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-25-o-ambarchi-an-introduction/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 18:59:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-25-o-ambarchi-an-introduction/</guid>
        <description>Modern music has few people prolific as Australian guitarist and multi-instrumentalist Oren Ambarchi. He started out as free jazz drummer in his native country before moving to guitar, which he plays experimentally and unconventionally, producing sounds alien to traditional music.
His music is of a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>5/4 Respect: A Tribute to Math Rock
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-25-54-respect-a-tribute-to-math-rock/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 18:53:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-25-54-respect-a-tribute-to-math-rock/</guid>
        <description>Although they have often used larger set ups, Hella, at its barebones, is guitarist Spencer Seim and drummer extraordinaire Zach Hill, who have played together since high school. They released their first EP, Leather Diamond, in 2001. Even in that early release, the Sacramento, California band have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>5/4 Respect: A Tribute to Math Rock
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-54-respect-a-tribute-to-math-rock/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 20:13:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-54-respect-a-tribute-to-math-rock/</guid>
        <description>Shellac are another great Math Rock band. You may know them for including prolific producer Steve Albini, or you may know them for the sound, which is pretty much abrasion itself. From the distorted, almost noisy guitars, to the vocals, aggressively shouted, often about violence and fighting and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>5/4 Respect: A Tribute to Math Rock
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-54-respect-a-tribute-to-math-rock/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 17:47:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-54-respect-a-tribute-to-math-rock/</guid>
        <description>Possibly the most original of all the bands I will be covering, and by far the most influential, Slint first formed in their native Louisville, Kentucky in 1986. In addition to reuniting for some live shows in 2005 and 2007, they existed for 5 years, breaking up in 1991 after the completion of their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Did the best team really win?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-did-the-best-team-really-win/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 21:37:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-did-the-best-team-really-win/</guid>
        <description>Picture the scene: despite a good performance from Birmingham, Arsenal grind out a 3-1 result. I collect £45 from a bet, Arsenal collect their first trophy since 2005 and play the rest of the season free from pressure, knocking Barcelona out of the Champion’s League and bringing the title race into …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are foreign managers victimised in the Premier League?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-are-foreign-managers-victimised-in-the-premier-league/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 20:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Riaz Agahi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-are-foreign-managers-victimised-in-the-premier-league/</guid>
        <description>One of the stories that has emerged over the transfer window period is the clash between certain premier league managers. Houllier is such a manager, who has received criticism due to his conduct over the signing of Darren Bent and what is seen as an insulting bid for Blackpool’s Charlie Adam.
Bruce …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
