<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/aya_hayakawa/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/aya_hayakawa/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>A Christmas Carol</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-a-christmas-carol/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laura Casas,Aya Hayakawa,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-a-christmas-carol/</guid>
        <description>3 stars
This ‘musical play’ is an original adaptation of a well-known and loved novella, thanks to the fresh use of music and direction. The use of carol-singing and handbell performances to break up the well-known narrative play a role in creating a Christmassy and joyful environment on stage, but …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College DramSoc Presents: 11 Miles</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-imperial-college-dramsoc-presents-11-miles/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aya Hayakawa,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-imperial-college-dramsoc-presents-11-miles/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
Based on the real journal entries, 11 Miles follows Captain Scott’s journey to the South Pole with his four companions: Evans, Wilson, Bowers, and Oates. The audience comes to understand the meaning behind “11 miles” during the play as they hear about the tragedies that struck the team on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Touching the Void Review</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-touching-void-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aya Hayakawa,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-touching-void-review/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
Based on Joe Simpson’s mountaineering memoir and adapted by David Greig, Touching the Void is a story about the adventures of Joe and Simon to Siula Grande in the Peruvian Andes. As the double meaning of the title infers, the significant factor of the play are the feelings of the characters …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Music of the Night</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-music-of-the-night/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aya Hayakawa,Laura Casas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-music-of-the-night/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
In theatrical performances, the orchestra has a supporting function, often lacking the appreciation that it deserves. In this one-night-only show of hit songs from the most famous musicals, the orchestra is on stage alongside the singers, as opposed to being in the pit. This unusual …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Magic Flute - Mozart’s classic</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-magic-flute-mozarts-classic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aya Hayakawa,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-magic-flute-mozarts-classic/</guid>
        <description>It isn’t easy to picture a more magical setting than sitting in the historical auditorium of the Royal Opera House as you listen to the overture, eagerly waiting for the curtain to rise.
Back for its seventh revival at Covent Garden, Mozart’s Die Zauberflöte (The Magic Flute) manages to retain the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Lovely Bones: A Different Viewpoint on Death</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-lovely-bones-different-viewpoint-death/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aya Hayakawa,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-lovely-bones-different-viewpoint-death/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
The first thing to capture your attention when entering the theatre is the great mirror which extends above the stage. The reflective structure is only one of many creative tools present in this production through which the main character’s unique story-telling is done. The minimal but …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
