<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/eb1408/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/eb1408/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Put lead in your pencil
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-put-lead-in-your-pencil/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 21:11:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emilie Beauchamp,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-put-lead-in-your-pencil/</guid>
        <description>Life drawing is an activity that a lot of people would like to do, but sometimes don’t dare to. For some, the nudity and sterility of classical art classes and the applied attention of overly zealous pseudo-artists in the room can be very intimidating, or maybe simply boring. But rejoice, as a new, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Not waving but possibly drowning
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-not-waving-but-possibly-drowning/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 22:38:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emilie Beauchamp,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-not-waving-but-possibly-drowning/</guid>
        <description>The Argentinian dance troop came to town preceded by its reputation. Some six years ago, Fuerzabruta re-opened the Roundhouse with an acrobatic extravaganza that left a permanent mark in the minds of so many Londoners as the most amazing show they had ever seen. The group, directed by Diqui James …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Grand-age
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-a-grand-age/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 02:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emilie Beauchamp,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-a-grand-age/</guid>
        <description>This autumn, a new theatre company has joined the ranks of the prestigious London scene: the Michael Grandage Company (MGC). Born from the union of two notorieties of the UK repertoire, artistic director Michael Grandage and executive producer James Bierman, this new troop has only just revealed its …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Breaking a fourth wall
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-breaking-a-fourth-wall/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 02:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emilie Beauchamp,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-breaking-a-fourth-wall/</guid>
        <description>If you are a fan of extraordinary theatrical experiences and still have room on your Christmas gift list, have a look at the world acclaimed show Fuerzabruta passing by London next January. This Argentine-born multi-sensory spectacle, translating literally into ‘brute force’, uses state-of-the-art …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Obama Claims Second Term
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-obama-claims-second-term/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 12:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emilie Beauchamp,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-obama-claims-second-term/</guid>
        <description> Last Tuesday, 6 November 2012, Americans re-elected Barack Obama as the President of the United States, for a second and last four year mandate. It was a slim victory after a harrowing campaign, nothing as glamorous as his first ‘Yes we can’ pinnacle, but still a win. Shall we finally see Obama …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
