<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/pg405/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/pg405/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Priya&#39;s Epic South American Adventure
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-7-18-priyas-epic-south-american-adventure/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2011 12:45:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Priya Garg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-7-18-priyas-epic-south-american-adventure/</guid>
        <description>[photo id=17]Click the linked text to read more about Priya&amp;rsquo;s trip
For eight weeks starting in September 2010 we decided to embark on an epic, whistlestop tour of South America, following the well-renowned gringo trail. Beginning in Rio de Janeiro, we soaked in the Latin vibrancy and passion …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Return of the Mummy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-return-of-the-mummy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 21:03:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Priya Garg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-return-of-the-mummy/</guid>
        <description>Arequipa, informally termed “la ciudad blanca” due to its luxurious white buildings, almost Arabic in stone and construction, lies in the Andes mountains overlooked by the looming snow-peaked volcano of El Misti, which rises majestically some 5822 feet above the city. Bordering El Misti lay the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Trekking to Machu Picchu
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-12-trekking-to-machu-picchu/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 16:16:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Priya Garg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-12-trekking-to-machu-picchu/</guid>
        <description>Cusco (or Qosqo in the native Quechua) is the historic capital of the Inca Empire in South-Eastern Peru. It consists of windy cobbled streets, black whorled iron fences, spacious plazas, expansive and luxurious fountains, ceramic plant pots and is home to a constant whisper of “Inca Trail Senorita?” …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bolivia: calamity and comfort
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-27-bolivia-calamity-and-comfort/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 15:27:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Priya Garg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-27-bolivia-calamity-and-comfort/</guid>
        <description>We descended via a smog-filled cliff overhung by green leaves, to a city clustered within a valley, full of tiny red houses. We passed by unfinished brick buildings, tumbling mechanics, crumbling newsagents, two children stroking a graffiti-covered wall and an elderly woman with a baby swung across …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Some Santiagan satisfaction
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-some-santiagan-satisfaction/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 18:25:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Priya Garg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-some-santiagan-satisfaction/</guid>
        <description>After finally recovering from my bout of food poisoning, we ventured out of the suburbs of Santiago and up through the drastically arid bush to the national park. Here we were able to see the Santiagans relaxing and socialising in typical South American fashion – as always, every day and night is a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tall tales and the runs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-21-tall-tales-and-the-runs/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2011 12:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Priya Garg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-21-tall-tales-and-the-runs/</guid>
        <description>Mendoza is a cosmopolitan city in the north of Argentina, crushed by an earthquake and rebuilt from the foundations, leading to expansive sunny reading parks with blue tiled fountains, cathedrals, large plazas and shopping malls. In the parks lie big wooden chests in which you can pick out copies of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The underrated sound of silence
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-the-underrated-sound-of-silence/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 19:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Priya Garg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-the-underrated-sound-of-silence/</guid>
        <description>A bus took us round meandering long corners and sharp curves on our way to San Carlos de Bariloche, which rests at the foothills of the Andes, until we finally reached Argentina’s answer to the Lake District. Snow-capped mountains lay in the distance as we rumbled towards our destination, huge …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tragic tourism perils
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-tragic-tourism-perils/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 20:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Priya Garg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-tragic-tourism-perils/</guid>
        <description>After many buses and a short internal flight, we hauled ourselves and our somehow heavier backpacks to the small town of Foz do Iguaçu, the closest resting point in Brazil en route to the famous Iguaçu Falls of the dramatic ‘terra de cataratas’ (land of the waterfalls). The Iguaçu Falls are formed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ambling Argentinean escapades
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-ambling-argentinean-escapades/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 20:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Priya Garg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-ambling-argentinean-escapades/</guid>
        <description>Surviving a semi-camo twenty four hour bus journey, we arrived at the slightly grubby omnibus terminal in the iconic metropolis of Buenos Aires. Throwing ourselves onto the Subte (Argentina’s answer to the tube) we were presented with an antique wooden carriage complete with grey leather sashes …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Finding tranquility in chaos
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-finding-tranquility-in-chaos/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 18:43:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Priya Garg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-finding-tranquility-in-chaos/</guid>
        <description>Our second day in Rio de Janeiro had arrived and we wanted to see the acclaimed towering figure that stands guard atop Mount Corcovado, Christ the Redeemer. From nearly every vantage point in Rio – whether roaming down the random ´Rues´ in Botefugo or actually climbing the winding road past Santa …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My South American debut
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-my-south-american-debut/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 20:20:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Priya Garg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-my-south-american-debut/</guid>
        <description>We emerged from twenty-three hours of flying like wild animals, bleary eyed and not used to natural light. As the sun of Rio de Janeiro washed over us, we stumbled out of the airport dragging our bags behind us.
Almost immediately we were presented with a display of what is termed ‘Latin passion’. A …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
