<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/freddie_ugo/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/freddie_ugo/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The Game Awards: Nominees, Discussion and Editor’s Top Picks of the Year. Time to get Hyped!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-game-awards-nominees-discussion-editors-top-picks-of-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freddie Ugo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-game-awards-nominees-discussion-editors-top-picks-of-year/</guid>
        <description>Shitty weather, extreme fatigue and incessantly annoying Christmas music. There are many signs that the end of the year is upon us, but one that is much cheerier – and a great topic of discussion – is The Game Awards. Effectively the Oscars of video games, The Game Awards celebrates the best games …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Most Influential Games of the Decade: Felix Games Breaks it Down</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-most-influentiual-games-decade-felix-games-breaks-it-down/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freddie Ugo,Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-most-influentiual-games-decade-felix-games-breaks-it-down/</guid>
        <description>Redefining Open World Adventures: The Legend of Zelda Breath of the Wild
Despite being one of a long list of amazing Zelda games, Breath of the Wild is set apart by its unique method of story-telling and its risky gameplay choices that definitely payed off. Breath of the Wild is unlike other Zelda …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Guide to Video Game Collecting in 2019</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-guide-video-game-collecting-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freddie Ugo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-guide-video-game-collecting-2019/</guid>
        <description>As an avid fan of all things gaming, I love to look over at my wall and see stacks of games lining the shelves. From the Atari 2600 to the Nintendo Switch, I love them all; unfortunately, I have a student budget which does not come close to fuelling my need for games. Over the years, though, I have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pokémon Sword and Pokémon Shield Review</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-pokemon-sword-shield-review-eight-gen-fresh-as-first/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freddie Ugo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-pokemon-sword-shield-review-eight-gen-fresh-as-first/</guid>
        <description>Right, listen up everyone. You’re all wrong. Pokémon Sword and Shield are amazing, the hate for it is, for the most part, unfounded, and here’s why.
First of all, a quick disclaimer: this is a review of Pokémon Sword and Shield. I have fully completed Shield and am working my way through Sword …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Retro Review: Fallout 1 (1997) - PC. The Beginning of an Illustrious yet Controversial Franchise</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-retro-review-fallout-1-1997-pc-beginning-illustrious-controversial-franchise/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freddie Ugo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-retro-review-fallout-1-1997-pc-beginning-illustrious-controversial-franchise/</guid>
        <description>So, this is where it all began. In 1997 Interplay Entertainment released Fallout: A Post Nuclear Roleplaying Game. Even though this is the first official Fallout game, it was originally developed as a sequel to 1988’s Wasteland. After Interplay lost the rights to Wasteland, Fallout took on its own …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sonic the Hedgehog. Wait... is it Good Now?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-sonic-hedgehog-wait-good-now/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freddie Ugo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-sonic-hedgehog-wait-good-now/</guid>
        <description>Earlier this year, Paramount released a trailer for the new Sonic the Hedgehog movie. One word describes this: terrifying. The render of Sonic was closer to a deformed cat than to what Sonic should look like in the games. Boasting human-like teeth that a dentist would be proud of (clearly flossing) …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Blizzcon 2019: The Ultimate Redemption Arc, or Just Another Out of Season April Fools’ Joke?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-Blizzcon-2019-ultimate-redemption-arc-or-april-fools-joke/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freddie Ugo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-Blizzcon-2019-ultimate-redemption-arc-or-april-fools-joke/</guid>
        <description>After the failure of last year’s Blizzcon with the likes of Diablo Immortal, and the recent controversy surrounding Activision Blizzard, all eyes looked to this year in anticipation of how they could redeem themselves. Oh, did they ever! Let’s take a deep dive into all the major announcements from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>POV: It’s Tricky to Rock a Rhyme That’s Right on Time</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-POV-tricky-to-rock-a-rhyme-thats-right-on-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freddie Ugo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-POV-tricky-to-rock-a-rhyme-thats-right-on-time/</guid>
        <description>The SSX franchise is the Tony Hawk’s Skateboarding of the snow (sorry Shawn White). Fast-paced, meticulous focus on gameplay, absolutely amazing soundtracks and a few failures recently with the franchise… But I am not here to tell you about all the bad with SSX, I’m here to spout about the pure …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fallout 1st, Not the 1st, 2nd or 3rd Thing Wrong with this Game…</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-fallout-1st-not-first-second-third-thing-wrong-with-game/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freddie Ugo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-fallout-1st-not-first-second-third-thing-wrong-with-game/</guid>
        <description>Bethesda. A name which, until recently, brought joy to many people’s ears. On the 14th November 2018, this all changed; the release of Fallout 76 was the beginning of a year of seemingly endless controversy. Why are we bringing this up again you ask? Well, after all the issues which have cropped up …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>POV: Cytus 2: Electric Boogaloo</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-POV-cytus-2-electric-boogaloo/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freddie Ugo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-POV-cytus-2-electric-boogaloo/</guid>
        <description>Hey all! This week I have been doing something a bit different: I have been religiously playing a mobile game! Now before you pull out the torches and pitch-forks, hear me out!
Cytus 2, released January 2018, is a rhythm game developed by Rayark Inc. This game did not seem like much to me at first …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>POV: The 2019 CTWC - The Year of Upsetris</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-POV-2019-CTWTC-year-upsetris/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freddie Ugo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-POV-2019-CTWTC-year-upsetris/</guid>
        <description>Following on from last week’s article covering the Classic Tetris World Championship, it is time to share the results!
It took place from the 19th - 21st and I was following it the whole way. Friday started fairly low-key. A quick Dr. Mario tournament followed by a speedrun competition in Tetris: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ring Fit Adventure - Review: Buff Dragons and Sentient Pilates Rings... What More do you Need?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-ring-fit-adventure-review-buff-dragons-sentient-pilates-rings-what-more-need/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freddie Ugo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-ring-fit-adventure-review-buff-dragons-sentient-pilates-rings-what-more-need/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
The latest in a long-running list of Nintendo’s whacky peripheral ideas: Ring Fit Adventure, fight demons whilst doing pilates. Last month Nintendo announced the game seemingly out of nowhere. The premise is odd, attach a joy-con to your left leg via a strap and attach another to the top …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Classic Tetris® World Championship: the Ultimate Test of Mental and Physical Acuteness</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-classic-tetris-world-championship-ultimate-test-mental-physical-acuteness/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freddie Ugo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-classic-tetris-world-championship-ultimate-test-mental-physical-acuteness/</guid>
        <description>Tetris. A game we all know and love. Some dub it the ‘Perfect Game’ and for good reason. Created in 1984 in the USSR by Alexey Pajitnov, it quickly took the world by storm with its addictive yet deceptively simple gameplay. Selling over 170 million copies to date, the general concept has remained …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>POV: Ah, the Glory Days Before Dawn of the Blue Shell!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-POV-glory-days-before-dawn-blue-shell/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freddie Ugo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-POV-glory-days-before-dawn-blue-shell/</guid>
        <description>On my way back home this weekend I was strolling past a CeX (Computer Exchange) shop when I caught a glimpse of something in the corner of my eye. For the decent price of £25, I happened upon a fully complete in box version of Super Mario Kart for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System. Given my …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>POV: This Game and I are Having a Fallout...</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-POV-this-game-and-I-having-fallout/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freddie Ugo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-POV-this-game-and-I-having-fallout/</guid>
        <description>So recently I have been trying to complete every game in the Fallout series in order. Yes, that’s right EVERY game… even the trashy PS2 game ‘Brotherhood of Steel’ that nobody remembers for good reason. The journey has been a right laugh and I only have 3 games left. Fallout 4 and Fallout 76 are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“This is for the Players”, but is it for the Leaders? Shawn Layden is the Latest Executive to Leave Sony</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-this-is-for-players-but-is-it-for-leaders-shawn-layden-latest-executive-leave-sony/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freddie Ugo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-this-is-for-players-but-is-it-for-leaders-shawn-layden-latest-executive-leave-sony/</guid>
        <description>After 32 years working at Sony, Shawn Layden becomes the latest in a long list of executives to leave the company. On 1st October he stepped down as the Chairman of Sony Worldwide Studios after 3 years in that position . There has been no official statement as to why he has stepped down, nor has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Smash Corner-Rosalina &amp; Luna, Fighting Stars</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-smash-corner-rosalina-luna-fighting-stars/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freddie Ugo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-smash-corner-rosalina-luna-fighting-stars/</guid>
        <description>This powerful duo first appeared in 2010 as a mysterious character of Super Mario Galaxy on the Wii. They are relatively new to the series, having only appeared once before in the Wii U version of the game. While not being as powerful as her previous iteration, there is still plenty of room to show …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Smash Corner-Jigglypuff- The Elvis of the PokéWorld </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-smash-corner-jigglypuff-the-elvis-of-the-pok-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freddie Ugo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-smash-corner-jigglypuff-the-elvis-of-the-pok-world/</guid>
        <description>This pink puff ball originated in 1996 as one of the first original 151 Pokémon. However, it was her popularity in the anime that got her into the first Smash game, and every game since. While not being as amazing as she was in Melee, Jigglypuff has definitely improved over her last couple of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Smash Corner - Ness,Totally Not Sans</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-smash-corner-ness-totally-not-sans/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freddie Ugo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-smash-corner-ness-totally-not-sans/</guid>
        <description>This obscure character originates from Mother 2, a game originally released in Japan but given a western release in 1995 as “Earthbound”. Despite his little-known status, Ness has appeared in every Smash Bros. game since the original on the N64. He has come a long way since, with ridiculous air …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Smash Corner - Link, Mute Discount Legolas</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-smash-corner-link-mute-discount-legolas/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freddie Ugo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-smash-corner-link-mute-discount-legolas/</guid>
        <description>Originating in 1986 as the not so eponymous main character of ‘The Legend of Zelda’, Link has grown to be one of Nintendo’s most beloved and well-known characters. Long-time fans of Link finally get their justice in Ultimate as this is truly the best iteration of Link we have had yet! Link is one of …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
