<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ps3110/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ps3110/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>What did Imperial get up to this year?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-19-what-did-imperial-get-up-to-this-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 13:26:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,Philip Kent,Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-19-what-did-imperial-get-up-to-this-year/</guid>
        <description>This year, Felix has covered a plethora of stories from all corners of the campus, covering stories relevant to staff and students alike. We recap the stories we’ve brought to you this year, and what to watch out for next year.
BUAV hit our front pages twice this year; firstly, the animal rights …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union bar name competition hijacked by 4chan
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-19-union-bar-name-competition-hijacked-by-4chan/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 13:19:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-19-union-bar-name-competition-hijacked-by-4chan/</guid>
        <description>Disaster struck on Saturday afternoon when the competition ran by Imperial College Union to name a new student bar was posted on the forum website 4chan, sparking thousands of entries from the website users.
A link to the initially insecure submission form for votes and other potential name …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial launches two week, £3,500 summer school for GCSE and A-Level students
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-19-imperial-launches-two-week-3500-summer-school-for-gcse-and-a-level-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 13:17:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-19-imperial-launches-two-week-3500-summer-school-for-gcse-and-a-level-students/</guid>
        <description>Imperial is to host its first ever “Global Summer School,” giving under-eighteens a chance to live and study at the university for two weeks, at the cost of £3,500 a head.
The course, designed to attract “the highest achieving students from all corners of the globe” offers attendees a chance to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students frustrated over impossible physics exam question
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-11-students-frustrated-over-impossible-physics-exam-question/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 22:48:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-11-students-frustrated-over-impossible-physics-exam-question/</guid>
        <description>Physics students have been left confused and annoyed over an exam question that was proved to be impossible to answer, adding to the plethora of mistakes in papers sat by students from multiple year groups in the department this term.
Second year students who sat the Quantum Mechanics exam last …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students given chance to name new bar
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-11-students-given-chance-to-name-new-bar/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 22:17:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-11-students-given-chance-to-name-new-bar/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Union are running a poll to name the new student bar out in Acton, located on the site of the new Woodward hall.
The new hall of residence in North Acton will open in September and will be home to over 700 first year students, and there will be a new bar and restaurant based on the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The transgender community at Imperial: those who are silently struggling
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-4-the-transgender-community-at-imperial-those-who-are-silently-struggling/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2015 23:37:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-4-the-transgender-community-at-imperial-those-who-are-silently-struggling/</guid>
        <description>The Felix Sex Survey found that 9 of the respondents do not identify with the gender they were assigned at birth. A third of those respondents said they were unhappy with their sex life, and a few commented about the issues they face as transgender individuals.
Some cited difficulty in finding …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mentality: We need to learn to address stress and realise we are all in this together
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-mentality-we-need-to-learn-to-address-stress-and-realise-we-are-all-in-this-together/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 00:58:24 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-mentality-we-need-to-learn-to-address-stress-and-realise-we-are-all-in-this-together/</guid>
        <description>Mentality was started as a campaign this year, run by a group of students and lead by Bethany Davison, a second year physics student.
They secured £400 in funding from Imperial College Union to spend on publicity and events promoting the survey and mental health awareness, and with Union staff …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial students twice as likely to be stressed than national student average
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-imperial-students-twice-as-likely-to-be-stressed-than-national-student-average/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 00:49:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-imperial-students-twice-as-likely-to-be-stressed-than-national-student-average/</guid>
        <description>Asimilar survey to the one conducted by Mentality was ran by the National Union of Students (NUS) back in 2013, which surveyed around 1200 students across the country via an online questionnaire.
The NUS found that 10% of students had already been diagnosed with a mental health problem, 2% were …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mentality makes recommendations to College to improve support for students
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-mentality-makes-recommendations-to-college-to-improve-support-for-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 00:42:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-mentality-makes-recommendations-to-college-to-improve-support-for-students/</guid>
        <description>Mentality made a number of recommendations towards the end of the survey, which they think would improve the services available to Imperial students.
One of their biggest recommendations was that College should put “students’ mental wellbeing as a strategic priority over the next five years,” by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Three out of four students at Imperial suffer from stress or have a mental health condition
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-three-out-of-four-students-at-imperial-suffer-from-stress-or-have-a-mental-health-condition/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 00:27:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-three-out-of-four-students-at-imperial-suffer-from-stress-or-have-a-mental-health-condition/</guid>
        <description>A College-wide survey has found that three out of four students have suffered from high levels of stress or a mental health condition whilst at Imperial.
The online survey, completed by over a thousand students, found that 39% of all respondents have suffered from mental stresses.
21% had or have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Homeless Book Critic evicted from alley by police near Parsons Green
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-22-homeless-book-critic-evicted-from-alley-by-police-near-parsons-green/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2015 11:08:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-22-homeless-book-critic-evicted-from-alley-by-police-near-parsons-green/</guid>
        <description>An Imperial student has reached out to homeless man Mark Burns, 43, by publishing his book reviews online. Mark lives in a tent in the alleyway behind a tube stop, and reads and reviews books given to him by passing commuters.
However it seems that he may not be able to retain his regular reading …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BUAV to launch judicial review against Home Office investigation into Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-21-buav-to-launch-judicial-review-against-home-office-investigation-into-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2015 23:02:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-21-buav-to-launch-judicial-review-against-home-office-investigation-into-imperial/</guid>
        <description>The High Court has granted the British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV) permission to bring a judicial review against the Home Office, in which they are hoping to again confront animal care at Imperial, and also “prove that the Home Office guilty of foul play”.
The BUAV are claiming …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The MPs that are now representing you
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-the-mps-that-are-now-representing-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 12:31:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-the-mps-that-are-now-representing-you/</guid>
        <description>Areas around South Kensington saw the expected election of several Conservative MPs, although popular student haunt Hammersmith did see the re-election of their current Labour MP, Andy Slaughter.
Chelsea and Fulham saw the re-election of conservative Greg Hands, who held a majority with 25,322 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Amazon soon to deliver to Sherfield
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-14-amazon-soon-to-deliver-to-sherfield/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 22:21:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-14-amazon-soon-to-deliver-to-sherfield/</guid>
        <description>A new Amazon collection point has been installed on campus, allowing staff and students to receive their parcels from South Kensington instead of waiting in at home.
The locker system, based on the Sherfield Walkway, has 84 units of varying sizes that can hold parcels for three days before they are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sport Imperial and College apologise to Women’s Rugby team
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-8-sport-imperial-and-college-apologise-to-womens-rugby-team/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 00:29:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-8-sport-imperial-and-college-apologise-to-womens-rugby-team/</guid>
        <description>The College has released the investigation findings surrounding Varsity 2015, with Sport Imperial and the College offering up apologies to the Women’s Rugby team.
The investigation follows allegations made by the Women’s Rugby team that they were treated unfairly compared to the men’s team, who also …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial student imprisoned after being caught with 30,000 child porn images
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-8-imperial-student-imprisoned-after-being-caught-with-30000-child-porn-images/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 00:15:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-8-imperial-student-imprisoned-after-being-caught-with-30000-child-porn-images/</guid>
        <description>A third year mathematics student has been sentenced to 18 months in jail after 30,000 images of child pornography were found on his laptop.
Nur Fitri Azmeer Nordin, 23, from Malaysia, was caught by police with his laptop open and next to a life-size mannequin of a boy last November, in his own home …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Freshers can now swap rooms in halls
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-8-freshers-can-now-swap-rooms-in-halls/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 00:10:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-8-freshers-can-now-swap-rooms-in-halls/</guid>
        <description>A new room swapping system will be put in place for the next academic year, that will allow first year students in Imperial accommodation to move from one room to another if they so wish.
The new scheme, proposed and put in place by Chris Kaye, the Deputy President (Welfare), was revealed in his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nearly 3,000 students take to the stage
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-8-nearly-3000-students-take-to-the-stage/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 00:07:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-8-nearly-3000-students-take-to-the-stage/</guid>
        <description>The Royal Albert Hall played host to this year’s Postgraduate Graduation ceremony on Wednesday, seeing the largest ever cohort of students cross the stage.
Three ceremonies took place throughout the day, and over 7,000 guests attended to watch their friends and relatives celebrate the completion of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial students most likely to vote Conservative, Felix poll finds
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-1-imperial-students-most-likely-to-vote-conservative-felix-poll-finds/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:09:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-1-imperial-students-most-likely-to-vote-conservative-felix-poll-finds/</guid>
        <description>35% of students will be voting for the Conservative party this year, although a further 30% will be giving the Labour party their vote, our Felix opinion poll shows.
Only 18% of students are voting for the liberal democrats, a significant drop in numbers since the last general election poll that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Review in response to Grimm’s death completed
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-4-30-review-in-response-to-grimms-death-completed/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2015 23:09:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-4-30-review-in-response-to-grimms-death-completed/</guid>
        <description>The inquest into the death of Professor of toxicology Stefan Grimm, 51, took place last month, six months after he was found dead in his own home in Northwood, Middlesex.
The inquest heard how Grimm was at the informal stage of the College’s performance management process after struggling to acquire …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Weeks to remain closed despite student protests
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-4-30-weeks-to-remain-closed-despite-student-protests/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2015 23:06:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-4-30-weeks-to-remain-closed-despite-student-protests/</guid>
        <description>Weeks hall is to remain closed for the next academic year despite students petitioning to save the space, and the student Union Council voting to campaign against the closure.
The Imperial College Union President, Tom Wheeler, announced in his report to council detailing his recent activity that he …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ebola may increase cases of malaria
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-4-30-ebola-may-increase-cases-of-malaria/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2015 23:03:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-4-30-ebola-may-increase-cases-of-malaria/</guid>
        <description>The most recent findings from the Medical Research Council (MRC) Centre for Outbreak Analysis &amp;amp; Modelling has predicted an extra 3.5 million cases of malaria as a result of the epidemic. Researchers based at the Centre have also found that the disease hits those under one year of age hardest, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sport Imperial have dropped the ball
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-20-sport-imperial-have-dropped-the-ball/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2015 14:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-20-sport-imperial-have-dropped-the-ball/</guid>
        <description>This week was meant to be a celebration of women at Imperial, as the women’s rugby team was set to headline Varsity for the very first time. The evening was meant to pay homage to the incredible progression of women’s sport and in fact women at Imperial in general, but in reality, due to the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College comfortably win Varsity 2015
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-19-college-comfortably-win-varsity-2015/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 23:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-19-college-comfortably-win-varsity-2015/</guid>
        <description>Varsity, the annual College-wide sports event took place on Wednesday, with matches taking part across London between teams of students from Imperial College (IC) and teams of Imperial College School of Medicine (ICSM) students. Imperial College stormed to victory ahead of the Medics, with IC …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Premature coach departures and misogynistic abuse from staff member for Women’s rugby
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-19-premature-coach-departures-and-misogynistic-abuse-from-staff-member-for-womens-rugby/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 23:42:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-19-premature-coach-departures-and-misogynistic-abuse-from-staff-member-for-womens-rugby/</guid>
        <description>Imperial’s Women’s rugby teams have been left fuming after their Varsity match on Wednesday due to transport mix-ups and alleged verbal abuse from a Sport Imperial staff member.
Coaches leaving the stadium earlier than planned resulted in the stands emptying during the women’s headlining game and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union Council reverses decision on campaign against closure of Weeks Hall
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-13-union-council-reverses-decision-on-campaign-against-closure-of-weeks-hall/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 01:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-13-union-council-reverses-decision-on-campaign-against-closure-of-weeks-hall/</guid>
        <description>Union Council met this Tuesday and voted to reverse its previous decision not to campaign against the closure of Weeks Hall.
The Union Council also voted in favour of #ICaProblem, a new student led campaign hoping to tackle the “lack of consultation, communication and transparency” in College …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College in mourning after first year student passes away
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-13-college-in-mourning-after-first-year-student-passes-away/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 01:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-13-college-in-mourning-after-first-year-student-passes-away/</guid>
        <description> Students across Imperial have come together to mourn the loss of first year student Georg Zänker, 20, who passed away on Saturday.
Georg fell from his second floor bedroom window in Willis Jackson Hall last Tuesday morning. Ambulances arrived at the hall just after 8:40am, and Georg was taken to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Candidates for the Big Elections are announced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-2-candidates-for-the-big-elections-are-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2015 17:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-2-candidates-for-the-big-elections-are-announced/</guid>
        <description>This afternoon the students standing in this year’s Big Elections were revealed, and we’ve listed who is running for what below.
553 students are running for the various roles this year; 70 more than last year. This year there are fewer students running for sabbatical positions.
Last year 16 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Misogynistic emails sent out to Rugby Club mailing list
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-27-misogynistic-emails-sent-out-to-rugby-club-mailing-list/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2015 00:07:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-27-misogynistic-emails-sent-out-to-rugby-club-mailing-list/</guid>
        <description>Emails sent to the ICU Rugby Football Club (ICURFC) mailing list recently have contained misogynistic content, despite previously being warned by Imperial College Union to moderate their “inappropriate” language.
One was sent earlier this month, describing players on the IC Netball team as “too …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial students sneak backstage at this year&#39;s BRIT awards
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-26-imperial-students-sneak-backstage-at-this-years-brit-awards/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2015 00:12:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-26-imperial-students-sneak-backstage-at-this-years-brit-awards/</guid>
        <description>Two Imperial College Television (ICTV) reporters managed to sneak past security and get backstage to the BRIT awards on Wednesday, and even managed to interview some celebrities before leaving undetected.
The two students turned up at the star-studded event based at the O2 arena brandishing poorly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Why did no-one tell us College wants to shut our halls?”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-19-why-did-no-one-tell-us-college-wants-to-shut-our-halls/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2015 23:51:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-19-why-did-no-one-tell-us-college-wants-to-shut-our-halls/</guid>
        <description>Residents of Weeks are infuriated by the College decision to close their hall, and have demanded an emergency Union Council meeting to revote on the decision not to campaign against the closure.
To add insult to injury, those who live in Weeks only found out about the potential closure once the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union Council votes in favour of new rent proposals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-15-union-council-votes-in-favour-of-new-rent-proposals/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2015 23:04:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-15-union-council-votes-in-favour-of-new-rent-proposals/</guid>
        <description>Students present at Union Council this week voted in favour of new rent proposals, which included lowering the suggested rates for the new student accommodation based in Acton. The new hall, now named Woodward, will open next academic year; students will face a commute time upwards of thirty minutes …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mascot Mayhem at Tri-Union Bar Night
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-13-mascot-mayhem-at-tri-union-bar-night/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2015 15:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-13-mascot-mayhem-at-tri-union-bar-night/</guid>
        <description>It seems that City and Guilds College Union (CGCU) have been foiled again; this time having their mascot, Spanner, stolen from right under their noses.
The mascot – a giant spanner imaginatively named, well, Spanner – is over a metre in length and weighs in at 64lbs [why am I reporting on a fucking …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union Council vote to support closure of Weeks Hall in Princes Gardens
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-union-council-vote-to-support-closure-of-weeks-hall-in-princes-gardens/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 21:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-union-council-vote-to-support-closure-of-weeks-hall-in-princes-gardens/</guid>
        <description>Union Council voted this week to support the closure of Weeks hall in order to transform it into space that could be used for childcare provisions for academics.
The resolve was one of many from a paper that also included the suggestion to either close or keep Pembridge Hall open too. Union Council …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial bungee jumps into RAG Week
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-imperial-bungee-jumps-into-rag-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 21:36:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-imperial-bungee-jumps-into-rag-week/</guid>
        <description>This week saw two days of bungee jumping, one evening of fire walking, a lunchtime of pancake-tossing and just under 900 doughnuts; all in the name of Raising And Giving (RAG).
RAG Week 2015 has seemingly taken over campus, with students unable to go anywhere without the shocking pink and custard …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union shop to sell not for profit sanitary products
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-union-shop-to-sell-not-for-profit-sanitary-products/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 20:54:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-union-shop-to-sell-not-for-profit-sanitary-products/</guid>
        <description>Christopher Kaye, Deputy President (Welfare), achieved victory in Union Council this week when his paper on reducing the cost of female sanitary products was passed by those present.
The paper outlined his plans to reduce the cost of the sanitary products available in the Union Shop Extra on the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Animal Protection and Education Society organise animal testing debate
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-animal-protection-and-education-society-organise-animal-testing-debate/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 20:51:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-animal-protection-and-education-society-organise-animal-testing-debate/</guid>
        <description>Last week, The Animal Protection and Education Society (APES) ran a successful talk addressing animal testing, including a speaker from People for the Ethical Treatment on Animals (PETA).
The debate, titled “Animal Testing: Vital or Unnecessary?” was held in the Sir Alexander Fleming Building (SAF) …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Physics apologise over test and coursework blunders
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-5-physics-apologise-over-test-and-coursework-blunders/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2015 23:45:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-5-physics-apologise-over-test-and-coursework-blunders/</guid>
        <description>An email was sent out this week to all second year physics students, apologising for the department’s response to a series of assessment blunders that went uncorrected.
An assessed problem sheet (APS) featured a mistake in one of the questions, and after students raised the issue, was told to “take …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students take to Council to condemn Counter Terrorism bill
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-5-students-take-to-council-to-condemn-counter-terrorism-bill/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2015 23:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-5-students-take-to-council-to-condemn-counter-terrorism-bill/</guid>
        <description>A bill being passed through government has come under fire for potentially supressing free speech at Universities, and now two students want to pass a paper through Imperial College Union Council, condemning the bill altogether.
The Counter Terrorism and Security Bill was read in the House of Lords …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Phone app designed to aid sickle cell anaemia management
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-5-phone-app-designed-to-aid-sickle-cell-anaemia-management/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2015 23:39:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-5-phone-app-designed-to-aid-sickle-cell-anaemia-management/</guid>
        <description>SiKL, a new app aimed to help Sickle Cell Anaemia (SCA) Patients, has been launched by Clinicians of Imperial Health Care Trust, after collaboration with the Sickle Cell Society and participants from the TalkLab Initiative.
SiKL works as a smartphone based disease management method supplementing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Bhangra to hit Wembley stage
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-5-imperial-bhangra-to-hit-wembley-stage/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2015 23:37:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-5-imperial-bhangra-to-hit-wembley-stage/</guid>
        <description>Saturday will see almost 4,000 students come together for the biggest student Bhangra dance competition in the UK. The event is organised by Imperial College London students.
The Bhangra Showdown will see eight student bhangra dance troupes go head to head on stage at Wembley Arena, with students …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s get it on
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-2-lets-get-it-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 13:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-2-lets-get-it-on/</guid>
        <description>We’ve officially launched the sex survey 2015!
We’ve brought back the classics such as where you’ve had sex on campus, the official National Student Sexual Satisfaction Survey (so much better than the NSS) and added in some new extras, such as porn preferences, long distance relationship stats and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Great Hall packed as hundreds flock to see the A Cappella Semi-Finals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-29-great-hall-packed-as-hundreds-flock-to-see-the-a-cappella-semi-finals/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2015 23:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-29-great-hall-packed-as-hundreds-flock-to-see-the-a-cappella-semi-finals/</guid>
        <description>The International Championship of Collegiate A Cappella (ICCA) Semi-Finals took over the Great Hall last Saturday, seeing three of our own groups competing and the Techtonics placing fourth.
Throughout the evening, nine different student a cappella groups preformed in the Great Hall, which was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Just what funding is available for clinical students?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-29-just-what-funding-is-available-for-clinical-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2015 23:55:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-29-just-what-funding-is-available-for-clinical-students/</guid>
        <description>NHS student bursaries are available to students on pre-registration health professional training courses, which include students in their fifth or sixth year of studying medicine. A fees-only bursary from the NHS covers tuition fees, and these are paid directly to the university, much like Student …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Survey reveals damning truth about medics’ financial hardship
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-29-survey-reveals-damning-truth-about-medics-financial-hardship/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2015 23:46:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-29-survey-reveals-damning-truth-about-medics-financial-hardship/</guid>
        <description>Recent survey results have shown that students in their final years of medicine face extreme financial difficulty, with one in two students saying that their financial situation might affect their ability to complete their degree.
A shocking 87% of students in their fifth and sixth year of medicine …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Coursework might be &#34;nullified&#34; over plagiarism
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-29-coursework-might-be-nullified-over-plagiarism/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2015 23:36:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-29-coursework-might-be-nullified-over-plagiarism/</guid>
        <description>Students were informed on Monday that the marks from an online coursework may be nullified after reports of “widespread plagiarism.”
Over 400 students completed the online coursework for the Business Economics module, which consisted of twelve multiple-choice questions, to be completed within two …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix investigates: the admin that didn’t remain anonymous
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-felix-investigates-the-admin-that-didnt-remain-anonymous/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 01:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-felix-investigates-the-admin-that-didnt-remain-anonymous/</guid>
        <description>Felix has reason to believe that a single student may be behind many of the popular Imperial Facebook pages.
We suspect the individual has now graduated, after completing an undergraduate degree in Aeronautics. Felix has managed to procure email correspondence and personal anecdotes from a number of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Facebook pages: the good, the bad, and the downright hilarious
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-imperial-facebook-pages-the-good-the-bad-and-the-downright-hilarious/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 01:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-imperial-facebook-pages-the-good-the-bad-and-the-downright-hilarious/</guid>
        <description>The rise of Imperial Facebook pages spans several years, but despite sprouting a number of different pages they are all for pretty much of the same audience. These include such as Imperial College Secrets, Spotted: Central Library and Humans of Imperial, some of which allow students to anonymously …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Another broken coach window and a suspension for ICSM boat club
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-22-another-broken-coach-window-and-a-suspension-for-icsm-boat-club/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2015 19:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-22-another-broken-coach-window-and-a-suspension-for-icsm-boat-club/</guid>
        <description>Another sports club tour has resulted in a broken coach window, with the club now currently suspended as a result.
The incident happened on the mixed Medics Boat Club tour to Leuven, Belgium, last weekend, as the coach was waiting at Dover to board the ferry. The coach was not in motion, and as we …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial students attempt to organise a &#34;Jihad themed&#34; orgy through Secrets Facebook page
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-22-imperial-students-attempt-to-organise-a-jihad-themed-orgy-through-secrets-facebook-page/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2015 16:35:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-22-imperial-students-attempt-to-organise-a-jihad-themed-orgy-through-secrets-facebook-page/</guid>
        <description>The Imperial Secrets facebook page has lent itself as a platform to a lot of odd posts, but one took a bizarre turn when it resulted in emails being sent to students inviting them to a “Jihad themed” orgy.
A post made on the page last week included an online survey asking people to sign up for the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Medics laughing all the way to the food bank
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-16-medics-laughing-all-the-way-to-the-food-bank/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 13:08:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-16-medics-laughing-all-the-way-to-the-food-bank/</guid>
        <description>Imperial medical students made a last-minute but sizable donation to the local food bank earlier this month, after collecting dried goods before the Christmas bop at the end of last year.
Students brought non-perishable foods to the Reynolds building on the last day of the autumn term, which were …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Care for a legal high that’s “Chaperon-ed by Imperial”?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-16-care-for-a-legal-high-thats-chaperon-ed-by-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 13:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-16-care-for-a-legal-high-thats-chaperon-ed-by-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Imperial Professor David Nutt has begun research on a legal high that mimics ecstasy but may also stop binge drinking. The drug, known as Chaperon, is still being developed but could one day be available as a cocktail in bars across the country.
The idea of Chaperon occurred around a year ago to the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Council of the year fails to meet quorum
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-16-first-council-of-the-year-fails-to-meet-quorum/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 13:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-16-first-council-of-the-year-fails-to-meet-quorum/</guid>
        <description>Union Council met on Tuesday for the first time this year, although with attendance being so low was unable to meet quorum. This means that there weren’t enough students present to allow any papers to pass and any decisions to be made. Email votes are taking place instead on the papers discussed. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union review recommends an increase in amenity funds for hall activities
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-16-union-review-recommends-an-increase-in-amenity-funds-for-hall-activities/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 12:59:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-16-union-review-recommends-an-increase-in-amenity-funds-for-hall-activities/</guid>
        <description>An increase of the Amenities fund from £1.50 to £2.00 per person per week has been recommended by Imperial College Union. The recommendation was made as part of the Student Amenities Fund Review, and was presented to Union Council on Tuesday by the Union President, Tom Wheeler.
The recommendations …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“It was a funny paper written by funny people.”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-16-it-was-a-funny-paper-written-by-funny-people/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 12:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-16-it-was-a-funny-paper-written-by-funny-people/</guid>
        <description>Felix spoke to Camille Grellet, a Bioengineer and the vice president of the French Society. Camille was in France during the attack, and told us how the country seemed to go into a state of shock. Stations, shops and locations of interest were closed whilst the terrorists were still on the run, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>One city mourns for another city’s loss
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-16-one-city-mourns-for-another-citys-loss/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 12:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-16-one-city-mourns-for-another-citys-loss/</guid>
        <description>The world was stunned by the news last Wednesday, when two masked gunmen entered the offices of Charlie Hebdo, a French satirical magazine. Within half an hour, twelve people had been shot dead, including the editor of the magazine, two policemen and several cartoonists that had drawn the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Undergraduate Aero students accidently sit postgraduate exam after paper mix up
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-16-undergraduate-aero-students-accidently-sit-postgraduate-exam-after-paper-mix-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 12:52:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-16-undergraduate-aero-students-accidently-sit-postgraduate-exam-after-paper-mix-up/</guid>
        <description>Undergraduate aeronautical students were given a postgraduate exam paper to sit this week, with no-one realising until the end of the exam the mistake that was made.
Third year, fourth year and postgraduate students sat their Computational Fluid Dynamics (CFD) exams on Monday, with undergraduates …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Here’s what you may have missed! Felix wraps up a stellar 2014
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-12-heres-what-you-may-have-missed-felix-wraps-up-a-stellar-2014/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 13:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-12-heres-what-you-may-have-missed-felix-wraps-up-a-stellar-2014/</guid>
        <description>It has been a busy year for Imperial College, with the Union and the University alike giving Felix lots of material and good reason to go to print (most of the time).
In January, College announced it would be conducting its Residential Experience Review, something we would see the results of this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Curiosity of one Imperial scientist
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-12-the-curiosity-of-one-imperial-scientist/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 12:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-12-the-curiosity-of-one-imperial-scientist/</guid>
        <description>Imperial scientists working on the Curiosity Rover have revealed how water may have shaped the landscape on Mars. Sanjeev Gupta, a Professor of Earth Science from the Royal School of Mines, teaches multiple undergraduate courses alongside his work with NASA on the Rover, and was part of the team …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Council votes against motion of No confidence for Rubgy Club Captain
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-10-council-votes-against-motion-of-no-confidence-for-rubgy-club-captain/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 15:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-10-council-votes-against-motion-of-no-confidence-for-rubgy-club-captain/</guid>
        <description>Union Council saw the motion of no confidence against Imperial College Union Rugby Football Union (ICURFC) Club Captain rejected Tuesday evening.
33 members of council were in attendance. 13 voted for the motion of no confidence to be passed, 15 voted against it and 5 abstained. Those who abstained …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>RCSU Science Challenge 2015 launches
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-9-rcsu-science-challenge-2015-launches/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2014 14:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-9-rcsu-science-challenge-2015-launches/</guid>
        <description>On Monday, 100 students gathered in the Sir Alexander Fleming Building for the launch of the Science Challenge 2015. The Science Challenge is an annual competition that is open to Imperial College London students and school students across the country, often drawing in hundreds of entries over the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Charity Week raises in excess of £80,000
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-9-charity-week-raises-in-excess-of-80000/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2014 13:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-9-charity-week-raises-in-excess-of-80000/</guid>
        <description>Charity Week, a fundraising event ran by Imperial College Union Islamic Society (iSoc) earlier this month, managed to raise £83,401.70, breaking all previous records the club held.
The week, spanning from the 29th November, included a black tie dinner; an auction; an intersociety quiz; a girls-only …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Postgraduate Loan System announced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-9-postgraduate-loan-system-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2014 13:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-9-postgraduate-loan-system-announced/</guid>
        <description>A student loan system has finally been introduced for postgraduate study. The decision, announced in the Chancellor’s Autumn statement, is said to “revolutionise’ access to postgraduate university courses.
The government-backed loans will be introduced for the 2016 to 2017 academic year, ready for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Publish and Perish: Professor sends posthumous email on &#34;How professors are treated at Imperial.&#34;
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-publish-and-perish-professor-sends-posthumous-email-on-how-professors-are-treated-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 04:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-publish-and-perish-professor-sends-posthumous-email-on-how-professors-are-treated-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>An Imperial professor who died “suddenly and unexpectedly” in September has allegedly sent a posthumous email to his colleagues, with the subject line: “How Professors are treated at Imperial College.”
Professor Stefan Grimm, aged 51, from the Department of Toxicology within the Faculty of Medicine, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>General Meeting on Higher Education Funding Policy fails to meet quorum
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-3-general-meeting-on-higher-education-funding-policy-fails-to-meet-quorum/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 00:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-3-general-meeting-on-higher-education-funding-policy-fails-to-meet-quorum/</guid>
        <description>The General Meeting took place Monday evening, but with only 45 people showing up, failed to meet quorum. The General Meeting, proposed by Imperial College Union Council member Andrew Tranter, aimed to finalise the Union’s stance on education funding and formalise a Higher Education Funding Policy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rugby Club launches petition to support Club Captain facing vote of no confidence
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-2-rugby-club-launches-petition-to-support-club-captain-facing-vote-of-no-confidence/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2014 15:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-2-rugby-club-launches-petition-to-support-club-captain-facing-vote-of-no-confidence/</guid>
        <description>ICURFC have launched an online petition that has already amassed 500 signatures at the time of press. The petition, to show support for the Club Captain, Thomas Hobson, who currently at risk of losing his position, was launched yesterday and has been signed by students and clubs and societies as a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>RAG holds successful charity bike auction
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-rag-holds-successful-charity-bike-auction/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 00:49:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-rag-holds-successful-charity-bike-auction/</guid>
        <description>RAG held their charity bike auction last Thursday, raising an impressive £4,500 after selling roughly 30 bikes.
The auction took place on the steps leading up to Queen’s Tower, and was attended by around 150 students. Half of the funds raised will go to the Bike Users Group (BUG), a student club …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Medicals Rugby team left broke after Union sanctions put in place
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-medicals-rugby-team-left-broke-after-union-sanctions-put-in-place/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 00:42:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-medicals-rugby-team-left-broke-after-union-sanctions-put-in-place/</guid>
        <description>Imperial Medicals Rugby Football Club, one of the rugby teams suspended earlier this term for smashing a coach window, appealed against the sanctions placed against them last week.
However, their appeal was rejected, and they could now be facing extreme financial difficulty as a club. With the costs …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College to investigate circumstances surrounding Professor’s death
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-college-to-investigate-circumstances-surrounding-professors-death/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 00:36:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-college-to-investigate-circumstances-surrounding-professors-death/</guid>
        <description>A professor from the Faculty of Medicine, Professor Stefan Grimm, was found dead in September of this year in Northwood, Middlesex.
Several colleagues of Professor Grimm spoke to the Times Higher Education (THE) and described how he was under a lot of pressure at work. They also said that he had …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This year’s University Challenge team finalised
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-this-years-university-challenge-team-finalised/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 00:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-this-years-university-challenge-team-finalised/</guid>
        <description>The University Challenge team has been finalised after an extensive selection process. The new team consists of 5 male students and was selected after passing several rounds of quizzes and a final trial stage.
The team consists of three undergraduate students and two PhD students. Ben Fernando, a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How much does it cost to live in London as a student?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-21-how-much-does-it-cost-to-live-in-london-as-a-student/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2014 13:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-21-how-much-does-it-cost-to-live-in-london-as-a-student/</guid>
        <description>With college claiming that their new bursary scheme is “most generous bursary provision of any of the leading UK universities” Felix decided to investigate just how generous the university is with its money compared to others.
It seems that despite concerns over student consultation on the matter, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Bursaries: how much will students have in their pockets now?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-21-imperial-bursaries-how-much-will-students-have-in-their-pockets-now/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2014 13:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-21-imperial-bursaries-how-much-will-students-have-in-their-pockets-now/</guid>
        <description>It was announced in Union Council last week that the bursary scheme for new entrants starting in Autumn 2016 was to change. It has altered to decrease funding for those from lower-income households and funding to increase for those students from households who have slightly more money.
The decision, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Shh... Philae is fast asleep.”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-20-shh-philae-is-fast-asleep/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 20:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-20-shh-philae-is-fast-asleep/</guid>
        <description>It’s the space mission that has had both scientists and members of the wider public waiting with baited breath. The Rosetta mission has been a nail-biter of a ride since the awakening of the craft back in January, and has left news rooms and control rooms alike buzzing all through summer as the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Council “condemns” Provost Board decision to alter bursary allocations
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-council-condemns-provost-board-decision-to-alter-bursary-allocations/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 20:03:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-council-condemns-provost-board-decision-to-alter-bursary-allocations/</guid>
        <description>Union Council on Tuesday voted to “condemn” the College’s Provost Board decision after the changes in bursary allocations for undergraduate students were announced.
A table of figures featured in Tom Wheeler’s Council Report showed the differences between his proposed allocations and the Provost …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Penalties for Rugby teams announced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-penalties-for-rugby-teams-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 19:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-penalties-for-rugby-teams-announced/</guid>
        <description>Earlier this week, in light of the recent incidents concerning anti-social behaviour, Imperial College Union released the penalties that will be held against both Imperial College Union Rugby Football Club (ICURFC) and Imperial Medicals Rugby Football Club.
The ICURFC has been suspended for two …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Council to call General Meeting to discuss Higher Education Funding
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-council-to-call-general-meeting-to-discuss-higher-education-funding/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 19:56:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-council-to-call-general-meeting-to-discuss-higher-education-funding/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Union Council agreed to a Union General Meeting last Tuesday, only the second General Meeting in five years and the first under the new constitution change.
A General Meeting needs 200 students to attend to meet quorum, and can be called to discuss any topic at any time.
The General …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Silwood redevelopments still uncertain
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-silwood-redevelopments-still-uncertain/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 19:53:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-silwood-redevelopments-still-uncertain/</guid>
        <description>A petition to “Protect Silwood from losing its identity” has amassed over 250 signatures, after it has been announced that redevelopment work on the site is to take place. However, with no straight answers yet available as to what this redevelopment may entail, rumours are running rife through the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>£4 million miniature robot laboratory opens on campus
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-13-4-million-miniature-robot-laboratory-opens-on-campus/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2014 14:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-13-4-million-miniature-robot-laboratory-opens-on-campus/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday the EPSRC Micro-Machining Facility for Medical Robotics was officially opened at Imperial College London. Costing £4 million, this new lab will allow the development of miniaturised surgical robotics that could reshape the way diseases are diagnosed and treated
Professor Alice Gast, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The responsibility of a student newspaper
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-the-responsibility-of-a-student-newspaper/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 22:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-the-responsibility-of-a-student-newspaper/</guid>
        <description>This week, another rugby team has been suspending following another stint of bad behaviour. Although this lessened the logistics of arranging our front page (literally, we could have just changed the name of the team from last week’s issue), it is becoming a much more difficult topic for us, as a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Another rugby team suspended after Imperial Medicals smash coach window
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-another-rugby-team-suspended-after-imperial-medicals-smash-coach-window/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 22:12:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-another-rugby-team-suspended-after-imperial-medicals-smash-coach-window/</guid>
        <description>Medic rugby players have been suspended pending investigation after smashing a window in a moving coach.
The players, members of the Imperial Medicals Rugby Club, were travelling to Bristol on their “School’s Tour” last Wednesday when the incident took place. The double glazed window on the side of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial iGEM team come second in the world
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-imperial-igem-team-come-second-in-the-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 19:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-imperial-igem-team-come-second-in-the-world/</guid>
        <description>The International Genetically Engineered Machine (iGEM) competition saw our own Imperial team receive a number of awards at the Global Jamboree this week. The competition sees teams from hundreds of Universities bioengineer products using synthetic biology techniques and pits their ideas against …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New flying robots lab to open on campus
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-new-flying-robots-lab-to-open-on-campus/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 14:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-new-flying-robots-lab-to-open-on-campus/</guid>
        <description>Imperial is opening a new lab to develop flying robots. The drone lab will be the most advanced in the UK, and will cost £1.25m to build. The testing lab is to be built on the South Kensington campus, as an investment into next generation robotics, and construction of the lab will begin in 2016.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Investigation into use of human tissue at Imperial condemned as “insensitive and highly misleading”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-3-investigation-into-use-of-human-tissue-at-imperial-condemned-as-insensitive-and-highly-misleading/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2014 11:24:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-3-investigation-into-use-of-human-tissue-at-imperial-condemned-as-insensitive-and-highly-misleading/</guid>
        <description>An “investigation” into the use of human tissues at Imperial by the Mail on Sunday has been condemned by the College and the Royal British Legion Centre.
The investigation, outlined in an article posted by the Mail on Sunday, detailed how “Human remains are being used in secretive weapons tests …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rugby team hits the headlines over stripping on tube platforms
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-30-rugby-team-hits-the-headlines-over-stripping-on-tube-platforms/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2014 17:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-30-rugby-team-hits-the-headlines-over-stripping-on-tube-platforms/</guid>
        <description>The Imperial College Rugby First XV team have been suspended pending investigation into reports that team members were stripping on a District Line tube.
The behaviour led to the train being terminated at Stamford Brook. All passengers were told to leave the train, and the police were called to the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICTV release new Metric Moments
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-29-ictv-release-new-metric-moments/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2014 23:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-29-ictv-release-new-metric-moments/</guid>
        <description>ICTV asked the hard hitting questions this Fresher&amp;rsquo;s Week, and recorded it all for our sweet viewing pleasure.
</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Medics say goodbye to Teddington
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-24-the-medics-say-goodbye-to-teddington/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2014 12:57:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-24-the-medics-say-goodbye-to-teddington/</guid>
        <description>The final day of sporting events at Teddington Sports ground took place last Saturday, 18th October. Things kicked off at midday and carried on late into the evening, with matches taking place throughout the day.
Imperial College London staff, some of the Officer Trustees and Senior Medical Staff …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ambulances arrive at the Union after RSM Dinner
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-24-ambulances-arrive-at-the-union-after-rsm-dinner/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2014 12:52:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-24-ambulances-arrive-at-the-union-after-rsm-dinner/</guid>
        <description>Two Ambulances were called to Beit Quadrangle last Friday night to collect two students who had been drinking in the Union bars. The students in question, two girls, had previously been to the Royal School of Mines (RSM) Freshers’ Dinner, although the reasons the ambulances were called were …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Graduands flock to Royal Albert Hall for Graduation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-24-imperial-graduands-flock-to-royal-albert-hall-for-graduation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2014 12:18:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-24-imperial-graduands-flock-to-royal-albert-hall-for-graduation/</guid>
        <description>It was Imperial’s favourite day off this week, as graduands came back to touch the Gast hand and finally graduate completely. More than 2200 undergraduates passed through the Royal Albert Hall to receive their degrees in three separate ceremonies that took part during Commemoration Day.
This was the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students left in the dark over cuts to amenities funds
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-17-students-left-in-the-dark-over-cuts-to-amenities-funds/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 14:28:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,Thomas Lim,Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-17-students-left-in-the-dark-over-cuts-to-amenities-funds/</guid>
        <description>College has slashed the Amenity funds for Halls of Residence by a quarter of a million– a move that has sparked fury amongst Hall Seniors and Wardens throughout the first few weeks of term.
The amount allocated to all halls this year was just over £150,000, down from approximately £373,000 in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sport Imperial announces: “… there are no plans for student sport to take place at Teddington”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-7-10-sport-imperial-announces-there-are-no-plans-for-student-sport-to-take-place-at-teddington/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 13:13:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-7-10-sport-imperial-announces-there-are-no-plans-for-student-sport-to-take-place-at-teddington/</guid>
        <description>In a news statement released today, Sport Imperial announced once and for all that, despite outcry from medics, the Teddington sports ground will no longer be used.
This follows the news that College is planning to purchase a new sports ground in Heston, spanning 27 acres and provides indoor and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Does watching violence on TV make men more violent?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-does-watching-violence-on-tv-make-men-more-violent/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 14:52:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-does-watching-violence-on-tv-make-men-more-violent/</guid>
        <description>New research has shown that men watching more violence on television could result in stunted in brain development, and the inability to control impulsive behaviours, including aggression.
A study, ran by a top brain journal, used brain imaging techniques to measure the mental abilities and volumes …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Talking to the Editors
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-talking-to-the-editors/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 14:34:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,Felix Editor,Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-talking-to-the-editors/</guid>
        <description> ## Joe Editor-In-Chief
Wow, well it certainly has been a year!
I started this job in October, with a small amount of training and the dusty cobwebs of my previous years of section editorship skulking miserably in the corners of my mind. Summer, as I’m sure you all know, is quite potent at clearing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Making light of the matter
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-12-making-light-of-the-matter/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 16:57:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-12-making-light-of-the-matter/</guid>
        <description>Last month, Imperial attracted the attention of the world’s media once again, with researchers based in Blackett Laboratory showing how to potentially create matter from light. Their paper, published in Nature Photonics, builds upon The Breit and Wheeler’s theory, made in 1934, and solves an 80 year …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A cast-iron case for climate sceptics
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-23-a-cast-iron-case-for-climate-sceptics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 13:46:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-23-a-cast-iron-case-for-climate-sceptics/</guid>
        <description>Climate change sceptics were thrown a cast-iron lifeline this week when it was revealed that the melting of ice caps containing iron could potentially be biologically beneficial. However, with some predicting that the iron equivalent of of 3,000 Boeing 747s may be leaked into the oceans per year, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wait... are people actually starting to enjoy science?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-16-wait-are-people-actually-starting-to-enjoy-science/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 01:46:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-16-wait-are-people-actually-starting-to-enjoy-science/</guid>
        <description>The third annual Imperial Festival took place last weekend on campus, and saw students, staff and members of the public alike come together for the ambitious public engagement endeavour. The scientists of Imperial, usually hidden away in their labs and lecture theatres, came out in full force to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Student Media and Union Censorship
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-student-media-and-union-censorship/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 02:04:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-student-media-and-union-censorship/</guid>
        <description>The Student Publication Association (SPA) is very much in its infancy, especially when compared to other media associations, such as the Student Radio Association. This is particularly surprising considering nearly every university has a newspaper, either independently ran or overseen by their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Breakthrough in HIV gene therapy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-breakthrough-in-hiv-gene-therapy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 04:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-breakthrough-in-hiv-gene-therapy/</guid>
        <description>For the first time ever, researchers have succeeded in making enzymes target and alter the genes of immune cells that are susceptible to HIV infection. A clinical trial tested the enzymes, known as ‘zinc-finger nucleases’ and found that they were able to disrupt the gene CCR5, which codes a protein …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Come one, come all: the female orgasm
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-17-come-one-come-all-the-female-orgasm/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 17:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-17-come-one-come-all-the-female-orgasm/</guid>
        <description>Look kid, it’s up to you…the big L, or the big O?”
These hallowed words were immortalised through the cinematic legacy of American Pie back in the glorious 90’s. Uttered by Natasha Lyonne, she outlined that the alternative to telling a girl you love her is simply to deliver a mind blowing orgasm. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Shine bright like a vagina
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-shine-bright-like-a-vagina/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 17:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-shine-bright-like-a-vagina/</guid>
        <description>What’s hard, metallic and found down your pants? Despite the common answer to this usually referring to some sort of recreational, copulation mimicry device, perhaps owned by a maternal figure, this time, the answer may in fact be an anti-viral cream.
A new cream containing silver nanoparticles is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>MDMA - a new high in research?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-mdma-a-new-high-in-research/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 09:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-mdma-a-new-high-in-research/</guid>
        <description>MDMA seems to be keeping clubbers and scientists alike on their toes at the moment, with research into the recreational drug on the rise. Despite the law heavily restricting drug experimentation even within the laboratory, there still seems to be an unrelenting interest into the potential medical …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
