<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/cb908/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/cb908/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Kana reasonably priced gaming mouse pack a punch?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-24-kana-reasonably-priced-gaming-mouse-pack-a-punch/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 23:31:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chris Bowers,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-24-kana-reasonably-priced-gaming-mouse-pack-a-punch/</guid>
        <description>The SteelSeries Kana is a gaming mouse promising a good specification but at a reasonable price. Armed with a high resolution sensor (3200dpi), two side buttons, two on-board profiles and a resilient, braided cable, it certainly looks good on paper. I’ve been using it for the past week, so let’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The power behind the web
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-the-power-behind-the-web/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 21:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chris Bowers,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-the-power-behind-the-web/</guid>
        <description>The web is changing. Sites such as Facebook and Twitter keep you hooked by constantly updating in real-time any activity that happens in your social network. This is incredibly powerful and last year the Union used this to create the incredibly successful real-time voting statistics page. Along with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A new ‘best’ method for creating passwords?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-a-new-best-method-for-creating-passwords/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 21:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chris Bowers,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-a-new-best-method-for-creating-passwords/</guid>
        <description>“Your password will expire in 10 days. Would you like to change it now?” This is the message that greets me when I log on to Outlook Web Access. I was first told my password was going to expire at the end of January, so why have I not yet done so? The act itself of changing the password is by no …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Prime tablet specimen
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-a-prime-tablet-specimen/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 22:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chris Bowers,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-a-prime-tablet-specimen/</guid>
        <description>I have to say, I’m not much of a tablet man. If I really must surf on the move I’m perfectly happy with my BlackBerry, and my laptop satisfies all my mobile computing needs. However, when a friend of mine bought the new Asus Transformer Prime tablet, I had to give it a go – so I borrowed it.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Etymotic MC2 headset review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-etymotic-mc2-headset-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 22:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chris Bowers,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-etymotic-mc2-headset-review/</guid>
        <description>The Etymotic MC2 headset is an in-ear, noise isolating headphone and microphone combination promising high-quality sound. It also has a single button that can be used for tasks such as answering calls or pausing what’s playing. I’ve been using them for the last week, and I have to say I’m finding …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lost focus? Try the Lytro
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-lost-focus-try-the-lytro/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 19:34:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chris Bowers,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-lost-focus-try-the-lytro/</guid>
        <description>Have you ever taken a picture, only to be disappointed when you later find it to be out of focus? You’re certainly not alone. Enter Lytro, the world’s first consumer-targeted light-field camera.
So what does that mean? In your everyday camera, what the sensor captures when you press the button is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What does the future hold?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-what-does-the-future-hold/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 18:09:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chris Bowers,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-what-does-the-future-hold/</guid>
        <description>Ah, Issue 1500 is here. While some of my fellow editors may be getting nostalgic, technology and history don’t seem to get along. Technology and the future, on the other hand? Well, everyone sees them as going hand-in-hand. So we’ve decided to jump 1500 issues into the future – approximately fifty …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The BlackBerry Crumble
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-the-blackberry-crumble/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 21:25:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chris Bowers,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-the-blackberry-crumble/</guid>
        <description>As I’m sure many of you know, Research In Motion last week suffered its biggest ever service disruption, with millions of customers across the globe affected. Users lost access to push email, BlackBerry Messenger, Facebook and Twitter applications, and even in some cases their internet access. For a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Electricity through the air
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-electricity-through-the-air/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 10:36:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chris Bowers,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-electricity-through-the-air/</guid>
        <description>Cables, chargers everywhere. You’ve got one for your phone, another for your laptop, more for those multiple alarm clocks that get you out of bed in the mornings… the list goes on. And while we can transfer so much wirelessly these days – our keystrokes and mouse movements, our voices and even our …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Felix Tech Guide 2011
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-9-30-the-felix-tech-guide-2011/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2011 12:00:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chris Bowers,Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-9-30-the-felix-tech-guide-2011/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to Imperial! You’ve done well to make it here; for the next few years you will get to experience extreme levels of stress, a rapidly receding hairline and the effects of excess Red Bull consumption (seizure, in the case of one of my housemates).
Despite this, there’s much to be said for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How has the Internet changed the games industry?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-28-how-has-the-internet-changed-the-games-industry/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 11:02:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chris Bowers,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-28-how-has-the-internet-changed-the-games-industry/</guid>
        <description>The internet and games. They were always going to go hand-in-hand, and I’m sure the gaming industry would look very different today if not for the advent of personal broadband. Of course, there are the obvious benefits such as online multiplayer and downloadable content, but there are also slightly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Augmented reality is here
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-augmented-reality-is-here/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 20:25:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chris Bowers,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-augmented-reality-is-here/</guid>
        <description>Just what is augmented reality? I was at an augmented reality conference recently and the best definition was this: “Augmented reality is an integration of the real world with computer graphics that you can interact with.”
So we are looking at something that augments your reality with something you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>One stumble too many?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-one-stumble-too-many/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 19:02:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chris Bowers,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-one-stumble-too-many/</guid>
        <description>Google – a name we all know. I’m sure that the majority of you use one of the internet giant’s services on a near-daily basis. They of course burst into popularity with the now almost ubiquitous search engine, and have since made inroads into many areas of our digital lives. So their annual Google …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who knew climate change could be so much fun?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-who-knew-climate-change-could-be-so-much-fun/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 18:41:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chris Bowers,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-who-knew-climate-change-could-be-so-much-fun/</guid>
        <description>The year is 2020 and climate change has reached critical levels. The global temperature is rising, the Maldives are being evacuated, and countries have realised that their individual efforts are no longer enough. 2018 brought what scientists called the world’s first ever “hypercane”, and the serious …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ASUS EEE Slate
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-asus-eee-slate/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 08:25:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chris Bowers,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-asus-eee-slate/</guid>
        <description>Currently, the tablet market is undeniably dominated by Apple, with Google’s Android looking to take some share with Honeycomb. The tablet OS that has seen far less of the limelight so far however is Windows 7. Known of course as a desktop and laptop OS, it’s also perfectly useable on a tablet, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Not exactly cutting edge gaming
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-21-not-exactly-cutting-edge-gaming/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2011 11:58:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chris Bowers,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-21-not-exactly-cutting-edge-gaming/</guid>
        <description>Surgery Simulator literally consists of eight different operations. One of which is called ‘Road Traffic Accident’… this is the sort of level we’re operating on (pun intended). Oh, and I should warn you: “This product is a computer game and not for training or tuition purposes!!!” So you Medics that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cities in Motion: Finally, a SimCity destroyer?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-cities-in-motion-finally-a-simcity-destroyer/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 20:09:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chris Bowers,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-cities-in-motion-finally-a-simcity-destroyer/</guid>
        <description>Cities in Motion is a complex transport simulator based on a simple concept – you have to build and manage the public transport system in a city. While this isn’t the type of game I’d usually opt for, I decided to take the plunge and take a look at what it had to offer.
But first, I have to make a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Guitar Hero comes to a timely demise
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-guitar-hero-comes-to-a-timely-demise/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 20:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chris Bowers,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-guitar-hero-comes-to-a-timely-demise/</guid>
        <description>On February 9th, Activision announced they were discontinuing the Guitar Hero franchise, and as a result, their planned 2011 Guitar Hero title was also cancelled. Activision cited “declining interest in the music genre” as their reason, a phenomenon which is quite possibly down to an almost …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nintendo 3DS: an exclusive hands-on preview
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-nintendo-3ds-an-exclusive-hands-on-preview/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 20:44:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chris Bowers,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-nintendo-3ds-an-exclusive-hands-on-preview/</guid>
        <description>Last weekend I bagged tickets to an exclusive Nintendo 3DS hands-on preview – and first impressions were excellent! After a vague demonstration of StreetPass, “real-life” demonstrations of Street Fighter and Resident Evil, and a brief introductory video featuring Jonathan Ross (seemingly the new …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
