<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rosie_dutt/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rosie_dutt/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Explaining the Future book launched at UCL</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-explaining-the-future-book-launched-at-ucl/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rosie Dutt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-explaining-the-future-book-launched-at-ucl/</guid>
        <description>On Monday March 4th, Dr. Sunny Bains from the Department of Biochemical Engineering launched her new book Explaining the Future: How to Research, Analyze and Report on Emerging Technologies, published by Oxford University Press. The book – written for engineers, physical scientists, consultants, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Charles Dickens – was he the original science communicator?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-charles-dickens-was-he-the-original-science-communicator/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rosie Dutt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-charles-dickens-was-he-the-original-science-communicator/</guid>
        <description>When you hear of Charles Dickens, you most likely instantly think of classic works of literature, such as A Christmas Carol, Oliver Twist, or Great Expectations. However, seldom does one hear he was a man of science – let alone an early science communicator! Indeed, George Henry Lewes, a prominent …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mercury spacecraft BepiColombo makes its landing at the Science Museum</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-mercury-spacecraft-bepicolombo-makes-its-landing-at-the-science-museum/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rosie Dutt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-mercury-spacecraft-bepicolombo-makes-its-landing-at-the-science-museum/</guid>
        <description>The unknown. It is a concept almost every individual fears in one form or another; one that many question, but few have the ability to really explore. On May 16th, the Science Museum had the privilege of unveiling a full-size structural thermal model of BepiColombo, the first European spacecraft to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mobile phones make you hyper-social, not anti-social!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-mobile-phones-make-you-hyper-social-not-anti-social/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rosie Dutt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-mobile-phones-make-you-hyper-social-not-anti-social/</guid>
        <description>As we grow older, we begin to adopt a routine. This commences from the earliest of ages – from when we learn to brush our teeth in the morning, to sleeping at a particular time at night. With the advent of modern technology, checking our phones has also become embedded in our everyday lives.
Many …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
