<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rsp07/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rsp07/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Cold Fusion@London: event fails to reach critical mass
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-cold-fusionlondon-event-fails-to-reach-critical-mass/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 06:14:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-cold-fusionlondon-event-fails-to-reach-critical-mass/</guid>
        <description>The financial outcome of the charity event Fusion@London has finally become clear. As reported previously in Felix, there was initially a long, slow, and confusing period of uncertainty as to exactly what the situation was. Up until as recently as 1 May, there were still invoices that needed to be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ConFusion over event success
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-2-confusion-over-event-success/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 01:03:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-2-confusion-over-event-success/</guid>
        <description>This past weekend saw Fusion@London, an event budgeted to raise £78,897.50 in aid of the charity Cancer Research UK, take place. The main aim of the event was “to foster a closer relationship between the capital’s student population“. However, the success of the event is yet to be established. It …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Worth the Effort
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-27-worth-the-effort/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2010 17:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-27-worth-the-effort/</guid>
        <description>It has long been instilled in many a student’s mind that they should be coming out of University with at least upper second class honours if they’re to make the leap to employment afterwards. They say without a 2:1 in your respective degree, you’re destined to life in a dead-end job, and failing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial converted to Metric
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-27-imperial-converted-to-metric/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2010 17:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-27-imperial-converted-to-metric/</guid>
        <description>The answer to the question on everyone’s lips has finally been announced. After weeks of violent speculation, Imperial Student Union has revealed that the new club next year to replace dBs will be called Metric. Obviously as the name suggests, it is hoped that Metric will be an improvement on dBs. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Colin Hill against the union refurbishments
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-27-colin-hill-against-the-union-refurbishments/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2010 17:09:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-27-colin-hill-against-the-union-refurbishments/</guid>
        <description>As I’m sure most of you have read recently, the Union has decided to spend £2.4 million on renovating dB’s and da Vinci’s. Personally, I like the union the way it is; it’s a fantastic establishment where all my friends are, “cutting up some mad shapes on the D-Floor” is perfectly acceptable and the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rhys Davies just can&#39;t argue with trees
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-27-rhys-davies-just-cant-argue-with-trees/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2010 17:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-27-rhys-davies-just-cant-argue-with-trees/</guid>
        <description>Whilst walking through Hyde Park one day, I came across a very peculiar sight.
There was a man engaged in a very passionate argument. He swore, he cursed, he turned a funny colour. But his opponent would not be moved by his entreaties. I can&amp;rsquo;t be sure what the disagreement was about but I knew …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Angry Geek with this week&#39;s offering
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-12-angry-geek-with-this-weeks-offering/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 02:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-12-angry-geek-with-this-weeks-offering/</guid>
        <description>There&amp;rsquo;s something about group work at Imperial that just brings the best out of people, isn&amp;rsquo;t there? It&amp;rsquo;s like a cross between Ocean&amp;rsquo;s Eleven and that scene from the Power Rangers where everyone teams up and combines into a giant robot penis.
I think everyone knows how shit …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ben Gross on missed opportunities
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-12-ben-gross-on-missed-opportunities/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 02:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-12-ben-gross-on-missed-opportunities/</guid>
        <description>Last year the lives of the people of Gaza changed dramatically for the worse. 1400 were killed, many more homeless and desperate with short supplies. Last week, Imperial College was educated about Gaza. The aim of ‘Gaza Week’ was to inform us (Joe Public) of the importance of supporting the people …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stephen Long on the proposed smoking ban
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-12-stephen-long-on-the-proposed-smoking-ban/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 02:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-12-stephen-long-on-the-proposed-smoking-ban/</guid>
        <description>The other week, the idea of banning smoking in our Union Quad was mooted. On Monday, a proposal will be made to the Council to pass this into Union rules. This appears to me to be very ill thought- out, and hopefully after reading this article, it will to you too.
To begin with a disclaimer: yes, I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rhys Davies gets his heart broken, sweetly
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-12-rhys-davies-gets-his-heart-broken-sweetly/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 01:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-12-rhys-davies-gets-his-heart-broken-sweetly/</guid>
        <description>Valentine’s Day is nearly upon us and that can mean only one thing. Half of Imperial will be burning through their student loans in order to pay for an unforgettable night of passion with their respective beau or paramour. The other half will be watching Love Actually in the dark with a tub of Ben …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College&#39;s Most Famous Geeks
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-12-colleges-most-famous-geeks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 01:52:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-12-colleges-most-famous-geeks/</guid>
        <description>When the gong sounded, everybody cheered, for Imperial College London had won!
That was in year 2001, when the Imperial team - Siegfried Hodgson, John Douglas, Captain Gavin Estcourt and Alexander Campbell – defeated St. John’s College, Oxford by 250 points to 195 points, leaving in their wake …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Business School&#39;s Tanaka imprisoned
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-12-business-schools-tanaka-imprisoned/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 01:45:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-12-business-schools-tanaka-imprisoned/</guid>
        <description>If you are in second year or above, you may remember the halcyon days when Imperial College Business School was called the Tanaka Business School. The name came from Gary Tanaka, a Japanese-American fund manager who did a PhD in Mathematics at Imperial. He pledged £27 million to the College, who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sports of Yesteryear: Morphy Day
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-5-sports-of-yesteryear-morphy-day/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2010 17:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-5-sports-of-yesteryear-morphy-day/</guid>
        <description>As some of you may know, Imperial was founded when three different college’s joined together back in 1907; the Royal College of Science (RCS), the Royal School of Mines (RSM) and the City and Guilds College (C&amp;amp;G). There was a sense of belonging, a sense of identity to the constituent College’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ten years of independence: Tru Thoughts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-ten-years-of-independence-tru-thoughts/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 20:48:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-ten-years-of-independence-tru-thoughts/</guid>
        <description>What were your aims when you founded Tru Thoughts? What was the label’s raison d’etre? We started the label in 1999 from Rob Luis’ stairwell and the reason for starting the label was that we were running a weekly club night (called phonic:hoop) and we noticed promoters were coming in and pinching …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>France to ban the wearing of the niqab
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-france-to-ban-the-wearing-of-the-niqab/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 17:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-france-to-ban-the-wearing-of-the-niqab/</guid>
        <description>France, a country known mainly for cheese, wine, surrendering, gourmet food and the Eiffel Tower, is not a country I often praise. There is, however, one thing which I envy about France: the way the French Republic sticks to its principles – mostly.
This week, a French parliamentary committee …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC Business School climbs FT rankings
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-ic-business-school-climbs-ft-rankings/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 17:20:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-ic-business-school-climbs-ft-rankings/</guid>
        <description>The Financial Times World Rankings is one of the most respected international league tables for Business Schools. In their latest annual assessment, released this week, Imperial College Business School has moved up seven places to 32nd place in the world. Its Principal, Professor David Begg, has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How rubbish TV is these days...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-how-rubbish-tv-is-these-days/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 17:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-how-rubbish-tv-is-these-days/</guid>
        <description>Anyone who has lived in the new Eastside/Southside complex of halls in Princes Gardens (of which I am one!) would know that every kitchen comes with a flat screen plasma TV. To achieve superiority, this fact would be bragged about countless times in conversations with friends of other universities …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Worries for Irish politics
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-worries-for-irish-politics/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 17:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-worries-for-irish-politics/</guid>
        <description>This New Year, the media’s focus was back on Northern Ireland, my home country. Only this time it wasn’t about bombings, shootings or kidnappings, but the extra- marital affair of NI’s First Lady, Iris Robinson.
Good old normal politics had finally returned to Northern Ireland. But while an affair …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Diet tips for the fat and lazy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-diet-tips-for-the-fat-and-lazy/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 16:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-diet-tips-for-the-fat-and-lazy/</guid>
        <description>Suppose you’re worried about your weight. Perhaps you feel you could lose a few pounds. The modern way to deal with these feelings is to smother them with anti-depressants, so you could take a fistful of Prozac washed down with a tub of Ben and Jerry’s and call it irony.
Still, some people are picky …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reversing the arrow of time
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-reversing-the-arrow-of-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 16:49:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-reversing-the-arrow-of-time/</guid>
        <description>This may end up in the bullshit graveyard of sensationalist physics speculation, but seemingly impossible occurrences – such as a shattered pane of glass returning instantaneously to its original form, a Latte separating back into pure coffee and milk, or Megan Fox replying to my emails – are not as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Smoking stubbed out on campus?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-smoking-stubbed-out-on-campus/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 16:43:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-smoking-stubbed-out-on-campus/</guid>
        <description>John James, Deputy President (Welfare), presented a controversial paper to central Union&amp;rsquo;s Representation and Welfare Board (RWB) last Thursday, calling for a ban on smoking on all Union premises, including Beit Quad. The paper asks the Union to: Implement a ban on smoking in any part of Union …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Guilds Vice President AWOL? Not likely, he says
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-guilds-vice-president-awol-not-likely-he-says/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 16:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-guilds-vice-president-awol-not-likely-he-says/</guid>
        <description>In a long line of mishaps involving the City &amp;amp; Guilds College Union, their Vice President (Finance &amp;amp; Societies) Rikki Norris has been criticised for his absence about College, but has now spoken to felix to clarify the situation.
On 21st January, the CGCU’s news website Live! reported that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The State of our Union
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-the-state-of-our-union/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 16:23:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-the-state-of-our-union/</guid>
        <description>BEIT REDEVELOPMENT
Kadhim - Let’s start by talking about the third phase of the Beit Redevelopment. What’s the vision?
Ashley - Our aim is to create an atmosphere where people feel like they’ve got a high quality product but not extortionate prices. We want to have a venue that’s for students but …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brand New kicking back on Long Island
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-22-brand-new-kicking-back-on-long-island/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 15:10:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-22-brand-new-kicking-back-on-long-island/</guid>
        <description>As Brand New prepare for another stretch on the trans-global road they have become well-accustomed to in recent years, felix catches up with drummer Brian Lane at home in Long Island, New York. Home is clearly where the heart is for Brand New, but their first stop is London, a city they’ve found …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A glimpse of dark matter?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-22-a-glimpse-of-dark-matter/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 14:24:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-22-a-glimpse-of-dark-matter/</guid>
        <description>In early December last year, the particle physics community was abuzz with rumours of a discovery made by the Cryogenic Dark Matter Search (CDMS-II) collaboration in the US. Announcement talks were scheduled for 18th December, all seminars before that cancelled and there were rumours of a paper …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICE - The way forward?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-22-ice-the-way-forward/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 14:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-22-ice-the-way-forward/</guid>
        <description>When Ethiopia commenced construction of a dam on the Upper Omo river in 2006, groups downstream in Ethiopia and Kenya made their opposition clear. The dam, they said, would affect communities and wildlife by interfering with the annual supply of nutrient-rich floodwaters that nourish grazing areas …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to Wales
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-22-welcome-to-wales/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 13:53:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-22-welcome-to-wales/</guid>
        <description>I am a stranger in a strange land.
As much I adore this sprawling metropolis, the inkblot on the cosmic sketchbook that is London, I know in my heart that it’s not home. You see, I’m not from round these parts. I’m not even English – not that should shock one the most multicultural student bodies in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The glamour of American democracy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-22-the-glamour-of-american-democracy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 13:49:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-22-the-glamour-of-american-democracy/</guid>
        <description>The American campaign trail is a thing of beauty. An exhibition of pure democracy at work, it really encapsulated Churchill&amp;rsquo;s quotation: “It has been said that democracy is the worst form of government except all the others that have been tried”. Nowhere else would you find an Ivy League …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The lack of human rights in Gaza
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-22-the-lack-of-human-rights-in-gaza/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 13:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-22-the-lack-of-human-rights-in-gaza/</guid>
        <description>24th December, 2008. Many of us were most likely sitting at home with the family, enjoying a peaceful night in, or out partying with friends, as Christmas Eve should be. Yet some 2000 miles away, the mood could not be more different. On a 25-mile strip of coastal land steeped in history, controversy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College ranks top university for LGBT employment
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-21-imperial-college-ranks-top-university-for-lgbt-employment/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 22:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-21-imperial-college-ranks-top-university-for-lgbt-employment/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London has been listed among Stonewall&amp;rsquo;s Top 100 Employers 2010 for being one of the top employers of LGBT (lesbian, gay, bisexual and transgender) people. The Workplace Equality Index, released on 13th January, places Imperial at number 79 ahead of the only other HEI (higher …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Exhibition Road Project opposed by charities
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-21-exhibition-road-project-opposed-by-charities/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 22:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-21-exhibition-road-project-opposed-by-charities/</guid>
        <description>The Exhibition Road Project has come up against a hurdle still standing after a group of 30 charities are looking to carry on fighting their case to stop the removal of pavements on Exhibition road, creating a shared space for pedestrians and traffic.
On Friday they applied for a second High Court …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Not Who You Think We Are
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-21-not-who-you-think-we-are/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 21:29:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-21-not-who-you-think-we-are/</guid>
        <description>Shockwaves of anger and relief reverberated across the world on Christmas Day 2009 as the news of Umar Farouk Abdulmutallab’s failed bombing of Northwest Airlines Flight 253, en route from Amsterdam to Detroit. As news reports covered Boxing Day’s press, it was revealed that he was an Engineering …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Game, set, match Imperial College
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-21-game-set-match-imperial-college/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 21:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-21-game-set-match-imperial-college/</guid>
        <description>On Monday, Imperial won the first of their quarter-final matches against Edinburgh University in the latest episode of University Challenge. At this stage in the competition, Imperial needs one more win against Emmanuel College Cambridge to secure a place in the semi-finals.
The University Challenge …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The streets lined with Turkish Delights
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-14-the-streets-lined-with-turkish-delights/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 16:27:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-14-the-streets-lined-with-turkish-delights/</guid>
        <description>I have to say that there is no other city like this anywhere else on Earth. Being a city which encompasses both Europe and Asia really does represent a fusion of east and west, with traditional Islamic values standing side by side with those from neighbouring Europe. It is also a harmony of old and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Global Warming
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-14-global-warming/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 12:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-14-global-warming/</guid>
        <description>Firstly, welcome to 2010! Please wipe your feet.
Last year, nothing much happened. Specifically, representatives from all the countries of the earth met in Copenhagen, argued back and forth about Climate Change for ten days and then&amp;hellip;nothing. An “agreement” that not everyone agreed on. Bravo! …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Well Done Terrorism - you&#39;ve won again
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-10-well-done-terrorism-youve-won-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2010 01:29:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-10-well-done-terrorism-youve-won-again/</guid>
        <description>Well done terrorism – you’ve won again. A single guy is discovered with (potentially) explosive underpants and now millions of pounds of taxpayers’ money is being spent on full body scanners in airports. Initially, there was a fuss over liquids, which are still banned until 2011. Presumably someone …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
