<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/amm113/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/amm113/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Higher Education Policy decision deferred to campus-wide referendum
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-17-higher-education-policy-decision-deferred-to-campus-wide-referendum/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2014 14:21:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aamna Mohdin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-17-higher-education-policy-decision-deferred-to-campus-wide-referendum/</guid>
        <description>The Union’s Higher Education policy will go to a referendum later this year, after Union Council felt unable to make a decision without further consultation. Students will have the opportunity to choose from three funding models: free education, graduate tax and the current tuition fee loan system. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College to close its 4-year graduate-entry medicine course
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-13-college-to-close-its-4-year-graduate-entry-medicine-course/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2014 03:03:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aamna Mohdin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-13-college-to-close-its-4-year-graduate-entry-medicine-course/</guid>
        <description>College has recently announced the closure of the 4-year fast track graduate-entry medicine course. Students will instead have to apply for a new 5-year graduate medical course, which will open in 2015. The withdrawal of the 4-year option does not affect students currently on the programme.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Physicists are ready to turn light into matter within a year
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-23-imperial-physicists-are-ready-to-turn-light-into-matter-within-a-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 14:25:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aamna Mohdin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-23-imperial-physicists-are-ready-to-turn-light-into-matter-within-a-year/</guid>
        <description>Physicists at Imperial College London are ready to turn light into matter within a year, according to new research published in the journal Nature Photonics. If successful, the collider would have the capacity to demonstrate one of the most famous theories in physics: Einstein’s theory of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Eurovision voting pattern reveals no prejudice against the UK
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-eurovision-voting-pattern-reveals-no-prejudice-against-the-uk/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 01:57:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aamna Mohdin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-eurovision-voting-pattern-reveals-no-prejudice-against-the-uk/</guid>
        <description>Statisticians at UCL and Imperial College London have found that contrary to popular belief UK entries to Eurovision have not been “systematically shunned” by the rest of Europe. Statistical analysis of voting patterns have shown that while there is more to winning than just musical talent, there is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Should the Role of Government Chief Scientific Advisor be Democratised?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-17-should-the-role-of-government-chief-scientific-advisor-be-democratised/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2014 17:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aamna Mohdin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-17-should-the-role-of-government-chief-scientific-advisor-be-democratised/</guid>
        <description>What would happen if the next UK Government Chief Scientific Adviser (GCSA) was elected through a public vote? That’s exactly what a group of us from the science communication masters are attempting to find out. The GCSA is the head of the Government Office for Science, and the personal adviser on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial’s Defence Investment Holdings Top of List of London Universities
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-imperials-defence-investment-holdings-top-of-list-of-london-universities/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 05:03:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aamna Mohdin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-imperials-defence-investment-holdings-top-of-list-of-london-universities/</guid>
        <description>A London Student investigation found Imperial College London has the most invested in the arms industry. Compared with ten other London universities, Imperial’s holdings in defence companies comes out on top with investments totalling £3.9m. A Freedom of Information request found the College has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Care Data: Live saving tool or invasion of privacy?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-care-data-live-saving-tool-or-invasion-of-privacy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 17:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aamna Mohdin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-care-data-live-saving-tool-or-invasion-of-privacy/</guid>
        <description>The NHS has recently dispatched a leaflet titled “Better information means better care” to everyone in England. The leaflet describes a new initiative, care data, in which patient’s data from GP records will be extracted and shared with the Health and Social Care Information Centre. The NHS hopes to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College NHS Trust in Consultation to become a Foundation Trust
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-imperial-college-nhs-trust-in-consultation-to-become-a-foundation-trust/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 09:43:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aamna Mohdin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-imperial-college-nhs-trust-in-consultation-to-become-a-foundation-trust/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Healthcare NHS Trust is currently consulting on proposals to become a foundation trust. If successful, a foundation trust status will allow Imperial College Healthcare NHS Trust to become a not for profit entity that works independently from the government. The third public meeting …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brown Report Published
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-brown-report-published/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 03:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aamna Mohdin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-brown-report-published/</guid>
        <description>On 14th April 2013 the British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV) presented Imperial College London with a report that accumulated a list of various allegations of misconduct concerning animal experimentation. The report contained a video produced by the undercover investigator, which …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cops Off Campus – The Saga Continues
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-cops-off-campus-the-saga-continues/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 03:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aamna Mohdin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-cops-off-campus-the-saga-continues/</guid>
        <description>Students vow to “keep the momentum going” as the Cops off Campus campaign call another demonstration on 22 January. Three years on from the increase in tuition fees and the student protests that followed, university campuses are faced with fresh opposition as the recent protests against police …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
