<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/amanda_hertzberg/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/amanda_hertzberg/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>After the Collapse of Man Comes… Jellyfish?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-after-collapse-man-jellyfish/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Amanda Hertzberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-after-collapse-man-jellyfish/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
How art interacts with and depicts the changing climate is pivotal to how we think about climate change. This is the underlying idea of Eco-visionaries running right now at the Royal Academy of Arts. Very much a multimedia exhibition, it features works from DeepMind, AntFarm and Olafur …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Inside the Flashy Mind of Tim Walker</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-inside-flashy-mind-tim-walker/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Amanda Hertzberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-inside-flashy-mind-tim-walker/</guid>
        <description>2 stars
Dolls larger than humans. Hokusai’s The Great Wave inside of a room. A living mermaid floating in a box. In Tim Walker’s world everything is possible. As I walk through the door into the exhibition, I hear Tchaikovsky’s music playing in the background. On the walls hang Lewis Carroll-like …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Truth Isn&#39;t Always Satisfying</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-23-the-truth-isnt-always-satisfying/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 21:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Amanda Hertzberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-23-the-truth-isnt-always-satisfying/</guid>
        <description>There’s no doubt that a large chunk of the population are at least fascinated by conspiracy theories. Youtuber Shane Dawson has compilations of them on his youtube channel, each video with almost as many views as the British population. And we all have that friend who stays up at night listening to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Life, Love and Robots: A Conversation</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-life-love-and-robots-a-conversation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Amanda Hertzberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-life-love-and-robots-a-conversation/</guid>
        <description>The exhibition ‘AI: More Than Human’ (explored in the previous issue of Felix) is taking place at the Barbican right now, where visitors can explore the topic of artificial intelligence and machine learning, spanning back to the Middle Ages, then jumping to 1940’s Alan Turing to today’s newest …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>No Cirque du Soleil - show</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-no-cirque-du-soleil-show/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Amanda Hertzberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-no-cirque-du-soleil-show/</guid>
        <description>Following the theme of circus that started with last week’s almost painfully perfect Cirque du Soleil, the show I am reviewing this week is about all the not-so perfect stuff that goes on behind the scenes. Scottish circus performer and show director Ellie Dubois has created No Show, a show bringing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Circus With Totemic Status Like No Other</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-a-circus-with-totemic-status-like-no-other/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Amanda Hertzberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-a-circus-with-totemic-status-like-no-other/</guid>
        <description>If you were anything like me as a child, then you loved going to the circus. It was a rare occasion – it never happened more than once a year – but it was always magical. The whole atmosphere was buzzing before the show had even started; the smell of popcorn and cotton candy filling the air and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Politically charged art or abandoned bath house?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-politically-charged-art-or-abandoned-bath-house/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Amanda Hertzberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-politically-charged-art-or-abandoned-bath-house/</guid>
        <description>East London sits close to my heart, so when I heard Whitechapel Gallery had an exhibition related to gentrification and capitalism, I grabbed my Felix pen and notebook and ventured out of our comfortable West London.
The two artists in question; Michael Elmgreen and Ingar Dragset, from Denmark and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Super Duper Close Up</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-super-duper-close-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Amanda Hertzberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-super-duper-close-up/</guid>
        <description>One moment screaming passionately, the next sitting in the audience eating popcorn, Jessica Latowicki’s creative performance will feel like all of your anxieties embodied in front of you. Throw in a camera, some French skincare and a backdrop of a dark forest and you have Super Duper Close Up. …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
