<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/pk1811/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/pk1811/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>What did Imperial get up to this year?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-19-what-did-imperial-get-up-to-this-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 13:26:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,Philip Kent,Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-19-what-did-imperial-get-up-to-this-year/</guid>
        <description>This year, Felix has covered a plethora of stories from all corners of the campus, covering stories relevant to staff and students alike. We recap the stories we’ve brought to you this year, and what to watch out for next year.
BUAV hit our front pages twice this year; firstly, the animal rights …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Transport for London to accept Apple Pay
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-11-transport-for-london-to-accept-apple-pay/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 22:16:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-11-transport-for-london-to-accept-apple-pay/</guid>
        <description>Transport for London have announced that they will accept Apple Pay when it launches in the UK in July.
The move makes TfL the first public transport operator to accept the mobile payment technology.
The announcement follows Apple’s confirmation that Apple Pay will be making its way to Britain. At …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial centre identifies high cost of care for Afghanistan veterans
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-11-imperial-centre-identifies-high-cost-of-care-for-afghanistan-veterans/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 22:13:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-11-imperial-centre-identifies-high-cost-of-care-for-afghanistan-veterans/</guid>
        <description>Researchers at the Royal British Legion Centre for Blast Injury Studies have valued the cost of caring for members of the armed forces serving in Afghanistan who have lost limbs at just under £290 million.
When broken down, it cost £1.16 million per person to treat soldiers who required an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The main parties and their promises
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-1-the-main-parties-and-their-promises/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:05:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-1-the-main-parties-and-their-promises/</guid>
        <description>LABOUR
Economy
The front page of Labour’s manifesto pledges to obtain a surplus on the current budget as soon as possible. This differs from the Conservatives’ policy, as they pledge to eliminate the entire deficit, while Labour’s pledge still allows them to borrow for infrastructure investment – …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Highest ever voter turnout as Big Elections come to a close
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-19-highest-ever-voter-turnout-as-big-elections-come-to-a-close/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 23:44:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-19-highest-ever-voter-turnout-as-big-elections-come-to-a-close/</guid>
        <description>Last Friday saw the end of another year of campaigning and voting for the Imperial College Union sabbatical positions, with the results of the Big Elections 2015 announced during the results party in Metric.
The election, which also featured the Liberation Officers, Constituent Union positions and a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Big Elections 2015: Felix finds out who you’re voting for
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-13-the-big-elections-2015-felix-finds-out-who-youre-voting-for/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 00:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-13-the-big-elections-2015-felix-finds-out-who-youre-voting-for/</guid>
        <description>Update:Click here for a full breakdown of the results by faculty, year, and gender.
For the first time in its history, Felix has run an exit poll for the Big Elections. Now voting has closed, we can now announce our predictions for who will be next year’s sabbatical officers.
Our poll, which was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Election hopefuls grilled at Meet the Candidates
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-6-election-hopefuls-grilled-at-meet-the-candidates/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 13:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-6-election-hopefuls-grilled-at-meet-the-candidates/</guid>
        <description>Wednesday once again saw the annual broadcast of Meet the Candidates by Imperial College Television (ICTV), where candidates for the various Officer Trustee roles, as well as Felix Editor, Council Chair, and Student Trustees debated live on air as part of their campaigns to win the election.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What’s going on with student visas?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-27-whats-going-on-with-student-visas/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2015 00:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-27-whats-going-on-with-student-visas/</guid>
        <description> An influential group of MPs has criticised the Government’s student visa policy this week. In a report published by the All-Party Parliamentary Group on Migration, the MPs argued for re-opening of the “post-study work route” following graduation.
Up until 2012, international students could remain …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Visa expiry causes Commemoration Day to move
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-27-visa-expiry-causes-commemoration-day-to-move/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2015 00:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-27-visa-expiry-causes-commemoration-day-to-move/</guid>
        <description>In an email sent out earlier this month to undergraduate students expecting to graduate this year, the College announced a change from usual procedures for the annual ceremony.
The graduation day, known as Commemoration Day to commemorate the visit of Queen Victoria to the Royal College of Chemistry …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>£150 NHS student visa charge starts in April
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-27-150-nhs-student-visa-charge-starts-in-april/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2015 00:38:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-27-150-nhs-student-visa-charge-starts-in-april/</guid>
        <description>Despite complaints from many quarters, the Government will be implementing its previously announced plans to charge non-EU nationals (including students) for access to NHS services.
The proposals were initially announced as part of the Immigration Bill in October 2013.
Imperial College Union last …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ArtsFest fills the campus with free art and culture
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-27-artsfest-fills-the-campus-with-free-art-and-culture/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2015 00:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-27-artsfest-fills-the-campus-with-free-art-and-culture/</guid>
        <description>Last week, the Arts and Entertainments Board of Imperial College Union put on ArtsFest, a week-long celebration of the arts in association with Arts Imperial.
The week featured performances and events by all manner of Arts and Entertainments Board clubs, including the various musical groups, LeoSoc, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Questions Live looks into the tough subjects
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-20-imperial-questions-live-looks-into-the-tough-subjects/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 00:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thomas Lim,Philip Kent,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-20-imperial-questions-live-looks-into-the-tough-subjects/</guid>
        <description> Last Wednesday saw the very first broadcast of Imperial Questions Live, a new current affairs debating programme asking the big questions on campus.
The show, broadcast from the brand new Media Centre in the West Basement of Beit Quad, was presented by fourth year EEE student, Thomas Lim. The panel …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union Council condemns Counter-Terrorism Bill
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-union-council-condemns-counter-terrorism-bill/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 20:59:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-union-council-condemns-counter-terrorism-bill/</guid>
        <description>Also at Council this week was a motion against the Counter Terrorism and Security Bill (CTSB), which is currently concluding its passage through the Houses of Parliament.
The paper, submitted by Jawaad Farooq and seconded by Nida Mahmud and Shamim Ahmed, argues that the bill “discourages the free …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What keeps Felix surveys nice and secure?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-8-what-keeps-felix-surveys-nice-and-secure/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2015 21:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-8-what-keeps-felix-surveys-nice-and-secure/</guid>
        <description>Every year people ask how Felix keeps the details you give us in our surveys private and secure. To reassure all our readers, we now reveal how it works.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what we do to keep your response secure&amp;hellip; - Your survey response is stored containing only the information you give us, plus a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Girls in Peacetime not as twee as it sounds
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-girls-in-peacetime-not-as-twee-as-it-sounds/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 14:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-girls-in-peacetime-not-as-twee-as-it-sounds/</guid>
        <description>Twee is a word often used to describe Stuart Murdoch’s indie band, whose ninth album Girls in Peacetime Want to Dance was released on Matador on 19th January. However having listened to the album a number of times since it was released one is immediately forced to consider whether this label still …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Prince Charles opens new centre at St. Mary’s
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-30-prince-charles-opens-new-centre-at-st-marys/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 00:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-30-prince-charles-opens-new-centre-at-st-marys/</guid>
        <description>A new centre for innovative surgery has been opened by Prince Charles, the Prince of Wales, at St. Mary’s Hospital. The new centre, created and run by Imperial College London, has been set up to develop new surgical techniques – specifically ones which can make surgery quicker and easier.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Controversy as Imperial joins others in boycott of Universities “Green League”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-controversy-as-imperial-joins-others-in-boycott-of-universities-green-league/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 01:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-controversy-as-imperial-joins-others-in-boycott-of-universities-green-league/</guid>
        <description>Controversy has broken out over the decision by 69 of the 151 Universities eligible to take part in pressure group People &amp;amp; Planet’s University League to pull out of the survey. Imperial College were one of the institutions to not submit a return this year.
The survey, known until this year as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Proposal to cut 10 sabbaticals down to 6 at UCL falls through
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-12-proposal-to-cut-10-sabbaticals-down-to-6-at-ucl-falls-through/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 12:47:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-12-proposal-to-cut-10-sabbaticals-down-to-6-at-ucl-falls-through/</guid>
        <description>UCL Union has voted to not reduce the number of sabbatical officers in a close-fought debate at a General Assembly on Tuesday. The motion, which was voted for by a simple majority of students, failed to pass as it did not reach the 75% majority necessary to modify UCLU’s governing documents.
A …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Do you value your Imperial Degree?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-9-do-you-value-your-imperial-degree/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2014 14:51:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-9-do-you-value-your-imperial-degree/</guid>
        <description>Felix is launching a survey to find out of Imperial students are satisfied with their course, and see if students feel their degrees are value for money.
The &amp;ldquo;Imperial Value&amp;rdquo; survey is available until the end of term online at http://www.felixonline.co.uk/survey
A study by consumer …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cardiff Media strike comes to an end
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-21-cardiff-media-strike-comes-to-an-end/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2014 13:19:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-21-cardiff-media-strike-comes-to-an-end/</guid>
        <description>Student media at Cardiff University went on strike earlier this following a decision by the Student Senate (Cardiff’s version of Union Council) to force a re-election of Cardiff’s Vice-President of Media and Marketing.
Cardiff is the only other University to have a full-time Media Sabbatical Officer …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union’s Annual Report celebrates a succesful year
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-unions-annual-report-celebrates-a-succesful-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 20:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-unions-annual-report-celebrates-a-succesful-year/</guid>
        <description>Earlier this week, the Union released the 2013&amp;frasl;14 Annual Report. This document, prepared by Union managers and officer trustees, provides a summary of the activities of the Union over the last financial year.
As with previous editions, the report was opened by the exiting Union President, in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Penalties for Rugby teams announced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-penalties-for-rugby-teams-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 19:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-penalties-for-rugby-teams-announced/</guid>
        <description>Earlier this week, in light of the recent incidents concerning anti-social behaviour, Imperial College Union released the penalties that will be held against both Imperial College Union Rugby Football Club (ICURFC) and Imperial Medicals Rugby Football Club.
The ICURFC has been suspended for two …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>£1,000,000 ex-council flat sold in Chelsea
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-1000000-ex-council-flat-sold-in-chelsea/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 19:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-1000000-ex-council-flat-sold-in-chelsea/</guid>
        <description>A flat on Kings Road, Chelsea, has become the first ex-council flat to sell for near £1 million. The flat, which has three bedrooms as well as a communal courtyard, was bought by its former owners under the “Right to Buy” scheme in 1989 for the grand total of £48,000 (equivalent to around £110,000 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Professors win awards
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-17-imperial-professors-win-awards/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 15:19:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-17-imperial-professors-win-awards/</guid>
        <description>Two Imperial College academics have recently been awarded honours by their professional bodies, recognising outstanding achievement in their fields. Honorary Fellowship of the Institute of Physics (IoP) has been awarded to Professor Sir Peter Knight, an Emeritus Professor in Physics, while Professor …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Leicester&#39;s paper censored by Union
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-17-leicesters-paper-censored-by-union/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 15:17:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-17-leicesters-paper-censored-by-union/</guid>
        <description>Controversy has broken out at the University of Leicester over an attempt to censure its student paper, The Ripple, by the students’ union at Leicester. In an editorial posted on the paper’s website, Editor in Chief Jess Buckley expressed her disappointment with the Leicester union’s decision to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oxford University Students Union disaffiliates from NUS in close result
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-23-oxford-university-students-union-disaffiliates-from-nus-in-close-result/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 14:22:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-23-oxford-university-students-union-disaffiliates-from-nus-in-close-result/</guid>
        <description>Oxford University’s Students Union (OUSU), not to be confused with the Oxford Union, a debating society, narrowly voted to disaffiliate from the National Union of Students (NUS) in a referendum that concluded on Wednesday.
The vote follows a motion by OUSU’s Council last year to hold a referendum. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Head of Chemistry Department Appointed
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-24-new-head-of-chemistry-department-appointed/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 03:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-24-new-head-of-chemistry-department-appointed/</guid>
        <description>In an email to Chemistry students sent on 19 March, Professor Alan Armstrong has been named as the new head of the Chemistry Department. The current Head of Department, Professor Tom Welton, is stepping down from his role as his five-year tenure has expired, although the Department informed students …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Drugs Survey
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-felix-drugs-survey/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 19:08:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Gray,Philip Kent,Philippa M Skett,Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-felix-drugs-survey/</guid>
        <description> The full version is available online.
Out of the 762 responses that we received, 54% said that they had tried illegal drugs. Splitting this into male and female showed that 57% of men said that they had taken drugs, whereas 49% of women said that they had.
 57% of men and 49% of women said that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The next lot: an internship at Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-14-the-next-lot-an-internship-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 10:28:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-14-the-next-lot-an-internship-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Students and alumni have been outraged to discover the auctioning of a place at Imperial College for a one-week summer internship at the Institute of Biomedical Engineering that appeared on the morning of Wednesday 14 May. This placement had been made available to students of Westminster School, a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Summer Elections opens with re-election for Deputy President (Education)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-10-summer-elections-opens-with-re-election-for-deputy-president-education/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2013 17:47:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-10-summer-elections-opens-with-re-election-for-deputy-president-education/</guid>
        <description>The annual Summer Elections have come around once again, with nominations for the various Council Officers, Council Chair, and positions of the Graduate Student&amp;rsquo;s Union, the new name of the GSA.
Also up for election is Deputy President (Education), a post previously won by Jonathan London. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dialogue over Acton
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-9-dialogue-over-acton/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 12:18:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-9-dialogue-over-acton/</guid>
        <description>The Union has replied to the College’s response to the Against Acton campaign, started earlier this year following the unveiling of plans by the College to construct an 856 bed hall of residence in North Acton. Paul Beaumont, Union President, sent a list of requests to the College, which went to the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>RCS Motor race towards competition success
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-9-rcs-motor-race-towards-competition-success/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 12:08:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-9-rcs-motor-race-towards-competition-success/</guid>
        <description>Much celebration was had by members of RCS Motor Club as Jezebel, the vintage fire engine they maintain, was awarded ‘Second in Class’ at the 52nd HCVS London to Brighton Run, held last Sunday. The HCVS London to Brighton Run is an annual competition where commercial vehicles aged 20 years or older …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Royal Institution receives debt-clearing donation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-25-royal-institution-receives-debt-clearing-donation/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 18:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-25-royal-institution-receives-debt-clearing-donation/</guid>
        <description>In an email sent to members on March 20th, Sir Richard Sykes, Chairman of the Royal Institution, announced the receipt of an anonymous £4.4 million pound donation, clearing debts which have lead to the scientific body&amp;rsquo;s Central London home being placed on the market. Financial difficulties …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fish getting high
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-21-fish-getting-high/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 20:47:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-21-fish-getting-high/</guid>
        <description>Does any of your medication get washed away through the water system? If so, your medication could lead to aquatic life having a very exhilarating day indeed.
Research from Umeå University, Sweden has shown how an “unusually high” concentration of anti-anxiety drug, Oxazepam, in a river in Sweden …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You met the DeskJet, now meet the DrugJet
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-you-met-the-deskjet-now-meet-the-drugjet/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 20:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-you-met-the-deskjet-now-meet-the-drugjet/</guid>
        <description>Everyone has heard of the inkjet printer, you probably have one yourself. However, one application of the venerable office supply you haven’t heard of is printing drugs, recently developed at the UCL School of Pharmacy.
An inkjet printer works by delivering small droplets of ink onto the page, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tiny protons?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-tiny-protons/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 23:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-tiny-protons/</guid>
        <description>The radius of a proton has generally been considered to be 0.87 femtometers (fm), an incredibly tiny amount. However, a paper published in Science earlier this year suggests this miniscule distance may be smaller than previously thought.
A team from ETH Zürich took a muonic hydrogen, a hydrogen atom …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Suffer from hayfever? A solution may be at hand...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-22-suffer-from-hayfever-a-solution-may-be-at-hand/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 12:18:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jacob Ward,Philippa M Skett,Annina M Sartor,Maciej Matuszewski,Mimi Li,Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-22-suffer-from-hayfever-a-solution-may-be-at-hand/</guid>
        <description> What is hayfever? A little history&amp;hellip;
First scientifically described in 1819 by John Bostock, hay fever, also known as allergic rhinitis, is an allergic reaction to small particles in the air that most commonly causes nasal inflammation but may also result in watery eyes and itching throat. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Circuits you can just wash away
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-circuits-you-can-just-wash-away/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:19:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-circuits-you-can-just-wash-away/</guid>
        <description>A well-known property of modern silicon-based electronics is their resilience to change: a printed circuit board (PCB) doesn’t dissolve, and only melts at high temperatures. However, following research recently published in Science, this may no longer be the case, with the production of a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Unexpected science at the Imperial Fringe
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-unexpected-science-at-the-imperial-fringe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 12:02:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-unexpected-science-at-the-imperial-fringe/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College describe the Fringe as “a series of public events exploring the unexpected side of science”, and like the Edinburgh Fringe, and other events with this name, there is a focus on the stranger side the field it covers; in this instance, academic research.
The Imperial Fringe is part of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Planning permission for new Imperial West campus delayed
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-8-planning-permission-for-new-imperial-west-campus-delayed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2012 08:26:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-8-planning-permission-for-new-imperial-west-campus-delayed/</guid>
        <description>Councillors at the London Borough of Hammersmith and Fulham have postponed discussion of the planning permission for the new “Imperial West” campus for a second time, following the case officer taking unexpected leave. This follows on quickly from a recent High Court judgement that found that the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Sexism Survey
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-24-felix-sexism-survey/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 23:40:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie-Laure Hicks,Silvia Araguas Rodriguez,Philip Kent,Jonathan Kim,Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-24-felix-sexism-survey/</guid>
        <description>Over the past year, 10 articles and 231 comments have been written about sexism in science and at Imperial. Stephen Smith’s “Sexism at Imperial College” has been viewed over 7,500 times on the Felix website. Sexism is clearly an issue that concerns the Imperial community and 631 of you gave us your …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A cheaper way to make hydrogen
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-a-cheaper-way-to-make-hydrogen/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 11:13:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-a-cheaper-way-to-make-hydrogen/</guid>
        <description>A promising way to power vehicles and appliances in the future is through use of hydrogen fuel cells. These, however, require a source of hydrogen to work, and obtaining this hydrogen has typically been an expensive process.
The most common method to obtain the gas is to split water into oxygen and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Weighing a single atom
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-weighing-a-single-atom/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 20:39:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-weighing-a-single-atom/</guid>
        <description>A mass sensor has been developed by a group of Spanish scientists, lead by Julien Chaste from the Catalan Institute of Nanotechnology, capable of weighing individual molecules, atoms, and even protons.
Sensors of this type, known as nanomechanical mass sensors, have been developed before. However, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where was the debate?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-where-was-the-debate/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 22:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-where-was-the-debate/</guid>
        <description>On the Wednesday before elections opened, members of the Union had their questions answered live on STOIC by candidates for the ICU Sabbatical Positions, as well as the faculty union presidents and the student trustees. This is a fantastic idea – if the candidates want our vote, they should be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Motor Club races towards fire engine repair
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-motor-club-races-towards-fire-engine-repair/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 21:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-motor-club-races-towards-fire-engine-repair/</guid>
        <description>Members of RCS Motor Club have got one stop closer to fully repairing Jezebel, the RCSU’s 1916 fire engine, after successful remetalling of an engine bearing, and reconstruction of the engine. Jezebel has been off the road since the end of last year, following an engine fault when travelling back …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Sex Survey 2012
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-felix-sex-survey-2012/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 22:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Allinson,Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-felix-sex-survey-2012/</guid>
        <description>The number of respondents we had to the sex survey this year has been almost overwhelming. 1063 of you replied, and only about 20 of them as far as we could tell were blatant trolls (thank you guys btw for making us laugh).
Over the course of these next seven pages, we’ll delve into the details of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICU Cinema awarded compensation for Friday night Union losses
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-icu-cinema-awarded-compensation-for-friday-night-union-losses/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 23:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-icu-cinema-awarded-compensation-for-friday-night-union-losses/</guid>
        <description>A paper by ICU Cinema which has been passed by Imperial College Union’s Executive Committee, the policy-executing branch of the Union, requested compensation for £94.50 in predicted losses from showings during the Film Festival, running from 10 January until 20 January, due to entry charges to enter …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nominations open for Union Big Elections
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-nominations-open-for-union-big-elections/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 22:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-nominations-open-for-union-big-elections/</guid>
        <description>Nominations for the Union’s ‘Big Elections’ opened on Monday 13 February with students able to put themselves forward as candidates for departmental and sabbatical positions. The site’s look and feel has been radically changed from previous elections, and the voting statistics have reportedly been …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>World’s thinnest pane of glass unveiled
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-worlds-thinnest-pane-of-glass-unveiled/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 21:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-worlds-thinnest-pane-of-glass-unveiled/</guid>
        <description>A paper in 1932 by William Holder Zachariasen hinted at the atomic structure of glass, which at the time was unexplored. This deduction was based purely on the properties of glass known at the time. For example, the fact it does not have a crystalline structure indicated that molecules within it are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Abandon all hope all ye who neglect your community
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-abandon-all-hope-all-ye-who-neglect-your-community/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 23:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-abandon-all-hope-all-ye-who-neglect-your-community/</guid>
        <description>Back home in the Midlands, there is an extremely popular bus company known as Trent Barton. Like just about every other bus company in the world, you get on the bus, you pay some money, and they drive you to where you want to go. Some of their competitors are faster at getting to some destinations, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Graphene oxide filters out water
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-graphene-oxide-filters-out-water/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 22:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-graphene-oxide-filters-out-water/</guid>
        <description>In a paper recently published in Science, a team from the University of Manchester has reported that graphene oxide is capable of selectively filtering water molecules, leaving all other types of molecule blocked. This is a particularly surprising result for the team, who, from previous research, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Exhibition Road closes for grand opening
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-exhibition-road-closes-for-grand-opening/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 00:28:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-exhibition-road-closes-for-grand-opening/</guid>
        <description>Following two years of construction, Exhibition Road closed last Wednesday for its grand opening led by the Mayor of London, Boris Johnson. ‘No parking’ signs were put up in advance and the event saw a day long closure marking the opening of the brand new signature road running through the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Academics to boycott Elsevier journals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-academics-to-boycott-elsevier-journals/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 00:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-academics-to-boycott-elsevier-journals/</guid>
        <description>Following a damning blog post by Cambridge mathematician Professor Tim Gowers, nearly 3,000 academics have signed an online pledge to cease all work with Elsevier, a Dutch journal publishing house responsible for many publications including The Lancet.
Elsevier have come under frequent criticism for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Move to prevent Big Ben tower lean
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-27-move-to-prevent-big-ben-tower-lean/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 00:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-27-move-to-prevent-big-ben-tower-lean/</guid>
        <description>Members of the House of Commons Commission have met to discuss options to deal with the subsidence problems that the Palace of Westminster is experiencing. The palace, which was constructed in 1870, is slowly sinking into the ground, and the clock tower, which houses the infamous Big Ben, is leaning …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New milestones reached in fight against Alzheimer’s
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-new-milestones-reached-in-fight-against-alzheimers/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 22:41:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-new-milestones-reached-in-fight-against-alzheimers/</guid>
        <description>Alzheimer’s is an as-yet incurable disease that accounts for the majority of cases of dementia. A characteristic symptom of people with Alzheimer’s is memory loss, with the person affected gradually becoming increasingly forgetful; unable to remember their own identity, and eventually, complete …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An exciting new musical project
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-an-exciting-new-musical-project/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 20:43:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-an-exciting-new-musical-project/</guid>
        <description>Director Stuart Murdoch Screenwriters Stuart Murdoch
God Help The Girl builds on from a musical project by Stuart Murdoch (of Belle and Sebastian fame) that resulted in a set of EPs and an album of the same name in 2009. The tracks introduce the story of Eve, a girl with much promise and a bright …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Leap second announced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-leap-second-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 22:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-leap-second-announced/</guid>
        <description>Astronomers and engineers at the International Earth Rotation and Reference Systems Service (IERS) Earth Orientation Centre recently announced that a leap second will be applied at the end of June this year. Leap seconds are introduced by the IERS to make up for inaccuracies in timekeeping, made as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial academics awarded in New Year&#39;s Honours
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-imperial-academics-awarded-in-new-years-honours/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 22:06:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-imperial-academics-awarded-in-new-years-honours/</guid>
        <description>Three academics at Imperial College have received some of the highest awards in the country for their work in the sciences in the New Year’s Honours, announced on December 31. These honours are issued by the Monarch on the advice of the Government for exemplary service.
Professor Sir Stephen Bloom, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ent committee elections? What a joke!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-ent-committee-elections-what-a-joke/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 22:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-ent-committee-elections-what-a-joke/</guid>
        <description>Did you know that voting for First Year Entertainments Committee Members opened last week? Nope, me neither – until it was pointed out to me. In fact, for that matter, I never knew that you could stand for it! Imperial’s Union is a very democratic affair, and this is a good thing (though it is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A right royal roundup
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-a-right-royal-roundup/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 21:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-a-right-royal-roundup/</guid>
        <description>Hacks, cracks and website attacks
Without a doubt, the biggest thing to hit the gaming world this year would have to be April’s takedown of the PSN. Gamers were originally left in the dark about the whole situation, with Sony initially only offering the explanation that there was an ‘external …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science Societies
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-science-societies/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 19:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-science-societies/</guid>
        <description>November 26 saw the first of what is hoped to be an annual convening of the science societies of universities in the UK in a dinner, attended by some of the most prestigious names in the discipline.
Guests of honour included HRH The Duke of Kent; Nobel laureate Sir Paul Nurse, who received his prize …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Skyrim, Saints Row? You&#39;ve got nothing on Creatures!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-skyrim-saints-row-youve-got-nothing-on-creatures/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 21:11:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-skyrim-saints-row-youve-got-nothing-on-creatures/</guid>
        <description>With blockbusters such as Skyrim being released, and modern legends like Minecraft celebrating its birthday, it is often possible to overlook some real masterpieces. One of these is Creatures, and the sad thing is that many of you will probably have never heard of it!
Creatures is the brainchild of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nanocars with four-wheel drive
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-nanocars-with-four-wheel-drive/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 20:18:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-nanocars-with-four-wheel-drive/</guid>
        <description>Researchers at the University of Groningen, Netherlands have announced that they have succesfully produced a single-molecule ‘car’, capable of moving by use of its four ‘wheels’ when excited by a scanning tunnelling microscope (STM). This announcement follows previous research by the group, led by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The cunning of Dr Fox
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-the-cunning-of-dr-fox/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 21:58:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-the-cunning-of-dr-fox/</guid>
        <description>Last Friday, after a week of revelations over wrongdoing in his affairs, the Defence Secretary Dr Liam Fox, announced his resignation to the Prime Minister. The first Tory cabinet minister to resign has been replaced by Philip Hammond, whose Transport brief is now to be fulfilled by Treasury …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
