<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jlp210/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jlp210/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Time to tie up Bowie
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-4-30-time-to-tie-up-bowie/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 14:32:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jemma Pilcher,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-4-30-time-to-tie-up-bowie/</guid>
        <description>David Bowie is more than just pop star. He is a multi-instrumentalist, artist, mime artist, actor, lyricist, poet and record producer. Drawing on all sectors of the art world and modern life for inspiration, his intellectual songs and flamboyant image combine the familiar and the alien and have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Not an Italian job
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-21-not-an-italian-job/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 20:52:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jemma Pilcher,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-21-not-an-italian-job/</guid>
        <description>The Renaissance is generally considered to be an Italian affair. No one could doubt the profound part that the works of the Italians, such as Michangelo and Leonardo da Vinci, played in this era. But this is not the whole story. The 130 plus artworks which are currently on display at The Queen’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Doomy Night With Katatonia and Alcest
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-a-doomy-night-with-katatonia-and-alcest/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 22:51:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jemma Pilcher,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-a-doomy-night-with-katatonia-and-alcest/</guid>
        <description>Following the release of their sumptuous ninth album, Dead End Kings, the Swedish doom metal quintet Katatonia returned to London, for another evening of great music and melancholia. This time they were accompanied by the French shoe-gazing concept band Alcest and an American rock band, called …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get Katatonic with Dead End Kings
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-get-katatonic-with-dead-end-kings/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 03:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jemma Pilcher,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-get-katatonic-with-dead-end-kings/</guid>
        <description>Whenever I am asked which my favourite Katatonia album is, my standard response is to stare pensively into the distance for a moment and then simply reply ‘every Katatonia album’. And now their ninth studio album Dead End Kings has entered the equation&amp;hellip; my answer remains the same.
Since their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gold for Bronze
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-gold-for-bronze/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 20:56:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jemma Pilcher,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-gold-for-bronze/</guid>
        <description>Classically, bronze is thought of as the material of antiquity. The discovery of the endurable properties of such copper alloys certainly allowed our ancestors to make more robust tools and weapons than their stone-age predecessors. Its use as an artistic medium, however, from the ancient world to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Summer Lightning
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-summer-lightning/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 20:52:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jemma Pilcher,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-summer-lightning/</guid>
        <description>Jemma Pilcher is a fresher ariving at Imperial with an impressive portfolio following an art foundation. Phoenix commissioned this shoot to show off three beautiful bodices from her back catalogue. - Ed
I am fascinated by the language of clothing; what does an ensemble say about its wearer? These …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
