<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/em2512/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/em2512/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s all about that Rex (no pteranodon)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-18-its-all-about-that-rex-no-pteranodon/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2015 20:16:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ellen Mathieson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-18-its-all-about-that-rex-no-pteranodon/</guid>
        <description>First things first, it’s not as good as Jurassic Park. And really it never was going to compare to the original. It’s battling years of love and nostalgia, and the film that inspired countless people to spend at least a couple of years as a kid wanting to be an archaeologist (usually somewhere …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can you even spell A Cappella?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-can-you-even-spell-a-cappella/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 10:54:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ellen Mathieson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-can-you-even-spell-a-cappella/</guid>
        <description>It’s a well-known fact that comedy sequels are tricky. For every occasional good one, there is a whole host of bad ones. Pitch Perfect was one of 2009 most surprising hits, making back its money in a big way and having one of the most downloaded soundtracks of the year.
With almost all of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Once more into the lens: The History of Projection
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-once-more-into-the-lens-the-history-of-projection/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 11:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ellen Mathieson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-once-more-into-the-lens-the-history-of-projection/</guid>
        <description>The field of optics was founded during the scientific revolution, leading to large improvements in lenses. Photographic paper was first developed in the 19th century, around the same time that the first phonographic sound recordings were happening. Once these three existed, it was only a matter of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“You all look the same to me”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-you-all-look-the-same-to-me/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 16:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ellen Mathieson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-you-all-look-the-same-to-me/</guid>
        <description>This week I somehow found myself with a day free, so made the choice to go and see a triple bill of Whiplash, Birdman and Foxcatcher, which between them have accumulated an impressive selection of award nominations and wins, including nineteen Oscar nominations. So there was one thing about them …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Are you paying attention?”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-are-you-paying-attention/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 12:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ellen Mathieson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-are-you-paying-attention/</guid>
        <description>Director: Morten Tyldum
Screenplay: Graham Moore
Cast: Benedict Cumberbatch, Keira Knightley, Matthew Goode, Charles Dance, Allen Leech, Mark Strong
Rating: 4&amp;frasl;5
T_he Imitation Game _is the story of Alan Turing, a story that most Imperial student probably knows. He is the father of computing, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to surive a horror film
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-how-to-surive-a-horror-film/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 21:44:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ellen Mathieson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-how-to-surive-a-horror-film/</guid>
        <description>It’s late night on Halloween, and you and a group of friends are walking home from your party of choice. One of you takes a wrong turning and somehow you suddenly lost in a part of London you don’t know. You stop and ask for directions, but no-one is being helpful. And even though there are only …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>&#34;Are you feeling horny?&#34;
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-are-you-feeling-horny/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 19:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ellen Mathieson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-are-you-feeling-horny/</guid>
        <description>From the very beginning, Horns is a film that doesn’t really seem to know what it’s meant to be. I’m always suspicious of a film that describes itself with more than two genres, but when you are a supernatural thriller incorporating elements of fantasy, comedy and romance, with a bit of drama to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Powerful Man moves from the Union to the Blue Cube
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-24-a-powerful-man-moves-from-the-union-to-the-blue-cube/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2014 12:37:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ellen Mathieson,Stephen Ball,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-24-a-powerful-man-moves-from-the-union-to-the-blue-cube/</guid>
        <description>Dr Philip Power is finally leaving the Union after 16 years of involvement at Imperial College London, first as an undergraduate, then a postgraduate and finally as a member of staff for Imperial College Union.
During his time as a student at Imperial, first in the Department of Mathematics and then …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Night of Sun, Sex and Slavery with Imperial Cinema
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-a-night-of-sun-sex-and-slavery-with-imperial-cinema/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 13:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ellen Mathieson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-a-night-of-sun-sex-and-slavery-with-imperial-cinema/</guid>
        <description>It’s amazing how things happen and time passes without you realising it. For some of you reading this, the upcoming Spring All-Nighter could very well be your last. This could be your final chance to sit in a crowded room and spend an evening, a night and part of a morning watching some of the best …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>MTSoc Produce the Producers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-19-mtsoc-produce-the-producers/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2014 02:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ellen Mathieson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-19-mtsoc-produce-the-producers/</guid>
        <description>Somehow on a blustery Tuesday evening I found myself invited to the dress rehearsal of MTSoc’s latest performance, The Producers. For those unfamiliar with this play, the basic plot is thus: After Max Bialystock&amp;rsquo;s latest show closes - a failure after only one night - he swears to return as the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
