<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ac1507/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ac1507/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Buffer – Because you want to tweet better
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-buffer-because-you-want-to-tweet-better/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 20:28:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Afonso Campos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-buffer-because-you-want-to-tweet-better/</guid>
        <description>The proliferation of Twitter is ubiquitous to say the least and despite the service being almost universally loved by its users, annoying your followers with a barrage of tweets is not a gargantuan task to accomplish. Enter Buffer.
Buffer is a simple, yet highly effective web application that lets …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The business of hair styling
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-the-business-of-hair-styling/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 20:49:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Afonso Campos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-the-business-of-hair-styling/</guid>
        <description>I meet Drew Foster at his brand new hair salon in the heart of Shoreditch early one morning. I am there as he opens up shop. There is a familiar atmosphere to the place, not unlike that of a mid to late sixties music video awash with distant pastel colours. Hues of green, pink and blue are adorned …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Draw yourself a new path
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-draw-yourself-a-new-path/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 20:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Afonso Campos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-draw-yourself-a-new-path/</guid>
        <description>You may not yet have heard of PathMotion – a rather unorthodox, yet compelling new careers website with a lot of potential; the brainchild of entrepreneur David Rivel.
I sat with him at a London diner to hear his story. His enthusiasm is not only breathtaking, but also contagious. There is no …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>If you read nothing else this week...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-if-you-read-nothing-else-this-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 19:42:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Afonso Campos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-if-you-read-nothing-else-this-week/</guid>
        <description>Midnight in the Garden of Good and Evil, by John Berendt, is a welcome exception to my reading habits. It is not a work of fiction, but rather the enthralling true story of a murder and the events surrounding it. It is doubtlessly one of the finest works of modern American literature. It maintained …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Finance Society hosts first-of-a-kind trading game
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-finance-society-hosts-first-of-a-kind-trading-game/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 19:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Afonso Campos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-finance-society-hosts-first-of-a-kind-trading-game/</guid>
        <description>On the 29th of November, teams from several universities from all over the UK competed in a never before seen trading simulation. The trading game held at Imperial was part of the national UK Investment Banking Series, a competition initiated in 2010 by the Imperial College Finance Society (ICFS) …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Netball beat dirty, cheating King’s Medics
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-netball-beat-dirty-cheating-kings-medics/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 20:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Afonso Campos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-netball-beat-dirty-cheating-kings-medics/</guid>
        <description>Taking on medics at netball is always a daunting task and coming up against King’s Medics was no different to the norm. Tensions were high amongst the girls before the game had even got underway due to the umpires running late however, the team soon found thir rhythm once the match began.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Shakin’ your cocktail feather
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-shakin-your-cocktail-feather/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 19:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Afonso Campos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-shakin-your-cocktail-feather/</guid>
        <description>As the cold and dark winter draws swiftly around us there is but one thing to warm the cockles on a dreary evening. Cocktails, the perfect pick-me-up for pre or post-prandial pleasure. Imperial students, you’re now in the nexus of the UK’s cocktail scene, just down the road from the Savoy hotel …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A focus on: Basics of Islamic Finance
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-a-focus-on-basics-of-islamic-finance/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 19:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Afonso Campos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-a-focus-on-basics-of-islamic-finance/</guid>
        <description>So, what is Islamic Finance, really? Give me the basics.
To put it relatively simply, Islamic Finance is an alternative way of going about financial dealings; these are conducted in such a way that they comply fully with the religious requirements of Islam. It is generally fully governed by and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Football’s not coming home
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-footballs-not-coming-home/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 20:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Afonso Campos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-footballs-not-coming-home/</guid>
        <description>The dust hasn’t even had time to settle; the Davids Cameron and Beckham as well as HRH Prince William are making their way back to England defeated. The 2018 World Cup will be played in Russia and the next opportunity for England to host the event will be in 20 years time. Initial reports suggest …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial needs to start raising serious money
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-imperial-needs-to-start-raising-serious-money/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 21:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Afonso Campos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-imperial-needs-to-start-raising-serious-money/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College has long wished and pledged to be among the world’s elite of academia, continuously making the assertion that it can stack up proudly against the financial mammoths that are the top American universities, Oxford, and Cambridge. Its literature certainly highlights the College’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Did Physics break the economy? Can it save it?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-did-physics-break-the-economy-can-it-save-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 18:48:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Afonso Campos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-did-physics-break-the-economy-can-it-save-it/</guid>
        <description>At the apogee of the mathematical finance movement in the mid nineties, billions were being made by pioneering science and finance academics and those who had the foresight to see the increasing use of these techniques. Louis Bachelier, the informal father of the discipline about a century ago would …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The summer begins right now
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-7-the-summer-begins-right-now/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 23:03:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Afonso Campos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-7-the-summer-begins-right-now/</guid>
        <description>Being at one of the world’s top universities has its perks when it comes to getting employed. You are lucky enough that companies actively want to give you the chance to shine through a summer internship which could hopefully lead to the holy grail; the offer of a full-time job after your …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
