<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ck2513/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ck2513/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Will our government be reborn this Spring?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-4-will-our-government-be-reborn-this-spring/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 16:17:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-4-will-our-government-be-reborn-this-spring/</guid>
        <description>In some accounts of the ‘Constantinian shift’ towards Christianity as the state religion of the Roman Empire in the 4th century CE, part of the political efficacy of the move came through the assimilation to Christianity of a variegated iconography and diverse social practices associated with older …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>For Syriza and the Left Platform
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-9-for-syriza-and-the-left-platform/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 19:49:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-9-for-syriza-and-the-left-platform/</guid>
        <description>Syriza’s victory in the Greek elections in January is the most important event to take place in Spain and Greece since the outbreak of the 2010 Eurozone crisis forced the re-shuffle of popular left-wing parties. Syriza was formed in 2004, mainly from breakaways from the Greek Communist Party (KKE). …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Poppies will put them to sleep
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-poppies-will-put-them-to-sleep/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 18:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-poppies-will-put-them-to-sleep/</guid>
        <description>Recall the scene from the Wizard of Oz where the Wicked Witch of the West hinders the progress of Dorothy and company by sending them to sleep in a field of poppies. Does this not encapsulate a basic – symbolic – truth about these flowers? Pace John McCrae of In Flanders Fields fame, the soporific …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reflections on Oscar Pistorius, Marikana and the Media
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-reflections-on-oscar-pistorius-marikana-and-the-media/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 18:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-reflections-on-oscar-pistorius-marikana-and-the-media/</guid>
        <description>In Signatures of the Visible, Fredric Jameson states that “the visual is essentially pornographic” – that is, its end is in “mindless rapture”. That being said, as any reader of Orwell knows, there are degrees of equality; that is to say, while all ‘visuals’ (forgive the clumsy expression) are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Rising Wind of Japanese Nationalism
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-2-the-rising-wind-of-japanese-nationalism/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 12:45:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-2-the-rising-wind-of-japanese-nationalism/</guid>
        <description>Last week’s Felix film section discussed the ‘swan song’ – to use Fred Fyles’ phrase – of Studio Ghibli’s Miyazaki Hayao, The Wind Rises. I will begin by saying that the film is without doubt a ‘visual feast’, while its topic matter – loosely the life of the engineer of the most famous Japanese WWII …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lenin’s Imperialism and 700 years of Finance
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-23-lenins-imperialism-and-700-years-of-finance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 13:50:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-23-lenins-imperialism-and-700-years-of-finance/</guid>
        <description>Last week I gave a fairly standard summary on the start of the financial crisis, and a Guardian, perhaps Huffington Post, summary of subsequent economic ‘events’. This was to help put the findings of a recent economic research group into a little context and provide some background to my criticism …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The End of the Great Recession?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-16-the-end-of-the-great-recession/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 01:50:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-16-the-end-of-the-great-recession/</guid>
        <description>The ‘Great Recession’ is over. To quote the Times: ‘It’s official’. This verdict, coming as it does from ‘one of the country’s leading economic bodies,’ is very impressive no doubt. The National Institute of Economic and Social Research (NIESR) (from whence the claim), is an institution blessed with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ukraine Revisited
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-ukraine-revisited/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 02:10:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-ukraine-revisited/</guid>
        <description>Having written about the Ukraine when the events there were all just kicking off, I feel it is about time to return to the topic. Then I wrote full of youthful enthusiasm but now I shall have to take a more sober perspective. I could look at this (and to some extent I do) as a further sad …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Thoughts on the Imperial Elections
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-7-thoughts-on-the-imperial-elections/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 13:02:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-7-thoughts-on-the-imperial-elections/</guid>
        <description>I must have manifestos on the brain because after three weeks writing about a certain famous Communist one, I turn to our own election manifestos. Voting has occasioned the re-emergence of some long dormant reflections, recounted here.
The first thing that struck me about the Manifestos is their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Manifesto: Place in Marxist Thought
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-manifesto-place-in-marxist-thought/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 04:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-manifesto-place-in-marxist-thought/</guid>
        <description>To round up my three weeks of commentary on the Manifesto, I shall try and place it in Marxist thought. I was originally going to write a short critique of Marxist thought but it quickly grew to an unreadable length and so I have settled for this slightly less ambitious task. Thus this text is half …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Communist Manifesto: A History
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-28-communist-manifesto-a-history/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 07:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-28-communist-manifesto-a-history/</guid>
        <description>Pre-History: The world that formed The Manifesto was a world in the process of, to use Karl Polanyi’s term, a great transformation. The American and French revolutions had shown once and for all that the old absolutist orders were anachronisms that had somehow forgotten to die; the industrial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Communist Manifesto Turns 166
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-communist-manifesto-turns-166/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 03:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-communist-manifesto-turns-166/</guid>
        <description>To celebrate the 166th anniversary of the publication of the Communist Manifesto, I shall be writing a three part series on the Manifesto: on its theoretical contents, on its history and impact and on its flaws and its position in Marxist thought. What should never be forgotten about the Manifesto …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Deriving Ought from Is
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-17-deriving-ought-from-is/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 17:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-17-deriving-ought-from-is/</guid>
        <description>I agree with Fredric Jameson that we have witnessed a disturbing ‘return of traditional philosophy … beginning with its hoariest subfields, such as ethics.’ To quote another Marxist Antonio Negri’s Political Descartes, ‘every metaphysics is simultaneously a political ontology’ and this applies all …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Philsophical Investigations
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-philsophical-investigations/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 05:09:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-philsophical-investigations/</guid>
        <description>Beneath the differences between Wittgenstein’s Tractatus-Logico Philosophicus and his Philosophical Investigations there is a more fundamental continuity between the texts. This article relies heavily on two books, Alain Badiou’s Wittgenstein’s Anti-Philosophy and Saul Kripke’s On Rules and Private …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Our stake in the arms industry
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-our-stake-in-the-arms-industry/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 05:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-our-stake-in-the-arms-industry/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London has a £3.9 million stake in the arms industry, according to a report in the London Student. The report, published on Monday 27th January, details the shares that London universities have invested in various arms companies. Imperial has by far the largest stake with £3.9 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sorry for droning on...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-sorry-for-droning-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 17:51:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-sorry-for-droning-on/</guid>
        <description>At the time of writing, the Guardian has just run an online story about Obama. It seems he is ready to bypass congress when it comes to his 2014 agenda. Dan Pfeifer, Obama’s senior advisor for strategy appears particularly ‘American’ in the most pejorative European sense of the term: ‘We need to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Role of Role Models
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-the-role-of-role-models/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 09:53:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-the-role-of-role-models/</guid>
        <description>I will confess now that I have never really understood the appeal of role models. It has always seemed slightly ridiculous to treat someone as if they were an exemplary figure, and with a little maturity I also came to recognise the symbolic violence in raising that someone above their idiotic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NHS Data Sale: Ramifications?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-nhs-data-sale-ramifications/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 09:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-nhs-data-sale-ramifications/</guid>
        <description>All members of the broadly defined ‘left’ occasionally fall into the trap Yeats left us when he said ‘the best lack all conviction whilst the worst are filled with passionate intensity’. Thankfully, my spell amongst the ‘best’, demonstrated in the sickening sentimentality of last week’s piece, has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Now is the winter of our discontent
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-now-is-the-winter-of-our-discontent/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 03:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-now-is-the-winter-of-our-discontent/</guid>
        <description>Richard III marks the start of Shakespeare’s longstanding engagement with villainy. From the ‘motiveless malignity’ of Iago to the sublime tragic grandeur of the Macbeths, the roots of all can be spied in this early work; the scandalous graveside seduction, the poisonous force of Queen Margaret. And …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Student Protests in Ukraine
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-student-protests-in-ukraine/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 04:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-student-protests-in-ukraine/</guid>
        <description>The dramatic events in Ukraine in recent weeks have again brought the country into the headlines. The mainly student protests in Kiev are about reneged promises over further integration with the EU. Before we come to the table with our personal prejudices and biases over the EU (and both UKIP and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Orwellian Spanish Security Bill
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-the-orwellian-spanish-security-bill/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 21:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-the-orwellian-spanish-security-bill/</guid>
        <description>I learned this week that the Spanish government have recently been taking lessons from George Orwell. The new Citizen Security Bill is a title worthy of the delicious irony heaped upon the various ministries in 1984, while the Spanish government is trying to use it to introduce new laws that brings …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Since when was wealth common?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-since-when-was-wealth-common/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 16:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-since-when-was-wealth-common/</guid>
        <description>What could possibly link Angelina Jolie and the first female President of Sri Lanka, Chandrika Bandaranaike Kumaratunga? Why William Hague and last week’s Commonwealth summit, of course! There has been a bizarre image occasionally popping up over the past few months, of a rather smitten MP standing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Grub first, then ethics”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-grub-first-then-ethics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 02:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-grub-first-then-ethics/</guid>
        <description>Somewhere in the imposing tome, Less than Nothing, author Slavoj Žižek relates an anecdote about the attitudes taken by Bertolt Brecht and Dashiell Hammett in their respective McCarthy-inspired HUAC trials. Brecht tells the factual truth but phrases answers in such a way to suggest that he is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Atheism and the Irony of Religion
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-atheism-and-the-irony-of-religion/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 09:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-atheism-and-the-irony-of-religion/</guid>
        <description>Irony has always been, well, ironic. Take for example Aristophanes, great ancient Greek satirist of whom Nietzsche said ‘that transfiguring, complementary genius, for whose sake one pardons all of Hellenism for having existed’, and his play The Clouds. In a famous scene Socrates muses on the origins …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Royalties from the Royalty
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-royalties-from-the-royalty/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 10:46:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-royalties-from-the-royalty/</guid>
        <description>The British Monarchy as an institution is, we can all agree, quintessentially British. Defined by political impotence with a history of starting needless wars to satisfy stupid demands. A historical anachronism allowed to be a part of the elite out of politeness, with the mind to its occasional …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kelly-vison: Reflections on Journalism
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-kelly-vison-reflections-on-journalism/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 00:09:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-kelly-vison-reflections-on-journalism/</guid>
        <description>A condition for open press is respect for journalist protection. The film adaptation of the murder of the Balibo Five in East Timor suggests that the death of journalists is a sufficiently sparse phenomenon to warrant attention. The fact that I remember the 2006 murder of Anna Politkovskaya …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kelly-vison: How Noble are the Nobel Prizes?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-kelly-vison-how-noble-are-the-nobel-prizes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 00:08:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-kelly-vison-how-noble-are-the-nobel-prizes/</guid>
        <description>With the unsurprising news that Higgs and French physicist Englert were awarded the 2013 Nobel Prize in Physics, I feel that I can indulge in cross-subject chauvinism. No other prizewinner this year will be given for something of such profound importance. The most important Chemistry prize was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ralph Miliband: A Benefactor of Slander
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-18-ralph-miliband-a-benefactor-of-slander/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 21:29:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Kelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-18-ralph-miliband-a-benefactor-of-slander/</guid>
        <description>The recent Daily Mail ‘essay’ (to use Daily Mail sketch writer Quentin Letts’ wonderful euphemism) on Professor Ralph Miliband has demonstrated once more, in no uncertain terms, the vicious and quite frankly lunatic nature of some elements of the British Press. They have, quite rightly, come under …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
