<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sg4812/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sg4812/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Massive, Small Change
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-massive-small-change/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 20:58:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marcus S Bishop,Shiladitya Ghosh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-massive-small-change/</guid>
        <description>Many people in our world face severe challenges just to live and get by each day, though we may not see them around in our privileged lives as students at university. Engineers Without Borders UK is a charitable organisation that believes access to engineering and technical know-how can help …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Opening into the PG Open Day
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-an-opening-into-the-pg-open-day/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 03:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shiladitya Ghosh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-an-opening-into-the-pg-open-day/</guid>
        <description>One cold Wednesday afternoon earlier this week, your fantastic Features editor deigned to trespass and snoop around formally check out and report the annual Postgraduate Open Day happening at the South Kensington Campus. It was much less of a hassle than expected, as I had turned up with Joe Letts’ …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Business, Policy, and Economics for the Future: A Sustainable Approach
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-business-policy-and-economics-for-the-future-a-sustainable-approach/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 03:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shiladitya Ghosh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-business-policy-and-economics-for-the-future-a-sustainable-approach/</guid>
        <description>A fortnight ago you read about the IPCC report’s finger-pointing, 7 days later you glanced over the future of energy sourcing…now we will have you contemplate sustainable strategies for business, policy, and the general economics of the future! What exactly does sustainability mean? Simply put, a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Energy Problem: Which Way Forward?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-the-energy-problem-which-way-forward/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 09:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shiladitya Ghosh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-the-energy-problem-which-way-forward/</guid>
        <description>With David Cameron recently officially backing the development of a new nuclear power station in Britain for the first time in our generation, the UK looks to be more comfortable than not with accepting the presence of nuclear energy production operations, even as the discovery of healthy shale gas …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IPCC Climate Report 2013: An Ultimate Warning?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-24-ipcc-climate-report-2013-an-ultimate-warning/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 23:47:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shiladitya Ghosh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-24-ipcc-climate-report-2013-an-ultimate-warning/</guid>
        <description>The Intergovernmental Panel for Climate Change (IPCC) released merely one part of its six-yearly report last month, and alarm bells have begun ringing across the world: apparently, it is 95% certain humans have been the largest contributing factor to global warming since the 1950’s. A general …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>University Rankings and what to (not) make of them
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-27-university-rankings-and-what-to-not-make-of-them/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2013 23:40:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shiladitya Ghosh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-27-university-rankings-and-what-to-not-make-of-them/</guid>
        <description>No matter who you are or where you come from, you are, to some extent, proud of this esteemed institution’s very high rankings on various scales and from a variety of scorers around the world. It helps that the QS League Tables just got updated earlier this month to show Imperial rising to its …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Study Habits: A Definitive Guide
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-27-study-habits-a-definitive-guide/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2013 17:05:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shiladitya Ghosh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-27-study-habits-a-definitive-guide/</guid>
        <description>You’re freshmen now. No more school for you – all grown up! (Yeah, right. Still a teenager, aren’t you?) Ever since you got your school-leaving grades and (congratulations!) your Unconditionals, all everyone’s been talking to you about is how to prepare for the “big jump” from school to University: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Turning the heat back on?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-turning-the-heat-back-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2013 01:49:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shiladitya Ghosh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-turning-the-heat-back-on/</guid>
        <description>A researcher at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) has, through his self-devised technique, managed to successfully exercise control over heat the same way we enjoy control over light through mirrors and lenses (most disappointingly falling short of developing a giant heat ray, for the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
