<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/et1214/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/et1214/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The American Dream | Prints exposing US consumerism
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-the-american-dream-prints-exposing-us-consumerism/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 17:09:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elizaveta Tchebaniouk,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-the-american-dream-prints-exposing-us-consumerism/</guid>
        <description>The UK’s first major exhibition of modern and contemporary American printmaking, that has recently opened at the British Museum, spans twelve rooms and six decades. The American Dream: pop to the present is as ambitious as it is controversial, with critics questioning not only pop art’s artistic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Triumph of the American Rebels
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-10-triumph-of-the-american-rebels/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 14:57:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Elizaveta Tchebaniouk,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-10-triumph-of-the-american-rebels/</guid>
        <description>Abstract expressionism is a liberation. The art form’s leading American artists of the 1940’s and 50’s emphasized on spontaneous creative acts to express subjective emotion in opposition to the confining rules of realism. Though exhibited and referred as a collective for revolutionizing the art …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>But first, let me take a selfie
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-15-but-first-let-me-take-a-selfie/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 18:08:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elizaveta Tchebaniouk,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-15-but-first-let-me-take-a-selfie/</guid>
        <description>Does the appeal and purpose of performance art lie partially in its ephemeral nature? Or can photography be integral to preserving the performance for contemplation, and even to creating a new meaning in the work? It is the latter that Tate Modern’s exhibition Performing for the Camera explores by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Delacroix inspired 20th century art
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-how-delacroix-inspired-20th-century-art/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 11:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elizaveta Tchebaniouk,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-how-delacroix-inspired-20th-century-art/</guid>
        <description>Most would not expect the last painter of the grand style to be one of the first modern artists, and so it is quite daring and unique for an exhibition to make such a statement. Delacroix and the Rise of Modern Art sheds light on Delacroix’s overlooked role as being an early modern revolutionary in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>More than just a century of style
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-more-than-just-a-century-of-style/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 12:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elizaveta Tchebaniouk,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-more-than-just-a-century-of-style/</guid>
        <description>One enters the exhibition through a room with pillars that are kaleidoscopes of British Vogue magazine covers throughout the years, and is instantly transported to a magical world. The films at the end of the entrance corridor act to further set the scene and create that fantasy atmosphere which …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Guy Bourdin’s Glamour: Sinister, Surreal &amp; Sexual
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-guy-bourdins-glamour-sinister-surreal-sexual/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 20:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elizaveta Tchebaniouk,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-guy-bourdins-glamour-sinister-surreal-sexual/</guid>
        <description>Somerset House unveiled the UK’s largest ever exhibition of Guy Bourdin’s work, which spans the 40 year career of the French photographer, and features not only his most iconic photographs, but also never before seen material including Polaroid test shots, double-page spread layouts, contact sheets, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I’m Depressed. Let’s Sing About It.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-im-depressed-lets-sing-about-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 21:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elizaveta Tchebaniouk,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-im-depressed-lets-sing-about-it/</guid>
        <description>Why am I depressed? What is the cause of my depression?” aren’t exactly questions easily remedied by ringing up NHS Direct and asking. This opera, though, strives to find answers.
This contemporary opera takes inspiration from Robert Burton’s 1621 textbook The Anatomy of Melancholy, which was the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Voyeur at the Courtauld: Schiele’s Radical Nude Impresses
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-voyeur-at-the-courtauld-schieles-radical-nude-impresses/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 21:49:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elizaveta Tchebaniouk,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-voyeur-at-the-courtauld-schieles-radical-nude-impresses/</guid>
        <description>A mention of sex in any context, really, is usually enough to get people excited (pun intended). After all, to quote Oscar Wilde: “Everything in the world is about sex, except sex. Sex is about power”.
It is clear to spectators of The Radical Nude – the first solo exhibit of Egon Schiele’s nudes in …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
