<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/lh106/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/lh106/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Cheeky Charming Close Harmony Cabaret
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-6-11-cheeky-charming-close-harmony-cabaret/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 11:04:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Harrold,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-6-11-cheeky-charming-close-harmony-cabaret/</guid>
        <description>How did you meet and where did the name Three Little Maids come from?
Alex: I met Kate at Kings College where we both studied music, I went up to her on the first day and said “I think you’re really pretty” in her specs and floral shirt, Kate replied “Ok…my names Kate” and we went from there.
Jen: I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let The Sunshine...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-3-17-let-the-sunshine/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 16:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Harrold,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-3-17-let-the-sunshine/</guid>
        <description>A Tribal-Love-Rock musical. It is perfectly fitting then that ICU’s Musical Theatre Society chose Hair as their spring term 2010 production – a musical written by young people, for young people. Daring, absurd, surreal, lewd and crude all at once, Hair is also both fun and deeply political, tracking …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nothing On? Go See Noises Off!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-3-17-nothing-on-go-see-noises-off/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 16:04:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Harrold,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-3-17-nothing-on-go-see-noises-off/</guid>
        <description>When it comes to a play within a play, Dramsoc’s latest production takes full advantage of the confusion. Although I set out with the noble aim of relating to you the witty intricacies of the plot of Noises Off, at the time I was too busy wiping away tears of laughter to work out exactly what was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Soza Boy By Ken Saro-Wiwa
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-18-soza-boy-by-ken-saro-wiwa/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2010 16:53:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Harrold,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-18-soza-boy-by-ken-saro-wiwa/</guid>
        <description>This is not what you would call a normal book review, but that’s just because Sozaboy is not a normal book. It is not one of those novels that after you have finished reading you’ll put back on the shelf. No, when you will be done reading Sozaboy you will give to everyone you know. This is how I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jerusalem- Perfection In The West End?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-18-jerusalem-perfection-in-the-west-end/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2010 16:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Harrold,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-18-jerusalem-perfection-in-the-west-end/</guid>
        <description>The Royal Court Theatre production of Jerusalem is named after William Blake’s iconic poem of the same name. A favourite hymn to many, Jerusalem reveres the majesty of bucolic England – a countryside so beautiful that Christ himself must surely have been born here. It is with a sense of irony then …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Broadway Royalty Coming Through
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-18-broadway-royalty-coming-through/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2010 16:43:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Harrold,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-18-broadway-royalty-coming-through/</guid>
        <description>How did your concert at the New Player’s Theatre come about? How do you find the intimate concert atmosphere in comparison to being on a huge stage?
I performed in London late last year with Scott Alan. Simon Greiff produced Scott&amp;rsquo;s concert(s) and it was beautifully presented, with a lot of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Omigod You Guys, like a New Musical!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-omigod-you-guys-like-a-new-musical/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 18:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucy Harrold,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-omigod-you-guys-like-a-new-musical/</guid>
        <description>You know how it is, you wait all term for a new musical to open and finally one does. Two days before my exam. See what I sacrifice for you dear reader; who am I kidding? I needed a break and Legally Blonde the Musical was the perfect excuse.
The Savoy theatre places host to the show and is possibly …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
