<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ss11814/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ss11814/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>It ain’t easy being green
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-it-aint-easy-being-green/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 16:24:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sam Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-it-aint-easy-being-green/</guid>
        <description>Have you ever said to yourself “I love basketball, football and rugby with a passion but it would be a dream to play them all at once” ? Well then I have just the thing for you. A sport for those who fancy carrying the ball like rugby, but prefer a rounder shape. For those who fancy bouncing it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Because playing hockey on land is so last year
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-because-playing-hockey-on-land-is-so-last-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 16:20:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sam Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-because-playing-hockey-on-land-is-so-last-year/</guid>
        <description>I have two minor claims to fame: my brother featured in a Gocompare advert alongside Stuart Pearce and I learnt to swim in the same pool as Anthony Head’s children. Pretty impressive right? No, I know, but it means I have always seen swimming as an epic, almost vampire-slaying-esque activity. And …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Time to become Immortal
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-time-to-become-immortal/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sam Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-time-to-become-immortal/</guid>
        <description>Apparently one of the most hotly anticipated games of the NFL season happened a couple of days ago. Did you know? I certainly didn’t, but it was played between two giants of the game to decide who would progress for a chance at the Super Bowl. No, not a huge piece of crockery for mammoth breakfast …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Interview | David Henson MBE
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-interview-david-henson-mbe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 16:40:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sam Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-interview-david-henson-mbe/</guid>
        <description>I struggle to get out of bed some mornings. OK, most mornings. OK, OK, I’m still in bed watching Jeremy Kyle yell at someone for having 3 wives and 1 kid whom they all swear is theirs, but we’ve gone off topic. Seeing as this is ‘disability week’ I figured I should talk to someone who knows enough …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stick them with the pointy end
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-stick-them-with-the-pointy-end/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 14:59:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sam Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-stick-them-with-the-pointy-end/</guid>
        <description>Yes it’s a Game of Thrones reference, I need something to fill the void until the next season. But even that isn’t enough, so it got me thinking. Maybe I should try this swordplay thing? And where better than IC’s Fencing team? You will have read about their continued success in previous editions …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial girls can, always have been and will continue to
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-imperial-girls-can-always-have-been-and-will-continue-to/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 18:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sam Smith,Sam Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-imperial-girls-can-always-have-been-and-will-continue-to/</guid>
        <description>I have now been married for three wonderful months, and even though I may be the man of the house I can happily say my wife has a more proficient history in sport than I. Do note the lack of shame. I have no beef with such a statement. I am proud to talk about her previous achievements and will …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kabaddi! Kabaddi! Kabaddi!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-7-kabaddi-kabaddi-kabaddi/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 13:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Sam Smith,Sam Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-7-kabaddi-kabaddi-kabaddi/</guid>
        <description>Right, now I’ve got your attention, listen up. I’m the new Sport editor, I love playing sports, I love writing about sports, and right now I’m writing about one sport most of you probably haven’t heard of (including myself until a week ago). Apologies in advance for those expecting a heroic sports …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
