<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jm5014/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jm5014/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Three years after my roommate’s death I’m ready to move on
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-three-years-after-my-roommates-death-im-ready-to-move-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:56:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonathan Masters,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-three-years-after-my-roommates-death-im-ready-to-move-on/</guid>
        <description>A few weeks ago I finally came to the end of my three year course at Imperial, and although it is a cliché, the time has simply flown by. As I handed in the final final final draft of my undergraduate dissertation into turnitin, I suddenly burst into tears. Now it could have been a combination of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Raisins are a complete scam
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-raisins-are-a-complete-scam/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 16:57:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonathan Masters,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-raisins-are-a-complete-scam/</guid>
        <description>Raisins – also known as dried grapes – represent everything wrong with our civilisation and they seek to disrupt the foundations upon which this very nation stands, and this ingrate, Mr Ma, has the audacity to suggest that we need more raisins in Imperial in order to make his breakfast better. It …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>There will never be another Camelot
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-there-will-never-be-another-camelot/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 16:44:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonathan Masters,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-there-will-never-be-another-camelot/</guid>
        <description>The first feeling I had when viewing the trailer for Jackie was a familiar weariness: here was a story that sounded interesting, but was to be packaged in a three-hour-long portentous montage of shots of Natalie Portman looking sad out of windows. What I am happy to report, however, is that Jackie – …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Eurovision: make an effort
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-eurovision-make-an-effort/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 16:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonathan Masters,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-eurovision-make-an-effort/</guid>
        <description>You can listen to as much Jamie XX as you like, you can watch black and white films with French subtitles, but there is not a single person on this earth who when viewing the Eurovision song contest doesn’t enjoy the sheer ridiculousness of it. Every year, each one of us remembers that Azerbaijan is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sweat over something more important
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-sweat-over-something-more-important/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 08:41:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonathan Masters,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-sweat-over-something-more-important/</guid>
        <description>This quote struck me last week: “air conditioning must be the top priority for sabbaticals”. This is possibly one of the stupidest, most ignorant statements ever committed to this paper. Everybody knows that the library is hot from floors three upwards, and as a result a petition has been signed by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Son of Saul stares into the abyss
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-son-of-saul-stares-into-the-abyss/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 10:11:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonathan Masters,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-son-of-saul-stares-into-the-abyss/</guid>
        <description>Although admirable is an adjective too-often used to describe films whose artistic vision falls short of the final product, there is no word that I can think of more suited to describe Hungarian Holocaust drama Son of Saul. In most Holocaust dramas, the cinematic narrative is structured in order to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We need to talk about Israel
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-we-need-to-talk-about-israel/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 09:50:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonathan Masters,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-we-need-to-talk-about-israel/</guid>
        <description>It’s like that old saying goes, ‘you wait for one anti-semitism scandal, and then three come along at once’. First was the election of Malia Bouattia as NUS president, whose labelling of Birmingham as a Zionist outpost was quite problematic, then came the four-year-old posts of MP Naz Shah saying …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Changing your profile picture won’t help
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-19-changing-your-profile-picture-wont-help/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2015 22:40:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonathan Masters,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-19-changing-your-profile-picture-wont-help/</guid>
        <description>When ‘Le Tricolour’ was first adopted by the Nation of France in 1794, the three colours were meant to represent the Royalty (the white portion), with the red and blue representing the arms of the city. Their representations of the three colours then changed with the coming of the French revolution …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Labour HQ moving to High Street Kensington
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-labour-hq-moving-to-high-street-kensington/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 14:23:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonathan Masters,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-labour-hq-moving-to-high-street-kensington/</guid>
        <description>In the most exciting development in High Street Kensington since the Odeon was shut down, this week it was announced that the Labour headquarters would be uprooting from its current offices in Westminster and relocating to within walking distance of Imperial College London.
This comes as a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Goldsmiths Diversity Officer in Race Row
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-21-goldsmiths-diversity-officer-in-race-row/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2015 20:06:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonathan Masters,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-21-goldsmiths-diversity-officer-in-race-row/</guid>
        <description>A petition has been launched to remove Bahara Mustafa, the current Diversity officer for Goldsmiths University, from her position following a recent tweet featuring the inflammatory hashtag “Kill all white men”.
This follows a long line of controversies from Ms Mustafa, the first of which saw her …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jo Johnson announced as Minister of Universities and Science
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-jo-johnson-announced-as-minister-of-universities-and-science/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 12:34:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonathan Masters,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-jo-johnson-announced-as-minister-of-universities-and-science/</guid>
        <description>Jo Johnson, newly elected MP for Orpington in the London Borough of Bromley, has succeeded Greg Clark (a former economist) as Minister of State for Universities and Science.
Questions have been raised about his credibility for the role considering he has no formal science education, whilst others …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Documentary TV: The Theroux Effect
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-documentary-tv-the-theroux-effect/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 12:28:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonathan Masters,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-documentary-tv-the-theroux-effect/</guid>
        <description>Those of you that have a TV Licence, or have had a look at BBC IPlayer recently (much more likely), will have seen that Louis Theroux – the mild mannered, inherently awkward, bespectacled documentarian – has a new series, of which three episodes have already been broadcast early, due to the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Do you want a firetruck with your beer?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-1-do-you-want-a-firetruck-with-your-beer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:34:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonathan Masters,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-1-do-you-want-a-firetruck-with-your-beer/</guid>
        <description>Craft beer has seen an exponential increase in popularity in the last four years, and with that increased demand have come entrepreneurs seeking to profit.
However, some of those capitalising on the trend were more likely to be found in the lab than down the bar only a few years ago. Imperial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The £40k campaign condemning Lib Dems
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-1-the-40k-campaign-condemning-lib-dems/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:11:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonathan Masters,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-1-the-40k-campaign-condemning-lib-dems/</guid>
        <description>If you paid attention to your news feed in the last week, the likelihood is that the story of the National Union of Students (NUS) spending £40,000 on a campaign against the Liberal Democrats has come across your radar.
The most iconic of the posters displays two clenched fists, with the words ‘liar …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>From Ex Machina to Blade Runner
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-20-from-ex-machina-to-blade-runner/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 16:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonathan Masters,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-20-from-ex-machina-to-blade-runner/</guid>
        <description>Ex Machina was released at the end of January, a film I would recommend to many people. Written and directed by regular Danny Boyle collaborator Alex Garland, it explores the concept of the definition of humanity through the paradigm of artificial intelligence where the plot sets in motion a Turing …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
