<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ts2915/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ts2915/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>LFF: Manchester by the Sea
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-5-lff-manchester-by-the-sea/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 20:37:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Stephens,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-5-lff-manchester-by-the-sea/</guid>
        <description>If you were to rely on the list of previous winners of the Best Actor Oscar as a definitive list of cinema history’s greatest performances, you would probably have one clear go-to when thinking of acting techniques for a sure-fire win (apart from being white): shouting. It has seemed throughout the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LFF: La La Land
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-5-lff-la-la-land/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 20:30:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Stephens,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-5-lff-la-la-land/</guid>
        <description>It turns out Ryan Gosling is as roguishly charming and wonderful in person as we all hoped he would be. I was lucky enough to see La La Land for the first time at a London Film Festival screening, after which he appeared to a hurricane of cheers and thrown roses/knickers for a Q&amp;amp;A. When asked …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A dark descent into artistic depths
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-a-dark-descent-into-artistic-depths/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 14:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Stephens,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-a-dark-descent-into-artistic-depths/</guid>
        <description>Looking for a startling way to open your movie? A slow-motion montage of obese elderly women dancing, completely naked save for cheerleading pom-poms and marching band hats, ought to do the trick. Nocturnal Animals, the latest feature from fashion-bigwig-turned-film-director Tom Ford, opens with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A beginner’s guide to Denis Villeneuve
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-a-beginners-guide-to-denis-villeneuve/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 14:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Stephens,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-a-beginners-guide-to-denis-villeneuve/</guid>
        <description>Hugh Jackman –was it as scary to work with him in Prisoners as it looked? What the were all the spiders about in Enemy? And how the hell do you pronounce that last name?! There are many questions we’d love to ask Denis Villeneuve, the man who’s gone from abduction drama to existential horror to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Five great true crime films that aren’t Goodfellas
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-10-five-great-true-crime-films-that-arent-goodfellas/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 12:46:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Tom Stephens,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-10-five-great-true-crime-films-that-arent-goodfellas/</guid>
        <description> Let’s get one thing out of the way: Goodfellas is an incredible film. Based almost to the letter on the autobiography of wiseguy gangster Henry Hill, it’s got a very strong claim to be the all-time best of its director Martin Scorsese’s. If you haven’t seen it already, it’s on Netflix - I’d advise …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LFF – A marriage of reason and nightmare
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-9-5-lff-a-marriage-of-reason-and-nightmare/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 20:40:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Stephens,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-9-5-lff-a-marriage-of-reason-and-nightmare/</guid>
        <description>High-Rise is the kind of film throughout the majority of which you don’t know whether to laugh or cry. Most dystopian films can be tough to stomach at the best of times – surely half the point of cinema is to escape into a world that’s not quite as screwed up as this one is? – but there are those …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LFF – Black Mass is a competent film, but nothing more
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-9-5-lff-black-mass-is-a-competent-film-but-nothing-more/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 20:35:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Stephens,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-9-5-lff-black-mass-is-a-competent-film-but-nothing-more/</guid>
        <description>There&amp;rsquo;s an episode of David Mitchell&amp;rsquo;s brilliant YouTube series Soapbox in which he talks about the problem with gangster movies: one great film about gangsters gets made in the seventies, he argues, and suddenly everyone thinks they can make three hour long dirges filled with smoky …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>X
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-x/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 11:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Stephens,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-x/</guid>
        <description>Test
</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICU MTSoc Presents Sweeney Todd
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-icu-mtsoc-presents-sweeney-todd/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 12:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Stephens,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-icu-mtsoc-presents-sweeney-todd/</guid>
        <description>Isuppose you can never really tell which of your friends would make the most convincing serial killer. When auditions were running for MTSoc’s production of Sweeney Todd back in December, the titular role of the murderous barber was hotly contested with auditionees flocking in from as far afield as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All’s fair in love and finance
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-alls-fair-in-love-and-finance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 09:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Stephens,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-alls-fair-in-love-and-finance/</guid>
        <description>There are many ways a movie can go about breaking the fourth wall: direct communication with the audience can come in the form of subtle wink-wink moments of dialogue, such as _Kingsman: The Secret Service_’s conversations about classic spy films; the perfectly-timed stare at the camera that Eddie …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A transgender revenge dramedy? It&#39;s a Christmas miracle!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-a-transgender-revenge-dramedy-its-a-christmas-miracle/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 14:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Stephens,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-a-transgender-revenge-dramedy-its-a-christmas-miracle/</guid>
        <description>Transgender revenge dramedies are somewhat hard to come by in a cinema. In fact I’m not sure many of them exist at all. If you need to bump up your street cred, then, Tangerine will definitely be the edgiest film you’ll see this month, perhaps this year. Fortunately it’s got enough substance in it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Danny Boyle does the Job
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-danny-boyle-does-the-job/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 09:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Stephens,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-danny-boyle-does-the-job/</guid>
        <description>It was a bit of a shock when Ashton Kutcher was picked to star as the Apple-founding billionaire in 2013’s biopic Jobs; he’s not the most likely actor I would have picked for a historical breaking of typecasting, but a role as one of the most iconic and influential men of the modern technological …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
