<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ann09/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ann09/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Being informed and the Right to Know
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-being-informed-and-the-right-to-know/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 19:37:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-being-informed-and-the-right-to-know/</guid>
        <description>However different American healthcare is from British healthcare, it wouldn’t be unreasonable to assume that the principles of consent are similar. One such principle is that valid consent needs to be informed; one must be aware of the implications of a decision to have a procedure, the benefits, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Croquet Club dormancy debated
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-4-croquet-club-dormancy-debated/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2012 00:47:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-4-croquet-club-dormancy-debated/</guid>
        <description>A Clubs and Societies Board (CSB) meeting on 27 February 2012 resulted in a decision to close the dormant Croquet Club along with 6 other clubs. According to Deputy President of Clubs and Societies (DPCS) Monya Zard’s “Clubs to Close” paper, the decision was on the grounds that the club had less …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President and Provost roles introduced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-4-president-and-provost-roles-introduced/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2012 00:29:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-4-president-and-provost-roles-introduced/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College is to have a Provost. Where once there was a Rector there will be two positions, a “President &amp;amp; Rector” and a “Provost of the College”. What is a Provost, one wonders. By definition, a provost is the head of a college. What, then, is a rector?
Following a decision by Imperial’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wilson review could lead to rehousing
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-wilson-review-could-lead-to-rehousing/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 22:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-wilson-review-could-lead-to-rehousing/</guid>
        <description>There is uncertainty about the future of halls of residence, Wilson House, this week as it is scrutinized for feasibility. Due in the coming weeks, the report of an on-going feasibility study will help determine if and when Wilson House will be closed for refurbishment, potentially during the next …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fewer students apply to university
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-fewer-students-apply-to-university/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 23:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-fewer-students-apply-to-university/</guid>
        <description>There has been a fall in university applications for 2012 entry, Universities and Colleges Admissions Service (UCAS) statistics have revealed. Referred to as a “headline drop of 7.4% in applicants” by UCAS Chief Executive Mary Curnock Cook, the newly published data includes all applications that met …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Medicine Faculty Principal appointed
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-new-medicine-faculty-principal-appointed/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 22:38:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-new-medicine-faculty-principal-appointed/</guid>
        <description>Professor Dermot Kelleher has been appointed Principal of the Faculty of Medicine. The Vice-Provost for Medical Affairs and Head of the School of Medicine at Trinity College Dublin since 2006, Professor Kelleher is to take up the role on October 1 2012.
Following Professor Sir Anthony Newman Taylor, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Academics criticise White Paper
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-academics-criticise-white-paper/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 20:12:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-academics-criticise-white-paper/</guid>
        <description>In a letter to The Daily Telegraph this week, academics, including professors from Imperial College London, Oxford and Cambridge, criticised government White Paper proposals for higher education reform, specifically the idea of universities being run by private companies, i.e. for profit. They warn …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Blast Injury Centre set up at Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-blast-injury-centre-set-up-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 20:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-blast-injury-centre-set-up-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>A new £8m Royal British Legion Centre for Blast Injury Studies at Imperial College has officially opened this week. The Centre aims to provide a better understanding of the injuries caused by roadside bombs, or Improvised Explosive Devices (IEDs). These are the leading cause of death and injury for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College to tackle feedback
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-college-to-tackle-feedback/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 19:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-college-to-tackle-feedback/</guid>
        <description>The issue of assessment and feedback at Imperial has been addressed at this year’s Rector’s Away Day.
The Rector’s Away Day, which this year took place on October 21, is an annual meeting of senior Imperial staff. The focus of this year’s event was the ‘student experience’ and how it can be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>University applications fall by 9%
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-university-applications-fall-by-9/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 19:58:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,Alexandra Nowbar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-university-applications-fall-by-9/</guid>
        <description>After years of steady increases, university applications are currently 9% lower than last year’s level at this time with 7000 fewer applications so far. Although the deadline for most courses is January, these figures from UCAS (University and College Admissions Service) are the first official …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Could the American university system work here?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-could-the-american-university-system-work-here/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 22:59:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-could-the-american-university-system-work-here/</guid>
        <description>Yes - Alexander Karapetian
We shouldn’t be so quick to react negatively towards the recent intention to change towards the American style system of having a Grade Point Average (GPA) by UCL. Students under the UK classification system are often under great pressures to attain a degree with 2:1 or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fire engine Jezebel clocks up 50,000 miles
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-fire-engine-jezebel-clocks-up-50000-miles/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 21:01:24 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-fire-engine-jezebel-clocks-up-50000-miles/</guid>
        <description>Jezebel, fire engine and mascot of the Royal College of Science Union, has now reached 50,000 miles on the clock.
Jezebel is a 1916 Dennis N type fire engine with a 1926 pump. The Royal College of Science Motor Club (RCS Motor Club), consisting of past and current students, have been undertaking …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix nominated for Guardian Student Media Awards
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-6-felix-nominated-for-guardian-student-media-awards/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 23:08:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-6-felix-nominated-for-guardian-student-media-awards/</guid>
        <description>Felix has been shortlisted for Student Publication of the Year in the Guardian Student Media Awards 2011. The other finalists in this category are Cherwell (University of Oxford), Mouth (Kingston University), River (Kingston University) and York Vision (University of York). In addition, 2 of the 5 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Murrayfail
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-murrayfail/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 20:57:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-murrayfail/</guid>
        <description>Andy Murray may have made his name as a great British and mediocre international tennis player but when it comes to fending off burglars (otherwise known as false alarms) he really ought to leave it to the pros. Kim Sears, his girlfriend, questions Murray’s decision to defend her honour with a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Treasury finally appoints Chief Scientific Advisor
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-treasury-finally-appoints-chief-scientific-advisor/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 19:11:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-treasury-finally-appoints-chief-scientific-advisor/</guid>
        <description>A Chief Scientific Advisor (CSA) has finally been appointed to the Treasury, previously the only remaining government department without a CSA. The position is being filled by James Richardson, who will retain his role as the Treasury’s director of public spending. CaSE director, Imran Khan, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dyson provides money for Imperial engineering scholarships
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-dyson-provides-money-for-imperial-engineering-scholarships/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 19:10:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-dyson-provides-money-for-imperial-engineering-scholarships/</guid>
        <description>The James Dyson Foundation has set up a £1 million scholarship scheme for postgraduate design and engineering students. The Dyson vacuum cleaner creator said that engineering needed to be promoted to help the UK’s economic recovery.The donation will be used to fund four postgraduate bursaries of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union unveil ambitious future for Summer Ball
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-union-unveil-ambitious-future-for-summer-ball/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 21:26:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-union-unveil-ambitious-future-for-summer-ball/</guid>
        <description>The Union have unveiled ambitious plans to “increase the size, scale and profile” of the Summer Ball in years to come, saying that the “ultimate aim” would be to host the event “in Hyde Park or a similar venue” and attract a huge number of students from across London. The news comes with just a week …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Police warn about bicycle thefts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-police-warn-about-bicycle-thefts/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 20:46:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-police-warn-about-bicycle-thefts/</guid>
        <description>The police are investigating a recent series of bicycle thefts from the bike shed, including one student who placed a lock around the front wheel and thus lost the whole bike, apart from the front wheel. The suspect, caught on CCTV, tends to wait for a user to let him in, as a card is required for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Medics’ union faces £40,000 funding cut
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-medics-union-faces-40000-funding-cut/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 19:20:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-medics-union-faces-40000-funding-cut/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College School of Medicine Students’ Union (ICSMSU) is facing a £40,000 cut to its funding, as Imperial College Healthcare Charity withdraws its support over the next 5 years, with a 20% reduction each year. This will be especially detrimental to the electives fund and ICSM Gazette. ICSMSU …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The naked truth...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-the-naked-truth/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 20:59:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-the-naked-truth/</guid>
        <description>Ah, The Full Monty. No, I’m not talking about today’s centerfold (It seems so long since we had one!), but the movie, which was on TV on Monday night. Gritty Northern themes, like unemployment and Sheffield, spruced up with humour – this usually makes for a solid film.
It opens with a brilliantly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial behind UCL in student experience survey
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-imperial-behind-ucl-in-student-experience-survey/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 21:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-imperial-behind-ucl-in-student-experience-survey/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College has been ranked 62nd in the 2010 Times Higher Education Student Experience Survey (down one place from 2009 and one place below UCL). Over 13,000 undergraduates throughout the country rated aspects of university life out of 7, including academic and sports facilities, quality of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is social networking ruining our lives?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-is-social-networking-ruining-our-lives/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 19:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-is-social-networking-ruining-our-lives/</guid>
        <description>Ben Good– No
December 23, 2006 at 20:41, “Ben has joined Facebook”. It was a simple page, no friends, no photos and a fake birth date to get around the age restrictions. If you had told me then that this, and other social networking sites, would be the cornerstone of social interaction for our …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Year, same old you...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-new-year-same-old-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 21:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-new-year-same-old-you/</guid>
        <description>Self-improvement can and should be done at any time. Needing an arbitrary start date for the “new you” is pretty pathetic since you were more than aware of your flaws already, weren’t you? That bit of flab is nothing new even if you christen it “Christmas excess”. New Year’s resolutions conveniently …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The nativity: from a ladies point of view
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-the-nativity-from-a-ladies-point-of-view/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 21:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-the-nativity-from-a-ladies-point-of-view/</guid>
        <description>Male chauvinists have assured me that it is my job to care about domestics. But to show that I am not merely using this as an excuse to slack off work and am taking my responsibilities as a female seriously, I want to tell you about my role model, Baboushka (aka Babs in my book). One could think of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All this Royal Wedding tosh has got me reminiscing...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-all-this-royal-wedding-tosh-has-got-me-reminiscing/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2010 22:02:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-all-this-royal-wedding-tosh-has-got-me-reminiscing/</guid>
        <description>Very fleetingly, at the age of nine I had a special interest in marrying Prince Harry. I chose Harry over William believing us to be better suited if we were closer in age (6 years rather than 8). I then proceeded to foster sincere hopes of such a relationship in the future. My ideas of the wedding …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
