<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/julia_dabrowska/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/julia_dabrowska/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>70 Years of STEM Nobel Prizes &amp; Fields Medals</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-70-years-STEM-nobel-prizes-fields-medals/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Julia Dabrowska,Christine Parry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-70-years-STEM-nobel-prizes-fields-medals/</guid>
        <description>Below are 70 years worth of noteworthy awards in maths and science - but first, in recognition of our affiliated Imperial scientists, here’s a summary of our awardees &amp;amp; what they achieved:
1956: Cyril Norman Hinshelwood; Chemistry; for his research into the mechanism of chemical reactions
1958: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Seven Decades of Discovery</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-seven-decades-of-discovery/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Julia Dabrowska,Christine Parry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-seven-decades-of-discovery/</guid>
        <description>1949
Felix is launched, spawned from the University’s arts and culture magazine, Phoenix, after a need for news amongst the student community.
1950s
After WWII, the scientific community realised the full potential of its possibility and power, and feels an increased need to understand the social …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>From the Lab to your Plate – the Science Behind Five Intriguing Foods</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-lab-to-plate-science-behind-five-intriguing-foods/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Julia Dabrowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-lab-to-plate-science-behind-five-intriguing-foods/</guid>
        <description>Most foods are simple - some ingredients grow on trees, bushes or in fields, others are taken from animals, and depending on their nutritional value, undergo some level of processing. But with the modern era comes change, and as science is increasingly being installed in the kitchen (food science is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Shaken, not stirred” - Cocktails 101: A Guide for Dummies</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07--shaken-not-stirred-cocktails-101-a-guide-for-dummies/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Julia Dabrowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07--shaken-not-stirred-cocktails-101-a-guide-for-dummies/</guid>
        <description>Exams are over… at least for the majority of us, and what better way to celebrate (or grieve if you’ve still got some coming) than with some tasty ethanol-containing beverages? Thankfully, summer means a chance to venture out of your comfort zone and try something more unique than your typical Union …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Cookie Dough: everything you never knew you needed in your life!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-my-cookie-dough-everything-you-never-knew-you-needed-in-your-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,Julia Dabrowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-my-cookie-dough-everything-you-never-knew-you-needed-in-your-life/</guid>
        <description>After reviewing Naked Dough last month, when we got the chance to try out another cookie dough place, My Cookie Dough, the excitement was real. Although both serve cookie dough, this place adds a completely different twist onto what we thought we were expecting, replacing raw cookie dough with baked …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Did we just hear someone say brunch? </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-did-we-just-hear-someone-say-brunch/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Julia Dabrowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-did-we-just-hear-someone-say-brunch/</guid>
        <description>What comes to mind when you see the word ‘brunch’? Probably a bunch of millennials eating crunchy avocado toast, Insta-worthy smoothie açai bowls or stacks of warm waffles (drizzled with maple syrup and topped with fresh summer berries of course), and all of this costing you lots and lots of £££. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Naked Dough: the good, the bad and the ugly</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-naked-dough-the-good-the-bad-and-the-ugly/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Julia Dabrowska,Eva Tadros,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-naked-dough-the-good-the-bad-and-the-ugly/</guid>
        <description>Remember that cute little stand that sells big tubs filled with mouthwatering cookie dough that we told you about in the “2 Girls, 1 Dessert” article earlier this year? Well, we felt like we just had to go back and satisfy our cravings, so we bring you the ultimate guide to (almost) every single …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tapioca: your favourite bubble tea ingredient  explained!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-tapioca-your-favourite-bubble-tea-ingredient-explained/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Julia Dabrowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-tapioca-your-favourite-bubble-tea-ingredient-explained/</guid>
        <description>You’ve probably encountered, or at least heard of, tapioca at some point in your life (at least if you’ve ever come close to having boba tea or tapioca pudding). A chewy masterpiece, sometimes simply referred to as ‘pearls’, tapioca is in fact a starch extracted from the cassava root, a plant …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Can I Get Uhhh..” - Your 101 Guide to All Things Caffeine</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19--can-i-get-uhhh-your-101-guide-to-all-things-caffeine/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Julia Dabrowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19--can-i-get-uhhh-your-101-guide-to-all-things-caffeine/</guid>
        <description>Imagine this: you, craving caffeine as any typical student, walk into a coffee shop (or, depending on the time of year, stumble into the Library Café). Scanning the menu, you see many options – cappuccinos, espressos, mochas, lattes… why is choosing a coffee so hard when you don’t speak Italian and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Low-fat, reduced fat and fat-free foods: a healthy choice or a myth?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-low-fat-reduced-fat-and-fat-free-foods-a-healthy-choice-or-a-myth/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,Julia Dabrowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-low-fat-reduced-fat-and-fat-free-foods-a-healthy-choice-or-a-myth/</guid>
        <description>Hey, could you please grab a Greek yoghurt when you’re in Tesco? Just make sure it’s the low-fat one - thanks!”
Sound familiar? Nowadays, we’re constantly surrounded by a myriad of fat-free, low-fat and reduced fat products as the food industry’s attempt to maximise profits gains momentum – taking a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2 Girls, 1 Dessert</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-2-girls-1-dessert/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,Julia Dabrowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-2-girls-1-dessert/</guid>
        <description>Watching all those Food Insider videos on Facebook on a mundane afternoon undoubtedly leaves us all drooling, daydreaming about those Instagram-worthy desserts – just think of the food envy your friends will experience when they see a boomerang of that food! So naturally, you tag your friends …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>101 Ways to eat Pasta</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-101-ways-to-eat-pasta/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,Julia Dabrowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-101-ways-to-eat-pasta/</guid>
        <description>So you’ve got through your first week of uni madness - the wild balance of parties, events, and socials with possible introductory lectures or just straight up normal classes. Food this week has probably just been frozen pizza, toast, and of course all the sweets from Freshers’ Fair because who has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Freshers’ 10 under £10</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-20-freshers-10-under-10/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,Julia Dabrowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-20-freshers-10-under-10/</guid>
        <description>Freshers is upon us and you know what that means – time for our bank accounts to hate us. So you keep tapping that contactless on every night out – if you don’t see the money leaving, it’s not really gone, right? If only it worked like that. It can be quite tempting to splash out during freshers and …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
