<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/divyenvanniasega/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/divyenvanniasega/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Mayhem in the Commons</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-mayhem-in-the-commons/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-mayhem-in-the-commons/</guid>
        <description>After significant pressure, Theresa May agreed to a series of votes this week to test the opinion of the House of Commons on Brexit. On Tuesday she put her deal to another vote after getting further minor concessions from the EU and still lost by 149 votes. This was a humiliating defeat. After …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What to do with a man like Neeson?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-what-to-do-with-a-man-like-neeson/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-what-to-do-with-a-man-like-neeson/</guid>
        <description>Liam Neeson, whilst promoting his latest film, described a story of how a friend of his had been raped by a black man and how, following this, he wanted to kill a black man to avenge his friend. This is undeniably racist; he saw black men as indistinguishable and, therefore, killing any black man …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Female Genital Mutilation: A Hidden Crisis</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-female-genital-mutilation-a-hidden-crisis/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-female-genital-mutilation-a-hidden-crisis/</guid>
        <description>Despite increased legal protections, FGM is still a significant issue that affects thousands of women and young girls in the UK.
What is Female Genital Mutilation(FGM)?
The World Health Organisation (WHO) defines Female Genital Mutilation (FGM) as ‘procedures that involve partial or total removal of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>May’s Brexit deal voted down by calamitous margin</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-may-s-brexit-deal-voted-down-by-calamitous-margin/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-may-s-brexit-deal-voted-down-by-calamitous-margin/</guid>
        <description>Theresa May lost the vote on her Withdrawal deal by 230 votes, and she only has herself to blame. This defeat was an inevitable consequence of the incompetent way she has handled Brexit.
Theresa May’s problems are profound and difficult to solve but she gave herself no chance at all by her approach …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sri Lankan Politics is in a sorry state of  Affairs</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-sri-lankan-politics-is-in-a-sorry-state-of-affairs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-sri-lankan-politics-is-in-a-sorry-state-of-affairs/</guid>
        <description>Over the last month there has been significant political turmoil in Sri Lanka which kicked off on the 26th October when the President of Sri Lanka, Sirisena, attempted to sack Wickremesinghe, the Prime Minister. Sirisena has tried to replace him with Rajapaksa, who was the sitting President Sirisena …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to avoid a mess like Brexit: let’s adopt a new voting system</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-how-to-avoid-a-mess-like-brexit-let-s-adopt-a-new-voting-system/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-how-to-avoid-a-mess-like-brexit-let-s-adopt-a-new-voting-system/</guid>
        <description>Since the Brexit referendum we’ve seen Brexit come to dominate British politics. It has been incredibly divisive and has created more problems than it has solved. It has sent both of the major political parties into turmoil. We need to ask ourselves how we got here and more importantly how can we …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>F1 season review: post Japanese Grand Prix</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-f1-season-review-post-japanese-grand-prix/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-f1-season-review-post-japanese-grand-prix/</guid>
        <description>Following the Japanese Grand Prix Vettel’s chances of winning the 2018 F1 Championship have diminished to barely more than a dream. Following a season in which both Hamilton and Vettel have been closely matched throughout this is a bitter pill to swallow for Ferrari.
Following the first 10 races …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s Been a Long Summer in British Politics </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-it-s-been-a-long-summer-in-british-politics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-it-s-been-a-long-summer-in-british-politics/</guid>
        <description>It’s been a crazy summer in the world of politics with both major political parties in major turmoil. The Conservative party and the Labour party have been in open warfare over Brexit with each other and within their own camps.
The start of the summer started well for Theresa May, she suffered no …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bahá’í : a belief system suited to our troubled times?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-bah-a-belief-system-suited-to-our-troubled-times/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-bah-a-belief-system-suited-to-our-troubled-times/</guid>
        <description>The world has seen a resurgence of nationalism, fascism, and protectionism. These pose an existential threat to the world as we know it. Liberal democracies spreading wealth and freedom via free market capitalism have seen their support checked by the likes of Trump, Brexit and most recently the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The government’s handling of the Windrush scandal is a national disgrace</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-the-government-s-handling-of-the-windrush-scandal-is-a-national-disgrace/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-the-government-s-handling-of-the-windrush-scandal-is-a-national-disgrace/</guid>
        <description>The government’s past few years of immigration policy have been cruel and inhumane, as highlighted by the Windrush Scandal. The arbitrary target to cut immigration to the tens of thousands has spawned some nasty and unexpected consequences. The ‘hostile environment’ policy adopted whilst Theresa May …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brexit and Ireland: how can we solve the border crisis?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-brexit-and-ireland-how-can-we-solve-the-border-crisis/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-brexit-and-ireland-how-can-we-solve-the-border-crisis/</guid>
        <description>How do you solve a problem like the Irish border? This appears to be the biggest stumbling block in achieving a successful outcome for Brexit. It seems an impossible square to circle. Theresa May has committed to withdrawing from the customs union and single market, which would mean there would need …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Poor use of statistics is undermining our faith in public institutions</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-poor-use-of-statistics-is-undermining-our-faith-in-public-institutions/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-poor-use-of-statistics-is-undermining-our-faith-in-public-institutions/</guid>
        <description>The rise of statistics has led to many benefits in everyday life: we use statistics in medical research to determine what the best treatment; they inform decisions from stock markets through to how many pop tarts Walmart stocks; and, perhaps most significantly, statistics shape decisions made by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Referendums are not democratic
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-referendums-are-not-democratic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 14:38:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-referendums-are-not-democratic/</guid>
        <description>Referendums have been leading, and will continue to lead, to the slow erosion of Parliamentary sovereignty. The UK is a Parliamentary representative democracy, where the electorate elect a representative from their constituency to represent them in Parliament. These members of parliament should vote …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rhodes must stay
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-rhodes-must-stay/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 13:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-rhodes-must-stay/</guid>
        <description>In recent months, the ‘Rhodes Must Fall’ campaign has gained significant traction not only at Oriel college, Oxford but at several institutions in the UK and abroad. The campaign has attempted to have the statue of Cecil Rhodes removed due to his strong support for the apartheid movement in South …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
