<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rm2410/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rm2410/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>A life of sex, drugs and pas de cheval
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-a-life-of-sex-drugs-and-pas-de-cheval/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 22:30:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rocio Molina Atienza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-a-life-of-sex-drugs-and-pas-de-cheval/</guid>
        <description>Mayerling is dark and majestic ballet which depicts the decadent splendour of the Austro-Hungarian empire. It is based on the life of the tormented Crown Prince Rudolf who after forcefully marrying Princess Stephanie of Belgium is drawn into a spiral of political intrigue, violence, drugs, obsessive …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don’t give a tosca?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-dont-give-a-tosca/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 01:29:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rocio Molina Atienza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-dont-give-a-tosca/</guid>
        <description>Drama, passion and a thrilling unravelling of events makes Tosca an opera that will keep you on your toes during every act. Set against the backdrop of turbulent Rome in the 1800s, this opera could well be equated with a modern Hollywood drama.
It is named after one of the main characters, Floria …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flukeworms
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-flukeworms/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 16:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rocio Molina Atienza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-flukeworms/</guid>
        <description>The Artsfest exhibition is an annual institution that has existed since I arrived at Imperial. It is an important event for those who are involved with the Arts on campus. The show, which is planned to coincide with Imperial College’s festival of art, music and dance, features collaboration between …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Showing some flesh
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-showing-some-flesh/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 19:58:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rocio Molina Atienza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-showing-some-flesh/</guid>
        <description>_Lucian Freud Protraits _is a monumental exhibition, revealing the life-long strive of the artist to capture the mystery of human flesh. Freud, from his beginnings one of the greatest artists of the 20th Century, has struggled with his art, learning and challenging himself up to his death last …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Trauma on Chiltern Street
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-trauma-on-chiltern-street/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 21:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rocio Molina Atienza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-trauma-on-chiltern-street/</guid>
        <description>Trauma,GV Art’s new science-inspired exhibition revolves around the different manifestations of trauma. The exhibition explores physical and biological trauma, revealing the effect they have on those who suffer from them and investigating our own personal perception of them.
Science-inspired art …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Still Life
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-still-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 18:31:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isaid Benitez Cabral,Marie Chkaiban,Rocio Molina Atienza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-still-life/</guid>
        <description>Freedom, Sex, Appetite, Flow, Skin, Touch, Breath, Sensuality, Exposure
[photo id=12]
</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is it time to rethink the watercolour painting?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-is-it-time-to-rethink-the-watercolour-painting/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 08:54:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rocio Molina Atienza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-is-it-time-to-rethink-the-watercolour-painting/</guid>
        <description>Tate’s attempt at redefining our vision of a medium, watercolour, so commonly associated with amateurship and spinsters trying to show off their artistic talent is definitely successful. After viewing this exhibit your conception of what can be done with watercolours will have drastically changed, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tate Modern’s blockbuster Orozco
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-18-tate-moderns-blockbuster-orozco/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 08:39:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rocio Molina Atienza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-18-tate-moderns-blockbuster-orozco/</guid>
        <description>Is it worth going to see another exhibition full of quirky art put there just to leave the onlooker wondering how anyone can call it ‘Art’? Beyond the bewildering first impression, Orozco’s exhibition at the Tate evokes a personal and surreal world where playfulness comes side by side with death. On …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>High art awaits at the Wellcome Trust
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-high-art-awaits-at-the-wellcome-trust/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 18:53:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rocio Molina Atienza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-high-art-awaits-at-the-wellcome-trust/</guid>
        <description>An exhibition about mind-altering drugs is likely to elicit the curiosity of nearly everyone, since most of us are at least occasional consumers. Remember how full the Union is of inebriated students some nights of the week? So, I was ready to be surprised by what of artistic value anyone could …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
