<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/henry_alman/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/henry_alman/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>We&#39;ve moved to a new location: felixonlinesummer.uk</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2020-04-05-new-website/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2020-04-05-new-website/</guid>
        <description>Head to felixonlinesummer.uk for our Summer 2020 coverage!
</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ethical Investment Paper Passed by College Council</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-ethical-investment-paper-passed-college-council/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-ethical-investment-paper-passed-college-council/</guid>
        <description>The paper, written by the Union President, Deputy President (Finance and Services), and Ethics and Environment Officer, was originally submitted on the 22nd of November and was passed with minor amendments from the President’s Board.
It establishes a ‘working group’ that is mandated to investigate …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Interviews: Anne Barrett, College Archivist</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-felix-interviews-anne-barrett-college-archivist/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-felix-interviews-anne-barrett-college-archivist/</guid>
        <description>Felix: Most students probably aren’t really aware that the college has archives – do you interact with students a lot?
Some of them are – particularly the constituent college unions – and I do host evenings with different groups. When I had the City and Guilds Union members in, they were looking at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Halo Reach on PC: A Perfect Port, but a Flawed Game</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-halo-reach-pc-perfect-port-flawed-game/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-halo-reach-pc-perfect-port-flawed-game/</guid>
        <description>Let me make one thing clear: I am absolutely biased. Halo Reach was a significant part of my teenagedom; I spent a frankly unhealthy amount of hours sprinting around the wide landscapes and vast alien structures of the original game. It defined my social life – I’d host huge all-night LAN parties …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Space: The Final Frontier</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-space-final-frontier/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-space-final-frontier/</guid>
        <description>The College has, in recent years, struggled with the amount of space available on the South Kensington campus, and is separately making decisions like the sale of St. Mary’s and the construction of White City – but projects are still ongoing to optimise the space available. One such project is the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Most Influential Games of the Decade: Felix Games Breaks it Down</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-most-influentiual-games-decade-felix-games-breaks-it-down/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freddie Ugo,Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-most-influentiual-games-decade-felix-games-breaks-it-down/</guid>
        <description>Redefining Open World Adventures: The Legend of Zelda Breath of the Wild
Despite being one of a long list of amazing Zelda games, Breath of the Wild is set apart by its unique method of story-telling and its risky gameplay choices that definitely payed off. Breath of the Wild is unlike other Zelda …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Ongoing Direction of the Union</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-ongoing-direction-of-union/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-ongoing-direction-of-union/</guid>
        <description>It has been confirmed that Jon Tucker, the Business School’s Faculty Operating Officer, will be providing interim support to the Union following the departure of the Managing Director.
The decision was made after a discussion with College by Jill Finney, the Chair of the Union’s Board of Trustees, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Plans to Increase Halls Rent Again; Union to Negotiate Prices</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-college-plans-increase-halls-rent-union-negotiate-prices/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-college-plans-increase-halls-rent-union-negotiate-prices/</guid>
        <description>The price of rent in College-owned halls is set to increase again this year, with the student union acting in a consultation role with students.
The College’s total necessary revenue from halls rent is increasing by 12.2% in just one year in order to match a break-even model, in which revenue …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Managing Director of the Union Steps Down</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-managing-director-union-steps-down/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-managing-director-union-steps-down/</guid>
        <description>The Managing Director of the Union, Jarlath O’Hara, announced on 18th November that he will be stepping down from his role at the end of December. The announcement was made via an email sent internally to ICU staff, and marks the end of Jarlath’s four-year tenure in the role.
In the email, the only …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Strike Action: Pensions and Pay</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-strike-action-pensions-and-pay/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-strike-action-pensions-and-pay/</guid>
        <description>At 60 universities across the UK, university staff who are members of the University and College Union (UCU) are currently staging an eight-day walkout and strike action in response to the ongoing disputes regarding pensions, pay, and working conditions.
The Imperial branch of the UCU, however, is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union Kitchen Receives 2/5 Food Hygiene Rating</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-union-kitchen-receives-two-five-food-hygiene-rating/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-union-kitchen-receives-two-five-food-hygiene-rating/</guid>
        <description>The Union kitchen has received a low 2-out-of-5 rating for their food hygiene, after an inspection by a local council Environmental Health Officer (EHO) took place on August 23rd.
The areas assessed were hygienic food handling, cleanliness and condition of facilities, and management of food safety. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Food in Union Stops Due to Electrical Fault; “No Timeline” on Return</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-food-union-stops-due-electrical-fault-no-timeline-on-return/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-food-union-stops-due-electrical-fault-no-timeline-on-return/</guid>
        <description>The Union has not been providing food service in 568, its flagship venue on the South Kensington campus, for two weeks. The cause of the disruption is an “electrical fault” – specifically, that the circuit board to which the various kitchen appliances are attached to was being overloaded.
As a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Survey Shows What Students Really Think of Brexit</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-survey-shows-what-students-really-think-brexit/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-survey-shows-what-students-really-think-brexit/</guid>
        <description>A survey conducted by Dig-In – of freshers’ week welcome package fame – has demonstrated that a strong majority of students in the UK oppose Brexit. Out of over 35000 students surveyed, 38% stated that they ‘hated’ that the UK is leaving the EU, while a further 24% ‘dislike’ it – totalling for a 62% …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Plans to Put Path across Queen&#39;s Lawn</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-college-plans-put-path-across-queens-lawn/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-college-plans-put-path-across-queens-lawn/</guid>
        <description>The College is planning to place a path across the Queen’s Lawn – a move which has raised controversy amongst some students. The path will run across the diagonal of the lawn, based on analysis of timelapse photography showing the most-used path by pedestrians crossing.
The aim of the initiative is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Reports: Second Union Council</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-felix-reports-second-union-council/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-felix-reports-second-union-council/</guid>
        <description>As a reminder of the purpose of Council: the Council is the highest democratic decision-making body in the Union, at which the full-time Officer Trustees (OTs) and key student volunteers put policies into place, address ongoing issues by submitting and discussing papers, and receive updates from the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Record Turnout at Autumn Elections</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-record-turnout-autumn-elections/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-record-turnout-autumn-elections/</guid>
        <description>The Autumn elections ended on Thursday 24th October, with 329 student reps elected. Felix breaks down the data with the help of the Union Elections Team, and spoke to them about what made turnout so excellent this year.
To break down the data: the total turnout emerged at 34.31%, corresponding to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chemistry Introduces Roxy the Therapy Dog</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-Chemistry-Introduces-Roxy-Therapy-Dog/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-Chemistry-Introduces-Roxy-Therapy-Dog/</guid>
        <description>The Chemistry department has introduced weekly sessions with a therapy dog this term, in conjunction with the charity Therapy Dogs Nationwide, as one of a set of new wellbeing initiatives.
Originally, the suggestion for a ‘dog day’ was requested by students and reps, but the department felt that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Reveals Academic Strategy 2020-2025</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-College-Reveals-Academic-Strategy-2020-2025/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-College-Reveals-Academic-Strategy-2020-2025/</guid>
        <description>The Academic Strategy (AS) for the next five years has recently been unveiled by the College after a long development cycle. The Strategy will be used to inform the direction the College will take with regards to investing in new spaces, curriculum review, research foci, and more.
It builds upon the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College NHS Trust Staff Strike</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-imperial-college-nhs-trust-staff-strike/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-imperial-college-nhs-trust-staff-strike/</guid>
        <description>The strikes, organised by the United Voices of the World (UVW) trade union, took place on Monday 28th, Tuesday 29th, and Thursday 31st October, with an estimated 200 staff joining at some point over the three days. There are plans for further strike action over the coming weeks, for a total of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Counselling Service Expansion: A First Step</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-college-counselling-service-expansion-first-step/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-college-counselling-service-expansion-first-step/</guid>
        <description>The College has expanded the space available to the Student Counselling and Mental Health Advice Service, by renovating space in the old unoccupied Bernard Sunley hall in Evelyn Gardens. The new space opened on 7th October.
The budget for the expansion was around £150,000, which was used to convert …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Renews Times Partnership</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-imperial-renews-times-partnership/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-imperial-renews-times-partnership/</guid>
        <description>Imperial has renewed a partnership with The Times that gives both students and staff a free 12-month digital subscription, tied to their college accounts. The College originally started the partnership last year, but it was unknown whether it would continue.
The offering has been expanded this year, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mumps Outbreak Amongst Medics</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-mumps-outbreak-amongst-medics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,Eyad Abuelgasim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-mumps-outbreak-amongst-medics/</guid>
        <description>There has been an outbreak of mumps among medic students over the last week, rendering several students confined to their homes while they wait for the infection to pass.
The NHS recommendation for isolation is five days, by which time infectivity is largely reduced as mumps is a ‘self-limiting’ …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Gamification of Apps</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-gamification-apps/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-gamification-apps/</guid>
        <description>Gamification may be the best way to maximise revenue and grow the userbase of your app. It’s a well-known technique these days, the darling of UX developers everywhere, and a fundamental part of design. Once a niche, it has become the standard – integrated from the very conception of an app idea. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Launches J-IDEA Institute</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-imperial-launches-j-idea-institute/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-imperial-launches-j-idea-institute/</guid>
        <description>Imperial has launched a new institute as part of the School of Public Health in White City this week, targeted at predicting and preventing global health crises.
The institute, dubbed J-IDEA for the Abdul Latif Jameel Institute for Disease and Emergency Analytics, will utilise advanced mathematical …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Prince Andrew&#39;s Visit: Student Responses</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-prince-andrews-visit-student-responses/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-prince-andrews-visit-student-responses/</guid>
        <description>Our reporters generally noted several things.
Firstly, there were a very high – even a vast majority – of students who seemed unaware of the allegations against the Prince and thus were initially confused by the questions asked. This could be interpreted as either apathy, or a lack of knowledge. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Riot Games is Trying to Kill Blizzard: the 10th Anniversary Announcements</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-riot-games-trying-kill-blizzard-tenth-anniversary-announcements/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-riot-games-trying-kill-blizzard-tenth-anniversary-announcements/</guid>
        <description>The 10th-anniversary celebration of League of Legends took place a few days ago – and oh boy, did Riot pull out all the stops.
The day began with some fun streams with various Riot employees – such as a live concert of League music, a ‘Twitch Plays’, where the chat was used to drive a robot around …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Fossil Fuel Dichotomy at Imperial</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-fossil-fuel-dichotomy-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-fossil-fuel-dichotomy-imperial/</guid>
        <description>On the 10th of October, the UK Committee on Climate Change (CCC) delivered a report to government on how the government can engage the public in sustainable practices in order to reduce carbon emissions. The report was led by Dr. Richard Carmichael, an Imperial academic working with the Centre for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Meeting of Union Council: A Roundup</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-first-meeting-union-council-roundup/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-first-meeting-union-council-roundup/</guid>
        <description>The first Union Council of the year took place on the 8th of October. The Council is the highest democratic decision-making body in the Union, at which the full-time Officer Trustees (OTs) and key student volunteers put policies into place, address ongoing issues by submitting and discussing papers, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Prince Andrew Planning to Visit College</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-prince-andrew-planning-visit-college/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-prince-andrew-planning-visit-college/</guid>
        <description>There have been reports that Prince Andrew, The Duke of York, will be visiting Imperial’s White City campus on the 14th of October. The visit is in tandem with the ‘Pitch@Palace&amp;rsquo; entrepreneurship scheme that the Duke began in 2014, the penultimate ‘Boot Camp’ stage of which is being hosted on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The &#39;Welcome Carnival&#39;: Trouble at the Bars</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-welcome-carnival-trouble-at-bars/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-welcome-carnival-trouble-at-bars/</guid>
        <description>The Union’s ‘Welcome Carnival’ event, formerly known as the Freshers’ Ball, took place on Friday the 4th of October. Although historically the Freshers’ Ball has been a highly successful event – for many the highlight of Freshers’ Fortnight – the rebranded event fell flat this year.
The Carnival was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Guardian University League Tables: Imperial Maintains Position</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-guardian-university-league-tables-imperial-maintains-position/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-guardian-university-league-tables-imperial-maintains-position/</guid>
        <description>The Guardian university league tables for 2020 were published on 7th June. The tables rank UK universities both overall and for individual subjects.
Imperial maintained its overall position from last year in 7th, an impressive feat given that many London universities have declined. LSE, King’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union Awards 2019: Celebrating the Union&#39;s best</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-union-awards-2019-celebrating-the-union-s-best/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-union-awards-2019-celebrating-the-union-s-best/</guid>
        <description>The ninth Union Awards ceremony was held in Metric on June 6th, and saw the Union recognise and commemorate its top contributors for the year.
Winners included students and societies who demonstrated outstanding effectiveness in their roles, and have laid down a legacy that will benefit students …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dinosaurs were thriving before asteroid strike that wiped them out</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-dinosaurs-were-thriving-before-asteroid-strike-that-wiped-them-out/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-dinosaurs-were-thriving-before-asteroid-strike-that-wiped-them-out/</guid>
        <description>A new analysis has posited that dinosaurs were unaffected by long-term climate changes and flourished before their sudden demise by asteroid strike.
Scientists largely agree that an asteroid impact, possibly coupled with intense volcanic activity, wiped out the dinosaurs at the end of the Cretaceous …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New cholesterol-lowering drug could help patients unable to take statins</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-new-cholesterol-lowering-drug-could-help-patients-unable-to-take-statins/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-new-cholesterol-lowering-drug-could-help-patients-unable-to-take-statins/</guid>
        <description>A new class of oral cholesterol-lowering drug could help patients unable to take statins due to side effects.
The findings come from the largest study to date to test the effectiveness and safety of bempedoic acid, an oral medication - yet to be approved in Europe - which inhibits the body’s ability …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New hepatitis C cases down by almost 70% in HIV positive men in London</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-new-hepatitis-c-cases-down-by-almost-70-in-hiv-positive-men-in-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-new-hepatitis-c-cases-down-by-almost-70-in-hiv-positive-men-in-london/</guid>
        <description>New cases of hepatitis C amongst HIV positive men in London have fallen by nearly 70 per cent in recent years. The new analysis of data from three clinics in London found 256 men were diagnosed between 2013-2018. New infections peaked at 17 for every 1000 people studied in 2015 and fell to six by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>From single cells to multicellular organisms: witnessing  evolution</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-from-single-cells-to-multicellular-organisms-witnessing-evolution/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-from-single-cells-to-multicellular-organisms-witnessing-evolution/</guid>
        <description>Researchers from the George Institute of Technology and University of Montana have witnessed in real-time the development of single-cell algae into more complex multicellular organisms – and, astonishingly, the process took only 50 weeks, or just 750 generations. The only driving environmental …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Infectious diseases could be diagnosed with  smartphones in sub-Saharan Africa</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-infectious-diseases-could-be-diagnosed-with-smartphones-in-sub-saharan-africa/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-infectious-diseases-could-be-diagnosed-with-smartphones-in-sub-saharan-africa/</guid>
        <description>A new Imperial-led review has outlined how health workers could use existing phones to predict and curb the spread of infectious diseases.
The review was published in Nature, and involved researchers from Imperial, the Karolinska Institute, UCL, The University of KwaZulu-Natal, the Africa Health …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can machine learning predict ovarian cancer survival?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-can-machine-learning-predict-ovarian-cancer-survival/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-can-machine-learning-predict-ovarian-cancer-survival/</guid>
        <description>Researchers at Imperial College London and the University of Melbourne have created new machine learning software that can forecast the survival rates and response to treatments of patients with ovarian cancer.
The software has been able to predict the prognosis of patients with ovarian cancer …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lack of sleep is not necessarily fatal for flies</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-lack-of-sleep-is-not-necessarily-fatal-for-flies/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-lack-of-sleep-is-not-necessarily-fatal-for-flies/</guid>
        <description>Male flies kept awake do not die earlier than those allowed to sleep, leading researchers to question whether sleep is essential for staying alive. Whilst this study was in flies, the team speculate that if sleep is not essential for life in the same way food is, then it is possible that their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Poorest dying nearly ten years younger than the rich in “deeply worrying” trend for UK health</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-poorest-dying-nearly-ten-years-younger-than-the-rich-in-deeply-worrying-trend-for-uk-health/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-poorest-dying-nearly-ten-years-younger-than-the-rich-in-deeply-worrying-trend-for-uk-health/</guid>
        <description>The gap between the life expectancy of the richest and poorest sectors of society in England is increasing, according to new research from Imperial College London.
The study, which was published in the journal Lancet Public Health and funded by the Wellcome Trust, analysed Office for National …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The darker side of human data</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-the-darker-side-of-human-data/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-the-darker-side-of-human-data/</guid>
        <description>In 2014, the State Council of China announced the development of a digital ‘citizen rating system’ to determine each citizen, company, and local government’s “trustworthiness”, with the intent of building social trust and crushing China’s rampant counterfeiting and fraud issues.
To Westerners it may …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
