<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sa8713/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sa8713/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Halloween Horror Game Recommendations </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-halloween-horror-game-recommendations/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,Kai Lawrence,Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-halloween-horror-game-recommendations/</guid>
        <description>With Halloween right around the corner, there’s always plenty of scares including: coursework deadlines, peer pressure and our very own Horror game recommendations! We thought we’d give you a fright this Felix issues with our personal selection of horror games old and new, that you can enjoy this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>E3 – The good, the bad, and the dull</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-e3-the-good-the-bad-and-the-dull/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-e3-the-good-the-bad-and-the-dull/</guid>
        <description>The thing gamers look forward to more than upcoming release dates or the Steam summer sales is E3 – the Electronic Entertainment Expo. A showcase of everything to get hyped about and enjoy for the future in the world of gaming. So, without further ado, here’s our evaluation of the main conferences …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Video games: Teaching us about the future</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-video-games-teaching-us-about-the-future/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-video-games-teaching-us-about-the-future/</guid>
        <description>Games are primarily a form of entertainment to most people; a unique way to pass the time. However they can sometimes do a bit more than that. Depending on the game and at which point you’re in, games can teach us important things about society and empathy. Heck, they could even be considered …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Fortnite phenomenon – Battle Royale </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-the-fortnite-phenomenon-battle-royale/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-the-fortnite-phenomenon-battle-royale/</guid>
        <description>Unless you’ve been living under a rock, you’ve most probably heard of Fortnite. And what is it exactly? It’s the game that is currently trending amongst YouTubers, gamers, and angry ten year olds alike. And it has been for the past several months; in fact it’s basically a cultural phenomenon at this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Preconceived notions: reviews and sales</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-preconceived-notions-reviews-and-sales/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-preconceived-notions-reviews-and-sales/</guid>
        <description>We may not realise it, but our opinions of certain games, films, and TV shows are usually formed, even before we get to experience them ourselves. This is due to all the reviews we see, hear, or read about before or straight after a product’s release. Our brains are more likely to think something is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Just one more turn: the arbitrary endpoint</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-just-one-more-turn-the-arbitrary-endpoint/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-just-one-more-turn-the-arbitrary-endpoint/</guid>
        <description>Picture this. It’s 3am. The only sound you can hear is the rhapsodic music of your game. Sleep is trying to lure you into its pull. You try to resist its charms. You have lectures in the morning. You know the smart thing to do is to shut down the game, and go to sleep. But you can’t bring yourself …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Video games as an art form</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-video-games-as-an-art-form/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-video-games-as-an-art-form/</guid>
        <description>Are video games an art form? It’s a bit of a controversial question and to some people, usually “old” people and art critics, it’s no question at all. One of the biggest voices against considering games as art was the film critic Roger Ebert who battled against the perception of video games becoming …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In defence of video game walkthroughs</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-in-defence-of-video-game-walkthroughs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-in-defence-of-video-game-walkthroughs/</guid>
        <description>With the advent of video games and the internet also came the onset of walkthroughs, guides which tell you how to play a game and get through the story. They can vary in complexity, from telling you only the main points of what to do, to literally spelling out how to cover every little corner. This …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London Anime &amp; Gaming Con 2018</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-london-anime-gaming-con-2018/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-london-anime-gaming-con-2018/</guid>
        <description>Conventions, be it Comic Con or last weekend’s Anime and Gaming Con, are usually the kind of thing where only a small group of people really know what they’re all about. Most people either don’t know they exist or are hesitant to go out of fear or uncertainty about what it actually is and what it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>American Vandal: A detective mockumentary that goes beyond dick jokes </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-american-vandal-a-detective-mockumentary-that-goes-beyond-dick-jokes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-american-vandal-a-detective-mockumentary-that-goes-beyond-dick-jokes/</guid>
        <description>With so much TV hitting our screens nowadays, American Vandal will probably fly under a lot of radars due to its lack of big names and its ‘mockumentary’ label. I am here to convince you that this show is, without a doubt, a masterpiece and well worth a place on the top of your watchlist. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Visual novels – A unique form of storytelling</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-visual-novels-a-unique-form-of-storytelling/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-visual-novels-a-unique-form-of-storytelling/</guid>
        <description>A few years ago, you wouldn’t have been able to find more than one or two games on Steam catergorised under the ‘visual novel’ format. In recent years however, their popularity has been growing; now there are a number of visual novels that are considered mainstream. In spite of that, visual novels …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cute girls with a twist: Doki Doki Literature Club</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-cute-girls-with-a-twist-doki-doki-literature-club/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-cute-girls-with-a-twist-doki-doki-literature-club/</guid>
        <description>From the title and cute picture alone, you’re probably thinking that this is some anime-styled dating simulator and are judging both me, and my life choices. Let me assure you, this game is literally not what you expect; if you choose to experience it, you’ll be in for a wild, freaky and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Justice League fails to save the (cinematic) day</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-justice-league-fails-to-save-the-cinematic-day/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-justice-league-fails-to-save-the-cinematic-day/</guid>
        <description>Justice League had a lot to prove from the get go. With three critically panned films and only one moderate successfully movie in Wonder Woman, Warner Brothers and DC Comics had a lot to make up for and improve upon. While Justice League is ultimately a step in the right direction, it doesn’t quite …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Marvel Universe’s small screen efforts make for forgettable television</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-marvel-universe-s-small-screen-efforts-make-for-forgettable-television/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-marvel-universe-s-small-screen-efforts-make-for-forgettable-television/</guid>
        <description>After two years and five seasons worth of episodes between the characters, Marvel’s darker and grittier street level heroes finally come together Avengers-style. However, after all the build-up and a lacklustre performance from Iron Fist, the biggest question was whether Defenders would be able to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The imperfect ending
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-imperfect-ending/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 17:06:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-imperfect-ending/</guid>
        <description>Gaming isn’t all fun and games perhaps ironically. In fact gamers are often pressed for time, having to juggle life admin and professional obligations on top of their gaming habit. It’s fair to say we rarely have the time to complete many games, and if we do, more often than not we’re ‘rewarded’ …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The great age of the 3DS
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-the-great-age-of-the-3ds/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:25:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-the-great-age-of-the-3ds/</guid>
        <description> The 3DS has been the go-to portable games machine of its time, testified by the sales of over 65 million units, and is a shining example of how to make a perfect handheld console. Its only other portable rival, the Playstation Vita is as good as dead these days, and mobile games don’t even come …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dealing with escapism
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-dealing-with-escapism/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:22:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-dealing-with-escapism/</guid>
        <description>It should come as no surprise to anyone that life is a cruel mistress, especially if you’re in uni. With deadlines, exams and project work, it can quickly get overwhelming. Things can also be insanely frustrating (when for example, you put all your heart and soul into revising for a course but you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Clash of heroes | Fire Emblem Heroes
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-clash-of-heroes-fire-emblem-heroes/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 16:30:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-clash-of-heroes-fire-emblem-heroes/</guid>
        <description>After years of Nintendo-only games, we finally get a free-to-play Fire Emblem game for iOS and Android. This spinoff is a simplistic but entertaining spin on the strategy RPG series that offers long-time fans something light to enjoy between last year’s Fates and next year’s game for the Switch.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>eSports | Imperial vs UCL
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-esports-imperial-vs-ucl/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 17:29:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-esports-imperial-vs-ucl/</guid>
        <description>For most people, the 12th of March was just another Sunday. For a group of certain individuals, however, it was a chance for lasting and eternal glory. Well, more like temporary happiness for a few days, but hey, we all have to take what we can get.
This Sunday, an eSports tournament was held …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Games to feel good
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-games-to-feel-good/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 13:56:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-games-to-feel-good/</guid>
        <description> Truck Simulator | Or any simulator When you first hear about it, Truck Simulator sounds like a pretty boring game. You’re a truck driver and your job is to make deliveries from one city to another. You’re not even supposed to drive crazily; you’re supposed to obey the traffic laws and you actually …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Some Strings Attached | Casual
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-some-strings-attached-casual/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 13:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-some-strings-attached-casual/</guid>
        <description>This is a show about relationships in every sense of the word, though as its name may imply, the focus here is one of those casual, one-off encounters that many people are engaged with in this day and age. This idea is explored with a very simple premise; a woman, in the wake of her divorce, moves …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stressing out to chill out
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-stressing-out-to-chill-out/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 15:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-stressing-out-to-chill-out/</guid>
        <description>Once upon a time, games used to be hard. Like really, really fucking hard. You had to spend hours grinding and leveling up, looking for the right items or npcs and learn the technique needed to progress.
By comparison, the majority of games these days are relatively easy to play and get into. Not …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Left or right?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-left-or-right/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 16:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-left-or-right/</guid>
        <description>Video games are unique from TV shows and movies due to the sense of immersion they give players. Having the ability to make choices plays a large part in this. It’s not just any old story you get to experience, it’s one chosen and defined by you and that’s what makes it all the more intimate.
Of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>8-bit snacking
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-8-bit-snacking/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 17:34:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-8-bit-snacking/</guid>
        <description>There are a million reasons as to why food appears in video games which is to say there is only really one reason: everybody eats. It might seem obvious but it’s the truth and when you think about it, food plays a much larger role in video games than what you think.
Take Pac-man for instance, where …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Justice League Action
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-justice-league-action/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 17:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-justice-league-action/</guid>
        <description>Since there are a number of DC Comics adaptations on the horizon, it seems only fitting that an animated series be released to capitalise on its popularity. While Justice League Action is definitely entertaining, how much you personally enjoy it depends on what you’re expecting.
Justice League …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The ballad of Pokémon GO
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-the-ballad-of-pokmon-go/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 17:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-the-ballad-of-pokmon-go/</guid>
        <description>Ah, Pokémon GO. What it was and what it could have been. It was a sensation that gripped so many people only to come crashing down.
Let’s think back to early 2016 when Pokémon GO was just an innovating idea. One that got people excited. It was touted to be an AR game which would essentially be the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rebooted | A Series of Unfortunate Events
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-rebooted-a-series-of-unfortunate-events/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-rebooted-a-series-of-unfortunate-events/</guid>
        <description>The catchy theme song of this Netflix adaptation advises you to look away, warning you of a story that is dark and has no happy ending. If you actually listen to that advice, it would be an unfortunate event in of itself, as you would be missing out on a well-made, dark and incredibly self-aware …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Most anticipated games of 2017
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-most-anticipated-games-of-2017/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:51:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-most-anticipated-games-of-2017/</guid>
        <description> Mass Effect: Andromeda The Mass Effect series was iconic and well deserving of all its recognition. Its ending may have been polarising but it did not take away from the hours of rich game play and world building. It was a thrill to learn that another entry in the series was coming. Although not …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Invasion!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-invasion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 15:45:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-invasion/</guid>
        <description>Having four shows set in a shared universe and on the same channel meant a crossover was inevitable. It was certainly ambitious, especially on a TV network budget, but I’m glad to say they were able to pull it off.
With a diverse range of characters from DC comics, the crossover is essentially a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Varsity Games at Gfinity
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-varsity-games-at-gfinity/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 15:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-varsity-games-at-gfinity/</guid>
        <description>Esports have rapidly been gaining popularity recently and have been making a name for themselves across the gaming community. However, despite this spike in popularity, they have yet to be taken seriously or started building a community, bringing like-minded people together. An organisation called …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pokémon Sun and Moon
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-pokmon-sun-and-moon/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 15:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-pokmon-sun-and-moon/</guid>
        <description>It’s been a while since Pokémon Go’s surprise popularity peak, but with the release of the latest games, Sun and Moon, the Pokémon franchise is back in the limelight. The new games offer a fresh and updated take on the title while still staying true to the original formula; they remind us why the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Working Girls | The Girlfriend Experience
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-working-girls-the-girlfriend-experience/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 15:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-working-girls-the-girlfriend-experience/</guid>
        <description>This was an unusual show for a number of reasons. The show starts off fairly simple but slowly evolves into an intriguing drama with complexity and depth.
The series features Riley Keough as law student Christine Reade, who makes a decision to become an escort right about the same time she starts an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Eight signs you’re dating a gamer
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-eight-signs-youre-dating-a-gamer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 14:33:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-eight-signs-youre-dating-a-gamer/</guid>
        <description> Your SO (significant other) is simply the greatest, they seem to be perfect in all aspects. You think you’ve scored the jackpot and can’t do any better. But, you have a nagging suspicion about them: you think they might be a gamer. You don’t want to believe it, but you can’t deny certain features …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fallacies of masculinity in games
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-fallacies-of-masculinity-in-games/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 15:22:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-fallacies-of-masculinity-in-games/</guid>
        <description>In the olden times, the world was in a very different place. Just look at old stories and folk-tales to get an idea; they always sprang out of the aspirations and concerns of the time. After centuries of storytelling, it can get pretty tricky to cut those bonds. Obviously, society has massively …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Voltron: Legendary Defender
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-voltron-legendary-defender/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 15:07:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-voltron-legendary-defender/</guid>
        <description>Upon first hearing of the Voltron reboot, I was sceptical. The focus of the show was to be on giant flying robotic lions that could combine together to form an even larger robot. It made me think that it would be a lesser version of a Transformers/Power Rangers mash-up. Two things made me decide to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The evolution of female characters in games
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-the-evolution-of-female-characters-in-games/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 23:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-the-evolution-of-female-characters-in-games/</guid>
        <description>Once upon a time, Pac Man was as advanced as games got, with basic graphics and simple controls. We’ve definitely come a long way since then with regards to designs, gameplay and much more. With the change and progression of games, we’ve also seen a change in how female characters have been …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nine tips for gaming during lectures
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-10-nine-tips-for-gaming-during-lectures/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 12:21:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-10-nine-tips-for-gaming-during-lectures/</guid>
        <description> 1 Sit as far back as you possibly can (Obvious really)
2 Get a laptop and headphones and you’re basically sorted
3 Get a handheld console (mobile games don’t count)
4 Ok, maybe some of them do count
5 Play a game where it looks like you’re taking notes
6 Avoid games where you’ll be constantly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gaming: uni’s best stress relief
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-10-gaming-unis-best-stress-relief/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 12:16:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-10-gaming-unis-best-stress-relief/</guid>
        <description>If you’re a fresher, welcome to Imperial! If you’re a returning student, welcome back. Right now it’s only been a week or so of University so things are probably still feeling pretty relaxed. You’re just going through introductory lectures, there’s no coursework to be on top of, and you’ve basically …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Complex and Real parts of Love
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-the-complex-and-real-parts-of-love/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 09:25:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-the-complex-and-real-parts-of-love/</guid>
        <description>Created by Judd Apatow, Paul Rust, and Lesley Arfin, Love is simply great. I really enjoyed watching it; mostly for the fact that it’s different from all the usual rom-coms. It doesn’t have wishy-washy clichés but rather it dives into the complexities and realism of relationships.
Typically, one …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Zombies are coming
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-the-zombies-are-coming/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 09:03:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-the-zombies-are-coming/</guid>
        <description>Ever since it was introduced, The Walking Dead’s popularity has soared through the roof. Another Zombie apocalypse styled story, the franchise has a comic book, TV series, video game, and now, with Fear the Walking Dead, a spin-off TV series. With the main show still airing and already in place …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cartoon Corner: Vixen
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-cartoon-corner-vixen/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 09:24:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-cartoon-corner-vixen/</guid>
        <description>Spinning out of the CW’s live action DC shows is an animated one by the name of Vixen. This series takes place in its own corner of the called ‘Arrowverse’, offering a take on a different kind of hero, as well as using animation to do the things too expensive for live action. This venture is mostly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cartoon Corner: Spectacular Spider-Man
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-cartoon-corner-spectacular-spider-man/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 12:02:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-cartoon-corner-spectacular-spider-man/</guid>
        <description>Airing for only two seasons, The Spectacular Spider-Man animated series is one of the numerous shows cancelled before its time. With characterisation true to the spirit of the comics, intelligent storytelling, and superb action, this is one of the greatest portrayals of everyone’s favorite …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What makes an Adaptation?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-what-makes-an-adaptation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 12:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-what-makes-an-adaptation/</guid>
        <description>These days it seems like the most popular medium for TV shows to take inspiration from is the literary one. With several books, graphic novels and comics, sometimes with decades of mythology, it’s hard to see why not. When something works in a medium where scenes are static or left to the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Robot or Human?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-robot-or-human/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 11:42:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-robot-or-human/</guid>
        <description>What does it mean to be a human? That’s the question Channel 4’s sci-fi show Humans dances around. Created by Sam Vincent and Jonathan Brackley, this show tells a compelling story with multi-layered characters.
Based on an original Swedish series called ‘Real Humans’, created by Lars Lundstrom, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cartoon Corner: Avengers EMH
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-cartoon-corner-avengers-emh/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 11:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-cartoon-corner-avengers-emh/</guid>
        <description>Avengers Earth’s Mightiest Heroes is a fantastic journey into fun and adventure, with writing that embraces the best elements of Marvel media as well as the original comic book roots. With well done, serialised storytelling, an excellent voice cast and superb animation, Avengers EMH is a lot of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AKA Jessica Jones
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-aka-jessica-jones/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 11:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-aka-jessica-jones/</guid>
        <description>Lately there’s been some strong comic book TV adaptations debuting, ranging from the gritty atmosphere of Daredevil to the fun and colourful world of the Flash. Marvel’s Jessica Jones manages to bring another successful, while at the same time different, mood to the table. Focusing on the more shady …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cartoon Corner: The Boondocks
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-cartoon-corner-the-boondocks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 12:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-cartoon-corner-the-boondocks/</guid>
        <description>Created by Aaron McGruder and based on the comic strip of the same name, The Boondocks is a show that takes a sharp and satirical look at American society with an emphasis on social issues, as well as icons like Oprah Winfrey and Barack Obama. It was controversial right from the start (as you can …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cartoon Corner: One Punch Man
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-cartoon-corner-one-punch-man/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 11:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-cartoon-corner-one-punch-man/</guid>
        <description>This anime is one which is a stark departure from how typical anime, or indeed superhero stories, usually are and that is a completely good thing. The biggest quality of this show is that it feels fresh and new. It was originally a webcomic which was so popular it got its own animated adaption, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Retro Retrospective: Mad Men
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-8-retro-retrospective-mad-men/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 17:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-8-retro-retrospective-mad-men/</guid>
        <description>Last year marked the end of lots of things; Jon Stewart’s run on the Daily Show, Bill Cosby’s career, Meek Mill’s career, 2014, and many beloved TV shows. Of these, one was Mad Men, a series I discovered, binge watched, and fell in love with, all in the space of about two weeks. Centring on the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rise of Netflix (Fall of Cable?)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-rise-of-netflix-fall-of-cable/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 12:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-rise-of-netflix-fall-of-cable/</guid>
        <description>These past few years, we’ve seen a sudden shift in popularity of several online streaming sites with Netflix, Hulu and Amazon Prime being the most popular of the bunch. They’ve added competition into the television market and are growing in popularity by the day. Netflix have also been expanding …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FELIX reacts to virtual reality
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-felix-reacts-to-virtual-reality/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 12:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Indira Mallik,Cale E Tilford,Lef Apostolakis,Saad Ahmed,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-felix-reacts-to-virtual-reality/</guid>
        <description>The year of virtual reality is finally upon us. This week, the FELIX team tried Gear VR, Samsung’s mobile virtual reality headset.
It’s not as powerful as competitors like Oculus Rift or the HTC Vive, but it’s a decent introduction to VR for the unacquainted.
Lef Apostolakis, Science Editor
I tried …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cartoon Corner: Rick &amp; Morty
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-cartoon-corner-rick-morty/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 09:59:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-cartoon-corner-rick-morty/</guid>
        <description>Sometimes considered a loose and boisterous reimaging of Doc Brown and Marty, Rick and Morty is a fun and wild, animated science-fiction show where things are anything but classic Sci-Fi. If you haven’t heard of this show by now, you’ve either been subjugated by the rule of the canines or are …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
