<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/km2612/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/km2612/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Bukhara: Dreams of Another Land
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-20-bukhara-dreams-of-another-land/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2015 17:30:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-20-bukhara-dreams-of-another-land/</guid>
        <description>“But there is no such thing as a Silk Road!”
I didn’t quite know how to react. What did she mean? Had my grand plans of an adventure along the ancient Silk Road this summer all been in vain, chasing an imaginary past in the vast and stifling wastelands of Turkestan?
I was giddy in anticipation of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Art In The City: Our Summer Guide
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-18-art-in-the-city-our-summer-guide/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2015 22:02:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-18-art-in-the-city-our-summer-guide/</guid>
        <description> BP Portrait Award 2015 Like the RA’s Summer Exhibition and standing in the courtyard of The Globe to see some Shakespeare as a groundling, the NPG’s Portrait Award is a summer tradition. This year saw over 2,700 entries to the competition, all vying for the top prize of £30,000, and – more …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC Choir Enthrals with Rapturous ‘O Fortuna’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-ic-choir-enthrals-with-rapturous-o-fortuna/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 13:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-ic-choir-enthrals-with-rapturous-o-fortuna/</guid>
        <description>Carmina Burana is a piece almost every person recognises, if not in name then for the monumental ‘O Fortuna’, used countless times in popular culture. This could very well have been why the IC Choir chose to perform it in their Spring Concert, alongside Bob Chilcott’s ‘Songs and Cries of London …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Indian Queen — Purcell’s Final Flourish
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-the-indian-queen-purcells-final-flourish/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 13:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-the-indian-queen-purcells-final-flourish/</guid>
        <description>To call this production of The Indian Queen at the ENO Purcell’s opera might be seen as unfaithful to the extent to which Peter Sellars has reinvented the work. First performed in 1695 only a short walk away at Theatre Royal in Drury Lane, The Indian Queen was Henry Purcell’s final work, for he was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mark Rylance - Long Live The King
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-mark-rylance-long-live-the-king/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 13:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-mark-rylance-long-live-the-king/</guid>
        <description>It is easy to forget how magical London is at night but as I crossed Millenium Bridge to reach the Globe Theatre, perfectly perched on the riverside, this feeling rushed back to me. With St. Paul’s Cathedral illuminated behind, I was suspended in a state of wonderment as I entered the Sam Wanamaker …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Press Nights – The Absurdity Of It All
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-press-nights-the-absurdity-of-it-all/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 12:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-press-nights-the-absurdity-of-it-all/</guid>
        <description>One of the perks of writing for the Felix Arts section has of course got to be all of the free tickets we get: plays, exhibitions, opera, you name it (even puppetry…)! I still find it amazing to think that these art establishments actually somewhat value our work, even if it is just that free …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hitting The Right Notes: ICSO at Cadogan Hall
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-hitting-the-right-notes-icso-at-cadogan-hall/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 12:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-hitting-the-right-notes-icso-at-cadogan-hall/</guid>
        <description>Tonight was a first in two respects; not only was it my first time attending a concert in the gorgeous Cadogan Hall but it was also in fact the first ever time I had seen the Imperial College Symphony Orchestra (ICSO) perform. And so, as you can imagine I was suitably excited.
This was their Spring …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Favourite Album – The Shape of Jazz to Come
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-6-my-favourite-album-the-shape-of-jazz-to-come/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 13:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-6-my-favourite-album-the-shape-of-jazz-to-come/</guid>
        <description>1959, probably the most important year in the history of jazz, a turning point away from bebop and its roots in blues and dixieland, towards a new path for jazz: free jazz. In the same year Miles Davis released Kind of Blue and Dave Brubeck came out with Time Out, a lesser known artist called …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fireworks – A carnival of horror
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-3-fireworks-a-carnival-of-horror/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 14:11:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-3-fireworks-a-carnival-of-horror/</guid>
        <description>Death. Darkness. Claustrophobia. Darkness. Madness. Darkness. Dalia Taha’s new play Fireworks is not the celebration that the title suggests. Telling the story of two families battling for sanity in a besieged Palestine, Fireworks examines how children rationalise and interact with war and death, a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Could College pay for your next holiday?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-17-could-college-pay-for-your-next-holiday/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2015 19:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-17-could-college-pay-for-your-next-holiday/</guid>
        <description>How many people knew there was such a thing as the Imperial Exploration Board? Apparently not that many, as I found out when telling people that I had received their endorsement for a cycling expedition myself and a few friends are planning this summer across Central Asia. And so, I decided to talk …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Revealing the Costs of War
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-7-revealing-the-costs-of-war/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2015 19:23:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-7-revealing-the-costs-of-war/</guid>
        <description>The debut work of 31-year-old playwright Diana Nneka Atuona, _Liberian Girl _has already made an impact, performing at the Global Summit to End Sexual Violence in Conflict last year and winning Atuona the Alfred Fagon Award for Best New Play of the Year in 2013. So what is all the commotion about? …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dor Guez — A New Israeli History
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-7-dor-guez-a-new-israeli-history/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2015 19:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-7-dor-guez-a-new-israeli-history/</guid>
        <description>Dor Guez is a fascinating man. Born in Jerusalem to Christian Palestinian and Jewish Tunisian parents, he has been able to experience the Middle East with a truly unique eye, away from the prevailing Arab and Jewish Israeli narratives. Entitling this exhibition The Sick Man of Europe, Guez is making …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Viviane Sassen Like Never Before
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-7-viviane-sassen-like-never-before/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2015 19:12:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-7-viviane-sassen-like-never-before/</guid>
        <description>In my opinion, the ICA is simply not appreciated enough. It is on the front line of contemporary art and this means that, although all shows aren’t guaranteed to thrill (such is the risk of pushing boundaries!), you will have an exciting time no matter what — much better this than the rather …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>There’s More to Art than White Western Males
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-31-theres-more-to-art-than-white-western-males/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2015 19:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-31-theres-more-to-art-than-white-western-males/</guid>
        <description>Cyprien Tokoudagba is quite simply my favourite contemporary African artist yet hardly known outside a very small group of art consumers, left in the wake of the well established El Anatsui and Ablade Glover. Unlike the stereotypical loud, busy and somewhat overwhelming African art, Tokoudagba draws …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Revealing the Costs of War
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-31-revealing-the-costs-of-war/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2015 19:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-31-revealing-the-costs-of-war/</guid>
        <description>The debut work of 31-year-old playwright Diana Nneka Atuona, _Liberian Girl _has already made an impact, performing at the Global Summit to End Sexual Violence in Conflict last year and winning Atuona the Alfred Fagon Award for Best New Play of the Year in 2013. So what is all the commotion about? …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Tale of Two Halves from the RSC - Part I
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-21-a-tale-of-two-halves-from-the-rsc-part-i/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2015 20:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-21-a-tale-of-two-halves-from-the-rsc-part-i/</guid>
        <description>The Royal Shakespeare Company has shown once again that it defines how Shakespeare should be performed. Unusually at the Barbican as opposed to the Globe, the restraints of performing in the round were removed, opening up more options for staging and props. This allowed a realistic scene to be set, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Frieze - Where Art Goes to Die
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-18-frieze-where-art-goes-to-die/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 15:47:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-18-frieze-where-art-goes-to-die/</guid>
        <description>When men die, they enter into history. When statues die, they enter into art. This botany of death is what we call culture. These powerful opening lines from the 1953 film ‘_Les Statues Meurent Aussi_’ (‘_Statues Also Die_’) - originally made as a critique of the West’s consumerist attitude towards …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Helix: A Marriage of Design and Health
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-18-helix-a-marriage-of-design-and-health/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 15:44:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-18-helix-a-marriage-of-design-and-health/</guid>
        <description>This week, I had the opportunity to visit The HELIX Centre for Design in Healthcare, part of Imperial’s Institute of Global Health Innovation. Based at St. Mary&amp;rsquo;s Hospital in Paddington, the centre aims to provide solutions in healthcare through intelligent and low cost design. Formed less …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Contrasting Worlds - The 2014 Turner Prize
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-18-contrasting-worlds-the-2014-turner-prize/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 15:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-18-contrasting-worlds-the-2014-turner-prize/</guid>
        <description>Tate Britain’s two main shows may be similar in name but in reality are worlds apart. The first, an exhibition of J.M.W. Turner’s late works, is a life-affirming homage to one of Britain’s greatest painters and offers glimpses into the beginnings of modern art. The other, shamefully named after this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Art: The V&amp;A Ceramics Collection
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-18-my-art-the-va-ceramics-collection/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 15:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-18-my-art-the-va-ceramics-collection/</guid>
        <description>Tucked away on the sixth floor of the V&amp;amp;A, the ceramics section is my little artistic idyll in London. Even on weekends it is virtually empty, so you can sit back and enjoy the craftsmanship without the hassle you get with the better known art establishments. Huge glass cabinets filled to the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Foodie Insight #02: Why I’m Vegetarian
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-foodie-insight-02-why-im-vegetarian/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 20:34:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-foodie-insight-02-why-im-vegetarian/</guid>
        <description>As the joke goes: “How do you know if someone is vegan? Oh don’t worry, they’ll tell you”. A lot of people, including myself, are put off by these militant activists, encamped on their moral high ground looking disdainfully down at the rest of us.
In this article, I have instead tried to take a more …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Lunchtime Guide to Art
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-a-lunchtime-guide-to-art/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 12:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-a-lunchtime-guide-to-art/</guid>
        <description>Have you ever been left needing your art fix half way through a day of mindlessly dull lectures? Well look no further than this guide, my Lunchtime Guide to Art, which tells you about all the amazing galleries and museums that are on offer within a stone’s throw of Imperial’s South Kensington …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Glare - The Future of Opera Looks Bright
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-glare-the-future-of-opera-looks-bright/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 12:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-glare-the-future-of-opera-looks-bright/</guid>
        <description>A blinding light descends on the crowd, momentarily dazzling us. In that moment, the world of this production descends, transporting us into a dystopia, disconcertingly similar to our own, where nothing can be taken for granted.
Glare tells the story of Alex (Amar Muchhala) and his relationship with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Blood Swept Lands: Why do we remember war?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-blood-swept-lands-why-do-we-remember-war/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 20:54:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-blood-swept-lands-why-do-we-remember-war/</guid>
        <description>The UK has been blown over in support for Paul Cummin’s recent work at the Tower of London_ Blood Swept Lands and Seas of Red _to such an extent that the installation, which began being partly dismantled on Wednesday, was prolonged until the end of the month. Moreover, such was the public reaction …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wounded: Is This War’s True Legacy?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-wounded-is-this-wars-true-legacy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 20:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-wounded-is-this-wars-true-legacy/</guid>
        <description>I was a bit apprehensive of this new exhibition at Somerset House. I feared it might just be an attempt for Bryan Adams, the photographer, to try and reinvent himself, having been a washed up pop star for so long. Moreover, the advertising made it seem like just another one of those populist …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Arts Editorial - London: From Old to New
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-arts-editorial-london-from-old-to-new/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 21:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-arts-editorial-london-from-old-to-new/</guid>
        <description>This week feels like an homage to the greatness of London as a cultural centre. In what other city do you have such a wide variety of art on offer, whatever your taste? First of all, we have Dara’s My Art article, where she professes her undying love for the Barbican Centre, so often derided as a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Editorial – The Style Week
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-editorial-the-style-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 21:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-editorial-the-style-week/</guid>
        <description>Style. It’s different to fashion. Fashion suggests something fleeting, with trends that slip by like wind. Style, in contrast, is much more constant. It evokes a timeless ideal of chic-ness, a trend that will never go out of style; in other words, a classic.
This week’s issue is devoted to Style, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Scientific sound art at GV Art
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-scientific-sound-art-at-gv-art/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 04:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-scientific-sound-art-at-gv-art/</guid>
        <description>What: NOISE &amp;amp; Whispers Where: GV Art Gallery, W1 When: 8th Nov - 14th Dec 2013 Price: FREE
Mendel Kaelen received his BSc and MSc in neurological and behavioural sciences at the State University of Gronigen, and is now doing a PhD at Imperial College. He also works as a sound artist and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Murder, poverty, passion, rage
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-murder-poverty-passion-rage/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 22:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-murder-poverty-passion-rage/</guid>
        <description>What: Woyzeck Where: Omnibus Clapham, SW4 When: 19th Nov to 7th Dec 2013 Price: £15, concessions £12
Through an ominous mist and a haunting cello note, I enter the theatre. Two figures sit there, hacking away at timber, as I cross the woodchip floor to my seat. This is just how Georg Büchner’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>British Museum strikes gold with Beyond El Dorado
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-british-museum-strikes-gold-with-beyond-el-dorado/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 09:44:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-british-museum-strikes-gold-with-beyond-el-dorado/</guid>
        <description>High in the Andean jungle, to the sound of drums, flutes and trumpets, ‘El Dorado’, the golden one, the future king of the Muisca tribe, prepares to dive into sacred Lake Guatavita. Covered from head to toe in gold dust, he tosses emeralds into the water below as an offering to the ethereal spirits …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>1:54 - African Art
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-154-african-art/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 09:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-154-african-art/</guid>
        <description>I love contemporary African art. Raw talent exists throughout the continent of colour and exuberance, but a pitiful lack of funding leaves the majority of it undiscovered. However, with its newly burgeoning economies, a tidal wave of new and exciting art from the continent is about to hit us, with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>More Than A Hipster Art Safari
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-more-than-a-hipster-art-safari/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 00:26:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-more-than-a-hipster-art-safari/</guid>
        <description>The Frieze Art Fair, now in its 11th year, is one of the world’s leading contemporary art fairs, and has helped shape London into a nucleus of creativity and vision.
This year, 152 galleries were invited to assemble in one space in Regent’s park, and display the best of what they could offer. And …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
