<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/business/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Last orders as craft beer steals market share
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-last-orders-as-craft-beer-steals-market-share/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 11:15:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alastair Heffernan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-last-orders-as-craft-beer-steals-market-share/</guid>
        <description>In the UK back in 2006 the majority of pubs served mostly identical lagers on keg; variety was achieved by a changing assortment of warm cask ales that often left younger drinkers wanting. In the US, the situation was similar; bars served a narrow range of indistinguishable beers: Bud Light, Coors …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Old dog, new tricks?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-16-old-dog-new-tricks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 14:56:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alastair Heffernan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-16-old-dog-new-tricks/</guid>
        <description>Back in June, Twitter CEO Dick Costolo (@dickc) tweeted: “Welcome back, @jack !!”. He was referring to Jack Dorsey, one of the co-founders of Twitter. This enigmatic tweet, short even by Twitter standards, signalled to those in the know that Dick Costolo had stepped down as CEO of the micro-blogging …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Become a property owner in London
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-become-a-property-owner-in-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 21:48:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Tsim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-become-a-property-owner-in-london/</guid>
        <description>Imperial houses some of the wealthiest students in the UK. At Imperial, students are only able to live in college provided student accommodation for their first year, before moving out with friends or becoming a hall senior. As SW7 is the most expensive postcode in the UK, rent in the neighbourhood …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What happens at uni...stays at Unii.com
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-what-happens-at-unistays-at-uniicom/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 15:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Business,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-what-happens-at-unistays-at-uniicom/</guid>
        <description>In 2011, Marco Nardone graduated with a degree in Physics from Imperial College. In just two years, the 25-year-old has become CEO &amp;amp; founder of the UK’s biggest student-only social networking platform, Unii.com.
The journey to becoming a social networking entrepreneur has been exciting, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Shell Ideas360 comes to students!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-shell-ideas360-comes-to-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 10:36:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Tsim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-shell-ideas360-comes-to-students/</guid>
        <description>Shell Ideas360
Shell Ideas360 is an international competition open to all students which aims to produce the leading ideas to tackle the global energy, food and water issues of today. Students are invited to develop game changing ideas with an emphasis on innovative ideas which can be implemented to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Interested in enterprise?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-11-interested-in-enterprise/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 23:08:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-11-interested-in-enterprise/</guid>
        <description>Imagine you are not at Imperial. You have never heard of Felix and you are not sitting here reading this article. What a dream. No dull lectures, ridiculously difficult coursework, or seemingly un-passable exams. But imagine that it wasn’t out of choice – imagine you never obtained the opportunity …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Axe VAT for the hospitality industry
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-axe-vat-for-the-hospitality-industry/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 00:25:24 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Tsim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-axe-vat-for-the-hospitality-industry/</guid>
        <description>How can reducing VAT help the economy?
With high unemployment levels and increasing difficulty in finding jobs, the job market in the UK along with the economy needs boosting. One method suggested by the VAT club founded by Jacques Borel is that a reduction in VAT would increase sales and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Student Finance
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-student-finance/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 13:35:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Tsim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-student-finance/</guid>
        <description> Hopefully anyone who is eligible has already applied for Student Finance England. SFE offers student loans and grants which help cover university fees and living costs. Imperial College London also offers bursaries/scholarships which can be applied for.
Why open a student account? With the start of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stop talking, start interviewing
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-29-stop-talking-start-interviewing/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 14:34:24 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ananya Das,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-29-stop-talking-start-interviewing/</guid>
        <description>Ananya Das: You have a fantastic entrepreneurial career, have there been moments when you needed ‘A Kick in the Pants’ similar to in Stop Talking, Start Doing? If so, who or what did you turn to for a bit of encouragement or motivation?
Sháá Wasmund: Being constantly motivated to work hard is one of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Facebook celebrity? Looking for a job?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-facebook-celebrity-looking-for-a-job/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 00:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Business,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-facebook-celebrity-looking-for-a-job/</guid>
        <description>The eternal procrastinating tool… Facebook. Or is it? Adzuna, a social job search engine, has developed a way to help you get hired with a little help from your friends. Launched out of a central London pub in July 2011, this small London startup, with over 1.5 million monthly visitors, classifies …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Next Adventure: The Start-up Life
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-the-next-adventure-the-start-up-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 21:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Business,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-the-next-adventure-the-start-up-life/</guid>
        <description>The Next Adventure: Why The Start-Up Life Might Be For You.
It’s a strange thing, the transition from university to the world beyond. For people used to setting their own schedules, to blazing a bit of a trail, to grabbing the talented people around them to embark on a creative project, it can feel …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Gate to an Imperial success story
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-21-the-gate-to-an-imperial-success-story/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 13:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Business,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-21-the-gate-to-an-imperial-success-story/</guid>
        <description>Exams… Library, presentations… Library, coursework&amp;hellip; Library. Being an Imperial College student is usually associated with the “nerdiness” stigma. If you weren’t already one when you got in, the general idea is that by the time you leave, you will have become a super studying sleepless monkey. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Finding your way around the Valley
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-finding-your-way-around-the-valley/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 23:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Business,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-finding-your-way-around-the-valley/</guid>
        <description>When it comes to the crunch explaining what ‘Silicon Valley’ actually represents – ask yourself – do you really have a clear understanding? For most of us, I suppose the influence from popular social media tools and cool high tech gadgets will probably relate us to multinational corporations like …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Identify your Dream Team!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-identify-your-dream-team/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 23:53:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nitin B Nihalani,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-identify-your-dream-team/</guid>
        <description>I’m sure you’ve all heard the phrase ‘two heads are better than one’. Seems pretty obvious, right? By this logic, it follows that three heads are better than two, four better than three and so on. Unfortunately, when it comes to startups, the equation is not quite so simple. Finding the right team …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students&#39; Projects given Chance to Shine
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-students-projects-given-chance-to-shine/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 02:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Giridhar Kesavan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-students-projects-given-chance-to-shine/</guid>
        <description>Think social responsibility and you don’t normally think of banks. Discovering social enterprise, learning business skills, pitching for sponsorship and inspiring volunteering were just some of the themes explored in theImperial College Finance Society (ICFS) led Corporate Citizenship conference on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>From Fine Art to the App Store
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-from-fine-art-to-the-app-store/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 02:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ausrine Kersanskaite,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-from-fine-art-to-the-app-store/</guid>
        <description>Just a short while ago, I was a Fine Art graduate slowly coming to realisation that conceptual art &amp;amp; me is not a good match. Back then, looking for a ‘real’ job, I accidentally stumbled across Songkick and got to be one of the lucky ones to become their intern. Starting out as a Data Warrior …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Getting in with the Crowd
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-getting-in-with-the-crowd/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 01:54:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Taylor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-getting-in-with-the-crowd/</guid>
        <description>Start-ups have to raise money, whatever the business there will be a need at some point. The biggest issue for most ishow.
Traditional options are Business Angels – wealthy individuals who provide capital and advice in return for equity, and venture capitalists who generally provide higher sums of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hackers Unite!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-hackers-unite/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 23:11:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sam Wong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-hackers-unite/</guid>
        <description>ackathons are magical. Hackathons are non-compulsory, unpaid, but last long enough to warrant overtime pay and a day off in a normal corporate environment. Yet somehow participants are highly engaged, and manage to produce creative solutions in a much tighter timeframe. Why do Hackathons work? What …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get up and Chase the Dream!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-get-up-and-chase-the-dream/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 22:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Annabelle Mayers,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-get-up-and-chase-the-dream/</guid>
        <description> For some, overcoming endless hurdles is a memory they wish to leave behind with school PE lessons. For others the uncertainty, challenge and commitment involved in developing a start-up is what provides the buzz that gets them out of bed each morning.
Motivations: There are a multitude of reasons …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Calling all Entrepreneurs!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-calling-all-entrepreneurs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 12:53:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pranav Tulsian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-calling-all-entrepreneurs/</guid>
        <description>Ever wondered what it would be like to own a billion dollar company? Ever debated the pros and cons of starting a business over a career? Ever wondered if you can start your own business? Ever thought about starting your own business but don’t know how? Silicon Valley Comes to Imperial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Entrepreneurs ‘hail’ new app
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-entrepreneurs-hail-new-app/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 02:13:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Business,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-entrepreneurs-hail-new-app/</guid>
        <description>Last Monday, Imperial Entrepreneurs invited the people behind Hailo –The Black Cab App, to its weekly event, Startup Mondays. Russell Hall, one of the co-founders of Hailo spoke to us about their success story and what makes Hailo so popular, to a point that even celebrities and serial entrepreneurs …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Shacking up with Business
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-shacking-up-with-business/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 02:09:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Deepka Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-shacking-up-with-business/</guid>
        <description>We all know that estate agents and landlords aren’t exactly a student’s best friend, and many of us have personally fallen victim of pushy sales tactics, resulting in a less than ideal but extortionately expensive student flat. Such experiences prompted Ben, a final year student at Bournemouth …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Silicon Valley, South Ken
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-silicon-valley-south-ken/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:12:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Serge Vasylechko,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-silicon-valley-south-ken/</guid>
        <description>Two weeks ago Imperial saw the launch ICStartup - an initiative that aims to inspire a new generation of student entrepreneurs. It will act as a central hub for entrepreneurial news and events around college, connecting an otherwise disparate and rich ecosystem of societies and organizations that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Good service vs. good marketing
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-good-service-vs-good-marketing/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 20:40:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximo Sanz Hernandez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-good-service-vs-good-marketing/</guid>
        <description>What should you do if you stumble upon a great idea for a product with high demand in a certain market segment? Many first-time entrepreneurs have found themselves in this situation before, and most of them do not manage to turn their idea into a successful business. While there are many things that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Productivity solutions
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-productivity-solutions/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 20:38:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Business,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-productivity-solutions/</guid>
        <description>Personally, I do not think that procrastination is entirely bad. While we delay the work, we may find out a shortcut or a better way to finish the work in short time. As Aaron Burr wisely said, “Never do today what you can do tomorrow. Something may occur to make you regret your premature action.” …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to stop wasting time
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-how-to-stop-wasting-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 12:39:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Deepka Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-how-to-stop-wasting-time/</guid>
        <description>This week I met Dr. Magdalena Bak-Maier, a personal development and learning expert, executive coach to top level scientists and entrepreneurs, and author of Get Productive. The premise of the book is simple: instead of feeling overwhelmed by having too much to do, you can learn how to use your …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are you a Student Upstart?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-are-you-a-student-upstart/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 19:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paolo Strampelli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-are-you-a-student-upstart/</guid>
        <description>What do Steve Jobs, Bill Gates and Mark Zuckerberg have in common with each other? Apart from being incredibly successful businessmen, all began their companies during the period that they should have been in college - and all dropped out to do so. Indeed, a look through more recent history gives …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Graduates from the University of SIFE
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-graduates-from-the-university-of-sife/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 19:46:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xiao Chi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-graduates-from-the-university-of-sife/</guid>
        <description>The Insight Into Business Program (IIB) works closely with secondary schools throughout London to improve the financial literacy and business acumen of young students today.
High unemployment rates amongst young people today is a continuing problem within the UK. With the high costs of college …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Spilling all the beans
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-spilling-all-the-beans/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 19:41:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-spilling-all-the-beans/</guid>
        <description>I’m sat on a couch at The Beans Group head office, waiting to interview its founder, James Eder. I’ve been there only a matter of seconds and I’m already finding myself forced to adjust my expectations. The mental images evoked by the word ‘office’ certainly weren’t matching the scenes before my …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College Hackathon launched
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-imperial-college-hackathon-launched/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 21:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sangjin Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-imperial-college-hackathon-launched/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College has one of the best Computing and Electrical Engineering Departments in the World, producing the most disciplined and talented software developers and programmers consistently. These programmers often benefit from high salaries and fabulous perquisites from their employers. Imperial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>More Airports for the UK?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-more-airports-for-the-uk/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 20:52:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>George Howard,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-more-airports-for-the-uk/</guid>
        <description>Ever since its conception, the future expansion of Heathrow airport has been the topic of discussion of many a government. Generations of our ‘representatives’ have used the topic to their political gain, including the current coalition, who opposed the famous 3rd runway to help them garner support …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stay ahead of the game with Traderversity
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-stay-ahead-of-the-game-with-traderversity/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 22:46:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Craig Glastonbury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-stay-ahead-of-the-game-with-traderversity/</guid>
        <description>Traderversity is an exciting new, free, virtual trading game designed exclusively for UK university students. The interactive online game at www.traderversity.com lets students try their hand at trading with real-time access to the stock market without investing any real money. Creating healthy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Putting a Katz amongst the pigeons
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-putting-a-katz-amongst-the-pigeons/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 22:43:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Deepka Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-putting-a-katz-amongst-the-pigeons/</guid>
        <description>Jason Katz, a renowned investment banker who turned his hand to private equity, visited Imperial College to share his knowledge and advice in an event organised by the Imperial Speaker’s Club and the Imperial Investment Club.
Katz, clad in casual business attire, began to address the audience in his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reporting Science in Financial Times
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-reporting-science-in-financial-times/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 22:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nina Kearsey,Be?at Gurrutxaga-Lerma,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-reporting-science-in-financial-times/</guid>
        <description>To begin, as interviews commonly do, with some scene-setting by way of a weather report, it was a cold albeit sunny morning (one of those ironies so common to the English winter) when we met with the Financial Times’ Clive Cookson to talk science and business. Both a scientist and journalist by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Apprentice Challenge 2012
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-apprentice-challenge-2012/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 19:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Annabelle Mayers,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-apprentice-challenge-2012/</guid>
        <description>Whilst many students were having a lie-in on Saturday 21 January, the 16 students selected to participate in the 2012 Imperial Apprentice Challenge arrived at the Business School, complete with suits, laptops, and determination, ready to conquer the challenges organised by the Imperial Entrepreneurs …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A not so happy birthday
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-a-not-so-happy-birthday/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 19:52:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rajvinder Virdee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-a-not-so-happy-birthday/</guid>
        <description>On January 1, 2012, a major economic milestone was reached: the Euro’s 10th birthday. Although the Euro had officially been in existence since 1995 and was introduced into financial markets in 1999, it wasn’t until 2002 that notes and coins were issued in circulation. The Euro is an important …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bankruptcy... A Kodak Moment?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-bankruptcy-a-kodak-moment/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 21:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paolo Strampelli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-bankruptcy-a-kodak-moment/</guid>
        <description>Filing for bankruptcy… a Kodak moment” joked someone in an elevator at one of Goldman Sachs offices, according to the twitter account @GSElevator. On Thursday 19 January, (ex) photographic giant Eastman Kodak Co. filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy. Low on cash, unable to effectively sell its assets, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Democracy and capitalism: an unhappy marriage?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-democracy-and-capitalism-an-unhappy-marriage/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 20:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Zuehlsdorff,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-democracy-and-capitalism-an-unhappy-marriage/</guid>
        <description>When Lehman Brothers filed for bankruptcy on 15 September 2008, it marked the most dramatic collapse of an U.S. firm in history. In many ways, the name of the once fourth biggest investment bank in the United States has become a synonym for the global financial meltdown that shook the world in 2008 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brand Identity
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-brand-identity/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 19:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandru Podgurschi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-brand-identity/</guid>
        <description>Bloomberg BusinessWeek recently published an article by Larry Popelka titled “The Key to Success? Your Corporate Mission.” It investigates the particular case of the Chevrolet Volt and it is perfectly summed up by one line: “Most consumers no longer shop for products. They shop for a company.” What …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>About turns on the road to academia
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-about-turns-on-the-road-to-academia/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 19:47:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Be?at Gurrutxaga-Lerma,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-about-turns-on-the-road-to-academia/</guid>
        <description>In the age of privilege, when very few attended and graduated from university, achieving the degree of Doctor was a rare feat even amongst the educated. Doctors were revered in many of the royal courts of Europe and granted privileges reserved only to the highest peers of the realm: in Spain, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The UK should adopt the Euro
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-the-uk-should-adopt-the-euro/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 20:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Business,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-the-uk-should-adopt-the-euro/</guid>
        <description>In last Wednesday’s Autumn Statement, George Osborne confirmed that the UK economy’s health was far worse than his office had expected. He blamed the ongoing Eurozone crisis of negatively affecting the UK’s economic growth, by pointing out the negative impact the former had had in our country’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why is the UK economy sinking, too?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-why-is-the-uk-economy-sinking-too/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 20:47:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Business,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-why-is-the-uk-economy-sinking-too/</guid>
        <description>The Eurozone crisis has all the traits of a perfect story: a choral drama with a fuzzy and mistrusted antihero, pompous and obscure villains, few and powerless heroes, and many victims; the plot is so twisted that its outcome remains as mysterious as exciting, and its consequences so open to chance …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are you a Gangster?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-are-you-a-gangster/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 20:32:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Serge Vasylechko,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-are-you-a-gangster/</guid>
        <description>Walking up towards the exit from the SAF lecture theatre I saw two people approach me who asked that exact question. “Are you a gangster?” Unsurprisingly, it made a few other people turn their heads around in wonder, as they were also leaving the lecture hall after a presentation on social economy. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Paper days are over
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-the-paper-days-are-over/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 20:03:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marie-Laure Hicks,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-the-paper-days-are-over/</guid>
        <description>Take the tube and read a newspaper. Most people there are doing the same, but their number is in rapid decline. Between 2007 and 2009, newspaper circulation dropped by 25% in the UK. Only the US saw a heavier decline. This $50bn business, employing 400,000 people in the US alone, is in trouble. In …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Autumn harvest?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-autumn-harvest/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 19:49:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rajvinder Virdee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-autumn-harvest/</guid>
        <description>On Tuesday, George Osborne, Chancellor of the Exchequer, updated Parliament on the current economic situation of our nation, and what the government plans to do about it. The Autumn Statement is seen as an important event in government, as it offers an opportunity to reflect on pledges made in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Western tragedy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-a-western-tragedy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 19:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Business,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-a-western-tragedy/</guid>
        <description>As a result of the so-called “Euro debt crisis” – whose solution seems to be too distant still to be clear – several of the euro club countries have been bailed out. Starting with Greece (2009), Ireland (2010) and Portugal (2010) have also been rescued, and in all the cases, the process followed a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Silicon Valley comes to Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-silicon-valley-comes-to-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 20:24:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nitin B Nihalani,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-silicon-valley-comes-to-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College has joined the elite list of universities participating in ‘Silicon Valley comes to the UK’ (SVC2UK), an annual event that brings successful Silicon Valley entrepreneurs to inspire students across the UK. Silicon Valley comes to Imperial (SVC2I), hosted by Imperial Entrepreneurs and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Virgin of the Rock*
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-the-virgin-of-the-rock/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 20:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rajvinder Virdee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-the-virgin-of-the-rock/</guid>
        <description>Last Thursday the Government announced that Northern Rock was to be bought by Virgin Money. Northern Rock was famously nationalised in February 2008 as the Credit Crunch took its first victim this side of the Atlantic. The deal that has just been negotiated says that Virgin will pay £747m upfront …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Thomas Young’s Entrepreneurial Endeavours
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-thomas-youngs-entrepreneurial-endeavours/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 21:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-thomas-youngs-entrepreneurial-endeavours/</guid>
        <description>It was perhaps due to the imperfect knowledge or absolute ignorance humankind had back then that true polymaths could still exist; nowadays, in the age of specialization, it seems almost impossible. But back in the old days, the same person, if gifted and lucky enough, could undertake forefront …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Groupon: Is the social buying giant losing fuel?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-groupon-is-the-social-buying-giant-losing-fuel/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 20:58:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-groupon-is-the-social-buying-giant-losing-fuel/</guid>
        <description>If you have found time to follow the news in between episodes of Made in Chelsea and The X Factor, then you will be aware that Groupon, considered the fastest growing company ever, has recently been valued at $12.7bn. The company’s rapid global expansion and large valuation (the highest since Google …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Business of British Biotechnology
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-the-business-of-british-biotechnology/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 21:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Motraghi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-the-business-of-british-biotechnology/</guid>
        <description>Alongside finance and high-tech computing, biotechnology can be thought of as one of the few sectors where Britain is still globally competitive. The British pharmaceutical industry, for example, receives 10% of global research and development funding, despite having only 3% of global sales. But …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The End of the Big Four?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-the-end-of-the-big-four/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 21:22:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rajvinder Virdee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-the-end-of-the-big-four/</guid>
        <description>PwC, Deloitte, KPMG and Ernst and Young – better known collectively as the Big Four. The word ‘Big’ really doesn’t do them justice; enormous, gigantic and colossal are more appropriate adjectives. It’s hard to get a grasp of how big they are compared to other accountancy firms until you look at the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Every man a king!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-every-man-a-king/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 21:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-every-man-a-king/</guid>
        <description>DISCLAIMER: These opinions are ficticious and form part of a celebration of Felix&amp;rsquo;s 1500th issue. Any resemblance to real opinions, living or dead, is purely coincidental.
Dear middle class voter, my words are addressed to you, dear friends:
Two hundred and thirty-five years ago, when our …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Comrades, unite!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-comrades-unite/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 21:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-comrades-unite/</guid>
        <description>DISCLAIMER: These opinions are ficticious and form part of a celebration of Felix&amp;rsquo;s 1500th issue. Any resemblance to real opinions, living or dead, is purely coincidental.
When German foreign minister Guido Westerwelle accused recipients of welfare of living in ‘late roman decadence’ and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Give me Liberty, or give me Death!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-give-me-liberty-or-give-me-death/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 21:05:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-give-me-liberty-or-give-me-death/</guid>
        <description>DISCLAIMER: These opinions are ficticious and form part of a celebration of Felix&amp;rsquo;s 1500th issue. Any resemblance to real opinions, living or dead, is purely coincidental.
When the US democracy was in its teens, a frenchman, Alexis de Tocqueville (1805-1859) visited the country. He had been …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You there, make way for liberty!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-you-there-make-way-for-liberty/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 21:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-you-there-make-way-for-liberty/</guid>
        <description>DISCLAIMER: These opinions are ficticious and form part of a celebration of Felix&amp;rsquo;s 1500th issue. Any resemblance to real opinions, living or dead, is purely coincidental.
This weekend Manhattan saw the earliest snowfall since the American Civil War. It fell on the Jack-o’-lanterns left …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fight for Freedom!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-fight-for-freedom/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 21:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-fight-for-freedom/</guid>
        <description>DISCLAIMER: These opinions are ficticious and form part of a celebration of Felix&amp;rsquo;s 1500th issue. Any resemblance to real opinions, living or dead, is purely coincidental.
The welfare state: we are told it exists to create equality in the country, to make it a fairer country. This is a lie! …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BlackBerry’s Outage and its Aftermath
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-blackberrys-outage-and-its-aftermath/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 22:40:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximo Sanz Hernandez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-blackberrys-outage-and-its-aftermath/</guid>
        <description>During the evening of Monday October 10 you were possibly one of the frustrated Imperial students that couldn’t get their BBM working. That was the day on which all BlackBerry devices lost their email and BlackBerry Messenger services. Some devices lost internet access as well, leaving many …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Business in History
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-business-in-history/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 22:29:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Be?at Gurrutxaga-Lerma,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-business-in-history/</guid>
        <description>Be it for ignorance, insecurity or psychological compulsion, micromanagement is an ancient curse no business or institution is safe from, and whose risks and consequences can only increase the higher the micromanager’s influence reaches. Though a well-known managerial style – at least known well …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Apple’s iPhone stands in the current market, or: ‘How we Apples swim’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-how-apples-iphone-stands-in-the-current-market-or-how-we-apples-swim/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 22:19:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shiang Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-how-apples-iphone-stands-in-the-current-market-or-how-we-apples-swim/</guid>
        <description>Just before the BlackBerry service collapse on October 10, the analyst firm Enterprise Management Associates conducted extensive research regarding the trend in enterprise mobile device management. This research concluded that more than 30% of BlackBerry users from within large enterprises are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Founder Stories: Storify and MinuteBox
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-founder-stories-storify-and-minutebox/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 22:52:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-founder-stories-storify-and-minutebox/</guid>
        <description>Last Friday, as part of the Imperial Entrepreneurs speaker series programme, the founders of Storify, Xavier Damman, and MinuteBox, Josh Liu, came to the Imperial Business School.
The evening kicked off with a presentation from Imperial Entrepreneurs about what they do and the set of events planned …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Economy in History
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-the-economy-in-history/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 22:46:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-the-economy-in-history/</guid>
        <description>Legend has it that, as for all faithful Muslims, the day came when the good King Musa of Mali announced to his people that he would be leaving Mali for the Hajj, the pilgrimage to Mecca. The announcement, though praised by the wise and respected by all his subjects, came with fear, as the trip from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The launch of the QE2
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-the-launch-of-the-qe2/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 22:42:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shiang Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-the-launch-of-the-qe2/</guid>
        <description>If central banks could instigate growth by simply printing more money, they would have done so a long time ago. A recent Bank of England (BoE) research report attests to the theory that cash injections are inflationary: while the Quantitative Easing (QE) package of £200bn had an initial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>QE, or not QE, that is the question
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-qe-or-not-qe-that-is-the-question/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 22:35:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-qe-or-not-qe-that-is-the-question/</guid>
        <description>There was a global economic meltdown in 2008. World governments have since spent their time running through plans A-Z to try and reboot economies, but so far any recovery has been wiped out by other problems such as the crisis in the Eurozone. The problem of what to do with the levels of debt has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Buffer – Because you want to tweet better
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-buffer-because-you-want-to-tweet-better/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 20:28:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Afonso Campos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-buffer-because-you-want-to-tweet-better/</guid>
        <description>The proliferation of Twitter is ubiquitous to say the least and despite the service being almost universally loved by its users, annoying your followers with a barrage of tweets is not a gargantuan task to accomplish. Enter Buffer.
Buffer is a simple, yet highly effective web application that lets …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A new tech bubble
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-a-new-tech-bubble/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 20:17:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandru Podgurschi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-a-new-tech-bubble/</guid>
        <description>You might have still been running around your primary school grounds in the late 1990s, but the Internet was about to witness its largest market revolution. While Silicon Valley has seen its fair share of bubbles over the last decade, the dot-com bubble that marked the turn of the century was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Writing a business plan
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-writing-a-business-plan/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 19:12:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paolo Strampelli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-writing-a-business-plan/</guid>
        <description>If you are a young, aspiring entrepreneur, with an idea that will earn you millions (or at least enough money to pay for drinks on a night out), you are likely to eventually receive a speech from an older, more experienced entrepreneur on the importance of writing a business plan. A business plan …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Niche marketing on the net
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-niche-marketing-on-the-net/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 19:22:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nitin B Nihalani,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-niche-marketing-on-the-net/</guid>
        <description>These days it is quite difficult to find something in common with everyone in the world, apart from being human, but there is one thing that comes close: Internet users. There are about 2 billion of them according to internetworldstats.com. From a business point of view, this is the biggest market …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial students victorious in enterprise competition
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-imperial-students-victorious-in-enterprise-competition/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 19:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandru Podgurschi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-imperial-students-victorious-in-enterprise-competition/</guid>
        <description>On Monday February 21st, three teams representing Imperial College London, King’s College London and UCL competed in the London Apprentice 2011 in the first year of the event. Proudly organized by Imperial Entrepreneurs, the KCL Business Club and the UCL Entrepreneurs Society, the competition was a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FIG grows by finding eleven more businesses to invest in
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-fig-grows-by-finding-eleven-more-businesses-to-invest-in/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 20:36:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sina Ataherian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-fig-grows-by-finding-eleven-more-businesses-to-invest-in/</guid>
        <description>Read part one
In 2009, James King founded Find Invest Grow (FIG). FIG is a young company that funds and supports promising enterprises started-up by university students, including from Imperial College. James currently serves as its CEO. The firm is involved with fifteen different student-led …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The economy and small businesses
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-the-economy-and-small-businesses/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 05:51:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sina Ataherian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-the-economy-and-small-businesses/</guid>
        <description>The third business in our week on start-ups is Find Investment Grow (FIG). James King, its founder and CEO, gave his first Felix interview in October 2009, when he had just started his student-focused venture capital firm. In the year and a half since, his family of start-up businesses has grown …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The business of hair styling
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-the-business-of-hair-styling/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 20:49:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Afonso Campos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-the-business-of-hair-styling/</guid>
        <description>I meet Drew Foster at his brand new hair salon in the heart of Shoreditch early one morning. I am there as he opens up shop. There is a familiar atmosphere to the place, not unlike that of a mid to late sixties music video awash with distant pastel colours. Hues of green, pink and blue are adorned …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Draw yourself a new path
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-draw-yourself-a-new-path/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 20:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Afonso Campos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-draw-yourself-a-new-path/</guid>
        <description>You may not yet have heard of PathMotion – a rather unorthodox, yet compelling new careers website with a lot of potential; the brainchild of entrepreneur David Rivel.
I sat with him at a London diner to hear his story. His enthusiasm is not only breathtaking, but also contagious. There is no …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How they started up: introducing a week of interviews with real entrepreneurs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-how-they-started-up-introducing-a-week-of-interviews-with-real-entrepreneurs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 19:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sina Ataherian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-how-they-started-up-introducing-a-week-of-interviews-with-real-entrepreneurs/</guid>
        <description>Throughout the year, largely due to reader interest, the business section has a strong emphasis on finance. This fits with many Imperial students’ desire to learn more about the industry, in order to stay informed and help with their career choices. This being an undergraduate newspaper, this seems …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lehman loses law suit in US against Barclays
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-lehman-loses-law-suit-in-us-against-barclays/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 19:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sina Ataherian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-lehman-loses-law-suit-in-us-against-barclays/</guid>
        <description>The estate of Lehman Brothers lost a law suit on Wednesday against Barclays over the sale of its investment banking and brokerage businesses to Barclays. The sale was made in September 2008 in the same week that Lehman filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy. The company received $1.85 billion and was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Will the BoE raise its rates?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-will-the-boe-raise-its-rates/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 19:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sina Ataherian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-will-the-boe-raise-its-rates/</guid>
        <description>A mid growing concern over the Bank of England’s focus on and commitment to keeping its inflation targets, one more committee member joined calls to raise interest rates. According to minutes from the latest monetary policy meeting, three members now find “the case for removing some monetary …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The New Worlds Conference
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-the-new-worlds-conference/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 19:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marco Aliprandi,Henri Sartorius,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-the-new-worlds-conference/</guid>
        <description>On Saturday 5th February, the Imperial College Finance Society organised a landmark event – the first financial conference in its history. The aim of this conference was to present students with the opportunity to listen to experienced industry professionals about issues that have concerned the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is Microsoft a dying firm?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-is-microsoft-a-dying-firm/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 20:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rudolf Lai,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-is-microsoft-a-dying-firm/</guid>
        <description>Ten years ago, Microsoft’s products were synonymous with personal computing. The Internet was just stepping into households; Apple narrowly escaped bankruptcy, and its computers were seen as luxurious goods made for designers. In a blink of an eye, Apple became the largest technology company in US …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>iConnect: Eat for cheap!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-iconnect-eat-for-cheap/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 20:38:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Roland Sookias,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-iconnect-eat-for-cheap/</guid>
        <description>So what is ‘iConnect’?
iConnect is a project started by the Innovation Society. It was initially started as an online marketplace but now we’re launching the “Big Plan” – Group Buying for Imperial College at iConnectImperial.com. The idea is simple: if there are enough people willing to purchase the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The brand spanking new Bloomberg Assessment Test
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-the-brand-spanking-new-bloomberg-assessment-test/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 20:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucie Jichova,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-the-brand-spanking-new-bloomberg-assessment-test/</guid>
        <description>The other day, you might have received an email from the Careers Advisory Service informing you that Imperial is one of the lucky universities selected to test-drive a new Bloomberg Assessment Test (BAT) for free. “Hurry now! In the future, there will be a fee for taking this test,” it said. First …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A look into the Bank of England’s monetary policy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-a-look-into-the-bank-of-englands-monetary-policy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 19:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shiang Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-a-look-into-the-bank-of-englands-monetary-policy/</guid>
        <description>The Bank of England (BoE) has kept rates at record lows of half a per cent for almost two years. Its ‘quantitative easing’ has purchased assets totaling £200 billion in the last eighteen months. Interest in this extremely loose monetary policy sparked recently when the latest UK Consumer Price Index …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bank bonuses again rile politicians
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-bank-bonuses-again-rile-politicians/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 20:28:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-bank-bonuses-again-rile-politicians/</guid>
        <description>Business theorist Frederick Winslow Taylor believed that performance related pay was the way to encourage production and efficiency. Investment Banks have been paying bonuses on Wall Street and the Wharf for decades.
Investment Banks are split into various departments: back, middle and front office. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Municipal bonds: The latest bubble?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-municipal-bonds-the-latest-bubble/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 20:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lingxi Huang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-municipal-bonds-the-latest-bubble/</guid>
        <description>As the sovereign default crisis in Europe continues to send tremors through the global financial system, the next perfect storm in the market may already be brewing on the other side of the Atlantic. Meredith Whitney, whose fame is attributed to her accurate predictions of the 2008 subprime mortgage …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Finance Society hosts first-of-a-kind trading game
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-finance-society-hosts-first-of-a-kind-trading-game/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 19:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Afonso Campos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-finance-society-hosts-first-of-a-kind-trading-game/</guid>
        <description>On the 29th of November, teams from several universities from all over the UK competed in a never before seen trading simulation. The trading game held at Imperial was part of the national UK Investment Banking Series, a competition initiated in 2010 by the Imperial College Finance Society (ICFS) …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Books for intellectual City type sellouts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-books-for-intellectual-city-type-sellouts/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 19:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-books-for-intellectual-city-type-sellouts/</guid>
        <description>The only function of economic forecasting is to make astrology look respectable” said Ezra Solomon. For more funny lines from ivory tower economists, the fantastic ‘Freakonomics’ and ‘Superfreakonomics’ books by Steven Levitt and Stephen Dubner (both £5.30 from Amazon, £7,99 for kindle) show the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A focus on: Basics of Islamic Finance
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-a-focus-on-basics-of-islamic-finance/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 19:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Afonso Campos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-a-focus-on-basics-of-islamic-finance/</guid>
        <description>So, what is Islamic Finance, really? Give me the basics.
To put it relatively simply, Islamic Finance is an alternative way of going about financial dealings; these are conducted in such a way that they comply fully with the religious requirements of Islam. It is generally fully governed by and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s the Future for BP?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-whats-the-future-for-bp/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 21:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Betts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-whats-the-future-for-bp/</guid>
        <description>Why is BP a good choice for graduates?
Emma: We are interested in having a long term relationship with Imperial graduates as many of them have a desire to use their degree, and given Imperial’s focus on high quality engineering and science it is an extremely good match for us as an organisation. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rifts reappear less than a fortnight after G-20 pact
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-rifts-reappear-less-than-a-fortnight-after-g-20-pact/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2010 20:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lingxi Huang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-rifts-reappear-less-than-a-fortnight-after-g-20-pact/</guid>
        <description>After meeting in Seoul two weeks ago, governments from the G-20 group of the world’s 19 largest economies plus the EU agreed to halt competitive currency devaluation in hopes of allaying fears of an all-out currency war. The G-20 finance ministers vowed to address tensions in the currency markets. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial needs to start raising serious money
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-imperial-needs-to-start-raising-serious-money/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 21:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Afonso Campos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-imperial-needs-to-start-raising-serious-money/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College has long wished and pledged to be among the world’s elite of academia, continuously making the assertion that it can stack up proudly against the financial mammoths that are the top American universities, Oxford, and Cambridge. Its literature certainly highlights the College’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Midterm elections: what do they mean for US businesses?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-midterm-elections-what-do-they-mean-for-us-businesses/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 18:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sina Ataherian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-midterm-elections-what-do-they-mean-for-us-businesses/</guid>
        <description>As the Republicans retake the House of Representatives, analysts debate whether they will they ease the burden on businesses or let them down like it’s 1994
Tuesday saw the US midterm elections, ending months of speculation about the extent of predicted Democrat loses. These elections were seen as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>G-20 meets amid growing talk of a currency war
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-g-20-meets-amid-growing-talk-of-a-currency-war/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 19:30:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lingxi Huang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-g-20-meets-amid-growing-talk-of-a-currency-war/</guid>
        <description>After their meeting in Seoul, G-20 finance ministers expressed optimisim that a much-hyped global currency war may yet be avoided. Thoughts have now turned to the longer-term motivations for countries to manipulate their currencies to help exporters, and measures that can be taken against this.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Did Physics break the economy? Can it save it?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-did-physics-break-the-economy-can-it-save-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 18:48:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Afonso Campos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-did-physics-break-the-economy-can-it-save-it/</guid>
        <description>At the apogee of the mathematical finance movement in the mid nineties, billions were being made by pioneering science and finance academics and those who had the foresight to see the increasing use of these techniques. Louis Bachelier, the informal father of the discipline about a century ago would …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Two miners rumble in the Congo
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-two-miners-rumble-in-the-congo/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 19:33:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sina Ataherian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-two-miners-rumble-in-the-congo/</guid>
        <description>Last year, the Government of the Democratic Republic of Congo terminated the mining license of First Quantum Minerals, the Canadian owner of Kolwezi copper mine. This was a considerable blow for First Quantum, which spent US$750m developing the mine, a move that generated over a quarter of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The summer begins right now
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-7-the-summer-begins-right-now/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 23:03:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Afonso Campos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-7-the-summer-begins-right-now/</guid>
        <description>Being at one of the world’s top universities has its perks when it comes to getting employed. You are lucky enough that companies actively want to give you the chance to shine through a summer internship which could hopefully lead to the holy grail; the offer of a full-time job after your …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC Business School climbs FT rankings
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-ic-business-school-climbs-ft-rankings/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 17:20:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ravi S Pall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-1-ic-business-school-climbs-ft-rankings/</guid>
        <description>The Financial Times World Rankings is one of the most respected international league tables for Business Schools. In their latest annual assessment, released this week, Imperial College Business School has moved up seven places to 32nd place in the world. Its Principal, Professor David Begg, has …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
