<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/me1711/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/me1711/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>SUPERHOT is super fun
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-superhot-is-super-fun/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 11:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-superhot-is-super-fun/</guid>
        <description>Imagine a game where you are a super assassin, well-versed in the arts of weaponry and hand-to-hand combat. You mow down countless enemies, spraying them down with machine guns, splitting them in half with a well placed katana swipe or just beating them to a pulp, like the good old days. “Wait, why …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>War. War never changes... (Part 4)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-12-war-war-never-changes-part-4/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2015 12:40:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-12-war-war-never-changes-part-4/</guid>
        <description>Yes, the day of reckoning is upon us. Global productivity has come to a standstill. These are the news headline that will echo around the world on the day of the release of Fallout 4.
If you have spent any time on the internet in the past week, you know that Bethesda has made a good attempt at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A long time ago, in a game far far away...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-12-a-long-time-ago-in-a-game-far-far-away/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2015 12:38:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-12-a-long-time-ago-in-a-game-far-far-away/</guid>
        <description>If you love star wars, first person shooters or in fact games in general, you could not have missed the fact that the makers of Battlefield, DICE are remaking one of the best First Person Shooters (FPS) game ever.
When the original battlefront and its sequel came out and in my childhood I spent …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Squad, Go Go Go!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-squad-go-go-go/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 12:20:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-squad-go-go-go/</guid>
        <description>Back in yonder days when I first started playing computer games, the one that really filled my childhood after-school hours was one called Army Men. Basically it was a shooter revolving around the green plastic men, where you would control one of them and shoot the other plastic dudes using a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>3 Space Sims: Ready for Lift-off
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-3-space-sims-ready-for-lift-off/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 14:58:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-3-space-sims-ready-for-lift-off/</guid>
        <description>Elite: Dangerous
If you are talking about space games, the Elite series is one that stirs good memories for many a gamer. Sadly, the last entry in this illustrious series was released back in 1995, meaning that many of the newer generation of gamers never really had the opportunity to play this. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Next Big Gaming Trend: Space Simulations
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-the-next-big-gaming-trend-space-simulations/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 18:24:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-the-next-big-gaming-trend-space-simulations/</guid>
        <description>The past few years, ever since the release and subsequent re-release of DayZ, we have had an explosion of Zombie survival MMOs. In fact, I am surprised when there is a month when I don’t see news about a new one. However, it has become quite tiring, since there are only so many times I can wake up …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Review of 2014: Pretty Disappointing
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-review-of-2014-pretty-disappointing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 18:22:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-review-of-2014-pretty-disappointing/</guid>
        <description>2014 could have been such an amazing year. There was so much potential. We had the graphical promise of what could have been a true GTA rival (Watch Dogs), we could have had a spiritual successor to Halo (Destiny), we might have had the MMO that finally knocks WoW off its porch (Elder Scrolls …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2015: Three Games that Excite
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-2015-three-games-that-excite/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 18:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-2015-three-games-that-excite/</guid>
        <description>Star Wars Battlefront
My first ever shooter was _Star Wars Battlefront 2 _for the ps2. Trust me when I tell you that I wasted an extraordinary amount of my school years playing this game. It was a pretty epic game. However, it was released back in 2005, ten years ago. Therefore the announcements …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Simulating your Xmas Shopping...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-11-simulating-your-xmas-shopping/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 20:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-11-simulating-your-xmas-shopping/</guid>
        <description>Recently I was sitting in the Felix office absentmindedly jingling the bells (I know sad, right?), when a fellow section editor sent me the link to the game Christmas Shopping Simulator. This immediately gave me purpose in life, and faster than a elf can wrap a present I had clicked on the link to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Enforcing the Law: Simulator Style
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-enforcing-the-law-simulator-style/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 01:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-enforcing-the-law-simulator-style/</guid>
        <description>Recently Felix Games was offered a steam key to Enforce: Police Crime Action, to test and try out, review and break! And that is exactly what we have done.
A little overview; Enforcer is a “life-simulator” game, with an emphasis on the police force side of things. You are a police officer, starting …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Racism in football: Is the sport living in a deluded bubble?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-racism-in-football-is-the-sport-living-in-a-deluded-bubble/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 01:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-racism-in-football-is-the-sport-living-in-a-deluded-bubble/</guid>
        <description>Racism is unacceptable. Regardless of who you are, the situation you find yourself in, or any excuses you may offer up, the moment you bring up someone’s race is the moment that you have crossed the line. However, there seems to be one area where casual racism is endemic, and is rarely punished. I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Epic Return to Middle Earth
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-17-the-epic-return-to-middle-earth/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 18:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-17-the-epic-return-to-middle-earth/</guid>
        <description>Yes, ok, the Lord of the Rings: Shadow of Mordor was released a while ago, but after completing it just last week and being so thoroughly impressed, I felt that I really needed to share this with you guys. For all of you who missed it, the _Shadow of Mordor _is a new Stealth-RPG style Lord of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Godus? More like God-awful-us
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-godus-more-like-god-awful-us/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 20:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-godus-more-like-god-awful-us/</guid>
        <description>I am a big fan of big overarching civilization sims. Not just the really the strategic ones which give you control over empires, huge armies and the ability to control the entire world, but also the ones where you micromanage each individual citizen of your realm, telling them to chop down this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Endlessly Fun: Talking to Amplitude Studio
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-7-10-endlessly-fun-talking-to-amplitude-studio/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 16:44:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-7-10-endlessly-fun-talking-to-amplitude-studio/</guid>
        <description>Recently Felix games was invited to the press tour of Amplitude Studios, who are promoting their two newest games in their Endless Franchise: Endless Legend and Dungeon of the Legend. We were able to discuss their upcoming releases, Steam Early-Access, Indie Gaming as well as the gaming industry as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FELIX GAMING REVIEW – SECTION BATTLE ROYALE
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-19-felix-gaming-review-section-battle-royale/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 18:50:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-19-felix-gaming-review-section-battle-royale/</guid>
        <description> Felix News The games editorial team can now exclusively reveal that the Felix news section would be much better if there was a heavier focus on gaming news. Recent articles in the game section garnered a lot of views, and there were several calls for the current games editor to be instated as news …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Yearly Review: The Big ones
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-19-yearly-review-the-big-ones/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 18:45:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-19-yearly-review-the-big-ones/</guid>
        <description> Microsoft A year when the redmond based company only really got into the news because of the numerous U-turns they did, as well as falling really far behind to Sony in the next-gen console devices. However, dropping of the kinect device as well as a lowering of the price, allows the XBone to be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>KILLER ROBOTS
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-19-killer-robots/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 18:44:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-19-killer-robots/</guid>
        <description>Recently a new breakthrough was achieved in the field of robotics. Pepper, a robot from Japan, is now able to read emotions from its human masters.
Furthermore, it can change its behaviour according to this information. However, most horrifically, is the fact that pepper will be able to dance, joke …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Battlefield Hardline
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-19-battlefield-hardline/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 18:37:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-19-battlefield-hardline/</guid>
        <description>Recently EA announced a closed beta for its newest instalment in its Battlefield franchise. All you needed to do (and still can do at battlefield.com/hardline/beta) was give in your details and hope that EA decided to pick you. To be honest with you, I would honestly go for it. You only lose about 2 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>OS X, iOS and full-frontal Apple
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-11-os-x-ios-and-full-frontal-apple/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 21:33:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-11-os-x-ios-and-full-frontal-apple/</guid>
        <description> In recent times I have become quite disillusioned with Apple. The keynotes were kinda boring, and there was nothing really interesting. I usually tuned in to the keynotes just because I felt that I should. In fact, it got to the point that this time around, I almost missed the keynote. When I did …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Games I played during my Revision
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-28-the-games-i-played-during-my-revision/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 21:37:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-28-the-games-i-played-during-my-revision/</guid>
        <description> Mount And Blade Warband: Veiled Stars Mod Quick recap of what Mount and Blade is: M &amp;amp; B is a RPG style game, where you are dumped in the land of Calradia and have to make your way, raising armies, besieging cities and gaining power. The great thing about this game is the vibrant modding …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Farting your way to glory
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-28-farting-your-way-to-glory/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 21:23:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-28-farting-your-way-to-glory/</guid>
        <description>If you have ever watched south park, then you probably know that no taboo ever goes untouched. In episodes and movie we encounter swear words en masse, racial stereotypes, drugs, sex and unabashed toilet humour. Now imagine every south park episode that you have seen, take all the worst parts in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Updated Faster than Light
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-updated-faster-than-light/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 02:00:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-updated-faster-than-light/</guid>
        <description>This game is one of the indie scene’s big success stories. Back in 2012 it was one of the most successful kickstarter campaigns, achieving over 20 times the goal that the developers had asked for. It went on to win numerous awards, has been reviewed in these very papers, regularly tops the steam …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>August EP650 Headphones
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-august-ep650-headphones/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-august-ep650-headphones/</guid>
        <description>Almost a year and a half ago I stumbled across the wonderful world of Bluetooth headphones. For those of you who might remember, back then a naïve tech writer I had just decided to splash out on a pair of 20 quid headphones from Amazon, namely the SX-907. To date this still remains my most popular …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Dino Killing Simulator: Max&#39;s Verdict
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-11-the-dino-killing-simulator-maxs-verdict/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2014 18:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-11-the-dino-killing-simulator-maxs-verdict/</guid>
        <description>In games, I like shooting things. My targets tend to include Zombies, terrorists, counter-terrorist and now, due to an incredibly cheap game, dinosaurs. Yes, I am talking about Orion’s Dino horde. After seeing it for less than a quid on Steam, I was quite tempted to buy it and give it a go. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is Competition really that good?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-is-competition-really-that-good/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 05:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-is-competition-really-that-good/</guid>
        <description>I seem to be in a bit of a gaming rut at the moment. I bought a few games in the Steam sales and in Humble Bundles that I haven’t given due gaming time. Instead of exploring the vastness of my steam library, I am always playing the same game: CounterStrike Global Offensive. For all you who don’t …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chess Team wins at BUCA
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-chess-team-wins-at-buca/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 04:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-chess-team-wins-at-buca/</guid>
        <description>Two weekends ago, Imperial College London’s chess club fielded three teams for the British University Chess Association championship (BUCA), coming away with two cases of silverware. The first team competed in the open competition, where the real title of British Chess Champion was competed. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where are the Queens in Chess?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-28-where-are-the-queens-in-chess/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 07:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-28-where-are-the-queens-in-chess/</guid>
        <description>Recently the Imperial College chess team arrived back from BUCA. After multiple rounds, Imperial managed to dominate the entire tournament. It was a great weekend of fun and exciting chess games. However, throughout the event, one thing particularly struck me. Of a group of more than a 70 people, I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Episode 2.2: Anna’s Friend
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-19-episode-22-annas-friend/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 21:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-19-episode-22-annas-friend/</guid>
        <description>If you want to read about the start of Anna&amp;rsquo;s tale, here is the link: Episode 2.1 Anna&amp;rsquo;s Grace
After having met that strange man I decided to stay low for next few hours. However before I could even say “stay low” I heard yet another voice shouting something.
“Hey man, I’m heading over …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gaming in the Future
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-19-gaming-in-the-future/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 21:24:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-19-gaming-in-the-future/</guid>
        <description> Gaming is something I hold very dearly. I will defend my love with tooth and nail. Furthermore I like the status quo. I like the way I buy, play and interact with games, and in fact I could say that I am actually missing the past a bit. However I can see that gaming is changing, and maybe not …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Episode 2.1: Anna&#39;s Grace
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-12-dayz-episode-21-annas-grace/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 12:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-12-dayz-episode-21-annas-grace/</guid>
        <description>If you want to read about the start of Anna&amp;rsquo;s tale, here is the link: Episode 2: Anna&amp;rsquo;s Hunger
With newfound strength and vigour, I decided to go through the nearby houses to see if I could find anything to further help me survive. It seems lady luck was on my side, because the first …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Find the egg-laying chicken #yoyonotyolo
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-12-find-the-egg-laying-chicken-yoyonotyolo/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 12:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-12-find-the-egg-laying-chicken-yoyonotyolo/</guid>
        <description>ME: Introduce yourself:
MR: My name is Michael Rolph, I am the co-founder of Yoyo which has launched very recently here at Imperial.
ME: What is the history of Yoyo, how did you guys start out?
MR: I’ve got a personal background which is very much from the payment space. Ex-Barclaycard business, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mobile: Just flapping about?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-12-mobile-just-flapping-about/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 11:39:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-12-mobile-just-flapping-about/</guid>
        <description>No, this is not a review of Flappy Bird. Firstly, Flappy Bird does not need any review. I mean, the game is so incredibly simple (you tap to fly between pipes) that you could form any opinion of it faster than you could read it. Secondly, I still wish to have a life and Flappy bird seems to kill …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Episode 2: Anna’s Hunger
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-5-episode-2-annas-hunger/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 10:36:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-5-episode-2-annas-hunger/</guid>
        <description>If you want to read about episode 1, here is the link: Episode 1: Yannick&amp;rsquo;s tale
I woke up to find myself cold and thirsty on beach in Chernarus. All I had on me was the clothes I was wearing and a flashlight. Time to survive the Zombie apocalypse. I had no clue at all where I was, all I knew …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>QuizUp: Upping the game
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-5-quizup-upping-the-game/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 10:27:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-5-quizup-upping-the-game/</guid>
        <description>This is not the kind game that our section would usually review. In fact, when I told my fellow games editor Calum what I was planning to write about, he retorted in disgust “that’s not a proper game!” However, I believe that mobile gaming is here to stay, which means that we should start …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Return to paper?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-5-return-to-paper/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 10:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-5-return-to-paper/</guid>
        <description>Yes, Facebook, has turned 10. Ten years this giant has been sucking out our souls, killing our times and generally trying to inject itself into every aspect of our lives. Now they have introduced their next strategy in their multi-pronged attack to make themselves virtually indispensible, a reader …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>DayZ Stories Episode 1: Yannick’s tale
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-29-dayz-stories-episode-1-yannicks-tale/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 16:44:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-29-dayz-stories-episode-1-yannicks-tale/</guid>
        <description>I woke up to find myself cold and thirsty on beach in chernarus. All I had on me was a the clothes I was wearing and a flashlight. Time to survive the Zombie apocalypse. I saw immediately a town sign which said Камышово which, I knew from my limited Russian, was Kamyshovo. However my knowledge of my …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix on the move!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-29-felix-on-the-move/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 16:24:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-29-felix-on-the-move/</guid>
        <description>ME: Introduce yourself!
KW: I am a first year Computing student from London. I currently reside in the Southside Halls of Residence.
ME: What is your position in Felix?
KW: I am the sports editor. I follow most sports, particularly football, cricket and tennis, so I felt that when the opportunity …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Paying in style: #yoyonotyolo
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-29-paying-in-style-yoyonotyolo/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 16:19:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-29-paying-in-style-yoyonotyolo/</guid>
        <description>You must have seen it around these days, the proliferation of pink flyers littering imperial’s walkways. Flyers that seem to have the word yolo written on them. However fear not my dear students, our university has not descended into a swag-palace. No these flyers actually say yoyo on them, and what …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best Friends for ever?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-22-best-friends-for-ever/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 14:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-22-best-friends-for-ever/</guid>
        <description>If you read my christmas list, you probably know that I wanted to play BF4 for a while now. I play a lot of FPS, and the battlefield series always interested me from the off. It was the one game I had always missed out on. Especially this iteration, which has just built on the success of its …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>DayZ, Nothing About Flowers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-dayz-nothing-about-flowers/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 16:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-dayz-nothing-about-flowers/</guid>
        <description>Shivering in the cold, dressed in an assortment of scavenged clothes and gear I wait on top of the hill overlooking Balota Airfield. Through the scope of my Mosin, I watch down below hoping to see something interesting or somebody to talk to. I see some movement off to my left, and excitedly I turn …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who doesn&#39;t need a Roomba?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-who-doesnt-need-a-roomba/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 16:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-who-doesnt-need-a-roomba/</guid>
        <description>iPhone 5S
Considering how much of an apple fan I am, I think this is a bit of an obvious one. At the moment I have an iPhone 5, and I don’t see the 5S as enough of an upgrade to pay out that much money. I mean sure the 64-bit processor and the fingerprint scanner are all really nice, but do I want …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Santa’s checking his gaming list
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-santas-checking-his-gaming-list/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 16:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-santas-checking-his-gaming-list/</guid>
        <description> Battlefield 4 + Premium membership I have been playing shooter games forever, from Star Wars Battlefront 2 and Halo all the way to Counter-strike and Call of duty. The battlefield series has always interested me, and I almost splashed out for Battlefield 3. However I either never seemed to have the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Steamy love for PC Gaming
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-13-steamy-love-for-pc-gaming/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 12:47:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-13-steamy-love-for-pc-gaming/</guid>
        <description>Recently a lot of console love has been going round in the game section. With the releases of the PS4 and Xbox One, the reactionary Wii U article, I just felt that one big part of gaming, namely PC gaming was being a bit left out. Th erefore I wanted to bring it back into the spotlight by describing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rome 2, Totally worth it?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-rome-2-totally-worth-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 16:35:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-rome-2-totally-worth-it/</guid>
        <description>I have meant to write this article for quite a while. This game was released on the 3 of september 2013, almost two months ago. I had pre-ordered it almost a month earlier in my excitement. Let me just explain to you, I LOVED the Total War series. Beginning with Medieval, all the way to Empire, I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Xbox, One for you?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-13-xbox-one-for-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2013 22:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-13-xbox-one-for-you/</guid>
        <description>After a super successful Xbox 360, which most people claim won the last console generation wars, Microsoft is now releasing the next iteration into a less clear cut market. The hardcore gaming sector as such is being threatened by smartphone and tablet dominated casual games. This situation is now …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PlayStation 4 you?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-13-playstation-4-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2013 22:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-13-playstation-4-you/</guid>
        <description>Sony has been releasing top notch consoles for almost 2 decades now, and therefore the PS4 has a lot riding on its shoulders. While the PS3 was a great console, somehow it just wasn’t the best that we expected of Sony. Enter the PS4. Almost 5 years in the making, this console just like the Xbox One …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>5 Things Tablets are/have killing/ed
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-13-5-things-tablets-arehave-killinged/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2013 22:53:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-13-5-things-tablets-arehave-killinged/</guid>
        <description> Elegance of making a photo: In our day and age everything has a camera attached to it. Your phone, your mp3 player, my god, even your fridge could have a camera for all we know. Therefore it is not a surprise that your tablet has a camera. How many times have you seen someone with their tablet in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>10 Things Smartphones Slaughtered
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-6-10-things-smartphones-slaughtered/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 17:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-6-10-things-smartphones-slaughtered/</guid>
        <description> After last weeks Osama Awara’s “10 things the Internet has slaughtered”, I decided to write something in a similar vein, except of course exchanging one vital invention (internet) of our lives for something equally important (smartphones). So here goes (in no particular order).
Dedicated hand-held …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Apple’s New Keynote and What it Means for You
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-30-apples-new-keynote-and-what-it-means-for-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 15:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-30-apples-new-keynote-and-what-it-means-for-you/</guid>
        <description>As mentioned in last weeks news bubble Apple had a key note last tuesday. That day confirmed most rumours on the internet as well as some pleasant surprises. However if you are looking at the news, scratching your head and wondering how this will affect anything in your life, read on dear reader and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get rich quick, Youtube style!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-16-get-rich-quick-youtube-style/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 13:56:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-16-get-rich-quick-youtube-style/</guid>
        <description>All of you spend a significant amount of your life on youtube, be it watching handy tutorial videos, lets-plays, music videos and/or videos of cute-ass kittens (the last being the most time intensive). However have you ever wondered why some of these Youtubers, more often than not just average …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hardcore Pawn: IC Chess Takes the Americas by storm
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-hardcore-pawn-ic-chess-takes-the-americas-by-storm/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 23:57:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-hardcore-pawn-ic-chess-takes-the-americas-by-storm/</guid>
        <description>After a very successful year dominating British chess, the British Uni and London Uni Champions (your resident chess team) decided that they needed a new challenge. So when ex-President Sam “Sporter” Porter began organizing the trip to the US, a lot of excitement and anticipation started to arise. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The crippling effect of Technology
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-the-crippling-effect-of-technology/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 23:50:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-the-crippling-effect-of-technology/</guid>
        <description>This is a very interesting question I found myself talking about with a friend recently. Is technology really making us weaker, mentally and physically? If you consider that technology is part of the human condition, then you would disagree and I would be on your side. All the brilliant things that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gaming by creating games; deep!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-gaming-by-creating-games-deep/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 23:45:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-gaming-by-creating-games-deep/</guid>
        <description>Every so often a steam discount/sale comes along and I see a game for a price I cannot refuse. Surprisingly enough this happens more than I wish it would, and so I end up with a boatload of games that I have absolutely no time or energy to spend on them. Game Dev Tycoon was one of these games. An …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dumped Planetside (2), time to get revenge
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-dumped-planetside-2-time-to-get-revenge/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 19:27:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-dumped-planetside-2-time-to-get-revenge/</guid>
        <description>Ever wanted to take part into a continent wide battle for control of an entire planet? PlanetSide 2 (released November 2012) the revamp of the succesful MMOFPS PlanetSide allows you to do exactly that! It revolves around the control of the mysterious planet of Auraxis.
Featuring a gigantic map, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are we seeing Apple crumble?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-are-we-seeing-apple-crumble/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 16:36:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-are-we-seeing-apple-crumble/</guid>
        <description>Yet another Apple keynote has come and gone, and once again there is a sense of frustration in the air. At least that bitter taste on the tongue is one I have gotten used to after Steve jobs died, along with all his intuition, drive and creativity. For all the fancy technical terms that Apple likes …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>As Hitler once said: Execute PLAN Z!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-as-hitler-once-said-execute-plan-z/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 16:10:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-as-hitler-once-said-execute-plan-z/</guid>
        <description>As CollegeHumour once said: “The two things you could always kill in videogames were nazis and zombies, there was no moral ambiguity there. So to combine them is just brilliant!” Now combine this with the award winning game Sniper Elite, and it seems like you have a high chance of a really fun game. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Broke and Bored? Felix has the answer
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-broke-and-bored-felix-has-the-answer/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 16:04:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-broke-and-bored-felix-has-the-answer/</guid>
        <description> Ahead of you, dear reader, be you fresher or a returning student, is a substantial (or perhaps not so substantial) amount of work. To provide some relief from the never ending coursework and lab reports, this article will try to introduce you to some games that will serve you well this year, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Microsoft kicked everyone’s ass...hard
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-21-microsoft-kicked-everyones-asshard/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2013 00:29:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-21-microsoft-kicked-everyones-asshard/</guid>
        <description>Yeah, MS is back, baby! The most awesomest company on Earth has delivered this year in every possible area available. I’m like serious people, we did like everything. Not only have we revolutionised the smartphone world but also shaken up the PC market, tablets and games consoles.
With the Windows 8 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Apple iOS7
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-apple-ios7/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 22:52:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-apple-ios7/</guid>
        <description>Apple has finally caught up with the rest of the mobile OS world. The keynote at WWDC has revealed a slew of new features, and yours truly has access to the beta to test them out for you, my dear reader. A little disclaimer, since I only have beta access, my experience may not be the same as the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Xbox One: Ton of fun?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-29-xbox-one-ton-of-fun/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 12:38:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-29-xbox-one-ton-of-fun/</guid>
        <description>Hey, an article about the Xbox One, I hear you exclaim, shouldn’t that be in the gaming section? Well there probably will be one, describing all its features and games that will be available at release. However this article will focus on the Xbox One’s, as long with others, intrusion into the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Addicted Smartphone Syndrome
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-addicted-smartphone-syndrome/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 01:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-addicted-smartphone-syndrome/</guid>
        <description>Smartphones affect almost every aspect of the average student’s life. Marvels of modern technology, something underlined by the much quoted: “your smartphone has the equivalent processing power of the computers used for the Apollo space missions”, they have revolutionised the way we interact with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>World War Z
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-28-world-war-z/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 18:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-28-world-war-z/</guid>
        <description>Last year was the year of the Vampire, and it seems set that 2013 will be the year of the Zombie. Don’t understand me wrong, Zombies have always been present in movies, TV shows, games and books. However only recently this genre has achieved mainstream success, probably through a larger amount of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Revolution: wearable technology
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-revolution-wearable-technology/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 01:24:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-revolution-wearable-technology/</guid>
        <description>After the smartphone and table revolution, the next big thing in the tech world seems to be wearable gadgets. After the full saturation of these two markets, which are quite important for these kind of companies, the technology giants are attempting to claim this new area of the market. Potential …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Crackberry or Crapberry?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-crackberry-or-crapberry/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 23:47:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-crackberry-or-crapberry/</guid>
        <description>Back in the early days of mobile electronics, a BlackBerry phone was the thing to have. The first true smartphone, BlackBerry (formerly known as RIM), was the first company to really attempt to make a really portable computer. With the miniature keyboard, BBM, Mail services etc, it really was a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Apple, sweet or sour outlook?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-apple-sweet-or-sour-outlook/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 01:13:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-apple-sweet-or-sour-outlook/</guid>
        <description> Apple have undeniably changed the world. It used to be the most valuable company on Earth, ever. Now, stockholders are insecure and other brands have come close, if not eclipsed, the atmosphere of ‘coolness’ that Apple once made its own. Have they diverted off their successful path, have they done …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>¡Tres! ¡Uno! ¡Dos!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-tres-uno-dos/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 00:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-tres-uno-dos/</guid>
        <description>Ladies and gentlemen, we have come to the last album of our trilogy, and thus the last of these articles. However I promise last should not be least! ¡Tré!, as the last album is called, features the drummer on the cover as well as carrying his nickname. It was released a month before schedule, due …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>¡Dos! ¡Uno! ¡Tres!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-dos-uno-tres/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 22:10:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-dos-uno-tres/</guid>
        <description>The aptly titled album ¡Dos! is the second instalment in the rapid-fire trilogy that Green Day now has released. This album is a bit less clean than ¡Uno!, playing to a garage rock style vibe. Armstrong went as far to describe this as a second Foxboro Hot Tubs album. If you have heard of the Foxboro …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>iPhone 5, review is finally here
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-iphone-5-review-is-finally-here/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 21:17:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-iphone-5-review-is-finally-here/</guid>
        <description>In terms of iOS, 2012 was the year of the iPhone 5. After a rather disappointing iPhone 4S, the anticipation had been growing under the surface for a long time. When the iPhone 5 was revealed on the 12th of September of last year, it sported a radical new design, a better graphics processor, new A6 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>¡Uno! ¡Dos! ¡Tres!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-uno-dos-tres/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 00:50:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-uno-dos-tres/</guid>
        <description>Since 2009, after the release of 21st Century Breakdown, news surrounding Green Day was few and far between. However the american punk band has now not only released a set of albums, but the trio has now also become a quartet. The newest member of the group, that brought among others American Idiot, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is South Park going south?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-is-south-park-going-south/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 22:57:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-is-south-park-going-south/</guid>
        <description>Like it or not, South Park is a cultural phenomenon, often quoted, reminisced about or each episode carefully dissected. The fact that South Park just finished its 16th season does nothing to lessen its appeal; in fact the show has now been extended to finish in 2016 bringing it to 20 seasons. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We went to the Gadget Show
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-we-went-to-the-gadget-show/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 02:52:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,Felix Technology,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-we-went-to-the-gadget-show/</guid>
        <description>Last Friday three young whippersnappers (i.e. the Felix Tech team) made their way to the Gadget Show Live, in the ExCeL, hoping to see the newest tech on the market, as well as have some well-earned time off. Once we arrived there and got our shiny press passes sorted out, we decided to split up so …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wii wish U a merry Zmas
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-wii-wish-u-a-merry-zmas/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 02:39:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-wii-wish-u-a-merry-zmas/</guid>
        <description>The Wii U was released about a week ago, with a lot of curiosity surrounding its release, and I had the chance, last Friday, to actually play it! A trip to the Gadget Show Live, with very plain press passes, allowed me to not only jump all the cues, but actually get a look and feel of the Wii U and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>SX-907 Bluetooth Headphones
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-18-sx-907-bluetooth-headphones/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2012 13:07:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-18-sx-907-bluetooth-headphones/</guid>
        <description>Yes, dear readers, I have recently discovered the world of wireless headphones. Two weeks ago, bored and not feeling like untangling my normal headphones, I decided to peruse the various stores of the internet, to discover if the World Wide Web had anything to tickle my fancy. Lo and behold, on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My wild Irish prose
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-my-wild-irish-prose/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 21:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-my-wild-irish-prose/</guid>
        <description>Intro: Murchad mac Diarmata (1026 – 1070) was a King of Dublin and Leinster, and if you haven’t heard of him, no big deal. He didn’t really accomplish that much, and thus his name has been lost in the realms of history. However, last week, I decided, with the aid of Crusader Kings 2, to give the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pandering to every whim
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-pandering-to-every-whim/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 22:54:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-pandering-to-every-whim/</guid>
        <description>Everyone has heard of, scoffed at, ridiculed, played, dominated (cross out the ones that do not apply to you) World of Warcraft. For those of you who chose the two latter choices, this is the article for you. For all the rest, you can stop judging, get yourselves an account and then read this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Apple had another keynote
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-apple-had-another-keynote/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 22:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-apple-had-another-keynote/</guid>
        <description> t last week’s Apple keynote weall expected just the launch of the new iPad mini, but the keynote proved a surprise as Apple announced more new products and upgrades than most had expected.
Introduction Tim Cook came on stage, and like all previous keynotes spouted off facts and figures that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Windows 8 - the difference between 8, RT &amp; Pro
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-windows-8-the-difference-between-8-rt-pro/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 02:24:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jason Parmar,Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-windows-8-the-difference-between-8-rt-pro/</guid>
        <description>Windows 8 came out today, and the media world is buzzing to see if this will make or break Microsoft’s future. In the past Microsoft consumers faced more choices of varieties of Windows than in a trip to Subway! Starter, Home Basic, Home Premium and, and, and, were often subject to intense …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get your Christmas tablet treat early with Felix Tech
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-get-your-christmas-tablet-treat-early-with-felix-tech/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 20:59:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,Jason Parmar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-get-your-christmas-tablet-treat-early-with-felix-tech/</guid>
        <description> Seasons come and go, but Christmas never changes and considering that it’s only 65 shopping days away, you might as well get started making your wish list (parents do need something to spend money on!). So to help you get an idea, here are 4 budget tablets that might tickle your fancy!
iPad Mini On …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
