<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/aib116/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/aib116/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s nearly Easter – season of chocolate, chocolate, and more chocolate!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-it-s-nearly-easter-season-of-chocolate-chocolate-and-more-chocolate/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-it-s-nearly-easter-season-of-chocolate-chocolate-and-more-chocolate/</guid>
        <description>For unknown reasons, Easter is not my favourite holiday, and making food for it is not as pleasant as cooking for Christmas. So, Easter for me is more a holiday of sweets – especially Easter eggs. In my opinion, the only things that should be cooked during Easter have to have chocolate. Even if you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A couple of Asian-inspired recipes for you to fry!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-a-couple-of-asian-inspired-recipes-for-you-to-fry/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-a-couple-of-asian-inspired-recipes-for-you-to-fry/</guid>
        <description>Writing feels oddly therapeutic most of the time and I am not sure why I stayed away from it for so long – I mean, two weeks is a really long time, but I have an excuse! (I mean, I always have an excuse, don’t I?) I experimented with new ideas and tried new ingredients and culinary zones so I can …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the eleventh day of Christmas, my true love gave to me… BRUSSELS SPROUTS</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-eleventh-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-brussels-sprouts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-eleventh-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-brussels-sprouts/</guid>
        <description>You will need&amp;hellip;
 1 kg Brussels sprouts 50 gr butter 4 tsp vegetable oil 20 gr almonds 400 ml double cream 5 tsp lemon juice 5 tbsp breadcrumbs freshly grated parmesan (the more, the better) a pinch of salt black pepper   Simmer salted water in a saucepan. Add the Brussels sprouts and boil them …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the fifth day of Christmas, my true love gave to me… MINCE PIES</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-fifth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-mince-pies/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-fifth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-mince-pies/</guid>
        <description>Every country in the world seems to have its Christmas food. Here, they are Christmas cake and mince pies – which disappointed me at first. A lot. But, hey, British food can grow on you. Eventually.
Squashed peach and almond mince pies
This was the first mince pie I’ve tried and I was a bit like …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the first day of Christmas, my true love gave to me... THE BEST ADVENT CALENDAR</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-first-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-the-best-advent-calendar/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-first-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-the-best-advent-calendar/</guid>
        <description>To be clear, this is not an advertisement for any company out there. But this year I felt very nostalgic and I decided that I should revive the childhood years when I used to get advent calendars. Should I mention that I also used to eat them in one day? Maximum two, if I really felt like I should …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the second day of Christmas, my true love gave to me... EGGNOG</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-second-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-eggnog/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-second-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-eggnog/</guid>
        <description>You will need&amp;hellip;
 700ml whole milk 250ml double cream 5 eggs 3 cinnamon sticks 1 tbsp vanilla essence/pods 1 tsp nutmeg 150g granulated sugar 200ml dark rum (I know you want more, but you need to keep it low for the consistency)   In a saucepan, combine the milk, double cream, cinnamon, vanilla …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the seventh day of Christmas, my true love gave to me… CHRISTMAS ROAST PORK WITH RIB GRAVY AND APPLE BREAD SAUCE</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-seventh-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-christmas-roast-pork-with-rib-gravy-and-apple-bread-sauce/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-seventh-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-christmas-roast-pork-with-rib-gravy-and-apple-bread-sauce/</guid>
        <description>You will need&amp;hellip;
FOR THE ROAST - 2 kg pork belly (depending on how many people you plan to feed) - 3 tbsp salt
FOR THE GRAVY - 3 tbsp olive oil - 4 pork ribs - 2 onions, chopped - 2 carrots, chopped in big chunks - 1 litre chicken stock - 8 black peppercorns - fresh bay leaves - fresh thyme
FOR …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the sixth day of Christmas, my true love gave to me… GINGERBREAD MEN</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-sixth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-gingerbread-men/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-sixth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-gingerbread-men/</guid>
        <description>You will need&amp;hellip;
 400g plain flour 1 tsp bicarbonate of soda 2 tsp ground ginger 1 tsp ground cinnamon 125g butter (unsalted) 200g honey 2 eggs   Mix all the dry ingredients and then add in the butter. This step would be really easy if you have a food processor, but I imagine that, as a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the tenth day of Christmas, my true love gave to me… BEST FOOD GIFTS</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-first-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-best-food-gifts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-first-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-best-food-gifts/</guid>
        <description>Knowing that someone likes to cook makes picking a Christmas gift a lot easier for you. Felix came here with a list of our 10 picks – hopefully, Santa will see this and will know which one you would like to see under that Christmas tree.
 Chef’s knife – This says it all. You can never have enough …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the third day of Christmas, my true love gave to me... BISCUITS</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-third-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-biscuits/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-third-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-biscuits/</guid>
        <description>Just because they are a totally different thing to gingerbread, you need two to have both – trust me. Even if your family says “We don’t need two kinds of biscuits!”, what else would you give Santa when he delivers your gifts? Everybody knows that you make biscuits for Santa! So you have no choice. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the twelfth day of Christmas, my true love gave to me… SEA BASS WITH SWEET POTATO AND GREEN BEAN CURRY</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-twelfth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-sea-bass-with-sweet-potato-and-green-bean-curry/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-twelfth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-sea-bass-with-sweet-potato-and-green-bean-curry/</guid>
        <description>You will need&amp;hellip;
 2 large sweet potatoes 3 tbsp olive oil 1 onion, finely diced 3 garlic cloves, crushed 1 tbsp grated ginger 2 lime leaves (replaceable with 1 tsp lime juice) 1 tsp curry powder ½ tsp turmeric ½ masala ¼ tsp cinnamon 160 ml coconut cream 400 ml coconut milk 100 gr green beans 4 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Finally – time to celebrate with a nice meal out! </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-finally-time-to-celebrate-with-a-nice-meal-out/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-finally-time-to-celebrate-with-a-nice-meal-out/</guid>
        <description>If you are still reading this – congratulations! You’ve made it through the first half of this first term. While it’s not a big deal, I feel like I need a pat on the back every time I manage to get more than five hours of sleep, so… surviving for so long made me think that I actually have to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Have a sweet tooth? We sure do...</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-have-a-sweet-tooth-we-sure-do/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chun Yuan Hii,Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-have-a-sweet-tooth-we-sure-do/</guid>
        <description>Admit it, we all need our sugary boost sometimes (though this might be heavily frowned upon by my friend who wrote on healthy eating last week&amp;hellip;) Maybe it’s just me, but occasionally, after a nine-to-five day full of labs and lectures, you just want to have something warm, sweet, and – most …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Tis the season... again</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27--tis-the-season-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chun Yuan Hii,Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27--tis-the-season-again/</guid>
        <description>I’ll bet my lunch that you have already seen those shop-fronts decorated in orangey strips, the vampire Frappucino adverts outside Starbucks, your friends marking ‘Interested’ on Halloween-themed Facebook events, and those tacky, plasticky, not-even-scary masks lining the aisles of Tesco. Well okay, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An introduction to the art of cooking</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-an-introduction-to-the-art-of-cooking/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-an-introduction-to-the-art-of-cooking/</guid>
        <description>Writing Food is so difficult when you don’t have anyone suggesting “maybe you want to write about that?”, or when you just don’t feel inspired to write about their suggestions. So, while I struggled with finding a topic for this page, I realised that I did not say “Hi!” to you this year. So, here I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All the best books coming out this term</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-all-the-best-books-coming-out-this-term/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-all-the-best-books-coming-out-this-term/</guid>
        <description>The Floating World, by C. Morgan Babst (October 17th)
Normally I don’t find this kind of books fascinating – I sometimes add them to my to-be-read (TBR) list, but they just stay there forever. However, this book has something… probably the parents who abandon their daughter in the middle of a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Braised partridge with carrots and peas </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-braised-partridge-with-carrots-and-peas/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-braised-partridge-with-carrots-and-peas/</guid>
        <description>When we decided to make this an autumn-food edition, I haven’t realised that I am not sure what autumn food is. And despite the world being ‘in love’ with pumpkin this season – and by this I mean Pumpkin spice latte – I feel like the only thing that deserves to be mentioned is the pumpkin pie. But …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Timeless’ recommendations for Autumn reading...</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13--timeless-recommendations-for-autumn-reading/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13--timeless-recommendations-for-autumn-reading/</guid>
        <description>Adulthood is a Myth, by Sarah Andersen
I know you are stuck in between two assignments and three textbooks to read, so you definitely don’t have a lot of time to lose reading ‘for pleasure’, but I think that you can find five minutes here and there to realise that you are not the only one who has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Andrada’s trans-European culinary summer adventure
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-andradas-trans-european-culinary-summer-adventure/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 17:12:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-andradas-trans-european-culinary-summer-adventure/</guid>
        <description>Believe it or not, this is the last food tip of the year – and it makes me feel both sad and relieved. Because there is no dish that’s really good enough to celebrate the end of the year, the promise of summer and freedom, I decided to create the perfect trans-European food itinerary for you.
If you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lazy food edition | Chilled rice pudding with berry compote
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-lazy-food-edition-chilled-rice-pudding-with-berry-compote/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:39:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-lazy-food-edition-chilled-rice-pudding-with-berry-compote/</guid>
        <description> I’m back you fools and to celebrate let me share a story from my childhood.
When I was in elementary school, our teacher used to teach us different ‘life hacks’ based on science – she said. One of the most memorable things she ever said was that it’s better to drink a hot drink (hot tea) when it’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My friend, a fresher, got pregnant
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-my-friend-a-fresher-got-pregnant/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 17:41:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-my-friend-a-fresher-got-pregnant/</guid>
        <description>This is a story about a friend (yes, it is actually about a friend). Just like any good story, it starts with a nice (by British standards anyway) spring day with my best friend telling me that she’s pregnant.
“So what?” you ask. “People get pregnant all the time!” While that may be true, she is not …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Forests have been hiding in plain sight
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-forests-have-been-hiding-in-plain-sight/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 17:33:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-forests-have-been-hiding-in-plain-sight/</guid>
        <description>Scientists have been missing the forest for the trees; literally, it turns out. A team of international scientists have found that dryland forest cover could be 40% to 47% higher than previously estimated. This corresponds to 467 million hectares (Mha) of forest that have never been reported before …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Easter egg hunting
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-easter-egg-hunting/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 16:28:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-easter-egg-hunting/</guid>
        <description> I hope you’ve enjoyed hunting for Easter chocolate eggs and that you don’t feel sorry for not letting your younger sister get more than two. Good job, by the way. But now that you are out of your sugar coma, it’s time to start wondering what you are supposed to do with all those kilos of chocolate …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Spiced rack of lamb with char-grilled, smoked aubergine dip
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-spiced-rack-of-lamb-with-char-grilled-smoked-aubergine-dip/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 17:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-spiced-rack-of-lamb-with-char-grilled-smoked-aubergine-dip/</guid>
        <description> B ack home, lamb is usually cooked just as a traditional Easter dinner. Otherwise, I don’t believe we have lamb at any other point in the year. Probably, because of that I am quite reticent about cooking it – that and the fact that I hate my mom’s lamb. Mom, I love you, but you have no idea how to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Liquid Comfort
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-liquid-comfort/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 14:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-liquid-comfort/</guid>
        <description> This will start as usual, with a funny story. I wanted to write about some lamb ribs - see, I kind of have a thing with ribs, but then the subject changed to comfort food (I am stating this in case you didn’t notice already) and because East Europeans don’t do comfort foods, they do alcohol, here I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All hail the mighty Internet
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-all-hail-the-mighty-internet/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 15:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-all-hail-the-mighty-internet/</guid>
        <description>Good thing that nowadays, you are only a search away from “I want to try some Thai tonight!” or “How am I supposed to eat an artichoke?”. But sometimes the Internet does more bad than good and gives too many recommendations. I mean, how are you supposed to decide between that perfect steak and the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Valentine’s sweets
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-valentines-sweets/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 16:21:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-valentines-sweets/</guid>
        <description> Can you smell it? Try again! I know you can, but maybe you’ve just got used to it as it’s been here for some days already: LOVE. Oh, yes, you’ve heard me right. In case you didn’t realise, Valentine’s is coming in less than a week now. And if you are alone, it’s time to worry – you cannot spend one …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All hail the sublime starch, the chieftan of cuisine, the triumphant tuber | the potato
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-all-hail-the-sublime-starch-the-chieftan-of-cuisine-the-triumphant-tuber-the-potato/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 17:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanjay Bhattacharya,Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-all-hail-the-sublime-starch-the-chieftan-of-cuisine-the-triumphant-tuber-the-potato/</guid>
        <description> The humble spud. Where to start? How many foodstuffs can compare to the tuber that brought a whole nation to its knees – and I’m not talking about the Irish potato famine, but rather the introduction of potatoes to haute cuisine. People had been searching for a starch that was affordable yet …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Melanzane alla Parmigiana
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-melanzane-alla-parmigiana/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-melanzane-alla-parmigiana/</guid>
        <description>I still can remember my editor’s voice, before Christmas, saying that I might want to try writing more meaty recipes: quick and easy, student friendly meat dishes. I can even see him smiling while he reads this (maybe I should say “Hello!”) but well, this is another meat-free edition. But I have an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Basic food for basic students (you’re basic)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-basic-food-for-basic-students-youre-basic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-basic-food-for-basic-students-youre-basic/</guid>
        <description>For many of us, it’s revision week time! Yay!! Can you feel the enthusiasm? I can feel it all around campus – especially in the library late at night or when I see some girl crying in the bathroom; I’m not saying that men do not cry in the bathroom, but I for one cannot see them – the perks of using …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>EU Xmas
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-eu-xmas/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 15:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-eu-xmas/</guid>
        <description>It’s time to get ready for the Christmas dinner – if you already had it, well, it’s never too late to have a second or third one. I mean, it’s Christmas – you can celebrate it as many times as you want. And now that you are a student, time to try something different. I’m not saying that the food …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cosmic dust in your backyard
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-cosmic-dust-in-your-backyard/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 12:09:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,Ipsita Herlekar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-cosmic-dust-in-your-backyard/</guid>
        <description>Of the many things you might have been sweeping off your balconies and terraces, cosmic dust particles could have found their way in your dust pan. Cosmic dust grains are minute particles measuring around 0.01 millimetres in size and are remnants from the time our solar system was born. They contain …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Does this look burnt?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-does-this-look-burnt/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 12:08:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,Alexandra Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-does-this-look-burnt/</guid>
        <description>The perennial question. You notice that slightly-too-blackened edge of your fried chicken thigh during a friend’s thanksgiving dinner, and hesitate just a little, but eat it anyway because nothing can take that peri-peri pleasure away from you. I guess it’s common knowledge that burnt foods can be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lunch box edition
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-lunch-box-edition/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 11:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-lunch-box-edition/</guid>
        <description>Lunch at somewhere outside of university is ‘the thing’ nowadays, but who has time for that with all the lab reports and homework and tutorial sheets and so on? Besides the money it saves, eating in school seems to be a pretty good idea, especially if you have to stay in pretty late: socialising …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Better than GBK
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-better-than-gbk/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 15:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-better-than-gbk/</guid>
        <description>I must start this article by giving credits to my Anonymous Kitchen Helpers: they are the ones who remade the puff-pastry last time, after ruining it. It’s always great having helping hands, even if sometimes they can be more of a hindrance.
But now I am not going to talk about my experiences …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Following a recipe is not as easy as it sounds
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-following-a-recipe-is-not-as-easy-as-it-sounds/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 14:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-following-a-recipe-is-not-as-easy-as-it-sounds/</guid>
        <description> The most challenging thing for me is to follow a recipe: I rarely do it, as most of the time I only improvise with what I have in the kitchen or what is given to me (thank you, nice people who stopped eating my food and started bringing their own). So imagine me standing in front of a cookbook, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Home Comfort
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-home-comfort/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 15:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-home-comfort/</guid>
        <description>Do you remember when you were five and after a few cold autumn days, you got so sick that you couldn’t get out of bed? But, miraculously, your mum knew exactly what to do so you would feel better. More often than not, it was suspense chicken soup, and in just an instant, you felt better! Now I don’t …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why cook at all?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-why-cook-at-all/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 17:06:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-why-cook-at-all/</guid>
        <description>The easiest way to make friends, anywhere, anytime, but specifically in college? Cook! I don’t mean the morning milk-and-cereal or ready meals you buy and just put in the microwave for five to ten minutes, I mean real food, prepared ‘with love’, just as your mother used to do before you left. I am …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Into the Inferno
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-into-the-inferno/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 15:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,Theo Farah,En Lai,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-into-the-inferno/</guid>
        <description>Violent. Destructive.Catastrophic. These may be the words you think of when encountering the word volcano. Werner Herzog, one of the world’s most influential directors, together with volcanologist Clive Oppenheimer, take you on a trip to the heart of the earth, with the question: are volcanoes all …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Harrogate
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-harrogate/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 14:33:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,Adam Gellatly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-harrogate/</guid>
        <description>After its successful debut at HighTide Festival in Suffolk last year, Harrogate - written by Al Smith and directed by Richard Twyman – arrives in London at the Royal Court to kick off its UK wide tour. The one act play, coming in at just over 80 minutes, finds itself perfectly suited to the cosy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Pacifist’s Guide to the War on Cancer
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-a-pacifists-guide-to-the-war-on-cancer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 14:25:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,Ezra Kitson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-a-pacifists-guide-to-the-war-on-cancer/</guid>
        <description>Bryony Kimmings’ latest project might be her most ambitious. A Pacifist’s Guide to the War on Cancer is a poignant portrayal of life alongside cancer, experienced through the naïve eyes of a mother whose baby boy is diagnosed. This sombre premise is transformed with all Kimmings’ charm and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In defence of ‘nasty women’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-in-defence-of-nasty-women/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 14:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-in-defence-of-nasty-women/</guid>
        <description>On the evening of the 19th October, at the University of Nevada’s Las Vegas campus, the phrase ‘nasty woman’ entered the internet’s lexicon. These words were uttered by Donald Trump towards the end of the third and final election debate, in a contest that has been defined by mud-slinging, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC squander ten point lead to go 0 from 2
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-28-ic-squander-ten-point-lead-to-go-0-from-2/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 15:51:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,Harry Allingham,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-28-ic-squander-ten-point-lead-to-go-0-from-2/</guid>
        <description>ICURFC 1st XV turned up to a surprisingly calm Harlington, looking for their first victory of the season against the University of Surrey. With stand-in skipper Mike Wright choosing to go against the wind and the slope, IC started strongly with the new structure appearing to work successfully. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC Women’s SICK-O performance
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-28-ic-womens-sick-o-performance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 15:46:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,Xinjin Ho,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-28-ic-womens-sick-o-performance/</guid>
        <description>To kick off the 2016&amp;frasl;17 season, the women of disc Doctors (dD) took part in the annual SICKO Indoors Ultimate Frisbee tournament held in Brighton from the 8th to the 9th of October 2016. Things weren’t looking great for us at the start. It was the first week back at University and it dawned on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College Eagles land first trophy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-28-imperial-college-eagles-land-first-trophy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 15:43:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,Aleksandar Kirilenko,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-28-imperial-college-eagles-land-first-trophy/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Handball managed to secure first place at the annual Fresher’s Tournament, which is considered by many as the unofficial beginning of the Handball battle amongst London Universities. It took place in the Olympic Copperbox arena and hosted teams from London’s top handball …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>There should be more to foreign aid than emergency support
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-28-there-should-be-more-to-foreign-aid-than-emergency-support/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 15:16:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,CATNIP FELIX,Eva Coles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-28-there-should-be-more-to-foreign-aid-than-emergency-support/</guid>
        <description>If you were to hear mention of Haiti in a conversation, what would your initial thoughts be? Some of you would likely confuse it with Tahiti or have no clue as to what Haiti actually is. For most of you, though, I am sure the first thing to pop into your minds would be the devastating 7.0 magnitude …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Donald was not created in a vacuum
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-28-the-donald-was-not-created-in-a-vacuum/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 14:59:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,Shaul Simmons,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-28-the-donald-was-not-created-in-a-vacuum/</guid>
        <description>Donald Trump is, as a bullyish toddler of a man, a hugely amusing individual. Except, perhaps, to those in the US whose lives may be a little more impacted by his caricature lunacy.
 We have to look more deeply at the root of the problem: the Republican Party itself
 He is, at heart, a TV …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
