<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jt2010/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jt2010/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Become a property owner in London
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-become-a-property-owner-in-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 21:48:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Tsim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-become-a-property-owner-in-london/</guid>
        <description>Imperial houses some of the wealthiest students in the UK. At Imperial, students are only able to live in college provided student accommodation for their first year, before moving out with friends or becoming a hall senior. As SW7 is the most expensive postcode in the UK, rent in the neighbourhood …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stop Waffling. Eat it instead!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-stop-waffling-eat-it-instead/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 16:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Tsim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-stop-waffling-eat-it-instead/</guid>
        <description>This is not your average waffle shop. Wafflemeister boasts a secret Belgian recipe which dates back to the 1950’s. The freshly made waffles are topped with a range of toppings from Belgian chocolate fudge and freshly whipped cream to fresh fruit and natural gelato. Wafflemeister is all about …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Shell Ideas360 comes to students!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-shell-ideas360-comes-to-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 10:36:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Tsim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-shell-ideas360-comes-to-students/</guid>
        <description>Shell Ideas360
Shell Ideas360 is an international competition open to all students which aims to produce the leading ideas to tackle the global energy, food and water issues of today. Students are invited to develop game changing ideas with an emphasis on innovative ideas which can be implemented to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Axe VAT for the hospitality industry
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-axe-vat-for-the-hospitality-industry/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 00:25:24 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Tsim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-axe-vat-for-the-hospitality-industry/</guid>
        <description>How can reducing VAT help the economy?
With high unemployment levels and increasing difficulty in finding jobs, the job market in the UK along with the economy needs boosting. One method suggested by the VAT club founded by Jacques Borel is that a reduction in VAT would increase sales and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Student Finance
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-student-finance/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 13:35:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Tsim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-student-finance/</guid>
        <description> Hopefully anyone who is eligible has already applied for Student Finance England. SFE offers student loans and grants which help cover university fees and living costs. Imperial College London also offers bursaries/scholarships which can be applied for.
Why open a student account? With the start of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>RCSU – Year in Review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-rcsu-year-in-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 23:42:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Tsim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-rcsu-year-in-review/</guid>
        <description>This academic year is coming to a close with exams and final year projects and soon the next RCSU committee will be taking the reins. We hope that you have enjoyed reading RCSU Broadsheet this year and keep reading next year! The RCSU this year has had fantastic turn-outs to events, with Freshers …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science Challenge returns
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-17-science-challenge-returns/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 23:53:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Tsim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-17-science-challenge-returns/</guid>
        <description>The RCSU Science Challenge returns! With a total prize-pot of over £4,000 to give away and the chance to win an all-expenses paid trip to CERN, Geneva, this is a competition you don’t want to miss. The Science Challenge was created in 2006 to encourage scientific debate, reasoning and the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
