<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/skd09/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/skd09/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Scientists protest to protect research
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-24-scientists-protest-to-protect-research/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 22:57:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-24-scientists-protest-to-protect-research/</guid>
        <description>On Tuesday 15 May, around 80 physicists and chemists from around the UK held an unusual protest against their research funder by parading a coffin and a horse-drawn hearse down London’s Whitehall to Downing Street.
The protest marked the start of the Science for the Future campaign which is fighting …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Green light for JUICE-y space mission
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-green-light-for-juice-y-space-mission/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 11:20:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-green-light-for-juice-y-space-mission/</guid>
        <description>The European Space Agency (ESA) is to lead a billion-euro mission to Jupiter and its icy moons. The Jupiter Icy Moons Explorer (JUICE) spacecraft is scheduled to launch in 2022, arriving in the Jupiter system in 2030.
A five-tonne satellite will be sent out to Jupiter in order to make a series of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Polish Club at risk of being sold
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-polish-club-at-risk-of-being-sold/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 06:04:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-polish-club-at-risk-of-being-sold/</guid>
        <description>A petition has been set up to save the Polish Club, Ognisko Polskie, based in Princes Gardens, which is at risk of being sold. The South Kensington club includes the Ognisko restaurant, popular with staff and students from Imperial.
Ognisko Polskie has existed for seventy-one years, promoting the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial falls in student experience survey
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-4-imperial-falls-in-student-experience-survey/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2012 01:02:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-4-imperial-falls-in-student-experience-survey/</guid>
        <description>Imperial has dropped nine places from last year in the Times Higher Education (THE) Student Experience Survey to take joint 71st place with Canterbury Christ Church University. The University of Dundee topped the survey with a score of 85% while Imperial scored 73.4%, slightly lower than the average …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students compete for global health project prize
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-4-students-compete-for-global-health-project-prize/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2012 00:26:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-4-students-compete-for-global-health-project-prize/</guid>
        <description>At the end of last term, the Institute of Global Health Innovation (IGHI) held the final of a new competition in which five students presented a global health project with which they were involved, competing for a prize of £2000 to put towards their project.
The students had ten minutes each to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Last great ape genome sequenced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-last-great-ape-genome-sequenced/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 19:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-last-great-ape-genome-sequenced/</guid>
        <description>A decade after the completion of the human genome sequence, researchers have sequenced the genome of a female western lowland gorilla called Kamilah from San Diego zoo. This means we now have a fully sequenced, representative genome sequence from each of the four great ape groups: humans, chimps and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>£10 million awarded to College Healthcare
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-9-10-million-awarded-to-college-healthcare/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 01:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-9-10-million-awarded-to-college-healthcare/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Healthcare Trust has been awarded over £10m from the National Institute for Health Research (NIHR) to develop new treatments. The Trust successfully bid for the funding to support its newly refurbished Wellcome Trust McMichael Clinical Research Facility at Hammersmith Hospital. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cumulative culture makes us different
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-cumulative-culture-makes-us-different/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 20:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-cumulative-culture-makes-us-different/</guid>
        <description>In the 21st century, our minds are brimming with concepts from iPhones to genetic testing to superstring theory, that could not have been entertained by our human counterparts centuries or millennia ago. This is because our species has a unique capability for “cumulative culture”, a process through …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New clubs at risk of rejection given another chance
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-new-clubs-at-risk-of-rejection-given-another-chance/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 22:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-new-clubs-at-risk-of-rejection-given-another-chance/</guid>
        <description>New proposals set out by the Union could mean that some prospective clubs and societies at risk of rejection must hold a test event in order to judge their viability and popularity. The suggested changes aim to ease decisions made by the New Clubs Committee on whether to accept or reject …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Solving the gender gap
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-solving-the-gender-gap/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 23:29:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-solving-the-gender-gap/</guid>
        <description>There are currently 81 female professors at Imperial which make up just 15% of the total holding this senior post. Felix has investigated what Imperial is doing to combat gender inequalities and support the career progression of women. In fact, a substantial movement exists within the College and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rector takes pay cut amidst university pay rises
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-rector-takes-pay-cut-amidst-university-pay-rises/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 23:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-rector-takes-pay-cut-amidst-university-pay-rises/</guid>
        <description>An examination of thirteen of the UK’s top universities’ financial statements from 2010-11 has revealed that their leaders earned an average salary of £333,000, with an average pay rise of £9,700.
The highest paid was Professor Andrew Hamilton, vice-chancellor of Oxford University, who received a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Blast Injury Centre set up at Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-blast-injury-centre-set-up-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 20:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-blast-injury-centre-set-up-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>A new £8m Royal British Legion Centre for Blast Injury Studies at Imperial College has officially opened this week. The Centre aims to provide a better understanding of the injuries caused by roadside bombs, or Improvised Explosive Devices (IEDs). These are the leading cause of death and injury for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New academic health science partnership
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-new-academic-health-science-partnership/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 22:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-new-academic-health-science-partnership/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London is establishing ties with numerous healthcare providers in North West London including approximately eleven NHS Trust hospitals and institutions. The new Academic Health Science Partnership (AHSP), to be launched in April 2012, aims to improve the health and care of the local …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Online calculator launched
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-online-calculator-launched/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 21:04:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-online-calculator-launched/</guid>
        <description>A new online calculator was launched this week by Imperial, aiming to give prospective students better access to information on the financial support available to help fund their studies.
 We’ve been working &amp;hellip; to develop a financial support package that is attractive and reassuring to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Malaria vaccine enters phase III trials
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-malaria-vaccine-enters-phase-iii-trials/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 19:54:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-malaria-vaccine-enters-phase-iii-trials/</guid>
        <description>A malaria vaccine candidate called RTS,S has been raising a stir within the health industry since the pharmaceutical giant, Glaxo-Smith Kline, announced highly promising results in its on-going phase III trials in Africa. Whilst it is unwise to declare success too soon, it is hoped that these early …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC Radio in exposé shutdown
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-ic-radio-in-expos-shutdown/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 19:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-ic-radio-in-expos-shutdown/</guid>
        <description>IC Radio was shut down last Friday after the college received a serious complaint following a show in which the presenters discussed the “dirty little secrets” of an unnamed student organisation. The complaint is thought to have been from a former or current committee member of the organisation who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PhD coffee row in Mechanical Engineering
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-phd-coffee-row-in-mechanical-engineering/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 20:22:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-phd-coffee-row-in-mechanical-engineering/</guid>
        <description>An experiment in the Mechanical Engineering department whereby PhD students have been allowed to share the academic common room (701) with staff members has ended after six months – with the eviction of students. In an email sent to the students involved, Mike Lowe, Chair of the Space Committee, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>University applications fall by 9%
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-university-applications-fall-by-9/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 19:58:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,Alexandra Nowbar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-university-applications-fall-by-9/</guid>
        <description>After years of steady increases, university applications are currently 9% lower than last year’s level at this time with 7000 fewer applications so far. Although the deadline for most courses is January, these figures from UCAS (University and College Admissions Service) are the first official …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>&#39;Largest ever&#39; Graduation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-largest-ever-graduation/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 19:19:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-largest-ever-graduation/</guid>
        <description>Imperial’s largest ever Commemoration Day took place on Wednesday as 2,200 undergraduates received their degrees in science, engineering and medicine. The ceremonies, watched by around 6,000 friends and family members at the Royal Albert Hall, also marked the first time on stage for the new Chair of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Business School hands out iPads to new intake
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-6-business-school-hands-out-ipads-to-new-intake/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 22:55:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-6-business-school-hands-out-ipads-to-new-intake/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Business School is welcoming its ﬁrst students of a new Masters programme and providing them with a free iPad 2 with which to carry out their studies. The programme leaders of the MSc in Strategic Marketing are scrapping the traditional paper-based learning and teaching methods and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Post-study work route could be saved
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-post-study-work-route-could-be-saved/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 19:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-post-study-work-route-could-be-saved/</guid>
        <description>The government is reconsidering its student visa proposals announced at the end of January. These included raising the minimum level of English proficiency required for entry, limiting opportunities for work experience and part time work for students, total abolishment of the post-study work route …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Recriminations as Bo’ gets cut
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-recriminations-as-bo-gets-cut/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 05:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-recriminations-as-bo-gets-cut/</guid>
        <description>The Clubs and Societies Board (CSB) have allocated their funding for the next academic year, with the City and Guilds College Union (CGCU) taking a 30% cut whilst the Royal Society of Science Union (RSCU) allocation is to rise by 95%.
The CGCU’s 30% reduction was the largest cut suffered by any of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Protect campus free speech says report
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-protect-campus-free-speech-says-report/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 21:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-protect-campus-free-speech-says-report/</guid>
        <description>Universities UK has published a report on how universities can promote freedom of speech whilst “protecting the safety and wellbeing of students, staff and the wider community.”
The report firmly acknowledges the importance of freedom within the academic setting, saying that if universities are to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Measures to reduce hall rents considered
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-measures-to-reduce-hall-rents-considered/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 19:38:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-measures-to-reduce-hall-rents-considered/</guid>
        <description>The price of university hall accommodation has come under scrutiny as a survey is set to be launched by the Union into how hall rents could be reduced. The Union has obtained a breakdown of what makes up the rent and are debating a range of cost-saving measures. Students are encouraged to take part …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>£940 million cut to higher education funding
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-940-million-cut-to-higher-education-funding/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 20:11:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-940-million-cut-to-higher-education-funding/</guid>
        <description>University funding for teaching and research is to be cut by £940 million for the 2011-12 academic year, a decision described as “a challenging financial settlement” by the chief executive of the Higher Education Funding Council for England (Hefce) which announced the cuts last week. Universities …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>£9,000 fees “preferable” says Union President
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-9000-fees-preferable-says-union-president/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 19:33:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-9000-fees-preferable-says-union-president/</guid>
        <description>Tuition fees of £9000 a year would be “far more preferable” according to the ICU President, Alex Kendall, as well as the norm for “the majority of universities” according to the NUS President, Aaron Porter. These latest comments have arisen as the “Student Fees and Financial Aid Working Group” …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PhD funding blunder in Aeronautics Department
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-phd-funding-blunder-in-aeronautics-department/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 18:24:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-phd-funding-blunder-in-aeronautics-department/</guid>
        <description>Eleven PhD students in the Department of Aeronautics have been left angered and confused after their monthly bursary payments were cut in December and January. No forewarning was given to the students; a blunder described as “unfortunate” by the Head of Department.
Nine of the affected students are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fears for Humanities
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-fears-for-humanities/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 20:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-fears-for-humanities/</guid>
        <description>For many students, the option to balance their science degrees with humanities subjects is fantastic opportunity offered to ensure they acquire the widest range of skills during their time here. However, some of the proposed timetable changes could increase the pressure on humanities students. It is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Feasibility of longer day called into question
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-feasibility-of-longer-day-called-into-question/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 20:49:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,Sophia David,Zainab Ali,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-feasibility-of-longer-day-called-into-question/</guid>
        <description>It came as a shock to many last week when Felix reported that a College committee is investigating changes to the length of the College day. The proposals, which include extending the day to 8am until 7pm for undergraduates and until 8pm for postgraduates, on Mondays and Thursdays, are still under …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The human cost of the restructure
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-the-human-cost-of-the-restructure/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 21:53:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-the-human-cost-of-the-restructure/</guid>
        <description>The 14 academics lost to the Life Sciences department represent the most incredible array of talent, expertise and experience. The staff caught up in the restructuring, deemed unsuitable for the new department, have nevertheless contributed enormously to university life, being involved in teaching, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Has feedback improved?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-has-feedback-improved/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 21:48:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-has-feedback-improved/</guid>
        <description>The start of term saw Imperial announce a campaign to improve the assessment of students’ work. Ahead of the end of term surveys, Felix investigates the improvements that have been made. Has the college gone far enough or is there still more that should be done?
The National Student Survey showed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grim employment prospects as recession hits graduates
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-grim-employment-prospects-as-recession-hits-graduates/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 19:12:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-grim-employment-prospects-as-recession-hits-graduates/</guid>
        <description>Graduate unemployment has risen to 8.9%, a rise of one percentage point from the previous year. This is the conclusion of a survey by the Higher Education Careers Services Unit (HECSU) of 225,000 graduates questioned in January this year, after leaving university in the summer of 2008.
Employment …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Government rejects Browne Review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-government-rejects-browne-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 19:59:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-government-rejects-browne-review/</guid>
        <description>Government ministers have confirmed that university tuition fees will be capped in England, meaning that the government is rejecting a key element of the Browne report.
The report, led by Lord Browne, suggested universities should be allowed to set their own fees but face a levy on amounts over …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial wins as science is spared major cuts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-imperial-wins-as-science-is-spared-major-cuts/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 19:30:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophia David,Katherine Bettany,Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-imperial-wins-as-science-is-spared-major-cuts/</guid>
        <description>In the controversial Spending Review presented to Parliament on Wednesday, George Osborne revealed the details of the UK’s deepest spending cuts for decades, designed to reduce our budget deficit by £83 billion pounds before 2014&amp;frasl;15.
With Britain paying £120 million a day in debt interest …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
