<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/cet13/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/cet13/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>National Student Survey results reveal wide ranges in student satisfaction
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-25-national-student-survey-results-reveal-wide-ranges-in-student-satisfaction/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 10:26:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-25-national-student-survey-results-reveal-wide-ranges-in-student-satisfaction/</guid>
        <description> The results from the National Student Survey (NSS), which saw a number of universities omitted following a boycott, show a divide among Imperial students, with a wide range in satisfaction rates between undergraduate courses.
The survey, which is given to all final-year undergraduates, showed that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Manifesto breakdowns
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-manifesto-breakdowns/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:59:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,Cale E Tilford,Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-manifesto-breakdowns/</guid>
        <description> This piece aims to break down the main party manifestos and summarise a few key policies. This is by no means a full and in-depth analysis of each party. Mainly because the manifestos are long and complex, and it’s exam season. [Insert tinfoil hat theory that the timing of the election coincides …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Afterhours sessions in the Central Library
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-afterhours-sessions-in-the-central-library/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:29:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-afterhours-sessions-in-the-central-library/</guid>
        <description>How does one end up in the Library past midnight? Maybe you had a paper to submit tomorrow. You thought you had everything under control. You were halfway there but you made the mistake of taking a break and committing to an episode of the Great British Bake Off. Six hours later you get a text from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My first week with Switch
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-my-first-week-with-switch/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 17:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-my-first-week-with-switch/</guid>
        <description>The first thing I did after unboxing my Nintendo Switch was to lick the game cartridge. Videos of games and tech journalists doing the same went viral during the week of the Switch’s launch after Jeff Gertsmann of Giant Bomb discovered their bitter aftertaste. However, the taste serves a purpose …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The felix sex survey 2017 #callmedaddy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-16-the-felix-sex-survey-2017-callmedaddy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2017 19:22:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,Felix Editor,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-16-the-felix-sex-survey-2017-callmedaddy/</guid>
        <description>The 2017 felix sex survey is now LIVE! Fill it out here
</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The university meme page revolution
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-the-university-meme-page-revolution/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 15:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,Paul Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-the-university-meme-page-revolution/</guid>
        <description>T his strange world of memes which we currently find ourselves in – one where a president can be catapulted to the White House with the help of online fascists and Pepe the Frog – is terrifying. There was an undercurrent of darkness in the memes that defined 2016: we celebrated Harambe’s death as if …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Arrival
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-arrival/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 18:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-arrival/</guid>
        <description>At some point during their time at school, children will inevitably be asked to describe something in simple enough terms that even an alien, having just arrived on Earth, would understand. Like much of what is taught at school, this exercise is completely detached from reality. It assumes that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Harambe vigil in Hyde Park
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-harambe-vigil-in-hyde-park/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 13:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-harambe-vigil-in-hyde-park/</guid>
        <description>Up to 3000 are expected to attend a candle-lit vigil this Friday in Hyde Park to commemorate the life and death of Harambe, the Gorilla killed earlier this year at the Cincinnati Zoo and Botanical Garden in Ohio. The event, which was set up by third year Computing student Paul Balaji in response to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science Museum exhibition criticised
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-14-science-museum-exhibition-criticised/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 09:30:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-14-science-museum-exhibition-criticised/</guid>
        <description>Over 50 academics and other campaigners, including two members of Imperial College’s Science Communication unit, have signed a letter this week calling for the Science Museum to end its deal with Statoil, a Norwegian oil and gas giant, as the headline sponsor of the new children’s exhibition, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The vital importance of being mediocre
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-the-vital-importance-of-being-mediocre/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 18:39:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Vivien Hadlow,Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-the-vital-importance-of-being-mediocre/</guid>
        <description>University is a time for learning new things. By the time you leave you’ll (hopefully) be able to make nutritionally passable food, complete group projects without stabbing anyone, and compose the perfect passive aggressive group chat message about washing up. But, arguably apart from the content of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College contemplating smoking ban
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-college-contemplating-smoking-ban/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 11:08:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-college-contemplating-smoking-ban/</guid>
        <description>If you follow the IC Union pages on Twitter or Facebook you may have seen the recent poll they ran on the question of “Should smoking be allowed on campus?”.
The snap poll was taken by the Union not as their own initiative but in order to get a broader view of the student body’s opinion.
A College …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FELIX’s Guide to E3 2016
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-felixs-guide-to-e3-2016/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 08:36:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-felixs-guide-to-e3-2016/</guid>
        <description>Despite a number of premature announcements earlier this week, E3 looks to be as exciting as ever. For gamers there’s no time of the year that is more anticipated and for gaming journalists (which I don’t qualify as yet) there is none hated more. While a few early leaks and reveals have surprised …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Scratching an Itch
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-scratching-an-itch/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 09:26:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-scratching-an-itch/</guid>
        <description>Into, or, I Turned My Autobiography Into a Fictional Second-Person Surreal Coming-Out-Of-Age Dramedy and Now My Life Is Happier is not like many experiences you’ve interacted with before. In three short, distinct scenes it captures one person’s coming of age. Across these the screen focuses equally …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Escaping the uncanny valley
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-escaping-the-uncanny-valley/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 08:59:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-escaping-the-uncanny-valley/</guid>
        <description>A major criticism of the Uncharted trilogy has always been that it is more style than substance, that is focuses too heavily on glorious set-pieces and stunning scenery to mask its flaws. That is not to say that these games don’t have substantial playable elements – they do – but the gameplay that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PC Music are not dead
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-pc-music-are-not-dead/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 08:58:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-pc-music-are-not-dead/</guid>
        <description>Last Thursday’s Pop Cosmos was another of PC Music’s rare live shows, assembling together the collective for an evening of non-stop music. In the run up to the event at London’s Scala, gig-goers are told that this is an evening to “lose yourself in an immersive journey to the end of time.” The stage …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>That’s so Ratchet
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-thats-so-ratchet/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 09:17:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-thats-so-ratchet/</guid>
        <description>In the 14 years since Ratchet &amp;amp; Clank’s original release on the PS2, the platforming genre has seen a dramatic decline. Nintendo has been the sole torchbearer in a genre which was once the industry’s most successful; it continues to produce quality and innovative platformers while others have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In the music streaming wars we all lose
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-in-the-music-streaming-wars-we-all-lose/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 09:14:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-in-the-music-streaming-wars-we-all-lose/</guid>
        <description>Another week and yet another timed exclusive on a streaming service. This time it’s Chance the Rapper’s Coloring Book, exclusive to Apple Music for two weeks.
I’m growing fucking tired of this shit. It’s not like streaming services are actually distinguishable in functionality in any meaningful way. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Itch.io Game of the Week
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-itchio-game-of-the-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 09:30:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-itchio-game-of-the-week/</guid>
        <description>Dr. Langeskov is the first game by Crows Crows Crows – a studio formed by game writer and designer William Pugh of The Stanley Parable fame. The first person exploration game, that will be familiar to anyone who has played Pugh’s previous works, lasts around 20 minutes (it’s free, so don’t …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nintendo’s twilight years
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-nintendos-twilight-years/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 09:29:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-nintendos-twilight-years/</guid>
        <description>When The Legend of Zelda: Twilight Princess was first released in 2006, Nintendo was at a turning point. It had just released the Wii, which would radically alter its fortunes, after years of losing sales to Sony with the disappointing GameCube. The years preceding this represented some of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The protest album of the decade
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-the-protest-album-of-the-decade/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 09:05:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-the-protest-album-of-the-decade/</guid>
        <description>Hope was the word that came to represent Obama’s presidential campaign back in 2008. For a few brief moments the world – inspired by Shepard Fairey’s iconic poster – genuinely believed that change might finally come to neoliberal America. After eight years in office, Obama has grown old and the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Captain America: Civil War
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-captain-america-civil-war/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 10:13:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-captain-america-civil-war/</guid>
        <description>The struggle between good and evil – between superheroes and supervillains – has remained at the centre of the Marvel Cinematic Universe (and blockbusters in general) since its inception in 2008’s Iron Man. Without exception, the antagonists of the eleven following Marvel films have always …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>emily is away
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-emily-is-away/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:57:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-emily-is-away/</guid>
        <description>Emily is away is an interactive, branching visual novel set in MSN-inspired chat client. Its visuals and sound effects, from the classic Windows XP start sound to the low rumbling of a desktop computer, will be instantly familiar to those who grew up using Microsoft’s iconic communication software. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A different sort of storefront
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-a-different-sort-of-storefront/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:56:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-a-different-sort-of-storefront/</guid>
        <description>Itch.io is a platform that allows indie game developers to distribute their games for free. The majority of games available on the platform are either free, incredibly cheap or pay-what-you-want. Itch corp has even experimented with reverse sales - allowing developers to increase the price of their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>#HotTakes of the Week
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-hottakes-of-the-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 11:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-hottakes-of-the-week/</guid>
        <description>No more CDs from me
Never to be one out of the headlines, this week Kanye West described the minimalist, clear jewel box packaging to his last album Yeezus as an “an open casket to CDs r.i.p”. Apparently there will be no more CDs from him, with all future releases exclusive to digital platforms. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The dreamy synth-pop of Throwing Shade
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-8-the-dreamy-synth-pop-of-throwing-shade/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 16:51:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jeni Pillai,Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-8-the-dreamy-synth-pop-of-throwing-shade/</guid>
        <description>Throwing Shade, AKA Nabihah Iqbal, is an artist who educates. Her background in history and ethnomusicology (in which she holds a degree from SOAS) heavily influences her bi-weekly NTS Radio show, where she weaves sounds from all over the world into a culturally rich sonic tapestry, exploding with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Future of Pop
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-the-future-of-pop/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 11:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-the-future-of-pop/</guid>
        <description>Until recently, many saw the netlabel and electronic collective PC Music as the future of pop. However, even after a number of brilliant, innovative releases they’ve remained on the fringes. Danny L Harle’s debut EP Broken Flowers, their first release on a major label, might have had a single that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Unravelling the past
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-unravelling-the-past/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 11:56:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-unravelling-the-past/</guid>
        <description>Platformers (that aren’t made by Nintendo) have seen a revival in recent years, with a large focus on artstyle and graphical fidelity. Rayman Legends, LittleBigPlanet, Bionic Commando, and Shadow Complex are all notable for their presentation, whether realistic or stylised. Innovating within the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Take a hike with Firewatch
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-take-a-hike-with-firewatch/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 12:24:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-take-a-hike-with-firewatch/</guid>
        <description>Telltale’s The Walking Dead was met with critical acclaim when it was released in 2012, and arguably revitalised the dying adventure game genre. Firewatch has much in common with Telltale’s game, released by Campo Santo, a studio founded by creative leads who had previously worked on The Walking …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FELIX Music #HotTakes of the week
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-felix-music-hottakes-of-the-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 12:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-felix-music-hottakes-of-the-week/</guid>
        <description>He wanted the world to know his struggle
The Life of Pablo really wasn’t worth the hype (sorry Ben). And Mr. West certainly isn’t happy with all the critics who have dared to suggest it isn’t the god-like masterpiece he had hoped (Pitchfork gave it a 9.0 so I don’t know why he’s complaining). I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Deadpool – the Reddit of movies?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-deadpool-the-reddit-of-movies/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 12:01:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-deadpool-the-reddit-of-movies/</guid>
        <description>Critics have been predicting comic book movie fatigue ever since Marvel’s The Avengers back in 2012, yet audiences are turning out in droves to increasingly stale comic based blockbusters.
Many had hoped that Deadpool, the eighth installment in the X-Men series and the directorial debut of Tim …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FELIX Music #HotTakes of the week
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-felix-music-hottakes-of-the-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 11:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-felix-music-hottakes-of-the-week/</guid>
        <description>In a tweet that would probably enrage most Imperial students, Allen’s response to the Education Minister asked the same question school children have been asking for years. She’s right that a lot of people are unlikely to ever use the maths or science they learnt at school in real life, but the same …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gravity Rush Remastered
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-gravity-rush-remastered/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 11:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-gravity-rush-remastered/</guid>
        <description>There are very few games that have provided the same joy and awe as Super Mario Galaxy. I remember fondly the moment when I, as Mario, was able to run around a small spherical planet for the first time. I wasn’t defying gravity; I was adhering to it, in a way no game had ever done before. It didn’t …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Land’s End is a VR gem
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-lands-end-is-a-vr-gem/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 12:43:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-lands-end-is-a-vr-gem/</guid>
        <description>For a gaming device to truly succeed it needs a great launch title. Land’s End, a virtual reality puzzle adventure from the creators of Monument Valley, is the game that every owner of the device must play. Developers Ustwo truly understand the power of the new medium and where it works best, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FELIX reacts to virtual reality
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-felix-reacts-to-virtual-reality/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 12:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Indira Mallik,Cale E Tilford,Lef Apostolakis,Saad Ahmed,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-felix-reacts-to-virtual-reality/</guid>
        <description>The year of virtual reality is finally upon us. This week, the FELIX team tried Gear VR, Samsung’s mobile virtual reality headset.
It’s not as powerful as competitors like Oculus Rift or the HTC Vive, but it’s a decent introduction to VR for the unacquainted.
Lef Apostolakis, Science Editor
I tried …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rhodes must fall
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-rhodes-must-fall/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 11:52:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-rhodes-must-fall/</guid>
        <description>Last week Oriel College, Oxford confirmed that a monument commemorating Cecil Rhodes, a 19th century British imperialist, would remain despite a massive movement by students seeking the removal of the statue. Like many of the students at Oxford University, I’m disappointed by the college’s decision …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rolling in the deep (space)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-rolling-in-the-deep-space/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 10:07:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-rolling-in-the-deep-space/</guid>
        <description>Fiendishly difficult games have proven popular with gamers in recent years. Most of these games require fast reactions and an intimate understanding of each level or enemy. Tharsis is as difficult as games like Dark Souls and Bloodborne and it should be. Your spacecraft is on it’s way to Mars. It …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>That Dragon, Cancer
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-that-dragon-cancer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 10:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-that-dragon-cancer/</guid>
        <description>The titular metaphor of Ryan and Amy Green’s autobiographical exploration game – that cancer is a dragon – is used to describe their young son’s condition to a more innocent audience. Cancer is a beast that is likely to haunt most of us directly or indirectly throughout our lives. The sheer power of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is it human to adore life?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-is-it-human-to-adore-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 09:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-is-it-human-to-adore-life/</guid>
        <description>Adore Life is an album about the good and the bad parts of love. The title should really be a question because Jenny Beth and her band are conflicted: “Is it human to adore life?”
Savages stream of post-punk is extremely accessible and flirts with all sorts of sounds. The quartet come together …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Savages before breakfast
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-savages-before-breakfast/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 09:35:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-savages-before-breakfast/</guid>
        <description>In interviews, Savages have always described themselves as a live band: “you don’t understand who we are unless you see us play live.” They aim to create a reaction with their live act, something more than static head bobbing. Watching the video for ‘The Answer,’ the first song on their new album …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>SOPHIE, sweet like whipped cream
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-sophie-sweet-like-whipped-cream/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 09:33:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-sophie-sweet-like-whipped-cream/</guid>
        <description>Over the last few years, SOPHIE (the stage name of Samuel Long) has played many times in London and around the world. I’ve been lucky enough to see him twice. This time he played at Village Underground, one of London’s most hip venues. With each successive live performance he has debuted new …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Suicide Squad trailer is not okay
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-the-suicide-squad-trailer-is-not-okay/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 09:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-the-suicide-squad-trailer-is-not-okay/</guid>
        <description>When it comes to the shortcomings of Marvel or DC’s cinematic output, as a self-confessed comic book fan-boy, I’m usually pretty forgiving. Unfortunately, the first official trailer for DC’s latest film, Suicide Squad, which dropped last week, hints at a film with some serious flaws. It might only …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Business school still 4th best in UK says FT
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-business-school-still-4th-best-in-uk-says-ft/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 08:47:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-business-school-still-4th-best-in-uk-says-ft/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Business School’s full-time MBA program is the 35th best in the world and the fourth best in the UK according to the 2016 Financial Times MBA rankings released this week.
The list, which is published annually, ranks business schools based on the average weighted salary of students, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>12 Jar Jar Binks GIFs That Sum Up Your Life At Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-16-12-jar-jar-binks-gifs-that-sum-up-your-life-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 18:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,Felix Editor,Theresa Davey,Grace G Rahman,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-16-12-jar-jar-binks-gifs-that-sum-up-your-life-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description> 1. When You Arrive Sober At Your First ACC  2. When You Sit Your First Exam At Imperial    Tumblr   3. When You Can&amp;rsquo;t Decide Between Pieminister And The Salad Bar    Tumblr   4. When You Fall For Your Lab Partner    Tumblr   5. When It&amp;rsquo;s Five To Nine And You&amp;rsquo;re Desperate For The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FELIX&#39;s top games of 2015
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-12-felixs-top-games-of-2015/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2015 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-12-felixs-top-games-of-2015/</guid>
        <description> 4. Rocket League    Tumblr   Rocket League is the sequel to Supersonic Acrobatic Rocket-Powered Battle-Cars, a name which, while a bit of a mouthful, is a fairly accurate description of both games. It’s essentially a football game, but with cars. Obviously, cars don’t have feet so they couldn’t …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Problematic yet representative?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-4-problematic-yet-representative/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 15:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-4-problematic-yet-representative/</guid>
        <description>In an interview on IC Radio two weeks ago, our union president revealed a number of potentially problematic views. We all say things we later go on to regret; it’s symptomatic of the social media age. But, our union president chose to defend her contentious tweets, including one which some Imperial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FELIX’s Mercury Prize picks
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-felixs-mercury-prize-picks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 09:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,Peter Munton,Robert Garside,Fred S Fyles,Cale E Tilford,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-felixs-mercury-prize-picks/</guid>
        <description> _In Colour_Jamie xx Oh Jamie, you can do no wrong. Not in my eyes, the eyes of anyone who went outdoors this summer who was inundated with your invariably uplifting ‘Good Times’, and presumably, not in the eyes of the Mercury Music Prize people.
The flabbergasting combo of Jamie Smith, dance hall …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>MS MR
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-ms-mr/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 09:28:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-ms-mr/</guid>
        <description>It’s rare to find a band with such mesmerising on-stage chemistry. Last Tuesday at Electric Brixton, MS MR brought their dynamic live show to London.
Lead singer Lizzy Plapinger’s genuine excitement was evident in her sweat and tears; her presence put the audience in a state of awe. It was difficult …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>TĀLĀ live at ICA
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-tl-live-at-ica/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 09:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-tl-live-at-ica/</guid>
        <description>Gracefully floating from synth to drums, TALA immediately made the stage her own, pouring every part of herself into her singing, lyrics and production.
The ICA often plays host to multidisciplinary artists, but TALA has honed a single craft, the ability to reconstruct an electronic song …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Love, sex, and the internet
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-love-sex-and-the-internet/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 14:52:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-love-sex-and-the-internet/</guid>
        <description>Nina Freeman has made a name for herself developing weird and wonderful autobiographical games. Many of them only take minutes to play; however, in these vignettes, Freeman pushes the boundaries of the medium more than any ten hour epic has ever been able to do.
Much of the appeal of Freeman’s work …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grimes’ radiant Art Angels
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-grimes-radiant-art-angels/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 14:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-grimes-radiant-art-angels/</guid>
        <description>With Visions, Grimes (the stage name of Claire Boucher) gave us an album that combined the danceable sound of synthpop with introspection and sorrow of dark-wave. One of the defining albums of 2012, it was celebrated and adored by many including myself.
Upon first hearing ‘REALiTi’ (the original …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your internet history is up for grabs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-your-internet-history-is-up-for-grabs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 14:29:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-your-internet-history-is-up-for-grabs/</guid>
        <description>Since Edward Snowden’s leaks in 2013, many have compared the British state to The Party from George Orwell’s prophetic Nineteen Eighty-Four. The Party seeks power; not to improve the lives of others, but entirely for its own interests. From the transceiving television sets used to monitor the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The auditory overload of Garden of Delete
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-the-auditory-overload-of-garden-of-delete/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 14:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-the-auditory-overload-of-garden-of-delete/</guid>
        <description>From the guy who probably invented vaporwave, comes in even more weird shit. Experimental American musician, Daniel Lopatin (more commonly known as Oneohtrix Point Never) ruptures the walls of reality with his new record Garden of Delete.
Oneohtrix Point Never records have always managed to sound …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The triumphant return of Guitar Hero
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-the-triumphant-return-of-guitar-hero/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 14:23:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-the-triumphant-return-of-guitar-hero/</guid>
        <description>Until recently, the click-clack of plastic peripherals felt like a distant memory. Yet, only five years have passed since the death of the rhythm gaming industry. From billions to almost nothing, in 2010 Activision could do nothing as one of their most lucrative franchises melted away.
To observers, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Iglooghost’s latest EP is full on wonky
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-iglooghosts-latest-ep-is-full-on-wonky/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 14:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-iglooghosts-latest-ep-is-full-on-wonky/</guid>
        <description>Iglooghost is the latest signing to Flying Lotus’ Brainfeeder imprint, and the influence he’s had on the 18-year old producer is immediately noticeable in his latest EP, Chinese Nü Yr. The concept EP tells the story of a gelatinous worm-like creature as it travels through endless wormholes to pink …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why are Imperial students so apathetic about politics?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-30-why-are-imperial-students-so-apathetic-about-politics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 12:36:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-30-why-are-imperial-students-so-apathetic-about-politics/</guid>
        <description>The students of Imperial are, in my experience, greatly lacking in their enthusiasm for political and social issues when compared to their contemporaries at other institutions. While it might be true that there is growing resentment and disillusionment among students towards the political class, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Four Tet All Nighter
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-four-tet-all-nighter/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 11:54:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-four-tet-all-nighter/</guid>
        <description>The last time I spent a night at Brixton Academy the air was thick with smelly marijuana and fruity vapour. The fully engaged crowd swayed, bobbed and even lurched to the music, all focused on the man in the centre of the stage, walled in by a cube of screens and flashing lights.
 A night bathed in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Beach House’s latest is dream-popfection
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-beach-houses-latest-is-dream-popfection/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 11:51:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-beach-houses-latest-is-dream-popfection/</guid>
        <description>It’s rare to see bands produce such consistently great music, and the few that do offer substantial evolution of their sound over time. Beach House, on the other hand, have released six albums that all sound very similar, each a slight refinement of the one before. Thank Your Lucky Stars is no …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Comic Books: Where to Start?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-comic-books-where-to-start/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 13:39:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-comic-books-where-to-start/</guid>
        <description> The Wicked + The Divine The Wicked + The Divine was once described as the spiritual successor to Kieron Gillen and Jamie McKelvie’s Phonogram, the Britpop inspired comic series ‘where music is magic’, and whilst it borrows many of the themes of their earlier collaboration this series is far more …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
