<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/avirup_banerjee/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/avirup_banerjee/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Venezuela in crisis - the untold story</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-venezuela-in-crisis-the-untold-story/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Avirup Banerjee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-venezuela-in-crisis-the-untold-story/</guid>
        <description>War is a racket”, General Smedley Butler warned in 1935. Butler, who was the most decorated marine at the time of his death, was sent by his government to South America to establish one banana republic after another. The drums of war are at it again, this time in Venezuela, brought to you by the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>War, What Is It Good For? Absolutely Nothing!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-war-what-is-it-good-for-absolutely-nothing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Avirup Banerjee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-war-what-is-it-good-for-absolutely-nothing/</guid>
        <description>On 14th February 14, 40 Indian paramilitary soldiers were killed by a suicide bombing in Indian-Administered Kashmir. Whilst the bomber was born and raised in India (a fact ignored by the Indian media), he was funded and equipped by the Pakistan based terrorist organisation JeM, who have publicly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The World’s Largest Election in History - and no one is talking about it! </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-the-world-s-largest-election-in-history-and-no-one-is-talking-about-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Avirup Banerjee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-the-world-s-largest-election-in-history-and-no-one-is-talking-about-it/</guid>
        <description>The American election of 2020 is still 600 days away, yet even in the British press there is at least one article a day on any declared or even potential candidates to challenge Donald Trump. Yet very little focus has been given by the international press to the biggest election in human history …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>With Bolsonaro’s victory in the second round, Brazil goes down a tenebrous path</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-with-bolsonaro-s-victory-in-the-second-round-brazil-goes-down-a-tenebrous-path/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Avirup Banerjee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-with-bolsonaro-s-victory-in-the-second-round-brazil-goes-down-a-tenebrous-path/</guid>
        <description>In last week’s run-off election, Brazil’s fascist-in-chief Jair Bolsonaro won the presidency with 55% of the vote. Yes, fascist is the appropriate description, and let the record show that this was a far from a fair fight. From the 2016 impeachment of the former President Dilma Rouseff on flimsy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Save the American Supreme Court from the Republicans</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-15-how-to-save-the-american-supreme-court-from-the-republicans/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Avirup Banerjee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-15-how-to-save-the-american-supreme-court-from-the-republicans/</guid>
        <description>After the election of 1800, who would become the third President of the American Republic was very much a mystery. With the electoral college tied at 73 between Thomas Jefferson and Aaron Burr, the decision was left to the House of Representatives with Jefferson only winning the Presidency after the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Labour Party does not have a problem with Anti-Semitism</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-the-labour-party-does-not-have-a-problem-with-anti-semitism/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Avirup Banerjee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-the-labour-party-does-not-have-a-problem-with-anti-semitism/</guid>
        <description>The ancient Chinese had a curse: ‘may he live in interesting times’ – well these are interesting times when the president of the United States claims there are good people on the side of neo-Nazis and with the electoral success of far-right neo-Nazi political groups all over Europe and America. But …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>China’s House of Cards – The rise of Xi Jingping as China’s President for life </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-china-s-house-of-cards-the-rise-of-xi-jingping-as-china-s-president-for-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Avirup Banerjee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-china-s-house-of-cards-the-rise-of-xi-jingping-as-china-s-president-for-life/</guid>
        <description>In 1911, the Wuchang Uprising brought down the Qing Dynasty, thus bringing to an end the longest continuous imperial civilization of 8,000 years. One of the most powerful dogmas perpetrated by the ancient Mandarins that allowed the firm rule of the emperors was the idea that the emperors had a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Winter Olympic’s joint South &amp; North Korean delegation</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-the-winter-olympic-s-joint-south-north-korean-delegation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Avirup Banerjee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-the-winter-olympic-s-joint-south-north-korean-delegation/</guid>
        <description>One of the worst clichés trotted out during world sporting events, like the Olympics, is that sport should be above politics. Yet this couldn’t be further from the truth. Some of the most memorable moments in Olympic history have been steeped in politics: from Jesse Owens’ defying Adolf Hitler’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The trial of Winston Churchill and the British Empire he helped to build</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-the-trial-of-winston-churchill-and-the-british-empire-he-helped-to-build/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Avirup Banerjee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-the-trial-of-winston-churchill-and-the-british-empire-he-helped-to-build/</guid>
        <description>Carthage must be destroyed, the Roman Senator Cato the Elder decried at the end of all his speeches, irrespective of the original topic at hand. As a result of the tenacity of the war-mongering Roman elite, a once mighty civilization was reduced to rubble. Thus, if history teaches us anything, it is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The making of a modern monopoly</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-the-making-of-a-modern-monopoly/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Avirup Banerjee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-the-making-of-a-modern-monopoly/</guid>
        <description>In 1858, the British Crown bailed out and nationalised the most powerful company in human history. A company that had a standing army of 280,000 men, which it used to enslave a 6th of humanity and rule over an area in excess of 5 million km2. In fact, such was the power and influence of the British …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
