<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ad4812/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ad4812/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Sport to be reshuffled next year
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-sport-to-be-reshuffled-next-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abigail E de Bruin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-sport-to-be-reshuffled-next-year/</guid>
        <description>Since about January, there have been rumblings in the Union of a big sports shake-up. We got in touch with James Cox, current Deputy President (Clubs and Societies) to see what’s happening now that things are pretty much ready to be openly discussed. It appears we are set to go into a full year of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial to get HEFCE Funding
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-imperial-to-get-hefce-funding/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 13:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Abigail E de Bruin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-imperial-to-get-hefce-funding/</guid>
        <description>Imperial has been selected as one of 64 institutions to receive up to £50,000 of HEFCE Catalyst funding from the Student Safeguarding fund. This is part of the £2.45 million released by HEFCE for projects addressing sexual harassment on campus following the report from Universities UK’s Harassment …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial celebrates women in Science
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-imperial-celebrates-women-in-science/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 13:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abigail E de Bruin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-imperial-celebrates-women-in-science/</guid>
        <description>Tuesday evening saw the launch event of the Women@Imperial Week in the College Main Entrance. Women@Imperial Week is an annual celebration of the achievements of past and present female staff and students at Imperial.
The event started with a panel discussion titled “Gender Equality: Ongoing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>King’s Fossil Free leads to student arrest
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-kings-fossil-free-leads-to-student-arrest/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 14:24:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abigail E de Bruin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-kings-fossil-free-leads-to-student-arrest/</guid>
        <description>Anyone that’s been around Imperial a while will remember the Fossil Free Campaign posters that went up during first term a few years ago. These declared “Imperial’s getting coal for Christmas” as part of a larger campaign to try and get Imperial to divest from fossil fuels. Whilst the Imperial group …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Animal rights group protest Imperial’s receipt of animal research award
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-animal-rights-group-protest-imperials-receipt-of-animal-research-award/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 13:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abigail E de Bruin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-animal-rights-group-protest-imperials-receipt-of-animal-research-award/</guid>
        <description>Just before the end of last term we ran an article about the fact that Imperial College had been awarded for Public Engagement Activity in the annual ‘Openness on Animal Research Awards’. In response we were contacted by Cruelty Free International and given a press release from the animal rights …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial wins Animal Testing award
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-imperial-wins-animal-testing-award/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 23:59:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abigail E de Bruin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-imperial-wins-animal-testing-award/</guid>
        <description>Imperial has had a pretty rocky history with Animal Research within the College and its public image. From the low point of the 2014 Home Office statement that there was a “widespread poor culture of care”, such clear progress has been made that College have now been awarded for their work towards …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We cannot ignore the consent crisis
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-we-cannot-ignore-the-consent-crisis/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 13:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abigail E de Bruin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-we-cannot-ignore-the-consent-crisis/</guid>
        <description>Consent is a pretty hot topic at the moment. It’s been in this newspaper a lot and in fact in the national news a lot too. So why is it that consent is such a matter of importance in the public minds at the moment? Well, to put bluntly, if sex doesn’t involve it then it’s not sex – it’s rape. And …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Student accommodation situation dire
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-student-accommodation-situation-dire/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 13:35:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Abigail E de Bruin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-student-accommodation-situation-dire/</guid>
        <description>The skyrocketing price of student accommodation has been an ongoing issue in the minds of students, one that certainly feels all too familiar for Imperial students living in London. This week saw the publication Property Week being forced to withdraw a category from their Student Accommodation …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICSM Music Society Concert
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-icsm-music-society-concert/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 09:40:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abigail E de Bruin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-icsm-music-society-concert/</guid>
        <description>One of my favourite things about playing the French horn is that you get called in to play in concerts at the last minute pretty often. At Imperial the concerts usually tend to end up being actually really good and so it’s always quite exciting to get the opportunity to play with groups here. Last …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Bury Your Gays trope needs to die
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-the-bury-your-gays-trope-needs-to-die/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 08:55:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abigail E de Bruin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-the-bury-your-gays-trope-needs-to-die/</guid>
        <description>The 100 is a cult teen drama focused on post-apocalyptic America. It has a significant, primarily American following who mobilised quickly following the airing of an episode on the 3rd March to launch an enormous online campaign. During the show, a character is shot as part of the story arc that is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ending term on a high note (or several!)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-ending-term-on-a-high-note-or-several/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 12:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abigail E de Bruin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-ending-term-on-a-high-note-or-several/</guid>
        <description>After the all round success seen at ArtsFest last term for the Arts societies Imperial has seen them come roaring back to life for a series of incredible Easter term concerts. ICSM Drama put on a wonderful performance of Midsummer Night’s dream in the Union Concert Hall last week with snazzy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial at The Notting Hill Dinner Club
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-imperial-at-the-notting-hill-dinner-club/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 11:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abigail E de Bruin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-imperial-at-the-notting-hill-dinner-club/</guid>
        <description>Two weeks ago, the Union put on a whole load of student volunteering opportunities as part of the national campaign of Student Volunteering
The Student Development team from Imperial College Union worked closely with the Notting Hill Community Church to get students involved in the evening as part …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ladz on tour in record numbers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-ladz-on-tour-in-record-numbers/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 12:48:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abigail E de Bruin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-ladz-on-tour-in-record-numbers/</guid>
        <description>At Imperial probably one of my favourite things that we get to support Clubs, Societies and Projects with is tours. If I mention it to anyone at other Students’ Unions they can’t believe that we not only support students going on tour but also fund it. Though I guess that in a lot of other places …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Campaigning is hard work...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-19-campaigning-is-hard-work/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 23:52:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abigail E de Bruin,Benjamin Howitt,Tom Rivlin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-19-campaigning-is-hard-work/</guid>
        <description>Tom Rivlin: Deputy President (Clubs and Societies) candidate, 2015
Let’s get one thing out of the way first: yes, I did just lose in the Big Elections. Yes, I am extremely bitter about this. Yes, you can read the whole article as just a sore loser whining about losing sorely if you want.
That said I …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
