<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/cdd09/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/cdd09/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s the end of the world as we know it
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-its-the-end-of-the-world-as-we-know-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 21:44:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christopher D Dean,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-its-the-end-of-the-world-as-we-know-it/</guid>
        <description>It’s not every day you watch a film that begins as depressingly as Melancholia. In beautifully vibrant slow motion, we are forced to watch in horror as the world, and four of its inhabitants, come to a startlingly abrupt end by way of planetary collision. Birds fall from the sky, horses collapse, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Minotaur de force
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-minotaur-de-force/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 22:04:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christopher D Dean,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-minotaur-de-force/</guid>
        <description>Greek mythology is normally pretty messed up, but the tale of the Minotaur takes it to a new level. Born after King Minos’ wife got knocked up by a Bull sent from the Gods, the half human half beast was locked in a labyrinth and fed on human sacrifice. This reign of terror ended when Theseus killed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“I Wanna Go Back...”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-i-wanna-go-back/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 20:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christopher D Dean,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-i-wanna-go-back/</guid>
        <description>There has always been one paradoxical quote about Weezer that amused me. I’m paraphrasing, but it goes along the lines that “Weezer are the worst rock band in America to release two of the greatest albums of the last 20 years”.
Whilst I disagree, it’s easy to understand why they might be labeled as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>SVIIB Lives on, Despite Suffering a Loss
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-sviib-lives-on-despite-suffering-a-loss/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 21:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christopher D Dean,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-sviib-lives-on-despite-suffering-a-loss/</guid>
        <description>It’s been a tough few weeks for School of Seven Bells. The announcement of Claudia Deheza’s departure, one of the twin sisters whose vocal harmonies make their sound so distinctive, arrived suddenly and without warning on their Facebook account. Fans were shocked, and despite their decision to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rape Gaze...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-rape-gaze/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 19:41:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christopher D Dean,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-rape-gaze/</guid>
        <description>&amp;lsquo;Rape Gaze’. The phrase has been causing controversy in the last few weeks after Pitchfork issued a statement officially retracting its use from a review of Salem’s new album King Night.
First coined by the band CREEP, it refers to an emerging genre characterised by haunted, atmospheric music …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
