<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Editorial on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/editorial/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Editorial on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/editorial/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>So long... and thank you for all the fish
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-so-long-and-thank-you-for-all-the-fish/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:25:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-so-long-and-thank-you-for-all-the-fish/</guid>
        <description>It’s the final issue. I’ve ranted for some 28 editions now and you guys have taken it like champs. In my last editorial I’d like to say one final thing before I fade into irrelevance. I want to talk about complaining.
I’m a great complainer. I bitch and moan about everything. I quit an online …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What a week
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-what-a-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:21:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-what-a-week/</guid>
        <description>What a week. Since last Friday, shit has hit the fan. Much like an evil mastermind in a superhero movie, Donald Trump has announced to the world his evil plan to fuck over the planet: quitting the Paris Agreement. The only differences are that he’s as thick (but slightly more orange) as mustard, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>(1) 666 number of the beast
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-1-666-number-of-the-beast/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:19:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-1-666-number-of-the-beast/</guid>
        <description>Fun fact: we originally had big plans for issue 1666. We were gonna do a ‘pagan issue’ dedicated to religion, with a graphic illustration of the Devil splashed across the front cover. But then in April, May announced a snap general election and we were like ‘God damn’. We forfeited the pagan issue …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Summer lovin’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-summer-lovin/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:15:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-summer-lovin/</guid>
        <description>Summer is officially here. You can tell by the hoards of panting students waiting to get served at FiveSixEight. You can also tell because felix has succumbed to society’s pressures and has dropped to half its original weight in preparation for the beach. For real though yesterday was so hot I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is news?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-what-is-news/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:13:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-what-is-news/</guid>
        <description>In fact let’s go deeper. What is a newspaper? If it’s a publication propelled by the propagation of news to its readers, then let me tell you; you’re in for a treat because this is the newsiest, newspaper we’ve ever made. I’m obviously referring to the twelve page (centrefold included) sex survey …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Divest this
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-divest-this/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:10:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-divest-this/</guid>
        <description>Is Imperial morally bankrupt? I first asked myself this question in 2011 when I started my Biology undergraduate. My department had just sacked most, if not all of its plant scientists. There was no money in the field. Have I come close to an answer since? Maybe. Sometimes I’ve looked at Imperial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We’re back. Pitches?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-were-back-pitches/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:06:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-were-back-pitches/</guid>
        <description>Yay! The Easter break is over! Yay&amp;hellip;”
Lef suddenly stopped typing, an overwhelming feeling of sadness taking over him. He thought of all those hours he’d idly spent in bed, no stupid print deadlines, no stupid paper distribution cutting his sleep short. He thought of all that nutritious …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>k bye.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-k-bye/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-k-bye/</guid>
        <description>Finally, the last issue (of term). I have been waiting for this moment for too long. While I’m going to miss putting together this wonderful publication for the next few weeks, I’ll be honest with you, I’m super excited to lay back and relax, maybe get a massage, definitely re-balance my sleep and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Memememememememe
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-memememememememe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:57:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-memememememememe/</guid>
        <description>Chill. Happy thoughts. Breathe in, breathe out. This issue is about self-care, which ideally would have involved me taking a holiday and getting my tan on, maybe on a small, secluded beach in the Canary Islands. But obviously I can’t just leave you guys hanging. How are you supposed to do the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My manifesto
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-my-manifesto/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:55:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-my-manifesto/</guid>
        <description>Hello everyone. My name is Lef. Some of you might know me from my reign of terror as felix editor. Others might have spotted me making short sustenance runs to the union or the JCR (dem buns tho&amp;hellip;) and might have admired my luscious locks or strong eye-liner game. Regardless of your …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Elections should be fun
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-elections-should-be-fun/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:52:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-elections-should-be-fun/</guid>
        <description>Let’s be honest. Everything we do, we do in the name of fun. Sure you can use fancy lingo, such as pleasure, satisfaction, gratification, joy, and even gusto if you’re that kind of person, but at the end of the day, fun does the trick just fine.
The reason we make babies is because sex is fun. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Going green is hard
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-going-green-is-hard/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:50:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-going-green-is-hard/</guid>
        <description>Oh my god this issue is so green. SO GREEN I TELL YOU. Just reading it will make you healthier and add at least one year to your sad, Imperial-stunted life. You might wonder why. You might even vocally ask me on the off chance you spot me outdoors “why are you doing a Green Issue Lef? Caring about …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Love is love
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-love-is-love/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:47:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-love-is-love/</guid>
        <description>February is LGBT history month (yes, I know – I only just found out too) and my heart is filled with joy because for the first time ever I’m actually clued up. I also feel more a part of the queer community than I’ve ever felt before. I can’t really explain why, but it is what it is and I’m glad, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Feeeeeeeeeed meeeeeeee
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-feeeeeeeeeed-meeeeeeee/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:45:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-feeeeeeeeeed-meeeeeeee/</guid>
        <description>This issue is quite clearly dedicated to food. Whether you eat it, throw it up, get high on it, or get down and dirty with it (hey, we don’t judge) food is a fundamental part of the human existence. We carefully selected this week to talk about food, because Eating Disorder Awareness Week is coming …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Resistance is not futile. We think.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-resistance-is-not-futile-we-think/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:40:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-resistance-is-not-futile-we-think/</guid>
        <description>Well we honestly tried – you know, taking a break from the doom and gloom. With the end of 2016, we were eager to turn over a new leaf, start anew with starry eyes full of hope for the future. But since Trump’s inauguration last Friday, it’s just been an onslaught of bad news, dumb news, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hang in there kitties
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-hang-in-there-kitties/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:35:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-hang-in-there-kitties/</guid>
        <description>Blue Monday, alternatively known as the most depressing day of the year, came and went this week (Blue like hands without gloves flaunted at passing strangers on the street. Wait what?). By now you’ve come to terms with the fact that you probably spent way too much money over Christmas. You’ve also …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The post new year’s blues
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-post-new-years-blues/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:29:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-post-new-years-blues/</guid>
        <description>One of my friends recently pointed out I’m going through a quarter-life crisis, that we (our group of friends) all are. And I can see where he’s coming from. We’re all in our mid-twenties and we seem to permanently be at a crossroads. Transcending from adolescence into adulthood (it’s… a process) – …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>felix navidad
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-felix-navidad/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:24:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-felix-navidad/</guid>
        <description>It’s beginning to look a lot like Christmas. The tube is packed, the streets are clogged, shopping is a nightmare, and you keep embarrassing yourself, blurting out family secrets at dinners, to people you barely know.
Meanwhile, there are all these fake gifts everywhere: stupid, empty, gift-wrapped …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My head hurts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-my-head-hurts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:21:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-my-head-hurts/</guid>
        <description>This is a very special editorial, a very special issue even. Partly because I started writing it after smacking my head on the cold, hard asphalt just past Kensington Gardens (I know it looks cool to have your flowy hair trailing behind you as you cycle, but don’t do it kids. Don’t cycle without a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We’re almost there
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-were-almost-there/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:18:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-were-almost-there/</guid>
        <description>Another week, another quality paper. The holidays are fast approaching, and let me tell you I cannot wait. For a glorious three weeks I will not have to work like a madman and I can catch up on all the Westworld I’ve missed, and go through my inbox, print all my unread mail, put it in little …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The lady doth protest too much
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-lady-doth-protest-too-much/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:16:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-lady-doth-protest-too-much/</guid>
        <description>Warning: I’m really tired, I have a million things to do including packing a suitcase for a weekend escape (yay me), and this editorial has been a pain in the butt to write. So prepare yourself for some really wishy washy stuff, cause I’m on course to work 54 hours this week and at this point I just …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We’ve all got daddy issues
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-weve-all-got-daddy-issues/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:13:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-weve-all-got-daddy-issues/</guid>
        <description>Change is in the air. Imperial College has taken up recommendations to improve student satisfaction made by the Union, the Higher Education and Research Bill has just been amended, an education demo is taking place in London this weekend, and Donald Trump’s backtracking behaviour has captured the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It happened
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-it-happened/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:11:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-it-happened/</guid>
        <description>The dreaded day has come and gone. The world has changed. Donald Trump is a democratically elected world leader. I don’t think I’ve processed the tangible reality of the above sentence quite yet (and what a sentence: four years, eight years, or life?).
The man who inflamed an already polarised …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I’ve had it
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-ive-had-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 14:49:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-ive-had-it/</guid>
        <description>Three weeks in and I have nearly had it. Don’t get me wrong, editing a major cough newspaper is fun but it is exhausting. On Wednesday, I got an email from the printers at 19:51, ten minutes before leaving the office which wrote: “Hi Lef, If you run into trouble tonight pls call my home number on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Post freshers’ blues
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-post-freshers-blues/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 14:46:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-post-freshers-blues/</guid>
        <description>So. Here we are once again, two weeks in a row. One more week and it will have become an unhealthy habit, like smoking, binge-watching Netflix, or reassuming the leadership of UKIP.
This week everything sucks. For starters we’ve all got freshers’ flu, passing it on like a joint at a house party (the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
