<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/alex_montgomerie_corcoran/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/alex_montgomerie_corcoran/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>An album from the entire London jazz community</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-an-album-from-the-entire-london-jazz-community/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Montgomerie-Corcoran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-an-album-from-the-entire-london-jazz-community/</guid>
        <description>A whole scene captured in a brief moment, Brownswood Recordings’ We Out Here showcases the best of London’s young, growing jazz movement. Crossing the sounds of hip hop, jazz, neo soul, and afrobeat (and even slight acid house vibes on Moses Boyd’s track), this album brings together a carefully …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Abdullah Ibrahim’s set to remember: a co-op review</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-abdullah-ibrahim-s-set-to-remember-a-co-op-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Montgomerie-Corcoran,Juliette Guilloud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-abdullah-ibrahim-s-set-to-remember-a-co-op-review/</guid>
        <description>Last Tuesday, Abdullah Ibrahim, the 83 year old South African father of Cape Jazz, walked on to the Royal Festival Hall stage. He sat in front of his piano, placed his long hands on the keys, and introduced us to the concert with a medley of melodies retracing his work. The attention of the audience …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nai Palm lights up London with a killer solo set</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-nai-palm-lights-up-london-with-a-killer-solo-set/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Montgomerie-Corcoran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-nai-palm-lights-up-london-with-a-killer-solo-set/</guid>
        <description>For the first time London had Haitus Kyote’s lead singer, Nai Palm, at Koko to perform her own solo music in a night which defined her new direction with music. It was amazing just to see her on stage, and to finally hear her voice properly; she truly is one of the most impressive singers around …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Felix guide to the London jazz scene: the clubs</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-the-felix-guide-to-the-london-jazz-scene-the-clubs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Montgomerie-Corcoran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-the-felix-guide-to-the-london-jazz-scene-the-clubs/</guid>
        <description>London boasts jazz venues renowned around the world and cozy holes-in-the-wall where you can catch a legendary performer ten years before they become famous:
Troy Bar
Hoxton Out of all the places on this list, Troy Bar has to be my favourite, just in terms of how full of life it is and the intensity …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Krept &amp; Konan abandon the London underground in their new mixtapes 7 Days and 7 Nights</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-krept-konan-abandon-the-london-underground-in-their-new-mixtapes-7-days-and-7-nights/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Montgomerie-Corcoran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-krept-konan-abandon-the-london-underground-in-their-new-mixtapes-7-days-and-7-nights/</guid>
        <description>Krept and Konan, the established rap duo from South London, put out a pair of albums two weeks ago in their first major releases since their return to the London music scene. The albums are drastically different in style: 7 Days feels more like a compilation of their attempts at different genres …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nai Palm strikes out on her own</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-nai-palm-strikes-out-on-her-own/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Montgomerie-Corcoran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-nai-palm-strikes-out-on-her-own/</guid>
        <description>Singer, songwriter, and guitarist Nai Palm has come out with her debut solo album, Needle Paw: an intimate collection of covers and originals wrapped in rich harmonies that gives a slightly new perspective on her already established compositions, as well as introducing some new and more personal …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
