<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/yyl114/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/yyl114/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>XU | the brainchild of BAO is a beautiful addition to the London food scene
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-xu-the-brainchild-of-bao-is-a-beautiful-addition-to-the-london-food-scene/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 17:10:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-xu-the-brainchild-of-bao-is-a-beautiful-addition-to-the-london-food-scene/</guid>
        <description>Two years into this half-university-student-half-food-blogger life of mine and I already have a lifetime’s worth of cringe worthy moments – mostly encountered during blogger events and restaurant invites. Imagine: turning up to the door of a launch event to know that my name had never been added to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Serving up Spring
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-serving-up-spring/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 16:26:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-serving-up-spring/</guid>
        <description> I was leaving college one evening after a long, dreary day huddled inside the dark warmth of ACEX (on top of some never-ending coursework), when I looked up to the sky, preparing for a deep, long sigh, as per any typical cold winter day. The sigh dissipated into thin air as the navy blue was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kombucha Kraft
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-kombucha-kraft/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 14:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-kombucha-kraft/</guid>
        <description>I try to be healthy. Sometimes. You see, when you have to sustain a food blog full of cakes and ice creams and burgers and doughnuts, you have to find a way to balance it out. And luckily for me, the healthy food world is not limited to chomping my way through an iceberg lettuce for dinner while …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Life in the blogosphere #tablesituation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-life-in-the-blogosphere-tablesituation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 15:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-life-in-the-blogosphere-tablesituation/</guid>
        <description>Gosh, what a morning, I thought to myself as I landed on a lush, green, velvet chair, flushed and out of breath from an intense power walking session down Park Lane (my definition of being ‘fashionably late’). A fellow blogger sitting opposite was doing her 5th re-run on Snapchat: “…it’s too early …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ten of the best</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-ten-of-the-best/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 15:23:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-ten-of-the-best/</guid>
        <description> 1 | Dirty Bones Shoreditch Fried chicken on waffles for brunch? Definitely. Hit up Dirty Bones for their boozy brunch menu with mac ‘n’ cheese burgers, short rib crumpets and more heart attack-worthy dishes!
   Christy Lam   2 | Café Loren Looking for a homey, warming breakfast? Café Loren in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bored of the classic waffle? Me too!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-bored-of-the-classic-waffle-me-too/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 16:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-bored-of-the-classic-waffle-me-too/</guid>
        <description>You should never make a comment about a restaurant before you’ve tried it.”
That was a strong lesson from a man, a total stranger, sitting at the table next to me, which ended our morning debate over the much hyped-about The Breakfast Club a few months back. For him, it was his holy grail breakfast …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ten of the best
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-ten-of-the-best/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 17:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-ten-of-the-best/</guid>
        <description> 1 | Bleecker Burger The Bleecker Black is probably the best burger in London, with two juicy patties with a layer of black pudding in the middle.
   Christy Lam   2 | Where the Pancakes Are A cute little pancake house serving delicious, homemade pancakes at the back of a bustling food market. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Want some fish in that taco?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-want-some-fish-in-that-taco/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 17:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-want-some-fish-in-that-taco/</guid>
        <description>There’s this one question I always get asked: how do I have the time to fit in lectures in the morning, project-work in the afternoon, while managing an Instagram story saturated with #bloggermail, press events and bearded baristas in tiny independent cafés in god-knows-where?
The answer is – I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Avocado for breakfast? So #2k16
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-avocado-for-breakfast-so-2k16/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 17:38:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-avocado-for-breakfast-so-2k16/</guid>
        <description>Mezze. A word meaning a selection of small appetizers. And a word that I have recently started noticing following a sharing plates trend that has finally hit the London food scene. After some hearty meals, I have adjusted my taste buds (and stomach) to this wonderful dining culture home to Turkey, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An immaculate conception?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-an-immaculate-conception/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-an-immaculate-conception/</guid>
        <description>Best friend in town? You just have to take them to one of the best restaurants in town and order three times your normal portion of food – and roll out of the restaurant with a six-month food baby hoping to ‘walk’ it off with a tube journey to the next.
So when my friend came down to London all the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Breakfast, Hong Kong style
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-breakfast-hong-kong-style/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-breakfast-hong-kong-style/</guid>
        <description>Plonk.
It was the sound of a quarter-inch thick china cup hitting the glass-topped wooden table, as my milk tea lands before me just three seconds after the waiter took my order.
My mind snapped out from my fuzzy morning daydream of fluffy bunnies jumping over lush green grass back into full …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2016 | a #food round up
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-2016-a-food-round-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 15:49:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-2016-a-food-round-up/</guid>
        <description> Number 1. Green Tea. You know that green tea has finally taken over the land of boring English Breakfast when even Starbucks has added a green tea latte to their permanent menu. Green tea has always been a popular drink in Asia for its many health benefits. Not only is it your best coffee …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chocolate, Christmas and Cheese
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-chocolate-christmas-and-cheese/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 11:47:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-chocolate-christmas-and-cheese/</guid>
        <description>If rolling in cash and taking baths in champagne in a mansion in Saint-Jean-Cap-Ferrat is your lifetime goal, may I suggest a better alternative: earning an OBE for “services to chocolate”.
Why did I suddenly draw light to this matter? All after an inspiring evening of chocolate with Chantal Coady …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where The Pancakes Are
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-where-the-pancakes-are/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 15:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-where-the-pancakes-are/</guid>
        <description>Evenings on a Wednesday for me are often spent alone in bed, propped up by a few lumpy pillows and my loyal companion, Netflix. The one that just passed was no exemption, with the addition of feeling betrayed after a solid five hours binge-watching the last episodes of The Crown, and left having to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Four hours of tapas-style dining later
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-four-hours-of-tapas-style-dining-later/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 14:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-four-hours-of-tapas-style-dining-later/</guid>
        <description>Sometimes I wish I could duplicate myself. One to go to those dreaded 9am lectures, one to do the laundry and one to tend to the exploding experiments in the lab. And at the end of the day, we can all gather and dine at one of the many restaurants on my to-visit list. There’s nothing wrong with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Make restaurants great again
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-make-restaurants-great-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 17:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-make-restaurants-great-again/</guid>
        <description>How do you differentiate between a good and an excellent restaurant? Is it the Michelin-starred chef behind the counter splattering sauce over thumb-sized morsels of food? Is it the extra 0.1 rating or half a star on OpenTable? Or is it the two-hour-long queue outside the no-reservation system every …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Italian for Brunch
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-7-italian-for-brunch/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 13:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-7-italian-for-brunch/</guid>
        <description>It’s not every day you meet a Michelin-star chef. Not hysterically screaming after catching a glimpse some 50-metres away, but to be within talking distance, and most importantly, taking a selfie.
All thanks to the cohort of lovely PRs, one such event filled up the Saturday afternoon rectangle in my …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Plates of simple luxury
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-plates-of-simple-luxury/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 23:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-plates-of-simple-luxury/</guid>
        <description>The luxury of Sunday mornings. The only morning in the week when it is entirely appropriate to put a hush to the endless list of unwatched Panopto recordings, lie-in until the church bells ring, then lazily roll out of the house in time for grocery shopping. Aside from snatching the half-priced …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Plot of France
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-10-a-plot-of-france/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 12:11:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-10-a-plot-of-france/</guid>
        <description>There is that one restaurant somewhere on your bucket list that you have never found the chance to visit. Until, one day, you’ve run out of places to try, bored of that same old burger from GBK, tired of that salmon nigiri set from Wasabi, when you finally drag yourself there, take a bite, and kick …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brb, I’m drowning in cocktails
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-brb-im-drowning-in-cocktails/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 09:41:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-brb-im-drowning-in-cocktails/</guid>
        <description>The lives of successful bloggers have always appeared somewhat glamourous, superficial and materialistic to me – press events around the world, nights in 5-star hotels, sponsorships from high-end brands… And all they seem to do for a living is just go take a few effortless photos for #ootd, film a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A food journey in Notting Hill
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-a-food-journey-in-notting-hill/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 08:37:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-a-food-journey-in-notting-hill/</guid>
        <description>As much as I regret moving to somewhere in the middle of Holland Park and Shepherd’s Bush for second year,living in close proximity to the beautiful neighborhood of Notting Hill definitely made up for the daily power walk sessions to catch the Circle line to college. Here are a few of my favourite …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let me eat cake
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-let-me-eat-cake/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 09:32:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-let-me-eat-cake/</guid>
        <description>Marie Antoinette once said, “Let them eat cake.” If I were a peasant back in the days of the French Revolution, I’d happily take her words as a genuine attempt to offer me cake, ditch my hunger for the stale baguettes and munch on the amazing French creations for the rest of my life, maybe a vanilla …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Minute trip to Taiwan
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-minute-trip-to-taiwan/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 09:05:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-minute-trip-to-taiwan/</guid>
        <description>Last Wednesday was another one of those typical rainy, gloomy days with me sitting, staring into space in the back of the Chem Eng library. I must have appeared to be either half asleep, or deep in thought pondering upon the underlying philosophy of a radiative heat transfer problem. Hangry, more …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Go-nuts for doughnuts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-go-nuts-for-doughnuts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 09:22:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-go-nuts-for-doughnuts/</guid>
        <description>Throwback to the seven years spent in an all-girls boarding school in the countryside. A weekend trip to the nearest town with an actual supermarket was a sacred privilege only to those of Year 9 and above, while you have to be at least in Year 12 to be allowed to step on the train on the opposite …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Back to Basics: Scones and Tea
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-back-to-basics-scones-and-tea/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 09:18:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,Sanjay Bhattacharya,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-back-to-basics-scones-and-tea/</guid>
        <description> If you had to pick one dish that represents Britain, what would it be? Mine would definitely be the traditional English afternoon tea. Probably the same as any typical Chinese girl.
Do not let the idea of afternoon tea scare you – this is going to be a casual affair, no extravagance, no posh …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Matrix of Eclairs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-matrix-of-eclairs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 09:34:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-matrix-of-eclairs/</guid>
        <description>Engineers are pretty obsessed with matrices.
As someone from Chemical Engineering, I love matrices. Don’t get me wrong here. I’m not talking about MATLAB, maths, or even anything related to numbers. I’m talking about food. Matrices of food. There is no better cure for OCD than staring at perfectly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Breakfast at Granger &amp; Co.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-breakfast-at-granger-co/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 12:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-breakfast-at-granger-co/</guid>
        <description>Your committed relationship to Wasabi for breakfast, lunch, dinner AND midnight snack is just not working any more. You’ve tried everything at Hummingbird from cupcakes to whoopie pies, risking diabetes and an E number overload. You’ve even set foot into Roots &amp;amp; Bulbs desperate for something …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
