<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/clemens_jakubec/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/clemens_jakubec/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Science for Heretics review – the heretics have not got it right</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-science-for-heretics-review-the-heretics-have-not-got-it-right/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Clemens Jakubec,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-science-for-heretics-review-the-heretics-have-not-got-it-right/</guid>
        <description>The scientific method is not absolute. Every good scientist should be aware of that. However, for scientists, science and the scientific method have proven to be the most effective ways of moving towards a more objective view on the universe around us. Barrie Condon is such a scientist. He is a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An intellectual perspective on progress and positivity in Enlightenment Now</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-an-intellectual-perspective-on-progress-and-positivity-in-enlightenment-now/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Clemens Jakubec,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-an-intellectual-perspective-on-progress-and-positivity-in-enlightenment-now/</guid>
        <description>Where is the world headed? Are things getting better or are we approaching a darker period of human history? In his new book Enlightenment Now: The Case for Reason, Science, Humanism, and Progress, American cognitive linguist Steven Pinker makes the case for a more positive outlook for the future of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Menasse’s ruminations on pigs and politics in the European Union</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-menasse-s-ruminations-on-pigs-and-politics-in-the-european-union/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Clemens Jakubec,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-menasse-s-ruminations-on-pigs-and-politics-in-the-european-union/</guid>
        <description>Is it possible to write a novel about the European Union? Not just a book about the history of the European Union with boring facts and figures about its multiple conventions and contracts, but a proper novel with characters that could symbolise the European Union. That is the question that Robert …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2017 roundup: the best books of the year</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-2017-roundup-the-best-books-of-the-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Alice Peberdy,Katie Cook,Clemens Jakubec,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-2017-roundup-the-best-books-of-the-year/</guid>
        <description>What was the best thing you read this year? Four of our Books Writers give their thoughts:
Morning and Evening, by Jon Fosse
Jon Fosse to tell the story of the Norwegian fisherman Johannes in only a hundred pages. To be exact, we only learn about the two most significant events in his life: his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In the relentless tread of time, a man searches for the greater miracle of life </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-in-the-relentless-tread-of-time-a-man-searches-for-the-greater-miracle-of-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Clemens Jakubec,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-in-the-relentless-tread-of-time-a-man-searches-for-the-greater-miracle-of-life/</guid>
        <description>Freedom – a word as awe-inspiring as it is undefined. There are many ways of tackling the issue of what freedom means on a general as well as on a personal level. In his 2013 novel The Greater Miracle Thomas Glavinic sheds light on the problem of freedom from a very personal perspective.
The novel …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The koala bear as a metaphor for life, death, and the struggle to survive </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-the-koala-bear-as-a-metaphor-for-life-death-and-the-struggle-to-survive/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Clemens Jakubec,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-the-koala-bear-as-a-metaphor-for-life-death-and-the-struggle-to-survive/</guid>
        <description>The animal was not black. It was not strong. It was lazy and had furry ears, a creature, that people laughed about. The best one could say about the animal was, that it was cute.” The koala is usually not an animal that people tend to spend a lot of time thinking about. Nevertheless, swiss author …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Austria’s far-right achieves a landslide win in parliamentary elections</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-austria-s-far-right-achieves-a-landslide-win-in-parliamentary-elections/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Clemens Jakubec,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-austria-s-far-right-achieves-a-landslide-win-in-parliamentary-elections/</guid>
        <description>It was a long Sunday for those eagerly awaiting the outcome of Austria’s 26th parliamentary elections. When the results started to come in during early afternoon, the winner was clear: the right wing, above all Sebastian Kurz and his conservative Österreichische Volkspartei (ÖVP) with 31.5% of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Right-wing parties predicted success in upcoming Austrian election</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-right-wing-parties-predicted-success-in-upcoming-austrian-election/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Clemens Jakubec,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-right-wing-parties-predicted-success-in-upcoming-austrian-election/</guid>
        <description>In the wake of a controversial presidential election which saw independent candidate Alexander Van der Bellen assume power last January, Austria is holding a parliamentary election this Sunday. In spring the parliament unanimously decided to hold early elections, after the two governing parties, the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
