<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ss10210/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ss10210/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Privatisation: the dangers of too much sponsorship
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-8-privatisation-the-dangers-of-too-much-sponsorship/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2012 08:47:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-8-privatisation-the-dangers-of-too-much-sponsorship/</guid>
        <description>It’s a searingly hot day in central London. The sun beats down on the Queen’s Lawn as an acquaintance and I pass by a monstrous, awkward marquee. Inside, emissaries from various companies appeal for students’ attention with all the enthusiasm of sleepy clams. The students scurry from table to table …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Greens and GM: a scientist’s dilemma
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-1-greens-and-gm-a-scientists-dilemma/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2012 12:43:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-1-greens-and-gm-a-scientists-dilemma/</guid>
        <description>I like the Green Party. I voted for them in May, on all three ballots, and I would vote for them again if there were a General Election tomorrow. But, as with most friends, they often disappoint me. While I was severely depressed by their pledge to offer homeopathic “medicine” on the NHS, and their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Privatisation: the Ministry interfering at Hogwarts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-1-privatisation-the-ministry-interfering-at-hogwarts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2012 12:20:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-1-privatisation-the-ministry-interfering-at-hogwarts/</guid>
        <description>Our universities are being privatised, or so many on the Left would have us believe. But how true is it? And is it necessarily a bad thing? In a series of features over the next few weeks, I will be investigating several areas of privatisation at Imperial and at universities across the UK, areas …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Keep the Cat free!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-9-keep-the-cat-free/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 13:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-9-keep-the-cat-free/</guid>
        <description>Following allegations that Felix has been prevented by College from printing, I would like to take the opportunity to reassure readers that it was solely an editorial decision to not run the piece on the Careers Advisory Service.
This was based on the fact that there were several factual …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Truth, lies and tall tales about “Work for your Benefits”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-truth-lies-and-tall-tales-about-work-for-your-benefits/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 23:58:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-truth-lies-and-tall-tales-about-work-for-your-benefits/</guid>
        <description>A spectre is haunting our futures – the spectre of unemployment. Most of us are soon-to-be graduates: some of us, inevitably, are the soon-to-be unemployed. With every month, increasing numbers of young people are finding themselves jobless, and increasing numbers are turning to the government for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sexism at Imperial College
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-sexism-at-imperial-college/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 23:01:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-sexism-at-imperial-college/</guid>
        <description>Not here, surely? Sexism is everywhere: in the media, in politics, in the arts, but at universities? The centres of liberal thought and tolerance? Where everyone is open-minded and friendly and – above all – extremely egalitarian? If there were ever a place where sexism shouldn’t exist, it is here. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tuition fees protests wastes good placards
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-tuition-fees-protests-wastes-good-placards/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 22:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-tuition-fees-protests-wastes-good-placards/</guid>
        <description>Apparently 2012 is going to be a bumper year for protests, and I am quite looking forward to them. As the late Christopher Hitchens once wrote, “seek out argument and disputation for their own sake; the grave will provide plenty of time for silence”. But what would the brilliant man have made of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Occupy the New Year, but grow up first
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-occupy-the-new-year-but-grow-up-first/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 23:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-occupy-the-new-year-but-grow-up-first/</guid>
        <description>Revolution! With its impassioned rhetoric and gritty anger the Occupy movement is intent on overhauling democracy as we know it. Bitter, disaffected people around the world are answering Occupy’s call, and governments are beginning to pay attention to the voice of the disillusioned masses! Reading …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>If Britain attacks Iran I&#39;ll quit my degree in protest
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-if-britain-attacks-iran-ill-quit-my-degree-in-protest/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 21:29:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-if-britain-attacks-iran-ill-quit-my-degree-in-protest/</guid>
        <description>I’m too young to properly remember what the run-up to the invasion of Iraq was like, but I imagine it was rather similar to the situation today with Iran. UN inspectors find no conclusive evidence of weapons, the media spreads irrational panic, diplomatic ties are removed, and then the carpet …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NHS Reforms? What NHS Reforms?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-14-nhs-reforms-what-nhs-reforms/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 00:20:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-14-nhs-reforms-what-nhs-reforms/</guid>
        <description>You’d think that when Parliament was on the verge of passing a bill to effectively abolish the NHS it would be front page news, but apparently not. By the time you’re reading this, the House of Lords will have decided whether or not to pass the 2011 Health and Social Care Bill. For both your sake …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>America&#39;s Tahrir Square
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-americas-tahrir-square/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 10:02:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-americas-tahrir-square/</guid>
        <description>You may not have heard about it, but there is currently a mass protest in New York’s financial district. Named #OccupyWallStreet after the Twitter hashtag, the protest against the banking industry started on September 17 and is scheduled to last until the protesters’ demands are met. Accusations of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Astronomy and plasticine
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-28-astronomy-and-plasticine/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 11:08:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-28-astronomy-and-plasticine/</guid>
        <description>Writing about music quickly makes you cynical about dull and repetitive festivals all over the country, all playing boring music and all with the same sex, drugs and rock ‘n’ roll attitude. But occasionally there comes along a festival so perfectly concieved that you can’t quite believe that it’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Media morons
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-media-morons/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 20:28:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-media-morons/</guid>
        <description>It is a strange quirk of the British media that it is generally harshly critical of the internal affairs of our government, yet often almost blindly supportive of our affairs outside the EU. Consider, for instance, NATO’s recent intervention in the Libyan civil war. Major newspapers rarely seriously …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lovebox
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-12-lovebox/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 15:55:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-12-lovebox/</guid>
        <description>If you’re looking for a festival with big names in central London, it doesn’t get any better than Lovebox. Set in the lovely Victoria Park in Hackney, Lovebox brings together some of today’s most popular artists, and all within cycling distance of Imperial.
The winner of 2008’s Best Medium Sized …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rodrigo Braga: Imperial’s own Stevie Wonder
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-rodrigo-braga-imperials-own-stevie-wonder/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 20:05:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-rodrigo-braga-imperials-own-stevie-wonder/</guid>
        <description>If this was the NME, I would start this article with a sentence like “Rodrigo Braga sounds like the illegitimate lovechild of Stevie Wonder and Paul Simon backed by a Samba band,” but it’s not, so I won’t. Rodrigo Braga is an excellent singer, guitarist and songwriter who performs meaningful and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Album of the Week: Director&#39;s Cut
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-album-of-the-week-directors-cut/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 05:39:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-album-of-the-week-directors-cut/</guid>
        <description>Kate Bush’s first album in six years, a rerecording of tracks from The Red Shoes (1993) and The Sensual World (1989), sees the 52-year-old mother completely reinvogorate albums which became dated very soon after release. This may sound like a cop-out, but the album is a truly fantastic aural …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Vegetable Lasagne,We’re spreading the love for vegetarians!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-vegetable-lasagnewere-spreading-the-love-for-vegetarians/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 19:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-vegetable-lasagnewere-spreading-the-love-for-vegetarians/</guid>
        <description>It is an unfortunately ubiquitous belief amongst non-vegetarian cooks that vegetables are an accompaniment to a meal rather than a meal in themselves. This means that meatless dishes can often go catastrophically wrong.
Vegetable lasagne is one of the most standard dishes there is and yet it is so …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Soufflé Omelette
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-souffl-omelette/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 19:46:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-souffl-omelette/</guid>
        <description>Ingredients:
· Eggs (2-3 per person)
· Some butter
· Seasoning
Time: ~25 minutes.
Impress your friends! Amaze your guests! Elevate your boring omelette ten levels in classiness and tastiness by making Une Omelette Soufflée! Anyone and everyone can make an omelette but this soufflé can cement your …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Darling Marling
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-darling-marling/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 20:22:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-darling-marling/</guid>
        <description>Laura Marling is a remarkable artist. She left home at 16 and moved to London carrying, you would like to imagine, only a guitar, a straw hat and a few vinyls. She then befriended – remarkably, given her shyness – members of lightweight-campfire-singalong bands Noah and the Whale and, later, Mumford …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
