<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ute_thiermann/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ute_thiermann/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The Union’s promises towards PG are good. Sticking to these promises would be better.</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-the-union-s-promises-towards-pg-are-good-sticking-to-these-promises-would-be-better/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ute Thiermann,Hannah Jones,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-the-union-s-promises-towards-pg-are-good-sticking-to-these-promises-would-be-better/</guid>
        <description>In the beginning of my period as GSU President, I had frequent meetings with the Union’s Managing Director, Jarlath O’Hara, and some of the Officer Trustees, particularly Rob Tomkies [Union President] and Alejandro Luy [Deputy President (Education)]. Damn, we had really good plans! For the first …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Best Supervision meant to Imperial College PG Students this year?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-what-best-supervision-meant-to-imperial-college-pg-students-this-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ute Thiermann,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-what-best-supervision-meant-to-imperial-college-pg-students-this-year/</guid>
        <description>&amp;ldquo;I would like to nominate Professor Dominik Weiss from the Earth Science and Engineering department for the best supervision award. He is just a great guy and I am lucky to have him as my supervisor! I am coming towards the end of my PhD and I couldn’t have done it without him.
Dominik has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Supervision Story </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-my-supervision-story/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ute Thiermann,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-my-supervision-story/</guid>
        <description>My objective to improve supervision at Imperial College has turned out to be a real conundrum. I hear endless stories of PG research students being unhappy with their level of supervision, the behaviour of their supervisors and precarious lab situations. Being aware of the sensitivity of these …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Super-talents need super-food – a PG perspective on h-bar cuts</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-super-talents-need-super-food-a-pg-perspective-on-h-bar-cuts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ute Thiermann,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-super-talents-need-super-food-a-pg-perspective-on-h-bar-cuts/</guid>
        <description>Life is our best teacher about how the biggest crises can be turned into the most fundamental opportunities for change. If there is one good thing about the h-bar food-cut tragedy, then it is the chance to take a step back and rethink how we provide and procure food at Imperial in general. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why “Supervision Stories”?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-why-supervision-stories/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ute Thiermann,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-why-supervision-stories/</guid>
        <description>On 7th December 2018, we published our first supervision story (together with the first ever postgraduate focused content in Felix!). The reaction from students and staff at the College was polarised, spanning from enthusiastic support to harsh criticism. While one brave ex-Imperial student took the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Share your PhD supervision story - anonymous and impactful</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-share-your-phd-supervision-story-anonymous-and-impactful/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ute Thiermann,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-share-your-phd-supervision-story-anonymous-and-impactful/</guid>
        <description>The quality of PhD supervision is becoming a hot topic, not only at Imperial College but across the whole UK. Decision-makers across Imperial College are becoming increasingly aware that the quality of supervision is the major predictor of satisfaction and wellbeing of any PhD student. Together with …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
