<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jal08/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jal08/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Former College IT technican Babar Ahmad sentenced to 12.5 years in prison
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-7-17-former-college-it-technican-babar-ahmad-sentenced-to-125-years-in-prison/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 11:04:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-7-17-former-college-it-technican-babar-ahmad-sentenced-to-125-years-in-prison/</guid>
        <description>Former College alumnus and IT staff member Babar Ahmad has been sentenced to 12 and a half years in prison after a long battle by US prosecutors in Connecticut. Ahmad admitted to &amp;ldquo;conspiracy and providing material to support the Taliban.&amp;rdquo;
This result followed an eight-year legal battle …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Animal Research Licence Holder Resigns from Role after Animals in Science Committee Report
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-7-10-college-animal-research-licence-holder-resigns-from-role-after-animals-in-science-committee-report/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 16:56:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-7-10-college-animal-research-licence-holder-resigns-from-role-after-animals-in-science-committee-report/</guid>
        <description>Today during a statement by Norman Baker MP, it has emerged that the College’s Establishment Licence Holder has resigned from the position with immediate effect.
This decision follows a report published last week on breaches of animal research regulation that have occurred within the last few years. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sport Imperial to suspend sporting activities at Teddington
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-7-7-sport-imperial-to-suspend-sporting-activities-at-teddington/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2014 11:12:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-7-7-sport-imperial-to-suspend-sporting-activities-at-teddington/</guid>
        <description>College has recently announced the suspension of all sports activities at the Teddington Sports Ground in Richmond for next academic year.
Sports Imperial said: “With the acquisition of Heston we’ll be taking stock of the facilities we now have and the best way to make use of them to deliver a good …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Report Published About Animal Research Problems at College
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-7-3-new-report-published-about-animal-research-problems-at-college/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2014 10:40:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-7-3-new-report-published-about-animal-research-problems-at-college/</guid>
        <description>“The regime at ICL [Imperial College London] clearly fell short of the standard required by the Animals (Scientific Procedures) Act 1986 (ASPA)” according to yesterday’s report by the government’s Animals in Science Committee (ASC).
The report, carried out by a Working Group of the ASC, provides a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Acquiring New Sports Ground in West London
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-26-college-acquiring-new-sports-ground-in-west-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2014 13:15:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-26-college-acquiring-new-sports-ground-in-west-london/</guid>
        <description>College is in the final stages of buying a new 27-acre plot of land two miles from Harlington for the use of Imperial’s sports teams. The site has outside space for 5 football pitches and 2 rugby pitches, an assortment of tennis, netball and cricket facilities and a shooting range. Meanwhile inside …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Talking to the Editors
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-talking-to-the-editors/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 14:34:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,Felix Editor,Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-talking-to-the-editors/</guid>
        <description> ## Joe Editor-In-Chief
Wow, well it certainly has been a year!
I started this job in October, with a small amount of training and the dusty cobwebs of my previous years of section editorship skulking miserably in the corners of my mind. Summer, as I’m sure you all know, is quite potent at clearing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sabbatical Officer Name Change
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-17-sabbatical-officer-name-change/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2014 14:35:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-17-sabbatical-officer-name-change/</guid>
        <description>This week, Council agreed to change the name of the Deputy President (Clubs &amp;amp; Societies) and Deputy President (Finance &amp;amp; Services) roles to Deputy Presidents (Activities &amp;amp; Development) and (Activities &amp;amp; Finance) respectively.
This change is the result of a “Officer Trustee Role …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Students Find Success at Mayor’s Low Carbon Entrepreneur 2014 Competition
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-6-imperial-students-find-success-at-mayors-low-carbon-entrepreneur-2014-competition/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 02:14:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-6-imperial-students-find-success-at-mayors-low-carbon-entrepreneur-2014-competition/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday, Imperial students James Winfield and Dominic Jacobson won the Mayor of London’s Low Carbon Entrepreneur 2014 award. Sharing the prize money with SolarBox (created by two students from LSE), Winfield and Jacobson’s idea, called Crowd Power Plant impressed the judges enough to win …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union announces residence consultation meeting for new Acton hall
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-2-union-announces-residence-consultation-meeting-for-new-acton-hall/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 12:43:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-2-union-announces-residence-consultation-meeting-for-new-acton-hall/</guid>
        <description>Next Wednesday members of College staff and construction managers will meet in the Union Dining Hall to provide feedback on the progress of the construction of new halls of residence, in Acton.
The meeting, attended by Jane Neary, Director of Campus Services; Paul Noke, Head of Residential Services …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union Council Cancelled Yet Again
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-23-union-council-cancelled-yet-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 14:26:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-23-union-council-cancelled-yet-again/</guid>
        <description>This Tuesday Union Council was cancelled due to failing to achieve quoracy again.
An email was sent around on Monday announcing the cancellation after an administrative member of staff received a large number of apologies of absence via email.
This is the second Union Council meeting to be cancelled …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College begins new study on the possible effects of mobile phones on child cognitive development
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-23-college-begins-new-study-on-the-possible-effects-of-mobile-phones-on-child-cognitive-development/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 14:24:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-23-college-begins-new-study-on-the-possible-effects-of-mobile-phones-on-child-cognitive-development/</guid>
        <description>This week College researchers began a new study investigating the possible effects mobile phones and other wireless devices may have on the mental development of children. The Study of Cognition, Adolescents and Mobile Phones (SCAMP) will focus on thinking skills, attention span and memory, tracking …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New study claims that lectures are ineffective
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-16-new-study-claims-that-lectures-are-ineffective/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 01:38:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-16-new-study-claims-that-lectures-are-ineffective/</guid>
        <description>According to an American study from academics at the Universities of Washington and Maine, “students in classes with traditional lecturing [were] 1.5 times more likely to fail than were students in classes with active learning.”
The study, a result of the analysis of 255 published and unpublished …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial comes bottom in Times Higher Ed. Student Experience Survey for ‘fair workload’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-16-imperial-comes-bottom-in-times-higher-ed-student-experience-survey-for-fair-workload/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 01:37:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-16-imperial-comes-bottom-in-times-higher-ed-student-experience-survey-for-fair-workload/</guid>
        <description>Yesterday saw College coming in 43rd place in the Times Higher Education (THE) Student Experience Survey 2014. Ranked on 21 different attributes, from the strength of the students’ union to the fairness of the workload, the data was gathered by YouthSight over the course of last academic year.
While …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Academic Teaching and Support Staff recognised at Union Student Academic Choice Awards
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-16-academic-teaching-and-support-staff-recognised-at-union-student-academic-choice-awards/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 01:31:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-16-academic-teaching-and-support-staff-recognised-at-union-student-academic-choice-awards/</guid>
        <description>Yesterday, 8 College staff members received prizes at the Union’s annual Student Academic Choice Awards (SACAs).
Presented by several student representatives, the awards recognise the efforts of staff in College that enhance students’ academic experience.
Students made 591 nominations, which …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oxford Union President Arrested
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-oxford-union-president-arrested/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 01:59:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-oxford-union-president-arrested/</guid>
        <description>According to the Tab Oxford, this week the Oxford Union President Ben Sullivan was arrested by Police and questioned concerning allegations over an incident of rape and another of attempted rape.
Sullivan was woken up by police at 7.10 AM on Wednesday morning and was released on bail until June 18. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Postgraduate Graduation ceremony in Royal Albert Hall
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-postgraduate-graduation-ceremony-in-royal-albert-hall/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 01:58:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-postgraduate-graduation-ceremony-in-royal-albert-hall/</guid>
        <description>This week 2,700 students graduated from various postgraduate course in the Royal Albert Hall.
The ceremony, held on Wednesday, was the last postgraduate graduation event held in the history of Imperial, students received their degrees while observed by an audience of 6,000 supporters, spread over …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Library Inches Closer Towards Air Conditioning
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-library-inches-closer-towards-air-conditioning/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 01:56:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-library-inches-closer-towards-air-conditioning/</guid>
        <description>After many years of complaints from students regarding the sweltering heat on the top floors of the Central Library, Felix is happy to announce that College has finally responded by providing air conditioning in the library.
According to documents filed with the City of Westminster Council by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College gets a 2:1 for Sexual Health
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-college-gets-a-21-for-sexual-health/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 01:55:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-college-gets-a-21-for-sexual-health/</guid>
        <description>In a Superdrug study of sexual health provision by universities nationwide College was rated 14th and provided with a 2:1 classification.
Using a list of the top 50 universities (as listed by the Good University Guide), Superdrug rated them against nine criteria regarding sexual health provision for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to get into Ghostblogging!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-how-to-get-into-ghostblogging/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 01:46:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-how-to-get-into-ghostblogging/</guid>
        <description>Choosing a platform
As soon as I had finished installing Ghost on a cloud virtual server, my good friend Luke G-B pointed out the existence another awesome blogging/CMS platform called WagtailCMS.
WagtailCMS is a Django-powered Content Management System created by Torchbox, a web design consultancy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Honors For Imperial Academics
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-honors-for-imperial-academics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 00:53:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-honors-for-imperial-academics/</guid>
        <description>Professor Erol Gelenbe (Dennis Gabor Chair, Dept. Electrical and Electronic Engineering) was recently awarded the honour of Chevalier de la Legion d’Honneur (Knight of the Legion of Honour) by French President Francois Hollande for 43 years of service in Higher Education and Research.
Professor …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Government plans to cut Disabled Students Allowance
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-29-government-plans-to-cut-disabled-students-allowance/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2014 12:46:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-29-government-plans-to-cut-disabled-students-allowance/</guid>
        <description>The Government recently announced changes to the Disabled Students&amp;rsquo; Allowance, expected to take place in 2016-17. The changes, which according to Universities and Sciences Minister David Willetts are set to modernise the system, will see a reduction in the amount of financial support the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Felix Guide to Revision 2014 - Part 1
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-8-the-felix-guide-to-revision-2014-part-1/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 13:52:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-8-the-felix-guide-to-revision-2014-part-1/</guid>
        <description>Most of you will be revising (or trying to) over the Easter break, either panicking or comfortably smug and prepared, having started revision before the year started.
Either way, following on from our Fresher&amp;rsquo;s study advice article, we at Felix would like to add our “two cents” into the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Scientists Discover Dwarf Planet
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-2-scientists-discover-dwarf-planet/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 11:14:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-2-scientists-discover-dwarf-planet/</guid>
        <description>The newly discovered dwarf planet 2012 VP113 was discovered by astronomers at the Carnegie Institution of Science, Washington last week.
2012 VP113, with a diameter of 450km is the smallest celestial body to lay claim to the title of the most distant planet in the solar system, usurping dwarf planet …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Evelyn Gardens Set To Close in 2015
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-27-evelyn-gardens-set-to-close-in-2015/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2014 11:49:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-27-evelyn-gardens-set-to-close-in-2015/</guid>
        <description>According to anonymous sources, the entire network of halls in Evelyn Gardens (providing accommodation for a total of 613 students), is set to close in 2015, with student accommodation spaces being transferred to the accommodation in Acton that is under current development.
The fate of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>RCSU Science Challenge Winners Announced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-24-rcsu-science-challenge-winners-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 03:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-24-rcsu-science-challenge-winners-announced/</guid>
        <description>On Monday the winners of the RCSU Science Challenge were announced at the Science Challenge Final, held at the Churchill War Rooms.
The competition was open to Imperial students and school children who were tasked with chosing one of three essay questions or the video question.
The overall winner of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Medics claim statins have few side effects
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-17-imperial-medics-claim-statins-have-few-side-effects/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2014 17:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-17-imperial-medics-claim-statins-have-few-side-effects/</guid>
        <description>According to College medical researchers, statins have virtually no side effects.
In a recent study looking at 29 trials during which 80,000 patients took statins (cholesterol lowering drugs) the team concluded that a minority of side-effects were contributed by the drugs. Instead they found that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial rises to 13th place in the THE World Reputation Rankings
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-17-imperial-rises-to-13th-place-in-the-the-world-reputation-rankings/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2014 17:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-17-imperial-rises-to-13th-place-in-the-the-world-reputation-rankings/</guid>
        <description>In the recently released Times Higher Education (THE) World Rankings College was ranked one position higher than last year, coming at 13th. Imperial received an overall reputation score of 20.9, with a slightly higher score for research than teaching. In terms of UK institutions, Imperial came 3rd …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Discovering Miso-gine-soc
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-discovering-miso-gine-soc/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 04:28:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-discovering-miso-gine-soc/</guid>
        <description>This week Felix discovered the existence of “GineSoc”, the alter-ego of the Imperial Men’s Hockey XI 2’s team. After discovering a certificate of “Gine” last week on a table outside the FiveSixEight (a bar located on Union premises), we carried out further research. Our investigations revealed the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your Candidates Revealed - Big Elections 2014
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-3-your-candidates-revealed-big-elections-2014/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 14:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-3-your-candidates-revealed-big-elections-2014/</guid>
        <description>President
Ahmed Raja, Alberto Perez Robledo, Charles Prichard, Irina Moraru, Jonathan Pratt, Plabon Saha, Thomas Wheeler
Deputy President (Clubs &amp;amp; Societies)
Abigail de Bruin, Christopher Witham, Irina Moraru
Deputy President (Education)
Bradly Kneisel, Irina Moraru, Pascal Loose, Selina Leung …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial students win inter-University Hackathon
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-28-imperial-students-win-inter-university-hackathon/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 07:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-28-imperial-students-win-inter-university-hackathon/</guid>
        <description>A team of 4 Imperial students last week’s student hackathon hosted at Kings University. The 4 computing students, Andrei-Loan Cioara, Nandor Licker, Tomas Virgl and Patrick Chilton took first place in the UK’s first inter-university hackathon, HackKings, where they triumphed over teams from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Management MSc Student passes away
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-27-management-msc-student-passes-away/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 16:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-27-management-msc-student-passes-away/</guid>
        <description>Last Friday an MSc Management student, Miss Tianlin Wang died. The cause of Miss Wang’s death is unknown at this current point in time.
This is a very tragic occurance and our thoughts are with Miss Wang’s friends, family and course mates.
A College spokesperson make the following statement:
“_With …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Medic diagnoses Da Vinci’s Vitruvian Man
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-imperial-medic-diagnoses-da-vincis-vitruvian-man/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 03:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-imperial-medic-diagnoses-da-vincis-vitruvian-man/</guid>
        <description>Imperial surgeon Mr. Hutan Ashrafian has recently diagnosed a picture of Leonardo Da Vinci’s Vitruvian Man, saying in an email to the Huffington Post: “I noticed that Leonardo da Vinci’s image of a man had a feature that may have been pathological.
Notably a lump in the left groin region, For an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chemistry &amp; Materials Departments display year on year NSS participation increase
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-chemistry-materials-departments-display-year-on-year-nss-participation-increase/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 03:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-chemistry-materials-departments-display-year-on-year-nss-participation-increase/</guid>
        <description>The Chemistry and Materials Departments have shown a marked improvement from the number of final year students who have completed the National Student Survey. At the time of writing, Chemistry had achieved 93.54% participation, 23.9% higher that last year’s final figure. In comparison the department …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Office of Fair Trading claims sanctions on students in debt unlawful
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-office-of-fair-trading-claims-sanctions-on-students-in-debt-unlawful/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 03:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-office-of-fair-trading-claims-sanctions-on-students-in-debt-unlawful/</guid>
        <description>After analysing the terms and conditions of over 100 UK Higher Education Institutions, the Office of Fair Trading (OFT) concluded that almost 75% included sections that could stop students graduating or progressing to the next year of study if they were in debt to their institution.
The OFT stated …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Immigration Bill has second reading in Lords
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-immigration-bill-has-second-reading-in-lords/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 02:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-immigration-bill-has-second-reading-in-lords/</guid>
        <description>The second reading of the Immigration Bill took place in the House of Lords last Monday. The reading stretched over a seven-hour period during which the Peers discussed several aspects of the bill, including a lengthy discussion about the prospective problems facing overseas students due to the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Calls for University of London vice chancellor to stand down
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-14-calls-for-university-of-london-vice-chancellor-to-stand-down/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 05:07:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-14-calls-for-university-of-london-vice-chancellor-to-stand-down/</guid>
        <description>There have been a series of unpleasant events related to student protests at the University of London which has resulted in calls for Adrian Smith to resign his position as vice chancellor. The police have been involved in a number of allegations that attacks have been made on protestors.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In Appointments We Trust
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-14-in-appointments-we-trust/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 05:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-14-in-appointments-we-trust/</guid>
        <description>During Tuesday’s Union Council meeting, one of the tabled papers proposed the ratification of two student trustees who were appointed last term.
The paper outlined the process that was used to vet the 10 candidates that applied for the two vacancies. During the Council meeting it transpired that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union Big Election Nominations 2014 Open!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-14-union-big-election-nominations-2014-open/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 04:34:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-14-union-big-election-nominations-2014-open/</guid>
        <description>The nominations for the Union’s Big Elections 2014 opened this Monday. These elections determine who will fill key roles at the Union during the 2014-15 academic year.
The roles being contested include 7 full-time roles (Union President, the Union Deputy Presidents, the ICSMSU President and the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>CU in Club Election Confusion
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-14-cu-in-club-election-confusion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 04:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-14-cu-in-club-election-confusion/</guid>
        <description>On Tuesday a member of the Imperial College Christian Union’s (CU) committee sent an email to all members on their mailing list explaining that in their upcoming society elections only candidates chosen by the current committee would be allowed to run for positions. In the email the committee member …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Halls residents finally receive comprehensive guidance about cleaning
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-halls-residents-finally-receive-comprehensive-guidance-about-cleaning/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 04:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-halls-residents-finally-receive-comprehensive-guidance-about-cleaning/</guid>
        <description>After months of delay Campus services have finally given halls residents a comprehensive guide to the cleaning provisions provided in halls. The division has recently sent students a booklet containing information about the services the cleaners will provide in different areas of the building, along …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tube strikes to cause chaos in February
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-tube-strikes-to-cause-chaos-in-february/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 17:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-tube-strikes-to-cause-chaos-in-february/</guid>
        <description>Transport for London have announced that next week there will be disruption to underground travel. On Wednesday 5 February and Thursday 6 February walkouts are expected. Services will be affected from as early as 21.30hrs on February 4 so don’t get caught out.
Talks to avert the strikes are being …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Changes to Alcohol Policy for Varsity 2014
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-changes-to-alcohol-policy-for-varsity-2014/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 17:13:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-changes-to-alcohol-policy-for-varsity-2014/</guid>
        <description>Imperial’s Sports Partnership has recently sent an email to stakeholder of the annual Varsity match outlining changes to the acceptance of alcohol during the event.
The declared Varsity Day Alcohol Policy affirms that the focus of the Varsity event should be on “sporting competition”. The email …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chemistry Department to move to Imperial West
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-chemistry-department-to-move-to-imperial-west/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 11:57:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-chemistry-department-to-move-to-imperial-west/</guid>
        <description>Following an email from the Rector to staff this morning it has been revealed that parts of the Chemistry department will be moved to the Imperial West campus.
As part of recent study of critical path issues on the entire College estate, master planners have established several parts of the South …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Farewell Science Museum Library
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-farewell-science-museum-library/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 09:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-farewell-science-museum-library/</guid>
        <description>This week the Science Museum announced that they have come to a mutual agreement with College to relocate the Science Museum Library as part of a scheme that will create a new Science Museum research centre at it’s South Kensington site.
The move, which will take place over approximately six weeks, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Council cancelled - will the DPFS role be renamed?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-council-cancelled-will-the-dpfs-role-be-renamed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 03:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-council-cancelled-will-the-dpfs-role-be-renamed/</guid>
        <description>After a low turnout at Tuesday’s Council meeting, the session was abandoned since they lacked the quorum level of attendance required for binding votes.
While the missing students may have been excused by the pull of examinations or projects, the Council body missed the chance to pass several …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Alan Turing Pardoned at Christmas
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-alan-turing-pardoned-at-christmas/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 03:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-alan-turing-pardoned-at-christmas/</guid>
        <description>December 24th: World War Two Codebreaker Alan Turing finally receives Posthomous royal pardon 61 years after being convicted for “homosexuality”.
Alan Turing, a mathematician known for helping GCHQ (Government Communications Headquarters) break the Nazi Enigma machine encryption during World War II, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Announces Residential Experience Review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-college-announces-residential-experience-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 03:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-college-announces-residential-experience-review/</guid>
        <description>College has set up a consultation process to review the “residential experience” at Imperial. The review process will be conducted by a panel chaired by Professor Myra McClure, College Consul from the Faculty of Medicine (non-clinical) and includes the Union’s President and Deputy President …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Alumnus In New Teaching Documentary
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-9-imperial-alumnus-in-new-teaching-documentary/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 17:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-9-imperial-alumnus-in-new-teaching-documentary/</guid>
        <description>Recent Imperial engineering graduate Nicholas Church appears in a new six-part BBC3 documentary about 6 new teachers who are taking part in the Teach First scheme.
The programme, first airing on January 9, 2014 at 9PM explores the trials and tribulations of the new teachers as they begin teaching in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College Welcomes New President in September
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-3-imperial-college-welcomes-new-president-in-september/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 12:21:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-3-imperial-college-welcomes-new-president-in-september/</guid>
        <description>After a search by College Council through an international list of candidates, Professor Alice P. Gast, President of Lehigh University and former Vice President for Research and Associate Provost at MIT is set to step into the role of President of Imperial College. Professor Gast will be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Further Council Discussion on International NHS fees campaign
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-10-further-council-discussion-on-international-nhs-fees-campaign/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 18:51:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-10-further-council-discussion-on-international-nhs-fees-campaign/</guid>
        <description>1850: Currently disussing the paper before: &amp;ldquo;Motion to Publish the Voting Records of Council Members&amp;rdquo;
1858: Members are debating further about whether to make voting records of Council members public, and when this should start.
1904: Vote: Majority of members have voted for the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>RCS Union Launches 2014 Science Challenge Competition and Questions
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-rcs-union-launches-2014-science-challenge-competition-and-questions/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 03:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-rcs-union-launches-2014-science-challenge-competition-and-questions/</guid>
        <description> On Tuesday the RCSU (Royal College of Science Union) celebrated the introduction to the next RCSU Science Challenge Competition with a launch event in the Sir Alexander Fleming Building.
As well as prospective entrants from Imperial and several secondary schools the event also played host to an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union releases 12/13 Annual Report
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-union-releases-1213-annual-report/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 13:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-union-releases-1213-annual-report/</guid>
        <description>This Tuesday the Union released their most recent annual report, covering last year’s activities. There have been some changes in the Union’s financial reporting methods, after the recent change to full charity status it now has to present financial statements according to the Charities SORP …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London Underground plans radical changes to tube system by 2015
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-22-london-underground-plans-radical-changes-to-tube-system-by-2015/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 03:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-22-london-underground-plans-radical-changes-to-tube-system-by-2015/</guid>
        <description>London Underground and the Mayor of London announced new changes that will have a large impact on London’s tube system. Under the proposed changes by 2015 most manned ticket offices at tube stations will be closed, leading to a loss of 750 jobs. These changes have been set in motion as part of a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Campus Services Dept. contacts students about cleaning error
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-22-campus-services-dept-contacts-students-about-cleaning-error/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 03:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-22-campus-services-dept-contacts-students-about-cleaning-error/</guid>
        <description>Last week Felix reported on College Campus Services’ decisions to change the campus cleaning services during a re-tendering of the cleaning contract. It transpired that one of the department’s decisions included reducing the frequency of cleaning in bedrooms and communal areas, at one stage …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cleaning in halls confusion
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-cleaning-in-halls-confusion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 02:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-cleaning-in-halls-confusion/</guid>
        <description>Since the start of the year, residents in College halls have been coping with a reduced cleaning service, with bedrooms being cleaned only once every four weeks rather than once a fortnight. This is the result of a cleaning review carried our by College’s Campus Services department, the department …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New postgraduate ħ opens
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-new-postgraduate-opens/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 03:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-new-postgraduate-opens/</guid>
        <description>A new postgraduate student and staff drinking and social venue on the South Kensington campus is set to open this Friday. In keeping with the Union’s trend of naming its drinking establishments with incredibly nerdy puns, the new space will be called ħ (pronounced h-bar), named after the reduced …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Looking at the Education and Student Strategy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-looking-at-the-education-and-student-strategy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 09:26:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-looking-at-the-education-and-student-strategy/</guid>
        <description>College has released a new Education and Student Strategy this week which “sets out our vision, aims and priorities for education and the student experience.” The scope of the document is a guide for the development of the education system and student experience over the next five years, providing a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Interview: Introducing the Education and Student Strategy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-interview-introducing-the-education-and-student-strategy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 09:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-interview-introducing-the-education-and-student-strategy/</guid>
        <description>Earlier this week Felix caught up with Professor Debra Humphris, Vice Provost (Education) and had a discussion about the new Education and Student Strategy that was released on Thursday.
Felix: So, you’re releasing the Education Student Strategy tomorrow?
Yes. I started it in December last year, we …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mascot Showdown
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-11-mascot-showdown/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 22:43:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-11-mascot-showdown/</guid>
        <description>Two of Imperial’s Faculty Unions, the Royal College of Science Union (RCSU) and the City &amp;amp; Guilds College Union (CGCU) have recently been involved with various “mascotry” activities over the last month. The activities began when the RCSU President Plabon Saba was escorted to the RCSU office in a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Freshers&#39; Pullout: Local Travel
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-27-freshers-pullout-local-travel/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2013 23:20:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-27-freshers-pullout-local-travel/</guid>
        <description>Transport in 5 modes:
Walking
Walking around is a great way to get to know the local area as well as nearby parts of London. You often find the best places to go while wondering around or walking to another engagement. Great places to walk to near South Kensington include Hyde Park (obviously), …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Hyperloop Hypothesis
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-8-13-the-hyperloop-hypothesis/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2013 09:32:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-8-13-the-hyperloop-hypothesis/</guid>
        <description>Los Angeles to San Francisco, a six hour, 382 mile drive along the West coast of the USA. Monotonous and arduous.
Let’s try a better route. Los Angeles to San Francisco by the Hyperloop? 30 minutes of comfort travelling at 760 mph. Sounds impossible? Welcome to the future!
You might be slightly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>University of London bans student protests
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-8-7-university-of-london-bans-student-protests/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 08:30:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-8-7-university-of-london-bans-student-protests/</guid>
        <description>After recent escalating tension between the University of London and the soon-to-be-extinct University of London Union a new act of aggression has been revealed. The University of London has sent a letter to the ULU banning protests by students on parts of the University’s property.
In the letter, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The GSU Election Manifestos
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-7-25-the-gsu-election-manifestos/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 04:28:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-7-25-the-gsu-election-manifestos/</guid>
        <description> For those of you who are blissfully unaware, the Graduate Students Union (formerly the GSA) elections are being held this week, although you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t know it. There&amp;rsquo;s a significant lack of social media campaigning, especially the usually active #voteicu twitter hashtag which normally …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Unfit To Practise
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-7-15-unfit-to-practise/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 15:09:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-7-15-unfit-to-practise/</guid>
        <description>Dr. Thilanga Iddamalgoda, a former Clinical Research Fellow at Imperial was arrested in August of last year in Trafalgar Square after plain clothed police officer PC Tiffany Anderson noitced his suspicious behaviour. Upon further examination it was discovered that Dr. Iddamalgoda, a former Senior …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You Say Goodbye, I say Hello
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-you-say-goodbye-i-say-hello/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 16:12:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-you-say-goodbye-i-say-hello/</guid>
        <description>So, it has come to the end of an era, well a year-long era. Goodbye Tim and hello… me. I’m sure the Supreme Editor himself is feeling bittersweet; it’s the end of a very tiring year, but also the end of a year of fun and boundless creativity.
 I’ve already had a few ideas for next year’s Felix, so …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Alleged animal abuse
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-2-alleged-animal-abuse/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2013 14:16:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-2-alleged-animal-abuse/</guid>
        <description>During the Easter break Imperial came under national scrutiny after a seven month undercover investigation by the British Union for the Abolition of Vivisection (BUAV) alleges that there is a poor standard of professional conduct by Imperial scientists. Researchers from Imperial, one of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Revenge of the hacks
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-revenge-of-the-hacks/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 21:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-revenge-of-the-hacks/</guid>
        <description>This may be old news to some, but at the start of term, the databases of several universities worldwide were hacked. Called “Project WestWind” according to the manifesto of “Team Ghost Shell”, the system intrusions were a protest about changes in modern education, both in terms of rising tuition …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Student debt fears?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-25-student-debt-fears/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 18:49:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-25-student-debt-fears/</guid>
        <description>Normally running is a cheap affair; running for the bus only costs several seconds of embarrassment and the occasional penalty of abject failure when the driver leaves you behind in the cold. The cost of running for a sabbatical role in the IC Union? For most merely the embarrassment of selling your …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>One small step for POTUS
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-one-small-step-for-potus/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 11:23:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-one-small-step-for-potus/</guid>
        <description>Last week was unusual in politics, with a politician making a clear statement about their position on what to some is considered a controversial topic. Barack ‘Big O’ Obama clarified what he had previously described as his evolving attitudes to same-sex marriage, finally saying in an interview on US …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bringing down the Bankers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-bringing-down-the-bankers/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 22:10:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-bringing-down-the-bankers/</guid>
        <description>In the wake of last week’s pay scandal concerning RBS CEO Stephen Hester a lot has been said in regards to the opulence of bankers’ bonuses. In fact in the private student accommodation in which I live we even held a debate at the weekend, with a slim majority voting for motion which stated that the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fighting for Florida
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-fighting-for-florida/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 22:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-fighting-for-florida/</guid>
        <description>By the end of the year, Americans will have elected a new President. However, with no clear majority in public opinion for either the Democrats or the Republicans, who will become the next Leader of the Free World? Who will answer the call from visiting extra-terrestrial dignitaries?
The main focus …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Politics behind the wand
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-the-politics-behind-the-wand/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 20:04:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-the-politics-behind-the-wand/</guid>
        <description>With Halloween having passed uneventfully last week, in the absence of reports about legions of zombies laying waste to our towns and cities, we present you the Felix Politics Guide to the Ministry of Magic from the Harry Potter Series.
The Ministry of Magic
The British Ministry of Magic is the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Looting, Libya, and chaos on Capitol Hill
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-9-30-looting-libya-and-chaos-on-capitol-hill/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2011 11:35:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-9-30-looting-libya-and-chaos-on-capitol-hill/</guid>
        <description>Dear Freshers and regular readers, welcome to a new year at Imperial; a new year that brings new experiences and new challenges. The politics team in Felix hopes to keep you interested in the politics of the outside world while you spend your year in the bubble of university life.
However, since …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is this the end of nuclear power?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-is-this-the-end-of-nuclear-power/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 21:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-is-this-the-end-of-nuclear-power/</guid>
        <description>On Friday 11th March 2011, an earthquake of magnitude 9.0 struck 230 miles off the coast of northern Japan. As well as triggering a devastating tsunami, the earthquake has also caused problems with a nuclear plant in Fukushima, with developments keeping the global community sitting on the edge of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Year’s Resolutions
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-new-years-resolutions/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 20:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,Rajat Jain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-new-years-resolutions/</guid>
        <description>Silvio Berlusconi
Well 2010 certainly has been an interesting year for the Italian Prime Minister. Barely surviving several votes of no confidence throughout the year and having his coalition partner Gianfranco Fini and four other coalition government members step down has done a terrible number on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Will you join my (Mili)band?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-will-you-join-my-miliband/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 20:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-will-you-join-my-miliband/</guid>
        <description>Ever since the new leader EDavid Miliband stood up to the batting plate, how has Labour, once preening in the glory days, adjusted to a life as the Opposition?
After getting over the drama of usurping his brother EDavid, EDavid had to face the inevitable mountain of conflict that was choosing a …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
