<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sb6213/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sb6213/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Treasures from the Levant
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-treasures-from-the-levant/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 14:02:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanjay Bhattacharya,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-treasures-from-the-levant/</guid>
        <description>To look on at the birth of a new restaurant is always exciting – I’ve been a part of it, having seen the place I worked at in Oxford rise from the ashes of a mediocre Italian cocktail bar, and realising that I really wanted to be a part of that. Teething problems ranged from gutters that drained …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All hail the sublime starch, the chieftan of cuisine, the triumphant tuber | the potato
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-all-hail-the-sublime-starch-the-chieftan-of-cuisine-the-triumphant-tuber-the-potato/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 17:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanjay Bhattacharya,Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-all-hail-the-sublime-starch-the-chieftan-of-cuisine-the-triumphant-tuber-the-potato/</guid>
        <description> The humble spud. Where to start? How many foodstuffs can compare to the tuber that brought a whole nation to its knees – and I’m not talking about the Irish potato famine, but rather the introduction of potatoes to haute cuisine. People had been searching for a starch that was affordable yet …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What’s really in your meal?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-whats-really-in-your-meal/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 15:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanjay Bhattacharya,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-whats-really-in-your-meal/</guid>
        <description>I have to be honest with you – chefs are doing the job for one of two reasons. Either they absolutely love the food, job and ethos or, they are doing it as it’s the only option available to them. Frankly, the peanuts that you get paid for working 14 hour shifts, often for six days straight, wouldn’t …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Me man. Me want Steak.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-me-man-me-want-steak/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 15:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanjay Bhattacharya,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-me-man-me-want-steak/</guid>
        <description>Steak: at its finest, a juicy, browned hunk of meat, bursting with flavour, and apparently quintissentialy manly. At its worst, a drab, uninspired piece of “grilling” that disappoints in every mouthful.
At their most basic, steaks harken back to the most simple of cooked foods that our proto-chef …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Quick and easy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-quick-and-easy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 17:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanjay Bhattacharya,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-quick-and-easy/</guid>
        <description>Imust confess – the last time I made a stew, it took me 72 hours from start to finish. Short ribs, cooked at 54oC for two-and-a-half days in my waterbath were mouthwateringly tender and exceptionally beefy, with a wonderful red wine sauce and plenty of just tender veg. But fear not! You don’t need …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Back to Basics: Scones and Tea
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-back-to-basics-scones-and-tea/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 09:18:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,Sanjay Bhattacharya,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-back-to-basics-scones-and-tea/</guid>
        <description> If you had to pick one dish that represents Britain, what would it be? Mine would definitely be the traditional English afternoon tea. Probably the same as any typical Chinese girl.
Do not let the idea of afternoon tea scare you – this is going to be a casual affair, no extravagance, no posh …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I don&#39;t often sign petitions...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-i-dont-often-sign-petitions/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 08:57:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanjay Bhattacharya,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-i-dont-often-sign-petitions/</guid>
        <description>I don’t often sign petitions. Most people wouldn’t consider me particularly politically active - while I exercise my right to vote, I am far too often happy to read the news, bitch about the state of governance in this country (or the US – it’s really fucked up over there), and then leave it, whilst …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pavlov(a)’s dog
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-pavlovas-dog/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 09:34:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanjay Bhattacharya,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-pavlovas-dog/</guid>
        <description>Not as complex to make as a fine éclair, but with just as much flair and style, a pavlova is a delicious summer pudding. Hailing from New Zealand or Australia, depending on who you believe, it was named after the famed ballerina Anna Pavlova, whose ethereal frills it resembles. It’s a pretty classic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Live and let live, as long as you’re not tasty
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-live-and-let-live-as-long-as-youre-not-tasty/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:59:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanjay Bhattacharya,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-live-and-let-live-as-long-as-youre-not-tasty/</guid>
        <description> Morals are tricky things to have. I try, like I’m sure most of you do, but there are grey areas for me. Food can contain many of them. Like all transcendental ideas, it is sometimes easiest to simply pick and choose them as you like, but when they tie in to the very substance we consume every day …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Vegan? Gluten free? Cake? Surely not.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-vegan-gluten-free-cake-surely-not/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 12:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanjay Bhattacharya,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-vegan-gluten-free-cake-surely-not/</guid>
        <description>Cakes as birthday presents are great – so quick, cheap and the effort everyone knows you went to means that even if you mess it up, people will pretend it tastes good. Fortunately, this recipe is virtually idiot-proof. Go ahead, test that statement.
Makes 1 small cake, for about 6 hungry people with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to mash potatoes properly
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-how-to-mash-potatoes-properly/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 14:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanjay Bhattacharya,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-how-to-mash-potatoes-properly/</guid>
        <description> Now, you’re all going to think I’m crazy - telling you how to cook steak one week, and then mash the next? Madness – this bloke must think we can’t cook for toffee! Well, I’ve taken all the feedback from the few of you who did read it and not think it was a complete pile of garbage, and am going to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to cook meat
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-how-to-cook-meat/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 11:31:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanjay Bhattacharya,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-how-to-cook-meat/</guid>
        <description>The next time you get the family come to London and take you out for a meal, pause for a second before you order the steak. I mean, fine, it’s not your credit card, and it’s typically the most expensive item on the menu, so surely you’re getting your money’s worth? You certainly wouldn’t pay that …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
