<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rahul_mehta/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rahul_mehta/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Reclaiming The Frame</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-reclaiming-the-frame/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rahul Mehta,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-reclaiming-the-frame/</guid>
        <description>There is the usual muttering of visitors who have brought the energy of the streets into the solemn exhibition. Long lines of guests shuffle their feet between photos, some craning their necks in myopic fascination at the monochrome photographs of Sir Don McCullin. Eventually, the crowds thin out as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>More than Human? Stephanie Dinkins</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-more-than-human-stephanie-dinkins/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rahul Mehta,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-more-than-human-stephanie-dinkins/</guid>
        <description>Stephanie Dinkins’ eureka moment came as she stood face-to-face with BINA48, a black female robot residing in a first-floor office in Vermont. The opportunity was thanks to the work of the Terasem Foundation, a group dedicated to testing the limits of uploading a mind into a computer. Faced with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Left Off the Shelf</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-left-off-the-shelf/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rahul Mehta,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-left-off-the-shelf/</guid>
        <description>Despite the power of prose and verse to drag us from our seat on the Tube (or grim university flat) to the Victorian slums or outer sectors of the Galactic Empire, British literature is still being held back. While the characters in books transcend time and space, the non-fictional people who write …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Homage to Joie De Vivre</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-an-homage-to-joie-de-vivre/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rahul Mehta,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-an-homage-to-joie-de-vivre/</guid>
        <description>I like it. I just don’t get it,” my neighbour-turned-philosopher laments to her friend. As the audience stumbles out of our shared reverie, the sentiment is echoed through the foyer. The performance was well-executed, from eerily lifelike puppetry to the clever weaving of fairytale themes. But there …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
