<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/imrajsingh/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/imrajsingh/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Sports Editor’s Experience of the Relationship Between Sport and Mental Health</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-sports-editors-experience-of-relationship-sport-mental-health/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imraj Singh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-sports-editors-experience-of-relationship-sport-mental-health/</guid>
        <description>For Felix’s 70th Anniversary we’ve asked sports clubs for content on mental health in sport. I am happy to see that Imperial athletes, alongside their sport AND studies, run a range of campaigns spreading mental health awareness. Additionally, some teams have taken steps to promote welfare by having …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC Fishing Society Finds Affordable Fishing in London</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-ic-fishing-society-finds-affordable-fishing-London/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imraj Singh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-ic-fishing-society-finds-affordable-fishing-London/</guid>
        <description>Okay now you’ve taken the bait. There is no Imperial fishing society, but I do recommend starting a society if enough of you are interested. Also I am gill-ty of not technically fishing in London, it was Epping, but Central line does go there! Affordability is also questionable, £40 for a full day …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Super Bowl LIII: GOAT defeats Rams</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-super-bowl-liii-goat-defeats-rams/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imraj Singh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-super-bowl-liii-goat-defeats-rams/</guid>
        <description>New England Patriots 13 - 3 Los Angeles Rams
Field general Tom Brady marches down the field throwing short bullets and long bombs. Precise, calculated, commanding and highly efficient. Ain’t no mercy for the weak.
This is the demi-god quarterback of yesteryear who overcame the largest point deficit …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get involved with sport at Imperial!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-get-involved-with-sport-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imraj Singh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-get-involved-with-sport-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Sport has been for myself, and many of my friends, an integral part of university life. Being at university can be stressful not only because of academic pressure, but also because of moving away from home, dealing with finances, making new friends and stresses from home, as well as being pushed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>WTF is Ultimate Frisbee? </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-wtf-is-ultimate-frisbee/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imraj Singh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-wtf-is-ultimate-frisbee/</guid>
        <description>Ultimate Frisbee, also known by cool kids as just ‘Ultimate’, is a relatively new sport, having only been developed in the late 1960s by a few students in New Jersey. Since its inception, the sport has exploded in popularity; from flinging cookie tin lids in a play-ground to being recognized by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>WTF is Futsal? Felix sport’s guide to little known high-velocity, quick-paced, team-orientated Spanish sport</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-wtf-is-futsal-felix-sport-s-guide-to-little-known-high-velocity-quick-paced-team-orientated-spanish-sport/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imraj Singh,Harry Lanz,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-wtf-is-futsal-felix-sport-s-guide-to-little-known-high-velocity-quick-paced-team-orientated-spanish-sport/</guid>
        <description>Futsal is a bit of a rogue sport: one of the rare beauties with a cult following. Relatively unknown in the UK, it has larger audiences in Argentina, Brazil, Spain, and Portugal – countries which have spawned some of the best football players in the world. That is no coincidence. The likes of Pelé, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Everyone should take up sports at Imperial – your clubs need you!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-everyone-should-take-up-sports-at-imperial-your-clubs-need-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imraj Singh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-everyone-should-take-up-sports-at-imperial-your-clubs-need-you/</guid>
        <description>I’ll be the Sports Editor for Felix 2017&amp;frasl;18, and want to encourage you to try sport. With 60+ sports clubs to choose from its often hard to figure out what sport you’d be interested in trying. From sports that require more of a soft touch rather than a hard hit, that are team or individual, or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Immortals through to semi-finals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-immortals-through-to-semi-finals/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 14:49:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imraj Singh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-immortals-through-to-semi-finals/</guid>
        <description>Defeated, downtrodden, but with a fervent desire to win; that’s how we entered the season. As Drake so eloquently put it, “started from the bottom now we’re here”. After a winless season last year we have now risen to the top. A new coaching squad and great new recruits (as well as veteran players) …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cambridge humiliated by Immortals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-cambridge-humiliated-by-immortals/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 16:23:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imraj Singh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-cambridge-humiliated-by-immortals/</guid>
        <description>It has been only two weeks since the Immortals fell victim to the Cambridge Pythons. With a lapse of concentration (from a heavily fatigued Defence) the score was 6-0 for Pythons when the bell did toll. The loss was particularly painful due to the honest fact we are the better team, and on that day …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Patriots leave it late to secure historic win
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-patriots-leave-it-late-to-secure-historic-win/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 16:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imraj Singh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-patriots-leave-it-late-to-secure-historic-win/</guid>
        <description>Super bowl came about due to a merger agreement between two of the rival American football leagues the AFL (American Football league) and the NFL (National football league). This became official in 1970 when the NFL we all know and love was created. At that time there were only 26 teams, the rest …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC American Football clip Falcons’ wings
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-ic-american-football-clip-falcons-wings/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 16:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imraj Singh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-ic-american-football-clip-falcons-wings/</guid>
        <description>The Kent Falcons were our first game this season, all the way back on the 6th of November. As memory serves, we lost that game in a narrow overtime loss. The team have come far since then, and we showed it this Sunday. The Falcons (no Super Bowl relation) were quickly given the ball after an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC American Football in playoff contention
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-ic-american-football-in-playoff-contention/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 16:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imraj Singh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-ic-american-football-in-playoff-contention/</guid>
        <description>It was an early rise. Apparently too early for some of our squad. We embarked on our journey to the University of East Anglia Pirates with a heavily depleted squad and a hubris that we would make them walk the plank once again.
The game started slow with the Pirates’ offense unable to move the ball, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC deserve Leo’s Oscar after beating Bears
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-ic-deserve-leos-oscar-after-beating-bears/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 16:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imraj Singh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-ic-deserve-leos-oscar-after-beating-bears/</guid>
        <description>Following a strong win and a defensive shut out against the UEA Pirates, the Immortals were looking to build upon their momentum and announce themselves as serious playoff contenders. Standing in their way were the Immortals’ fierce rivals, Royal Holloway.
The Immortals received the ball to start, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>American Football make Pirates walk plank
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-american-football-make-pirates-walk-plank/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 14:52:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Imraj Singh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-american-football-make-pirates-walk-plank/</guid>
        <description>It has been a rough road for the IC Immortals, recently relegated from the highest tier of American Football in the country, to Division one. Immortals have now had the sweet taste of victory that had been missed so dearly.
After a close overtime defeat, Immortals were fearful of a repeat of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC American Football still hungry for victory
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-14-ic-american-football-still-hungry-for-victory/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 14:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Imraj Singh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-14-ic-american-football-still-hungry-for-victory/</guid>
        <description>After finishing 0-8 last year, the Immortals took to the field against the Kent Falcons with a hunger to win. The first half was sluggish with the offence unable to move the ball and a host of conceded penalties. A similar scene was seen across the Falcons’ offence. The Immortals were able to force …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
