<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/suraj_g/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/suraj_g/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Mutation as a form as music</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-mutation-as-a-form-as-music/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Suraj G,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-mutation-as-a-form-as-music/</guid>
        <description>Rules are suffocating, their mere existence a constraint, bound by our own machinations. To create is to liberate. To break rules is to break free. Bach should be terrified of Ornette Coleman, and I’d reckon Chaplin would be dizzy after a Harmony Korine film.
Ambient music exists at the very end of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Minimum to maximum, ambient to aggressive</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-minimum-to-maximum-ambient-to-aggressive/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Suraj G,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-minimum-to-maximum-ambient-to-aggressive/</guid>
        <description>Aggression has, for the most part, been a matter of force or damage. They yell, the guitars scream, the drums roar. All a product of man’s basest tendencies, a primitive release. Reining it back, Live 2002, is in many ways a controlled exploration of the impulses preceding the violence. Its …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The lights are on, but nobody’s home</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-the-lights-are-on-but-nobody-s-home/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Suraj G,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-the-lights-are-on-but-nobody-s-home/</guid>
        <description>The duo consisting of Mike Milosh and Robin Braun, known together as Rhye, would in 2013 release Woman. Woman aggressively dealt with the softer parts of life and love. Bold in its message, but delivered with a fragile gentleness, almost soft to the touch; Woman did little to avoid the comparisons …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pandering to the collective</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-pandering-to-the-collective/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Suraj G,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-pandering-to-the-collective/</guid>
        <description>Panda Bear, born Noah Lennox, has become a prevalent figure within the indie music community. A purveyor of genres, Lennox and his artistic counterpart Avey Tare (Michael Portner) have created some of the wildest and most original compositions from the mysterious space they seem to occupy in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>No one ever really thought they were still making  music together</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-12-no-one-ever-really-thought-they-were-still-making-music-together/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Suraj G,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-12-no-one-ever-really-thought-they-were-still-making-music-together/</guid>
        <description>After the seminal In Search Of&amp;hellip;, N.E.R.D.&amp;rsquo;s offerings throughout the noughties were but a string of disappointing releases. As the collective fell off everyone’s radar, its most prominent member, Pharrell Williams, began his meteoric rise to stardom, though Chad Hugo and Williams would …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The new Taylor Swift album can’t come to the phone right now. Why? Oh, ‘cause it’s shit.</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-the-new-taylor-swift-album-can-t-come-to-the-phone-right-now-why-oh-cause-it-s-shit/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Suraj G,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-the-new-taylor-swift-album-can-t-come-to-the-phone-right-now-why-oh-cause-it-s-shit/</guid>
        <description>It’s not too long since the world was introduced to girl next door and singer-songwriter, Taylor Swift, with her guitar and her country tinged pop. Upon entering the scene, Swift instantly made massive waves in the music industry and pop culture, for better or worse, with singles like ‘You belong …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An aktual-ly good album this week</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-an-aktual-ly-good-album-this-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Suraj G,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-an-aktual-ly-good-album-this-week/</guid>
        <description>Born in Iran and raised in London, beat wizard Ashkan Kooshanejad, better known by his alias Ash Koosha, broke into the electronic scene with debut album Guud in 2015. Taking the freneticism of Flying Lotus’ signature LA beat weirdness further, it seemed to spectators that Koosha could do no wrong. …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
