<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/skh10/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/skh10/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Mystery molecule found for heroin high
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-mystery-molecule-found-for-heroin-high/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 18:36:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sean Harbison,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-mystery-molecule-found-for-heroin-high/</guid>
        <description>The euphoria experienced from taking heroin is caused by a molecule known as 6-monoacetylmorphine (6-MAM) and not morphine as previously thought, says a new study carried out by the Department of Drug Abuse Research at the Norwegian Institute of Public Health. This new understanding of how heroin …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rinse, rave, and repeat
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-rinse-rave-and-repeat/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 19:49:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sean Harbison,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-rinse-rave-and-repeat/</guid>
        <description>Creamfields UK is a two day dance festival held by the Cream clubbing brand from Liverpool. It is held on the August bank holiday weekend in England just outside of Liverpool and hosts a large number of DJs from a variety of different genres. The festival has really evolved – from its beginning as a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You’ll need a lot of Gray Matter to enjoy this one
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-21-youll-need-a-lot-of-gray-matter-to-enjoy-this-one/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2011 11:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sean Harbison,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-21-youll-need-a-lot-of-gray-matter-to-enjoy-this-one/</guid>
        <description>Gray Matter starts off as any mystery game would: a creepy old mansion, half an hour’s bus ride from Oxford, during the middle of a storm. Sam Everett is an American who practices magic and is searching for a secret magicians’ club known as the Daedalus Club. Her motorbike breaks down in the rain …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Old Games Revisited: Ocarina of Time
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-old-games-revisited-ocarina-of-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 13:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sean Harbison,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-old-games-revisited-ocarina-of-time/</guid>
        <description>The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time is easily my favourite game of all time. Having started playing it at age seven, this game has played an integral part in shaping my interest in games. The story tells of a young boy, Link, who is asked to save the land of Hyrule from a terrible danger. This …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dungeons: Being a Dungeon Lord ain’t all fun and games
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-dungeons-being-a-dungeon-lord-aint-all-fun-and-games/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 20:38:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sean Harbison,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-dungeons-being-a-dungeon-lord-aint-all-fun-and-games/</guid>
        <description>Dungeons, the sequel to the 90’s classic Dungeon Keeper, is a sim-management game that sets the player as a Dungeon Lord who must design their foul, evil cave of despair to entince in heroes&amp;hellip; before brutally murdering them at their peak to steal their ‘soul energy’. The idea is basic enough; …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>When in Rome, do as the Assassins have always done
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-when-in-rome-do-as-the-assassins-have-always-done/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 19:49:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sean Harbison,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-when-in-rome-do-as-the-assassins-have-always-done/</guid>
        <description>After having your mind completely blown by Assassin’s Creed II’s preposterous ending (spoiler), Brotherhood returns to connect the dots in the bizarre tale and explain what exactly is going on. But in doing so, does it bring any new and redeeming features to expand the series and is it worth it as a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Same old story for Fable 3
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-same-old-story-for-fable-3/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 18:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sean Harbison,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-same-old-story-for-fable-3/</guid>
        <description>Welcome back to the Kingdom of Albion! 50 years on from the setting of Fable II, Fable III tells the story of a prince having to overthrow the tyrant king that is his brother. The game takes you through the prince’s role at the head of the revolution having to complete quests in order to convince …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Vegas comes up trumps
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-new-vegas-comes-up-trumps/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 19:26:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sean Harbison,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-new-vegas-comes-up-trumps/</guid>
        <description>Fallout: New Vegas brings us back to post-apocalyptic America to travel the vast wastelands once again. The story begins with you awaking in a room to discover you’ve just gone through surgery after being found shot and left for dead.
You immediately are given the option to design your character. …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
