<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/tags/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/tags/tech/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Organs-on-Chips – A catalyst for drug testing?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-organs-on-chips-a-catalyst-for-drug-testing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Krithika Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-organs-on-chips-a-catalyst-for-drug-testing/</guid>
        <description>According to the World Health Organization (WHO), antibiotic resistance in bacteria is one of the biggest threats to global health today. Bacteria gaining resistance is a natural process, but this has been accelerated by the misuse of medicines. The consequence of this is that bacteria remain …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Should we trust governments with our faces?  </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-should-we-trust-governments-with-our-faces/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Hubert Kaluzny,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-should-we-trust-governments-with-our-faces/</guid>
        <description>London is one of the world’s most surveilled cities. Recently, China has begun using facial recognition to keep track of one of their district’s Muslim populations. Ethically speaking, I believe we can all agree that, this is one of the worst uses of modern technology we have seen to date. At the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Some of the biggest tech announcements of 2017 </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-some-of-the-biggest-tech-announcements-of-2017/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ignatius-Roy Hillcoat-Nalletamby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-some-of-the-biggest-tech-announcements-of-2017/</guid>
        <description>March 2017 saw the phoenix that is Nintendo rise from its ashes with the release of its new console the Nintendo Switch. Marketed as a truly versatile game console, the Switch can be played in three modes – TV mode for the traditionalists who like a big TV, tabletop mode for when a big TV screen …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why your toothpaste, a Toyota Prius, and a McLaren F1 car have more in common than you think</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-why-your-toothpatse-a-toyota-prius-and-a-mclaren-f1-car-have-more-in-common-than-you-think/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Mrazek,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-why-your-toothpatse-a-toyota-prius-and-a-mclaren-f1-car-have-more-in-common-than-you-think/</guid>
        <description>Steel disc brakes, like many other technologies that make today’s cars so safe and efficient were developed nowhere other than on the racetrack. Until a revised version of the Jaguar C-Type first took to the track in 1953, drum brakes were considered the only practical way of stopping a car. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tesla’s Semi announcement is really just a distraction   </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-tesla-s-semi-announcement-is-really-just-a-distraction/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Mrazek,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-tesla-s-semi-announcement-is-really-just-a-distraction/</guid>
        <description>What came first, the Model 3 or the Falcon Heavy?
What’s the first word that comes to mind when I say Tesla? Performance, ecology? What about delays? If you’ve followed Tesla or SpaceX, you’re undoubtedly aware of a mysterious time zone known as Elon Standard Time™. Symptoms include thinking the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The James Dyson Award – upgrading the world one clever project at a time </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-the-james-dyson-award-upgrading-the-world-one-clever-project-at-a-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ignatius-Roy Hillcoat-Nalletamby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-the-james-dyson-award-upgrading-the-world-one-clever-project-at-a-time/</guid>
        <description>In September 2017, shortlisted entries for this year’s Dyson Award were announced. For those of you who don’t know, the Dyson Award is an international award for current and recently graduated design engineering students, coordinated by the James Dyson Foundation. The main purpose of the award is to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gene Drives – A technology capable of changing entire species</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-gene-drives-a-technology-capable-of-changing-entire-species/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xiuchen Xu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-gene-drives-a-technology-capable-of-changing-entire-species/</guid>
        <description>Gene drive technology allows humans to introduce genetical modifications to species that are always passed on to the next generation, which allows a characteristic to become prevalent in a species over very few generations. The technology is powerful enough to wipe out whole species, and has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The October 4th Google Event: Pixel 2 and More</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-the-october-4th-google-event-pixel-2-and-more/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ignatius-Roy Hillcoat-Nalletamby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-the-october-4th-google-event-pixel-2-and-more/</guid>
        <description>Google announced a host of new products in San Francisco on the 4th of October this year. Everyone eagerly awaited the announcement, particularly the unveiling of the company’s second flagship smartphone, the Pixel 2. However, in true Google fashion, there were a few surprises in the announcement …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is Elon Musk Big Brother?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-is-elon-musk-big-brother/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Mrazek,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-is-elon-musk-big-brother/</guid>
        <description>Our story begins with the jellyfish, the first animal to have a nervous system – or rather a nervous net. An animal without a nervous net can’t respond to its environment, so its odds of survival could be likened to flipping a coin. Having one was a real breakthrough. Later on, the flatworm …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
