<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ec610/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ec610/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The ‘hidden homeless’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-the-hidden-homeless/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 19:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anna Perman,Elizabeth Crouch,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-the-hidden-homeless/</guid>
        <description>A few weeks ago, many people were saddened to hear that Martin Milligan, who many knew as the man who sold the Big Issue in the South Kensington pedestrian tunnel, had passed away.
People flustered by the morning commute who would usually put their head down and stride past a homeless person, would …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Anti-Social Path?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-an-anti-social-path/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 19:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elizabeth Crouch,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-an-anti-social-path/</guid>
        <description>In November last year the latest in a seemingly never-ending string of social networks launched. ‘Path’ was hyped as a new way to socialise online and claimed to be founded on scientific principles. Its creators call it ‘a personal network’ where users can augment existing relationships instead of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How much support does Imperial provide?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-how-much-support-does-imperial-provide/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 21:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elizabeth Crouch,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-how-much-support-does-imperial-provide/</guid>
        <description>There are three main places that you can initially seek out help:
The Student Counselling Service offers free, confidential counselling on a short term basis to all students of Imperial College London. It is found at South Kensington, Hammersmith and Silwood Park Campuses. Appointments can be made …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let’s be more open about mental illness
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-lets-be-more-open-about-mental-illness/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 21:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,Elizabeth Crouch,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-lets-be-more-open-about-mental-illness/</guid>
        <description>Two o’clock in the morning. I had got home from an amazing night out and was falling asleep when I heard people running in the corridor. It was a Friday night and we were Freshers, so I thought nothing of it; I turned over and pulled the duvet tighter around me.
Literally seconds later I was woken …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Celebrating science in media
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-26-celebrating-science-in-media/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2010 07:20:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elizabeth Crouch,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-26-celebrating-science-in-media/</guid>
        <description>On Monday the Public Awareness of Science and Engineering organisation, PAWS, held The European Science TV and New Media Awards Evening at the prestigious Institute of Engineering and Technology (IET). A fitting location to celebrate science in the media, as the IET was once home to the BBC many …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Surfing the Zooniverse
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-surfing-the-zooniverse/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 21:58:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elizabeth Crouch,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-surfing-the-zooniverse/</guid>
        <description>A grainy picture pops up in front of me. It’s an unimpressive sight. On the right of the picture a simple question pops up, “Is the galaxy simply smooth and rounded, with no sign of a disk?” I’m given 3 options; I click the one which best suits the blob in front of me. I answer a couple more …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Swine flu carried deadly mutation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-swine-flu-carried-deadly-mutation/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 18:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elizabeth Crouch,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-swine-flu-carried-deadly-mutation/</guid>
        <description>Researchers at Imperial have been part of a global team whose latest research is giving greater insight into what caused tens of thousands of fatalities during last year’s H1N1 pandemic.
Viruses are weirdly beautiful. Their DNA material is held in a delicate and unique protein casing; an arrangement …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is this the future of learning at Imperial?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-is-this-the-future-of-learning-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 19:56:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elizabeth Crouch,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-is-this-the-future-of-learning-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>I have to admit that I did feel slightly nervous as I sat down in the back of the Clore Lecture Theatre. I had a slight hope that something would become familiar to me and that I wouldn’t feel like a fish-out-of-water Humanities student in a Mathematics lecture&amp;hellip; no such luck!
However, I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Broken promises...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-broken-promises/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 19:36:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elizabeth Crouch,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-broken-promises/</guid>
        <description>In the last few weeks there have been some very disgruntled Liberal Democrat supporters. The feeling that the Lib Dems had ‘sold out’ and forgotten their election pledges is widespread. So in light of the spending review, have the Liberal Democrats broken their election promises?
It’s worth having a …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
