<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/baf12/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/baf12/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Alumnus goes Galactic
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-alumnus-goes-galactic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 14:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Parikshat Singh,Benjamin Fernando,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-alumnus-goes-galactic/</guid>
        <description>Vice President of Virgin Galactic and Imperial alumnus, Jonathon Firth, is involved in developing the first commercial spaceflight company. He attended the 2015 SpaceLab conference last month, where he cornered him for an interview.
Felix: Would you mind telling us a little about your background, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to map the Heavens
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-9-how-to-map-the-heavens/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 19:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Fernando,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-9-how-to-map-the-heavens/</guid>
        <description>Ben Fernando: So why is it important to measure distances in cosmology?
Alan Heavens: According to General Relativity, the Universe’s geometry is related to its matter content. So if we look at the geometry of the universe, we can tell something about what’s in it – which we’re obviously very …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A decade of discovery
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-11-a-decade-of-discovery/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 20:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Fernando,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-11-a-decade-of-discovery/</guid>
        <description>Could you please tell me a little about exactly what your involvement in the mission is?
I am the principal investigator on the magnetometer instrument, one of 11 different instruments on the spacecraft. Our team is investigating the magnetic fields and features around Saturn and its moons. I’ve got …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Acton halls with panoramic views
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-21-acton-halls-with-panoramic-views/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2014 13:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Ball,Benjamin Fernando,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-21-acton-halls-with-panoramic-views/</guid>
        <description>Felix paid a visit to the construction site of the new Halls, One Victoria Road, to investigate how things were progressing and to talk to Campus Services about the latest news and updates ον τηε προϕεχτ.
Currently, no decision has yet been taken on the future of Evelyn Gardens. All that is known …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Prof. Sir John Pendry, the physicist famous for inventing the invisiblity cloak
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-prof-sir-john-pendry-the-physicist-famous-for-inventing-the-invisiblity-cloak/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 23:34:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Fernando,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-prof-sir-john-pendry-the-physicist-famous-for-inventing-the-invisiblity-cloak/</guid>
        <description>Professor Sir John Pendry, FRS, holds a Chair in Theoretical Solid State Physics here at Imperial. In 2014 he was awarded the $1M Kavli Prize by the Norwegian Academy of Science and Letters in recognition of his work in the field of nano-optics. This article is a summary of an interview for Felix …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“I came from a generation that thought that misery and intellect were synonymous.&#34;
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-i-came-from-a-generation-that-thought-that-misery-and-intellect-were-synonymous/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 22:46:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Fernando,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-i-came-from-a-generation-that-thought-that-misery-and-intellect-were-synonymous/</guid>
        <description>BF: Why don’t you tell me a little bit about yourself, and why you want to be the next Dean?
TW: I grew up in North London on a council estate, and today turning up at the place that when I was young was the place to be to study science still shocks me. I do my research and my teaching, but how can …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dangerous Liasons In Fisher Hall Damage Wall
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-dangerous-liasons-in-fisher-hall-damage-wall/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 10:36:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Fernando,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-dangerous-liasons-in-fisher-hall-damage-wall/</guid>
        <description>[Tabloid Special]
Further concerns have been raised in recent weeks about the structural integrity of the Fisher Hall buildings in Evelyn Gardens, including the event mentioned in the above title.
Following a prior investigation of Fisher last year, this author visited again to examine the most …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Travel Chaos – Strikes Again!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-travel-chaos-strikes-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 00:51:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Fernando,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-travel-chaos-strikes-again/</guid>
        <description>London was plunged into travel chaos again this week: another tube strike left commuters stranded as parts of the city ground to a standstill. For those of you who somehow missed the first one, this is the second strike instituted by the Rail, Maritime and Transport Union (RMT) as they protest the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Obituary: Bob Crow
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-17-obituary-bob-crow/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2014 17:19:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Fernando,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-17-obituary-bob-crow/</guid>
        <description>London awoke to a shock on Tuesday morning with the news that Bob Crow, the leader of Rail, Maritime and Transport (RMT) union had died at the age of 52. During the RMT strikes last month that crippled London Crow sprang to national prominence as the situation pitted him against Boris Johnson, Mayor …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Balls to ask about Amendment to Immigration Bill
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-balls-to-ask-about-amendment-to-immigration-bill/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 03:22:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Fernando,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-balls-to-ask-about-amendment-to-immigration-bill/</guid>
        <description>The Union’s campaign to stop international students being charged for NHS services under the Government’s Immigration Bill received a strong boost late last month when Ed Balls, the Shadow Chancellor, agreed to look into an amendment to the bill that would exempt students from the charge. Responding …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why Volunteer?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-why-volunteer/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 20:05:24 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Fernando,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-why-volunteer/</guid>
        <description>Some people think that charity should be done as a completely selfless pursuit. Perhaps it should be! But the reality is that we’re all busy and want to enjoy our free time at Imperial, so why bother to do not-for-profit work? Here are a few reasons. Some of them are obvious, some are not…
1) You …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fisher Halls are Fishy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-3-fisher-halls-are-fishy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2013 23:08:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,Benjamin Fernando,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-3-fisher-halls-are-fishy/</guid>
        <description>Much of last year’s #AgainstActon campaign focused on the impending closure of Evelyn Gardens’ Fisher Hall. The huge campaign lasted months but the plans to create the halls were continued. In 2011, the college announced that the Fisher Hall was no longer required. This was due to the completion of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Help Soup Run feed London’s homeless
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-21-help-soup-run-feed-londons-homeless/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2013 00:59:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Fernando,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-21-help-soup-run-feed-londons-homeless/</guid>
        <description>Homelessness is probably London’s most visible social problem. We all see it daily, in the men and women who spend their days with a paper cup, begging for spare change in the capital’s allleyways. Some of us ignore them – after all, we can’t possibly help them all. Some of us give them a smile, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>North Acton: How bad is it really?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-north-acton-how-bad-is-it-really/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 18:55:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Fernando,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-north-acton-how-bad-is-it-really/</guid>
        <description>At first sign, North Acton station appears prettier than most – there’s even a cherry tree in front of the ticket barriers. Travel time from South Kensington: 45 minutes 18 seconds. That’s 45 metric minutes at 60 seconds/minute, not these new 80 second imperial-Acton minutes that the college use in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flight of the Phoenix!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-8-flight-of-the-phoenix/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 00:34:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Fernando,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-8-flight-of-the-phoenix/</guid>
        <description>How hard is it to steal a mascot? Apparently not hard if it’s the ICSM one! At least, so suggest reports of the theft of the Phoenix from inside the depths of Charing Cross Hospital earlier this week.
Our correspondent can confirm rumours that a crack team of six first year physicists (the Physsix) …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
