<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/gj309/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/gj309/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>George Jeffery’s A beginner’s guide to post-hardcore #9
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-george-jefferys-a-beginners-guide-to-post-hardcore-9/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 21:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>George Jeffery,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-george-jefferys-a-beginners-guide-to-post-hardcore-9/</guid>
        <description>Over the past ten weeks, I’ve tried to give an insight into the wonderful world of post-hardcore music. Hopefully I’ve achieved my goal in revamping the record collection of the old-timer P-H fans and perhaps even converted some people previously sceptical about this incredible genre. However, the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>George Jeffery’s A beginner’s guide to post-hardcore #8
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-george-jefferys-a-beginners-guide-to-post-hardcore-8/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 23:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>George Jeffery,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-george-jefferys-a-beginners-guide-to-post-hardcore-8/</guid>
        <description>This week we’ll be taking a detour into the mysterious world of so-called “math-core”. Math-core is to post-hardcore what Imperial is to UCL: the same, just a bit cleverer. There are countless math-core bands that have left their mark on post-hardcore music but the one I’m reviewing this week is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>George Jeffery’s A beginner’s guide to post-hardcore #7
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-george-jefferys-a-beginners-guide-to-post-hardcore-7/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 21:37:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>George Jeffery,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-george-jefferys-a-beginners-guide-to-post-hardcore-7/</guid>
        <description>A few of you may remember an article which appeared in Felix Music last term about a trampy man who played an acoustic gig on a boat. Well this man is about to have his Imperial fame replenished as this week I acquaint you with UK post-hardcore masterminds Meet Me In St. Louis.
The band, fronted by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>George Jeffery’s A beginner’s guide to post-hardcore #6
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-george-jefferys-a-beginners-guide-to-post-hardcore-6/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 22:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>George Jeffery,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-george-jefferys-a-beginners-guide-to-post-hardcore-6/</guid>
        <description>As promised, this week I will be beginning my rampage of digging up dead, old UK post-hardcore bands. The first band to be mentioned is, obviously, Reuben. Despite their ten-year lifetime and numerous outstanding releases, they failed to gain any mainstream success (as is the story for most bands in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A beginner’s guide to post-hardcore #5
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-a-beginners-guide-to-post-hardcore-5/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 22:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>George Jeffery,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-a-beginners-guide-to-post-hardcore-5/</guid>
        <description>This week’s band have arguably had the most mainstream success out of all the bands that will feature in this series and prove that post-hardcore music, while perhaps a relatively niche genre, comes in various shapes and sizes.
The Fall of Troy split recently after their brief but fruitful career. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A beginner’s guide to post-hardcore #4
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-a-beginners-guide-to-post-hardcore-4/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 11:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>George Jeffery,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-a-beginners-guide-to-post-hardcore-4/</guid>
        <description>What better way to wave goodbye to week 4 than with a timely fix of post-hardcore goodness. This week, I’ll be telling you all about Every Time I Die. As was the case with the second lesson’s band, Refused, Every Time I Die doesn’t strictly belong to the post-hardcore genre but for anyone following …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Beginner&#39;s Guide to post-hardcore
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-27-a-beginners-guide-to-post-hardcore/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 12:29:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>George Jeffery,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-27-a-beginners-guide-to-post-hardcore/</guid>
        <description>The point of this column is to give you enough guidance so that you can go out into the big bad world of post-hardcore and not end up naked, lying in filth and eating your own rancid faeces. That was meant to be symbolic for listening to poor music by the way. To set you up with a solid foundation, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A beginner’s guide to post-hardcore
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-a-beginners-guide-to-post-hardcore/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 22:52:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>George Jeffery,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-a-beginners-guide-to-post-hardcore/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the first instalment of this weekly guide to the darker side of alternative music. What better way to start than with the news that the almighty At The Drive-In have reformed after a ten-year hiatus. Those of you familiar with this band will probably be losing your noggin right now, but …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Now, not then, JCQ
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-now-not-then-jcq/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 21:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>George Jeffery,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-now-not-then-jcq/</guid>
        <description>This week I’m going back straight back to the UK post-punk/hardcore scene by way of a review of the debut full-length album of The James Cleaver Quintet (JCQ), That Was Then, This Is Now. Nearly two years ago the JCQ released their first and only EP Ten Stages of a Make Up to massive critical …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
