<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/dhl106/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/dhl106/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Confessions of a Food Editor
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-confessions-of-a-food-editor/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 21:11:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dana Li,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-confessions-of-a-food-editor/</guid>
        <description>Reviews. I hate writing reviews for places that I’ve eaten ‘on the house’. There’s something about dining for free, and the awkward moment when you don’t call for the bill. Do you just thank the waiter and bid him “Adieu!”? And when the restaurant gets my review in the post, I always wonder whether …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are you MADD?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-12-are-you-madd/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 16:10:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dana Li,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-12-are-you-madd/</guid>
        <description>Rupert Street. It’s not exactly a street name that shouts out “Food Mecca”, such an honour usually reserved for the likes of Brick Lane, Old Street and Borough Market. But think again. I visited Rupert Street, located in the centre of Soho, three times within a period of two or so weeks. Not for the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Venice: a pragmatist’s guide
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-venice-a-pragmatists-guide/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 04:24:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dana Li,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-venice-a-pragmatists-guide/</guid>
        <description>“What do you think of Venice?” I asked. “Tourist trap”, replied Dylan. When he next told me that he hadn’t even been, I decided his opinion was invalid: I wasn’t prepared to discuss the pitfalls of this dream destination, considering the countless praise it gets.
Fast forward a fortnight and I was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brad Pitt isn&#39;t the only reason I love &#39;Meet Joe Black&#39;
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-brad-pitt-isnt-the-only-reason-i-love-meet-joe-black/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 15:09:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dana Li,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-brad-pitt-isnt-the-only-reason-i-love-meet-joe-black/</guid>
        <description>The memorable scenes of Brad Pitt licking peanut butter off a spoon in Meet Joe Black is exactly how I’d like to imagine the grim reaper. Suave, suited and darn right fit.
It’s not Brad I wanted to talk about really, though, it’s the love of peanut butter. The legume delight.
Peanut butter ice …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ciccetti: the Italian gastro-fad
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-ciccetti-the-italian-gastro-fad/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 19:39:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dana Li,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-ciccetti-the-italian-gastro-fad/</guid>
        <description>Italian food is probably the cuisine that serves the most disparity in London. The big giants like Pizza Express, ASK and Zizzi lure the indifferent diners with their attractive 2-for-1 deals, but what say you to pasta that is freshly made on the day and pesto that is so brilliant, even Berlusconi …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gastronomical Musings
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-gastronomical-musings/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 19:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dana Li,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-gastronomical-musings/</guid>
        <description>Dana says:
MasterChef. Nothing quite like another cooking programme to shove down our already gagging throats. Except MasterChef&amp;rsquo;s been with us for almost twenty years so we can&amp;rsquo;t exactly blast it for old time&amp;rsquo;s sake. After creating various spin-offs to make celebrities think they …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Homemade sushi
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-homemade-sushi/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 20:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dana Li,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-homemade-sushi/</guid>
        <description>Japanese food is widely associated with expensive prices and not a lot of food. However that doesn’t always have to be the case. All you need to do is equip yourself with a tube map and a willingness to travel.
The best part of making your own sushi is that you can add any fish, seafood, meat or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kowtow to the master... Wafflemeister is in the house!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-kowtow-to-the-master-wafflemeister-is-in-the-house/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 19:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dana Li,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-kowtow-to-the-master-wafflemeister-is-in-the-house/</guid>
        <description>Have you ever tried Sainbury’s Belgian Waffles? They glow a certain shade of yellow that reminds me of the Mercedes Benz SLK320 in sunshine yellow. God knows just how many additives they employed for you to ‘Taste the Difference’.
These had put me off waffles for life.
Until a standard post-night …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Blown away by the Soleil
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-blown-away-by-the-soleil/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 19:22:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dana Li,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-blown-away-by-the-soleil/</guid>
        <description>Totem. Avid Inception fans will immediately think back to the object with which Dom Cobb differentiates between the real and the imaginary. Did it or did it not stop spinning? That is the question. For other Londoners, however, Totem signifies the latest touring Cirque du Soleil show at the Royal …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Awana: Malaysia’s pride
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-awana-malaysias-pride/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 20:58:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dana Li,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-awana-malaysias-pride/</guid>
        <description>People tell me a job as a food critic would get boring. Good food, VIP treatment and food babies (don’t pretend like you don’t know what I mean) – it’s a hard life, isn’t it?
Walking down towards Sloane Avenue, you bypass the size 0 mannequins adorned with Chanel handbags, Ferragamo coats and Jimmy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The best of the 1920s: Prohibition is back
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-the-best-of-the-1920s-prohibition-is-back/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 18:36:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dana Li,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-the-best-of-the-1920s-prohibition-is-back/</guid>
        <description>Those who paid attention in GCSE History will remember what a fantastic time 1920s America was: cue Rudolph Valentino, the first heartthrob of Hollywood’s silent films; thriving underground speakeasies under the Prohibition act and the infamous Valentine Day’s Massacre of Al Capone. Just don’t …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lunch at The Rembrandt
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-lunch-at-the-rembrandt/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 19:35:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dana Li,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-lunch-at-the-rembrandt/</guid>
        <description>The mere mention that I am having lunch at The Rembrandt in Knightsbridge brings gasps of excitement and jeers of disbelief. It’s not everyday that you dine in the Knightsbridge area, so I made every chance to boast about it!
Home to Harrods and resident restaurants such as Zuma, Petrus and …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
