<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ajf14/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ajf14/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Golden weekend for IC frisbee at regionals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-golden-weekend-for-ic-frisbee-at-regionals/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 17:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anthony Featherstone,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-golden-weekend-for-ic-frisbee-at-regionals/</guid>
        <description>The indoor frisbee season has well and truly got underway, and the Imperial disc Doctors (dD) were able to send three teams to the men’s indoor regionals, one of only two teams in the region to be able to do so. Having won this competition last year, expectations were high, but the team wanted to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC dD dazzle, dive and dart at mixed regionals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-14-ic-dd-dazzle-dive-and-dart-at-mixed-regionals/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 14:19:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anthony Featherstone,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-14-ic-dd-dazzle-dive-and-dart-at-mixed-regionals/</guid>
        <description>After a great start to the year for the disc Doctors (dD - Imperial’s Ultimate Frisbee club) with the women performing brilliantly at SICKO and our very own beginners’ tournament, the women in particular were outstanding, scoring an impressive number of points and maintaining the quality of their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Men’s 2nd XV reach 18-win streak
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-7-mens-2nd-xv-reach-18-win-streak/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 13:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anthony Featherstone,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-7-mens-2nd-xv-reach-18-win-streak/</guid>
        <description>The 2s continued their perfect streak with yet another win, this time at Fortress Harlington against Canterbury Christ Church. With the 1s on a rest week, the team had a big, loud crowd to back them up, and did not disappoint. The Imperial pack was unstoppable, winning every scrum, making it easy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flying high with Imperial frisbee
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-flying-high-with-imperial-frisbee/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 10:22:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anthony Featherstone,Lucy J Rowlands,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-flying-high-with-imperial-frisbee/</guid>
        <description>Imperial’s Ultimate Frisbee club, more commonly known as the discDoctors (or dD) were in a position to bring both a women’s team and a men’s team to nationals for the first time ever, with the men having qualified in the league throughout the season, and the women finishing highly at Outdoor …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
