<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jb3112/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jb3112/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Does parliament need more scientists?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-20-does-parliament-need-more-scientists/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2015 00:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Bezer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-20-does-parliament-need-more-scientists/</guid>
        <description>The impact of science has never been confined to the laboratory. Today, many of the most important and difficult decisions faced by politicians are fundamentally scientific, from the best way to tackle climate change to the recent vote to allow mitochondrial replacement therapy.
Robert Winston, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“This does not threaten the fabric of our society”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-this-does-not-threaten-the-fabric-of-our-society/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 19:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Bezer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-this-does-not-threaten-the-fabric-of-our-society/</guid>
        <description>“This does not threaten the fabric of our society in any way whatsoever: it’s an individual choice for someone who’s watched a child die of a horrible disease”.
For Robert Winston, a pioneer of IVF and one of the country’s most famous doctors, the recent decision by the House of Lords to approve the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sound field around recorder identified
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-3-sound-field-around-recorder-identified/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 15:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Bezer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-3-sound-field-around-recorder-identified/</guid>
        <description>Anyone who’s ever been to a primary school music recital may well have got the impression that the recorder is a rather simple instrument.
The physics behind it, however, is incredibly complicated.
Using a powerful supercomputer running for two weeks, a group led by Hiroshi Yokoyama from Toyohashi …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Genes responsible for Asthma uncovered
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-20-genes-responsible-for-asthma-uncovered/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 00:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Bezer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-20-genes-responsible-for-asthma-uncovered/</guid>
        <description>Epigenetic factors behind asthma and other allergic diseases have been identified by a group at Imperial College in research that could lead to better targeted and more effective treatments. Their paper, published in Nature, identifies 34 genes related to inflammation, inhibited in healthy people, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hubble takes 1.5 billion pixel photo of Andromeda
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-hubble-takes-15-billion-pixel-photo-of-andromeda/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 17:54:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Bezer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-hubble-takes-15-billion-pixel-photo-of-andromeda/</guid>
        <description>The Hubble space telescope has taken the highest resolution image ever made of a galaxy. The image is so detailed that it’s possible to resolve individual stars in a 61,000 light-year wide panorama.
Andromeda is the Milky Way’s nearest neighbour, 2.5 million light- years away from us. The image, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First UK organ transplant from a newborn
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-first-uk-organ-transplant-from-a-newborn/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 17:46:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Bezer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-first-uk-organ-transplant-from-a-newborn/</guid>
        <description>The UK’s first organ donation from a newborn baby has been performed at an Imperial College NHS Trust hospital.
The donor, a baby girl, was born after an emergency caesarean at Hammersmith hospital. She was deprived of oxygen during the difficult birth and suffered severe neurological damage. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Andrew Mitchell, MP, speaks at Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-andrew-mitchell-mp-speaks-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 01:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Bezer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-andrew-mitchell-mp-speaks-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Former cabinet minister and current MP for Sutton Coldfield, Andrew Mitchell spoke to students this week about the importance of aid and charity in improving the lives of people in the developing world.
In front of large audience in Blackett Lecture Theatre 1, Mitchell – perhaps best known to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Professor Keith Barnham talks about his vision for the future of solar energy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-professor-keith-barnham-talks-about-his-vision-for-the-future-of-solar-energy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 21:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Bezer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-professor-keith-barnham-talks-about-his-vision-for-the-future-of-solar-energy/</guid>
        <description>James: You originally started your career in particle physics—why did you change to researching solar panels?
Prof. Barnham: I loved particle physics: I worked at CERN and Berkeley and it was very exciting at both places.
When I joined Imperial, I spent much of my time at CERN. Collaborations were …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Everyone thought it was a bit of a crazy idea.”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-21-everyone-thought-it-was-a-bit-of-a-crazy-idea/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2014 13:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Bezer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-21-everyone-thought-it-was-a-bit-of-a-crazy-idea/</guid>
        <description>How did you get involved with Rosetta?
That goes back a long time. I was first involved in 1997. Our group is interested in space physics, making measurments of plasmas, particles and magnetic fields. At the time I was working on Cluster — a project to map the earth’s magnetic field. When the ESA …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rosetta probe successfully lands on comet
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-rosetta-probe-successfully-lands-on-comet/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 21:09:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Bezer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-rosetta-probe-successfully-lands-on-comet/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday afternoon, the signal came through that one of the most ambitious space missions ever attempted has successfully landed on a comet.
In the ten years since it was launched, Rosetta has travelled six billion kilometres to reach comet 67P/C-G, currently orbiting the sun between Mars and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Noble are the Breakthrough Prizes?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-how-noble-are-the-breakthrough-prizes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 21:06:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Bezer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-how-noble-are-the-breakthrough-prizes/</guid>
        <description>“I don’t like honours.”
When asked how he felt to have been awarded the Nobel Prize, the most prestigious honour that can be bestowed upon a scientist, Richard Feynman seemed rather unimpressed.
“I’ve already got the prize,” he said. “The prize is the pleasure of finding the thing out, the kick in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What you missed this summer in science
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-what-you-missed-this-summer-in-science/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 22:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Bezer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-what-you-missed-this-summer-in-science/</guid>
        <description>As you put in your personal statement, ever since you were born, you’ve had a deep and passionate curiosity about the intriguing wonders of science. Why not put this to good use by writing for Felix?
If you’re desperate to tell the world about your views on fracking, or a fascinating new discovery …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Travelling to space on a budget?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-travelling-to-space-on-a-budget/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 19:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Bezer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-travelling-to-space-on-a-budget/</guid>
        <description>Not many of us have a spare quarter-of-a-million dollars to blow on a half-hour joy-ride.
It seems that nobody has told this to Richard Branson.
After the gleaming white craft he had hoped would one day take him to the edge of space came crashing to the ground, killing one pilot and seriously …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You can’t teach an old virus new tricks
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-7-you-cant-teach-an-old-virus-new-tricks/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 12:57:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Bezer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-7-you-cant-teach-an-old-virus-new-tricks/</guid>
        <description>After spending 30,000 years lurking deep within the Siberian permafrost, an enormous virus has escaped its icy lair. Even after all those years encased in ice, it’s still deadly. But this isn’t the plot of a low-budget horror film. This is real science.
If you’re feeling worried, don’t panic. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hating headlines that tell you how to feel
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-hating-headlines-that-tell-you-how-to-feel/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 13:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Bezer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-hating-headlines-that-tell-you-how-to-feel/</guid>
        <description>Old people have always had it in for BBC3. Unlike the sleepy old BBC4, home of gentle documentaries presented by the lovely Lucy Worsley, BBC3 is an overactive puppy, full of rebellion and naïve excitement that spends most of its spare time engaged in an act of passion with the living room …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Radiation-free tumour detection method
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-28-radiation-free-tumour-detection-method/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 07:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Bezer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-28-radiation-free-tumour-detection-method/</guid>
        <description>Diagnosis and treatment of cancer often involves some of the most damaging procedures that doctors would ever intentionally inflict upon a human body. The effects of chemotherapy, for instance, are notorious, but radiation from treatment or scans can sometimes be just as harmful to a patient’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The pseudoscience shaking the Shroud
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-the-pseudoscience-shaking-the-shroud/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 03:11:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Bezer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-the-pseudoscience-shaking-the-shroud/</guid>
        <description>Alongside UFOs, homeopathy and all manners of conspiracy theories, the Shroud of Turin has long been known as a perennial source of pseudoscience. It has almost certainly lived up to its well-earned reputation this week. An army of journalists have flooded the internet with stories about a new paper …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Crystallography turns 100
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-crystallography-turns-100/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 05:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Bezer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-crystallography-turns-100/</guid>
        <description>There are few scientific techniques that have had such an enormous influence across so many disciplines as crystallography. In the past 100 years, it has led to no fewer than 28 Nobel Prizes for discoveries from right across the natural sciences, and remains one the best ways we have of determining …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ancient traces of water found on Mars
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-ancient-traces-of-water-found-on-mars/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 17:43:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Bezer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-ancient-traces-of-water-found-on-mars/</guid>
        <description>For a vehicle designed to last just 7 earth weeks, Opportunity has done remarkably well. Ten years to the day since the rover first landed on the surface of Mars, its new analysis of some of the oldest rocks ever found there show environments potentially suitable for life were around on the planet …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hubble gives us further insight into distant galaxies
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-hubble-gives-us-further-insight-into-distant-galaxies/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 09:59:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Bezer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-hubble-gives-us-further-insight-into-distant-galaxies/</guid>
        <description>18 years after the famous Deep Field image, a series of photographs from the Hubble space telescope are giving us a new insight into extremely distant galaxies that formed soon after the big bang. This new deep image is centred on a large galaxy cluster, Abell 2744, which acts as a gravitational …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Most distant gravitational lens yet discovered
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-24-most-distant-gravitational-lens-yet-discovered/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 23:51:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Bezer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-24-most-distant-gravitational-lens-yet-discovered/</guid>
        <description>The most distant example of a gravitational lens has been discovered by scientists in Germany. The large galaxy, 9.4 billion light years away from us, focuses light towards the earth, like a sort of cosmic telescope, enabling us to detect another smaller, more distant galaxy that would normally be …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
