<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ef510/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ef510/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Game of Thrones returns
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-game-of-thrones-returns/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 01:58:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Fulham,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-game-of-thrones-returns/</guid>
        <description>As Game of Thrones enters its fourth series, it’s easy to imagine that the show’s writers and producers would be pretty pleased with themselves: the huge success of the show, unforeseen at its inception three years ago, and a vast fanbase that stretches far beyond the usual fans of genre TV means …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The West Wing: A Retrospective
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-7-the-west-wing-a-retrospective/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 12:39:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Fulham,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-7-the-west-wing-a-retrospective/</guid>
        <description>The West Wing is widely acknowledged to be the best political drama ever shown on American television. The seven series were broadcast from 1999 to 2006, premiering the same year as Bill Clinton’s impeachment trial and finishing in the depths of George Bush’s second term, when the president had an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Three musketeers, one review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-17-three-musketeers-one-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 18:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Fulham,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-17-three-musketeers-one-review/</guid>
        <description>There are a few ways to instantly sell me on a new TV show, regardless of reviews or recommendations. The new BBC show, Musketeers, hit virtually all of the boxes: an adaptation of an all-time favourite book, a cast featuring Peter Capaldi and the hot artist from Heroes, and plenty of sword fights. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sherlock’s success: It’s Elementary?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-sherlocks-success-its-elementary/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 04:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Fulham,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-sherlocks-success-its-elementary/</guid>
        <description>Sherlock’s third series debuted on New Year’s Day to tremendous hype. After two years of being off-air, fans were hoping that it would match their high expectations. Now that the dust has settled on the last of the three episodes, what was the final verdict? As with anything, it depends who you ask. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Girls, uninterrupted
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-girls-uninterrupted/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 04:19:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Fulham,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-girls-uninterrupted/</guid>
        <description>It’s been a year since we last saw the girls of Girls, so the news that its third series would return with a double bill was definitely welcome. The ever-divisive show picks up a short while after we left off at the end of the second season, in which time there’s been more than a few developments. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Fang-tom Menace
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-the-fang-tom-menace/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 16:33:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Fulham,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-the-fang-tom-menace/</guid>
        <description>It was easy to respond to the news of NBC and Sky’s latest venture, Dracula, with a roll of the eyes. What with the frenzied spate of anything vampire-themed following the dubious success of Twilight, including the rise and fall of True Blood and The Vampire Diaries, it would appear that the show is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Television for the Attention Deficit
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-television-for-the-attention-deficit/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 18:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Fulham,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-television-for-the-attention-deficit/</guid>
        <description> Ever wanted to watch a new TV show without, you know, committing to it? We’ve all been there: start watching a new series, thinking it looks pretty cool, and next thing you know, you’re nine series in and have no idea why you’re still watching, but too emotionally invested to stop (here’s looking …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Television is dead, long live the internet
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-television-is-dead-long-live-the-internet/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 09:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Fulham,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-television-is-dead-long-live-the-internet/</guid>
        <description>Netflix are branching out. No longer content with being the mother of all procrastination techniques (in the battle of lab report against the entire series of Gossip Girl, there can only be one winner) and bringing in the internet streaming revolution, the American website has started showing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Five suggestions for TV-themed Halloween Costumes
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-five-suggestions-for-tv-themed-halloween-costumes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 00:58:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Fulham,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-five-suggestions-for-tv-themed-halloween-costumes/</guid>
        <description>Daenerys Targaryon (Game of Thrones)
Stick on a blonde wig and smudge dirt on your face. Don’t worry if you don’t have dragons to complete the costume; it’ll add to the authenticity when you knock on your neighbours’ door screaming, “Where are my dragons??”
Tobias Fünke (Arrested Development)
Who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Something Creepy This Way Comes
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-something-creepy-this-way-comes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 00:55:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Fulham,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-something-creepy-this-way-comes/</guid>
        <description>With Halloween only a week away, ‘tis the season to carve pumpkins and watch something spooky. One new show that fits the bill is Sleepy Hollow, one of the US’s new autumn shows, the first episode of which was shown last week on Universal. Whilst the show isn’t directly related to the film of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dark Days in Downton Abbey
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-dark-days-in-downton-abbey/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 19:18:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Fulham,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-dark-days-in-downton-abbey/</guid>
        <description>At the beginning of this week’s Downton Abbey, there was a warning for “violent scenes which some viewers may find upsetting”, leading me to wonder what the cause could possibly be. Given the most significant crisis thus far this season has been a matter of inheritance tax, it was difficult to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A bewildering journey into Ancient Greece
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-6-a-bewildering-journey-into-ancient-greece/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2013 10:15:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Fulham,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-6-a-bewildering-journey-into-ancient-greece/</guid>
        <description>With the demise of Merlin, the BBC were clearly in the market for a new family-friendly fantasy drama to fill the Saturday evening slot. Enter Atlantis, a retelling of the legend of Greek hero Jason, best known as leader of the Argonauts and slayer of the minotaur. Well, &amp;ldquo;retelling&amp;rdquo; is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who run the world?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-who-run-the-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 01:18:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Fulham,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-who-run-the-world/</guid>
        <description>&amp;ldquo;I don’t want to freak you out, but I think that I may be the voice of my generation.” So says Hannah Horvath, the main character of HBO’s Girls, in the very first episode of the show. It’s a line that’s come back to haunt Lena Dunham, the show’s creator, writer and co-producer, who also plays …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
