<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/guthrie_ruby/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/guthrie_ruby/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Amnioverse: A Perfect Album Listening Experience</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-amnioverse-a-perfect-album-listening-experience/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-amnioverse-a-perfect-album-listening-experience/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
I don’t think I’d be offending anyone by saying that most listeners of electronic music focus more on singles than albums. When you listen to Hybrid Minds or Bicep you normally wouldn’t play the whole album start to finish. However, there are electronic albums that actively work against …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rock Throughout the Ages</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-rock-throughout-ages/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Freeman,Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-rock-throughout-ages/</guid>
        <description>The roots of rock as a genre are buried deep in the other sounds of the 50s: blues, jazz, R&amp;amp;B and country, amalgamated together to form its own unique genre, known as rock and roll. This began in the deep south of the states, where the first electric guitars began to make a heavy impact on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Used to Be Lonely’ is keeping me company</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-used-to-be-lonely-is-keeping-me-company/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-used-to-be-lonely-is-keeping-me-company/</guid>
        <description>This summer Whitney released their second album – Forever Turned Around. A beautifully intimate project focusing on change in personal relationships. It’s definitely an album for the summer, but I believe Forever Turned Around is just as great at warming the spirit in the cold winter months. It’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Lowdown on BBC Introducing LIVE</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-lowdown-BBC-introducing_LIVE/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-lowdown-BBC-introducing_LIVE/</guid>
        <description>For twelve years BBC Introducing has been helping upcoming artists break into the industry. Every year the BBC holds an event (BBC Introducing LIVE), a relative candy shop for musicians to get insider information from the insiders themselves. Alumni of the service include Little Simz, Ed Sheeran, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pony: Sterilisation of Bedroom Pop or an Intentional Shift in Creative Direction?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-pony-sterilisation-bedroom-pop-intentional-shift-creative-direction/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-pony-sterilisation-bedroom-pop-intentional-shift-creative-direction/</guid>
        <description>3 stars
There are lots of bedroom pop artists breaking into the mainstream these days (Clairo, Gus Dapperton, Boy Pablo, Omar Apollo, etc.), but the undisputed king is Rex Orange County. After featuring on Tyler, the Creator’s Flower Boy, Rex leapt from 500 followers on SoundCloud to being one of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Loyle Carner Starter Pack: A &#39;How To&#39; Guide</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-loyle-carner-starter-pack-how-to-guide/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-loyle-carner-starter-pack-how-to-guide/</guid>
        <description>I should start by saying that I do enjoy Loyle Carner’s music. It’s just that since the release of Not Waving, But Drowning his musical formula has become annoyingly apparent. The guy has talent and lots of people get something from his music, but he ain’t immune to criticism. Now that I’ve …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fresh tracks!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-fresh-tracks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-fresh-tracks/</guid>
        <description>Lapalux laid the foundation of his discography on glitchy, rough, and voided ambient sounds. While not considered “experimental”, his style certainly didn’t draw in the more mainstream crowds. However, his most recent release demonstrates a calmer and more collected direction. This track is supposed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Introducing GioLeo: Imperial’s New Rap Duo</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-introducing-gioleo-imperials-new-rap-duo/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-introducing-gioleo-imperials-new-rap-duo/</guid>
        <description>Rapper and producer aren’t ever words that I associate with MechEng, and yet this last Saturday I sat down with Gio: MechEng student and lead vocalist of trap duo GioLeo. Along with fellow engineer Leo, the pair have been producing music together since the end of last year. Beginning this July under …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Justice has been served, and it sounds amazing</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-justice-has-been-served-and-it-sounds-amazing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-justice-has-been-served-and-it-sounds-amazing/</guid>
        <description>So, I sit down in the Woodward study room ready to sink my teeth into some epidemiology, cut to three hours later and I finally start working. This wasn’t your average YouTube/Facebook/ “really need to reply to these week-old emails” kind of procrastination - this was JUSTICE!
You all know Justice, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kicking Up a Fuss Over Them/Us</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-kicking-up-a-fuss-over-them-us/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-kicking-up-a-fuss-over-them-us/</guid>
        <description>As the curtain rises and faces stare with anticipation, for the last time until you exit stage, you feel your heart beat through your chest. Countless hours have gone into training, learning, creating, perfecting, and bonding with others on stage. I am, of course, referring to how I felt back when I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The music you didn’t even know you needed</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-the-music-you-didn-t-even-know-you-needed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-the-music-you-didn-t-even-know-you-needed/</guid>
        <description>I’m mad, I’m riled up and it’s all you guys’ fault. Why am I angry? I’ll tell you. The Friday before last I was ecstatic because I was going to Fat Freddy’s Drop at O2 Brixton. Talking to people from IC on the day and explaining what glory I was soon to witness I realised not a single goddamn person …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An album to cure your autumnal anguish</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-an-album-to-cure-your-autumnal-anguish/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-an-album-to-cure-your-autumnal-anguish/</guid>
        <description>The nights are colder, the days are shorter, and there isn’t much new music being released. Guess what I’m most upset about. As the icy winter chill grows, my mind has gone back to one of my favourite albums of the summer just gone, Slide by George Clanton. Clanton’s been creating for years but …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Masters of the Melancholic Movie Music</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-masters-of-the-melancholic-movie-music/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-masters-of-the-melancholic-movie-music/</guid>
        <description>A month ago, in the throes of feeling ill and in the dumps, I turned not to Netflix but my old DVD collection. After wiping away the dust and sifting through the selection, I found, tightly tucked at the back of the drawer, a bunch of DVDs all created by the most celebrated Japanese animation …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>REDUXER: Turning Water Into Wine</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-reduxer-turning-water-into-wine/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-reduxer-turning-water-into-wine/</guid>
        <description>Last June, the Leeds based indie rock band alt-J released their 3rd studio album, RELAXER. And it wasn’t good. Don’t get me wrong, I love alt-J just as much as the next guy; ‘Left Hand Free’ will forever get my feet tapping and my air drums rocking. But RELAXER was like looking in a fun-house mirror …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
