<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Liberation on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/liberation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Liberation on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/liberation/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Liberation and Community at Imperial is an Issue for Today</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-liberation-community-imperial-issue-today/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shervin Sabeghi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-liberation-community-imperial-issue-today/</guid>
        <description>Above: Only men were allowed to drink in the Union Bar fifty years ago
The rights and freedoms for minority groups around the world are never handed on a platter – they are hard fought through liberation movements. From international women’s suffrage in the late 19th century, the American Civil …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>World AIDS Day</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-world-aids-day/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freya Hepworth-Lloyd,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-world-aids-day/</guid>
        <description>It is estimated that over 100,000 people in the UK are living with HIV. An estimated 7,500 of those are undiagnosed. The life expectancy for people diagnosed early (15-59) is the same as the general population. However nearly half of HIV diagnoses are late.
HIV is transmitted through particular body …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Breaking the Taboo on Eating Disorders</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-breaking-the-taboo-on-eating-disorders/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emma Couves,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-breaking-the-taboo-on-eating-disorders/</guid>
        <description>Four years ago this week, I remember completing my UCAS form and putting Imperial as my first-choice university. At the time, I was oblivious really to my falling mental and physical health. My eating disorder started long before Imperial but it wasn’t until I got here, away from my family and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ramadan Reflections</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-ramadan-reflections/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ambreen Muhammed,Hind M Arekat,Khadijah Mahmoud,Aminah Ali,Sharmin Akbar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-ramadan-reflections/</guid>
        <description>Below are some personal reflections submitted on Ramadan, the holy month in which Muslims fast from dawn to sunset in order to gain consciousness of God in all their actions. We hope this article can show that, whilst Ramadan is a prescribed month, we all experience it in our own personal ways! …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Here’s what I’m up to at the moment!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-here-s-what-i-m-up-to-at-the-moment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laura Chen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-here-s-what-i-m-up-to-at-the-moment/</guid>
        <description>Hey guys! I am Laura Chen, the 18-19 International Officer. My role is to represent the international student body and to advocate for cultural diversity at Imperial College.
Imperial is a truly global community with 64% of its students being non-UK students and from all over the world. To engage …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>SCI{L}ENCE</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-sci-l-ence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-sci-l-ence/</guid>
        <description>Sci{l}ence is a weekly podcast for women in STEM. It gives women a platform to talk about what it is really like working in typically male-dominated fields. All the guests are highly accomplished and inspiring women in STEM, deliberately kept anonymous with disguised voices. This allows them to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Use Your Voice”</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08--use-your-voice/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tasneem Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08--use-your-voice/</guid>
        <description>It is a well-known truth that life at university can be extremely stressful and can consequently have a negative impact on our mental health. It has been shown that most mental health problems develop by the age of 24 , and in 2015-16 alone, 15,000 first-year students at UK universities reported …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An update from our LGBT&#43; Officer!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-an-update-from-our-lgbt-officer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jehna Devraj,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-an-update-from-our-lgbt-officer/</guid>
        <description>Imperial has three main avenues of LGBT+ representation: IQ: Imperial College LGBT+ Society, Imperial 600 (Imperial’s LGBT+ staff network) and the Union Liberation &amp;amp; Community LGBT+ Officer. Having a society, a staff network and an officer can be both a strength and a hindrance; it is always …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LGBT&#43; History Month</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-lgbt-history-month/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christopher Carter,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-lgbt-history-month/</guid>
        <description>As LGBT+ History Month draws to a close, IQ (Imperial College LGBT+ Society) is looking back on a successful month of inclusive and inspiring events. From film nights and quizzes, to bar nights and art exhibits, we’ve spent this month bringing Imperial’s LGBT+ community together to celebrate the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>National Student Pride 2019: More Pride, Less Prejudice </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-national-student-pride-2019-more-pride-less-prejudice/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-national-student-pride-2019-more-pride-less-prejudice/</guid>
        <description>As LGBT History Month draws to a close, National Student Pride (NSP), the UK’s largest LGBT+ careers fair, holds its annual conference at the University of Westminster.
NSP brings a vibrant mix of graduate careers fairs, conferences, debates, cinema screenings, parties, exhibitions, and workshops to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brexit and Disability?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-brexit-and-disability/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Hishi Aty,Sam Haselgrove,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-brexit-and-disability/</guid>
        <description>As you are probably aware, ever since the invocation of Article 50 on 29th March 2017, the entire country has been on-edge. Whether you are a ‘brexiteer’ or a ‘remainer’, everyone’s fear of the unknown and split opinions have made the process of leaving ever more… complicated, to say the least.
How …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Have you ever experienced discrimination?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-have-you-ever-experienced-discrimination/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-have-you-ever-experienced-discrimination/</guid>
        <description>Have you ever felt unintentionally, casually or subtly discriminated against within the college environment? What happened? How did it make you feel? How did it affect you in the long run? Felix is trying to start a conversation to better understand the impact this has on people by compiling some …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Meet the Disabilities Officer!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-meet-the-disabilities-officer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sam Haselgrove,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-meet-the-disabilities-officer/</guid>
        <description>Hey guys! My name is Sam, and I am the Disabilities Officer for the Student Union here at Imperial. My role is to represent the interests of and improve the university experience for the disabled community. There are a few ways of defining a disability; the way that I define it is through the social …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On creating a legacy</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-on-creating-a-legacy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Qiu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-on-creating-a-legacy/</guid>
        <description>Mathematical curves rise and fall, changing their assumed trajectory at a moment’s notice at inflection points. In life, too, there are certain times the prevailing greater wisdom considers to be inflection points –often-pivotal moments that mark so-called milestones. Examples include graduation and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On positive change</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-on-positive-change/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Qiu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-on-positive-change/</guid>
        <description>It has been an enormous privilege to be your Campaigns Officer this year. To see the dynamism and enthusiasm that transcends our university campuses when various campaigns jump into action has been not only educational, but most enjoyable.
This year I spearheaded a campaign of my own, called …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ramadan: What is it? What does it mean? And how do you balance it with exams?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-ramadan-what-is-it-what-does-it-mean-and-how-do-you-balance-it-with-exams/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adil Ali,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-ramadan-what-is-it-what-does-it-mean-and-how-do-you-balance-it-with-exams/</guid>
        <description>For most people on campus, last Thursday was largely unremarkable – aside from the weather deciding to behave itself.
But for some students, and for 1.8 billion Muslims worldwide, Thursday 17th May marked the start of the month of Ramadan. For the uninitiated, Ramadan is one of the biggest events in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s time to take five: Under Pressure is here!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-it-s-time-to-take-five-under-pressure-is-here/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ariana Sadr-Hashemi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-it-s-time-to-take-five-under-pressure-is-here/</guid>
        <description>Coming up on March 1st is University Mental Health Day; dedicated to promoting awareness for student wellbeing across the country. Without a doubt, studying at Imperial is incredibly stressful, which can take a serious toll on a student’s wellbeing; there are a lot of deadlines, revision, and exams …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Run for a liberation position!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-run-for-a-liberation-position/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ariana Sadr-Hashemi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-run-for-a-liberation-position/</guid>
        <description>This year, liberation has really taken off as a priority for Imperial College Union. Campus has seen awareness-raising events and celebrations including Black History Month, Disability History Month, Interfaith week, and the ongoing LGBT History Month (as shown by the currently-rainbow-hued Queen’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Here’s what I’m up to at the moment!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-here-s-what-i-m-up-to-at-the-moment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alessio Incitti,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-here-s-what-i-m-up-to-at-the-moment/</guid>
        <description>As part of LGBT History Month, IQ (Imperial College LGBT+) and I are running a series of events throughout February.
This weekend you can join IQ at the National Student Pride, one of the biggest student events of the year, featuring Courtney Act.
If you would like to learn more about LGBT history, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LGBT History Month: Why is it important?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-lgbt-history-month-why-is-it-important/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alessio Incitti,Sophie Quinn,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-lgbt-history-month-why-is-it-important/</guid>
        <description>If you’ve wondered why the Queen’s Tower is lit up in rainbow colours, it’s because Imperial is currently celebrating LGBT (Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, Transgender) History Month – an annual observance of the history and experiences of LGBT people that aims to promote acceptance and raise awareness of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Here’s what I’m up to at the moment!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-here-s-what-i-m-up-to-at-the-moment/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ariana Sadr-Hashemi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-here-s-what-i-m-up-to-at-the-moment/</guid>
        <description>From Felix articles to Under Pressure week, my term so far has been full to the brim with mental health talks and discussions. I’m well aware that, as this is the first year my position has existed, most of the things I start are too big for me to be able to finish. That said, I’ve managed to get …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Making sure to look after your friends</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-making-sure-to-look-after-your-friends/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ariana Sadr-Hashemi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-making-sure-to-look-after-your-friends/</guid>
        <description>The Under Pressure campaign this week has highlighted the stress associated with studying and various ways to deal with it. However, many students at Imperial struggle with their mental health in silence due to the pervasive attitude that having difficulties with mental health is a weakness. This is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Here’s what I’m up to at the moment!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-here-s-what-i-m-up-to-at-the-moment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhidian Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-here-s-what-i-m-up-to-at-the-moment/</guid>
        <description>As Ethics and Environment Officer, my job is to support and facilitate campaigns to make our university fairer, greener, and more sustainable. Below are some things I’ve been up to so far this term; if you think that there’s something I’ve missed, or that I could help you with, email me at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s time for us to make a stand on climate change</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-it-s-time-for-us-to-make-a-stand-on-climate-change/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhidian Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-it-s-time-for-us-to-make-a-stand-on-climate-change/</guid>
        <description>Unless you’ve been living under a rock, you’ve likely found it impossible to avoid Blue Planet II. Nowhere else is the beauty of the natural world as apparent as in our oceans, and the theatrics 1000 feet below the surface often uncannily mirror the dramas of our own day-to-day lives. We pick sides, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Here’s what I’m up to at the moment!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-here-s-what-i-m-up-to-at-the-moment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alessio Incitti,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-here-s-what-i-m-up-to-at-the-moment/</guid>
        <description>My number one priority for this year is to ensure Imperial becomes a more safe, welcoming, and inclusive space for transgender &amp;amp; gender-variant students. In the last few months I’ve been working to secure lasting advances for the Imperial trans community. Action I’m taking includes:
 Bringing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Here’s what cis people can do to protect trans folks</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-here-s-what-cis-people-can-do-to-protect-trans-folks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alessio Incitti,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-here-s-what-cis-people-can-do-to-protect-trans-folks/</guid>
        <description>20th November marked Transgender Day of Remembrance, an annual memorialisation of those who lost their lives as a result of transphobic violence in the last year. A vigil was held in London, among many other cities, where the trans community and their allies paused to remember Paola, who was stabbed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Inclusivity, disability, employment – to disclose or not disclose?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-inclusivity-disability-employment-to-disclose-or-not-disclose/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Hisham Abdel-Aty,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-inclusivity-disability-employment-to-disclose-or-not-disclose/</guid>
        <description>As someone with a disability myself, I always thought that it would be reasonable to presume that companies would be less likely to hire someone t­hat would ‘cost’ them more in terms of time and/or money for reasonable adjustments. Since it’s internship applications season I thought I would write …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The importance of raising disability awareness</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-the-importance-of-raising-disability-awareness/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-the-importance-of-raising-disability-awareness/</guid>
        <description>Before stepping up for this role earlier this year, I tried to look for the Disabilities Officer at the time to ask for some advice. I discovered, after three days of searching, that no one ran in the elections, so the position was not filled. Even though this position seems niche in the Imperial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Campaigning for a better Imperial</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-28-campaigning-for-a-better-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Qiu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-28-campaigning-for-a-better-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Earlier this year when I ran to become your Campaigns Officer, I spoke about the ways in which previous campaigns have changed the very fabric of the Imperial that we know and love. I referenced the way in which we lobbied for quality affordable accommodation for all our students, and for free …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Here’s what I’m up to at the moment!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-here-s-what-i-m-up-to-at-the-moment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chimdi E Igwe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-here-s-what-i-m-up-to-at-the-moment/</guid>
        <description>It’s rather tricky to run for a position that isn’t well defined – earlier this year, while campaigning for the role of BME Officer, more often than not I’d have to explain what the whole acronym meant (for those of you who still don’t know, that’s Black and Minority Ethnic); even then I’d have to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Working to create a truly global university</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-working-to-create-a-truly-global-university/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chimdi E Igwe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-working-to-create-a-truly-global-university/</guid>
        <description>Just last week, the government released its sixty-odd page Race Disparity Report, commissioned by the Prime Minister Theresa May early on in her tenure. The main takeaway, as the report’s name handily notes, was the general trend of disparity between minority experiences across the board: from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Campaigning for a better Imperial</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-24-campaigning-for-a-better-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Qiu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-24-campaigning-for-a-better-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Earlier this year when I ran to become your Campaigns Officer, I spoke about the ways in which previous campaigns have changed the very fabric of the Imperial that we know and love. I referenced the way in which we lobbied for quality affordable accommodation for all our students, and for free …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The importance of quality sleep</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-24-the-importance-of-quality-sleep/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Qiu,Patrick Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-24-the-importance-of-quality-sleep/</guid>
        <description>In today’s elite academic institutions and high-performing workplaces, sleep is often downgraded to a status of secondary importance. The thrill of instant gratification takes precedence over the dull and laborious wait that inevitably precedes the onset of sleep. When time is limited, our attention …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A call to arms! Why we need to change our mental health provision </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-a-call-to-arms-why-we-need-to-change-our-mental-health-provision/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ariana Sadr-Hashemi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-a-call-to-arms-why-we-need-to-change-our-mental-health-provision/</guid>
        <description>It’s a well-known fact that the majority of students at Imperial will experience some mental health difficulties during their studies. Typically, the first place they are sent is to the Imperial Counselling Service. However, to send students there by default operates under the assumption that the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Here’s what I’m up to at the moment!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-here-s-what-i-m-up-to-at-the-moment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ariana Sadr-Hashemi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-here-s-what-i-m-up-to-at-the-moment/</guid>
        <description>Stepping into the newly-created role of Mental Health Liberation Officer, I was acutely aware of the scale of the challenges faced. In the Mentality Survey, which was run two years ago, 70% of student at Imperial reported mental stresses or a mental health problem. It’s so important that we hit the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial survival guide</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-imperial-survival-guide/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Ariana Sadr-Hashemi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-imperial-survival-guide/</guid>
        <description>Coming to university can be a difficult and stressful time. There are loads of new things to try, club mailing lists to sign up to, and people to ask “Which Oxbridge college rejected you?” But along the way, it’s important to make sure that you’re taking good care of youself, not only physically, …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
