<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/xiuchen_xu/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/xiuchen_xu/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Tragedy of the Commons: A Drama That Our Planet Is Not Enjoying</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-tragedy-commons-drama-planet-not-enjoying/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xiuchen Xu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-tragedy-commons-drama-planet-not-enjoying/</guid>
        <description>You may have heard of the term tragedy of the commons before, or you may have even studied about it. It is an important economic concept and is extremely relevant to many of the prevailing environmental issues. The problem stems from deep within human nature and is at the heart of corruption and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>General Election 2019: What are the environmental policies and promises of the parties?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-general-election-2019-what-are-environmental-policies-promises-of-parties/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xiuchen Xu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-general-election-2019-what-are-environmental-policies-promises-of-parties/</guid>
        <description>There is a short &amp;lsquo;glossary&amp;rsquo; near the end of the article to explain certain bits of jargon!
The public concern towards environmental issues are at a peak, and this is reflected in the manifestos of political parties, which have a heavier focus on environmental policies than those of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Researchers Show Noise Pollution is Threatening the Survival of a Number of Species</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-researchers-show-noise-pollution-threatening-survival-species/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xiuchen Xu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-researchers-show-noise-pollution-threatening-survival-species/</guid>
        <description>New research from Queen’s University Belfast has indicated that noise pollution is threatening to over 100 different species.
The researchers found that noise affects the behaviour of a wide range of species including amphibians, birds, fish, mammals and reptilians. Noise pollution can affect …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Have a Halloween that isn’t Spooky for the Environment</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-have-halloween-not-spooky-for-environment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xiuchen Xu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-have-halloween-not-spooky-for-environment/</guid>
        <description>It’s the time of the year for trick or treating! However, being festive does not mean we should pollute and bring damage to our beloved planet.. Halloween activities can be incredibly wasteful, so here is a look at three ways we can make Halloween more sustainable.
Costumes
Halloween is the peak …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Giselle: A Bold Reimagination of a Classic Ballet</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-giselle-bold-reimagination-classic-ballet/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xiuchen Xu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-giselle-bold-reimagination-classic-ballet/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
Dada Masilo is famous for her works which rework the plots of well-known classical ballet pieces. Her previous works include her interpretation of Swan Lake which included twists such as a homosexual Siegfried, and social commentary on sexism and homophobia. Her vision for Giselle is equally …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Aftermath of the Extinction Rebellion Ban in London by the Police</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-aftermath-extinction-rebellion-ban-london-by-police/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xiuchen Xu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-aftermath-extinction-rebellion-ban-london-by-police/</guid>
        <description>As of Monday 14th October, the Scotland Yard has announced that all Extinction Rebellion (XR) protests must cease. The Met’s has banned all protests linked to the XR ‘Autumn Uprising’ under Section 14 of the Public Order Act. Since then, the police have cleared infrastructure from protest sites such …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FRIENDs for life</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-friends-for-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xiuchen Xu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-friends-for-life/</guid>
        <description>UUpon arrival to FRIEND animal sanctuary, we were greeted by the loud clucks of chickens and the turning heads of cows. We made our way through the muddy terrain to an open field, where we were welcomed by Dave, who was a full-time volunteer at the sanctuary. Behind him followed Ging whose puppy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Season of change</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-season-of-change/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xiuchen Xu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-season-of-change/</guid>
        <description>The Plant-Based Imperial campaign combines initiatives from Greening Imperial, Environmental Society (ESoc), VegSoc and Animal Protection &amp;amp; Education Society (APES). The main aim of the campaign is to reduce the carbon footprint of the college and work towards a more sustainable college. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pioneering treatments for healing chronic wounds</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-05-pioneering-treatments-for-healing-chronic-wounds/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xiuchen Xu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-05-pioneering-treatments-for-healing-chronic-wounds/</guid>
        <description>Chronic wounds differ from normal acute wounds, because they do not go through the normal healing process of inflammation, proliferation, and remodelling; instead they stop at the inflammation stage, and the healing process is stopped completely. Chronic wounds often require amputations, and may …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gene Drives – A technology capable of changing entire species</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-gene-drives-a-technology-capable-of-changing-entire-species/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xiuchen Xu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-gene-drives-a-technology-capable-of-changing-entire-species/</guid>
        <description>Gene drive technology allows humans to introduce genetical modifications to species that are always passed on to the next generation, which allows a characteristic to become prevalent in a species over very few generations. The technology is powerful enough to wipe out whole species, and has …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
