<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/farhat_eamon/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/farhat_eamon/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix 2019 General Election Poll: Results</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-felix-general-election-poll-results-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-felix-general-election-poll-results-2019/</guid>
        <description></description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pop Hits Take the West End: &amp; Juliet</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-pop-hits-take-west-end-juliet/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-pop-hits-take-west-end-juliet/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
Romeo and Juliet, is probably one of history’s most famous love stories which (spoiler alert) tragically ends in death. This modern retelling considers what could have happened if Juliet (Miriam-Teak Lee) was given a life beyond Romeo. She travels to Paris with an entourage consisting of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sun, Sex and Suspicous Parents: 1920s Edition</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-sun-sex-suspicious-parents-1920s-edition/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-sun-sex-suspicious-parents-1920s-edition/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
In a few weeks’ time we will be in a new decade, the 2020s. If it’s anything like the 1920s, it should be a blast! The Boy Friend gives a little glimpse into what life back then was like.. for young, pretty socialites at a finishing school on the French Riviera that is!
If you fit this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Will the UK be Voting On?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-what-will-uk-be-voting-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-what-will-uk-be-voting-on/</guid>
        <description>On December 12th, the British people will vote, but who and what are they voting for? Are they voting for thorough policies outlined in a manifesto or headline ideas performed on TV? Is it about the local candidate in their constituency or the celebrity like figure who leads that party?
This week, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Political Pacts are Cheating the Electorate</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-political-pacts-cheating-electorate/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-political-pacts-cheating-electorate/</guid>
        <description>Since the election was announced a little over two weeks ago, there have been some big movements in the area of political pacts. With the Remain Alliance instigated between the Lib Dems, Greens and Plaid Cymru and the Brexit party making its own unilateral alliance, some voters find themselves …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A fairytale on Old Compton Street - Soho Cinders</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-a-fairytale-on-old-compton-street-soho-cinders/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-a-fairytale-on-old-compton-street-soho-cinders/</guid>
        <description>After an initial run back in 2012, Soho Cinders is back off the west end at the Charing Cross Theatre, and its unique narrative and warm characters are more relevant than ever. Set on the iconic Old Compton Street in the beating heart of the West End, this modern Cinderella sees young Robbie (Luke …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fringe Parties: What are they good for?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-fringe-parties-what-are-they-good-for/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-fringe-parties-what-are-they-good-for/</guid>
        <description>The trigger has been pulled on what every political pundit is calling the most important general election of our generation. A choice between chaos with Johnson or a strong and stable Corbyn, or maybe it was the other way round? For many it is a choice between Brexit, championed by Boris Johnson, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Meet the Editors: Eamon - the cool one</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-meet-the-editors-eamon-the-cool-one/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-meet-the-editors-eamon-the-cool-one/</guid>
        <description>So you’ve come to London, rents are high, a pint costs £500 and you basically can’t step out of the house without breaking the bank. But it’s all worth it right? London is a city of endless possibilities with a very vibrant arts and theatre scene&amp;hellip; But where to start?
That’s where I come in. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brexit: the end of internationalism</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-brexit-the-end-of-internationalism/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-brexit-the-end-of-internationalism/</guid>
        <description>I consider myself many things: a global citizen, a European citizen and a British citizen, in no particular order. Their ideals have always complimented each other but for the first time, they have started to clash. The onset of Brexit, as we rapidly approach the 29th of March, has thrown my whole …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why Everybody’s Talking about Jamie and Aladdin, and other West End shows</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-why-everybody-s-talking-about-jamie-and-aladdin-and-other-west-end-shows/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-why-everybody-s-talking-about-jamie-and-aladdin-and-other-west-end-shows/</guid>
        <description>When it comes to theatre, London is an international capital of excellence. Some would argue it offers the best of the best when it comes to high quality cultural performances. While many have fallen under the spell of the big musicals and gripping plays, always yearning for their next chance to get …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lord of the Game of the Ring of Thrones</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-lord-of-the-game-of-the-ring-of-thrones/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-lord-of-the-game-of-the-ring-of-thrones/</guid>
        <description>London has many museums, the V&amp;amp;A, Science Museum, Natural History Museum and even some outside of South Kensington! One of these is the Museum of Comedy, located in Bloomsbury. On the last Sunday of every month for the foreseeable future, the small venue inside is seized by the “Hivemind” improv …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fuwa Fuwa: an exact soufflé science</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-fuwa-fuwa-an-exact-souffl-science/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-fuwa-fuwa-an-exact-souffl-science/</guid>
        <description>If you like delicious flavours and something different to fill your belly (and your Instagram feed) take a trip to the UK’s only soufflé pancake café!
Having first tasted these fluffy pieces of heaven in Hoshino Coffee, a chain with over 150 outlets across Japan, I was immediately hooked! London I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ORPHEUS - A silent musical extravaganza</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-14-orpheus-a-silent-musical-extravaganza/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-14-orpheus-a-silent-musical-extravaganza/</guid>
        <description>First performed at the Battersea Arts Centre in 2013 by Little Bulb Theatre company, Orpheus returns to the venue that inspired the original performance for a short run five years on. The venue itself has recently reopened, a phoenix from the ashes, after a devastating fire in 2015. The full …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London and Life Lessons</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-london-and-life-lessons/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-london-and-life-lessons/</guid>
        <description>Anyone who has grown up in a small town or community surrounded by the same people can relate to the feeling of social claustrophobia. During adolescence, when emotions are high and everyone wants to fit in, this becomes even more pronounced. In “Cuckoo”, written by Lisa Carroll and set in Ireland, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Cat in the Hat Strikes Back!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-the-cat-in-the-hat-strikes-back/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-the-cat-in-the-hat-strikes-back/</guid>
        <description>When books are made into movies, fans and critics flock like vultures to tease apart the catastrophe to come. When the holy works of Dr Seuss were converted into a musical by Monty Python’s Eric Idle, similar scenes could be predicted. The story tries to integrate characters from across the Seuss …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The grief of Brexit is nearly over</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-the-grief-of-brexit-is-nearly-over/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-the-grief-of-brexit-is-nearly-over/</guid>
        <description>There are five stages of grief: denial, anger, bargaining, depression and acceptance. We as a country have finally gotten near the end of our Brexit grief. First there was the denial that we as a country would ever vote for such a preposterous idea. Then there was anger as it became apparent our …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pain and Polyamory</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-pain-and-polyamory/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-pain-and-polyamory/</guid>
        <description>Pride and Prejudice, Sense and Sensibility, Emma; these classic Jane Austen novels are probably very familiar to the well-read student body at Imperial. However, the Austentatious theatre company brings some of her long lost (never written) works to the stage using the art of improv.
At the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A night at the opera – It’s all Chinese to me!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-a-night-at-the-opera-it-s-all-chinese-to-me/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-a-night-at-the-opera-it-s-all-chinese-to-me/</guid>
        <description>While most would consider opera a strictly European affair, the China National Peking Opera Company would disagree. Founded in 1955, this company is one of the state-funded national institutions for performing arts. Peking opera is a Chinese form of performing arts, developed from multiple regional …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>White is the new red when it comes to poppies!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-white-is-the-new-red-when-it-comes-to-poppies/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-white-is-the-new-red-when-it-comes-to-poppies/</guid>
        <description>This year marks 100 years since the Armistice that ended the horrors of World War I. The war was big and affected many, and shortly after, people began using red poppies as symbols of remembrance. It was a way of honouring the men lost as well as reinforcing the idea that war could never happen …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Should the Monarchy be Abolished?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-should-the-monarchy-be-abolished/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-should-the-monarchy-be-abolished/</guid>
        <description>What do Ellie Goulding, Ricky Martin and the Queen have in common? Other than the fact that they all used to be much more relevant 3 years, 20 years and 800 years ago respectively, they also all took part in the royal wedding celebrations over the weekend. Very much overshadowed by the spectacle of …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
