<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ejt11/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ejt11/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Tea &amp; Coffee Truths
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-tea-coffee-truths/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 03:23:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-tea-coffee-truths/</guid>
        <description>One day I may look back on my life and realise that my first love was not a person but a place&amp;hellip;
Our world is full, bursting and strained like never before. We have the power to suppress disease, pacify hunger, come and go as we so choose. Things have grown, unfurled like ivy tendrils that are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Immoralist
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-14-the-immoralist/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 03:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-14-the-immoralist/</guid>
        <description>Despite being published in 1902 I find that this novel reads as though it were fifty years ahead of its time. The tone of Gide’s writing is sparse, conservative and yet at times overwhelmingly beautiful. For a writer with an aversion to the novel in his formative years, Gide has blended meter, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>French Energy Giant to Invest in UK Fracking
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-french-energy-giant-to-invest-in-uk-fracking/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 17:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-french-energy-giant-to-invest-in-uk-fracking/</guid>
        <description>French resource company (and energy giant) Total is set to invest up to £13 million in the immediate future in the fledgling UK Shale Gas (fracking) industry.
A forty per cent stake of two exploration licenses in Lincolnshire will be turned over to the multinational owned by IGas Energy. It is the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Reappraisal of the British State
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-the-reappraisal-of-the-british-state/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 09:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-the-reappraisal-of-the-british-state/</guid>
        <description>On January 20th European tensions, sparked by Prime Minister Cameron’s utilisation of migration as a political chess piece, came to a head. The tone of UK-Europe relations were reflected in the words of German Foreign Minister (and Social Democrat), Walter Steinmeier.
“Many young people from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Zelda: a link to my past
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-13-zelda-a-link-to-my-past/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 12:36:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-13-zelda-a-link-to-my-past/</guid>
        <description>I remember the turbulent release period of Pokemon Gold &amp;amp; Silver back in 2001. As a gallant eight year old boy I had anticipated its arrival in April. Unfortunately the date of release coincided with the outbreak of ‘Foot-&amp;amp;-Mouth’ disease. As an Irishman, ensnared by water on all sides, the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ramblings on Personal Legend
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-ramblings-on-personal-legend/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 04:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-ramblings-on-personal-legend/</guid>
        <description>Paul Coelho’s best-selling novel, The Alchemist, reminds us to be true to ourselves and to seek out our ‘personal legend’. A king advises Santiago, the chief protagonist, that, “when you really want something to happen, the whole universe conspires so that your wish comes true.”.] This in itself is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Raw Words: Part Two
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-raw-words-part-two/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 22:11:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-raw-words-part-two/</guid>
        <description>The years continued to roll on, expanding until my childhood reverie waned. Ireland continued to be a panacea of opportunity. By 2008 Dad had replaced the BMW with a Range Rover. It consumed the driveway with its girth.
I remember being gathered around the television. The Madines were having a quiet …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Raw Words: Part One
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-raw-words-part-one/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 16:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-raw-words-part-one/</guid>
        <description>“As you go through life Shane, remember one thing. There’s a price to pay for everything.” The words of Aodhán Madine, my father, once spoken flippantly, now touch a raw nerve. Time has passed and they’re like daggers, sharpened by the whetstone of the crash.
We were happy back then. Through the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Role &amp; Responsibility of Comment
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-the-role-responsibility-of-comment/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 16:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-the-role-responsibility-of-comment/</guid>
        <description>Comment sections across a broad variety of newspapers all share a common thread. The bulk of their published material will prove emotive for a sizeable portion of its readership. Individuals may empathise with views expressed in a given article. Others may be offended. On occasion a given issue may …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fracking Versus Science Communication
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-fracking-versus-science-communication/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 03:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-fracking-versus-science-communication/</guid>
        <description>The word ‘fracking’ has become aligned with unconditional taboo in the United Kingdom in a two year interval. Strong public scepticism has been fuelled by the parade of paraphernalia arriving from the USA. Images ranging from flaming taps right through to ominous ‘frack pads’ litter the internet. In …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Boris: Resolute Vertebrate Jelly Part II
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-boris-resolute-vertebrate-jelly-part-ii/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 10:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-boris-resolute-vertebrate-jelly-part-ii/</guid>
        <description>“If the ball came loose from the back of the scrum, which it won’t of course, it would be a great, great thing to have a crack at.”
These were the words of Boris Johnson on a hypothetical bid for The Conservative Party leadership, speaking to the BBC’s Michael Cockerell for a May 2013 broadcast. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Boris: Resolute Vertebrate Jelly Part I
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-boris-resolute-vertebrate-jelly-part-i/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 00:02:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-boris-resolute-vertebrate-jelly-part-i/</guid>
        <description>The mayor for London, Boris Johnson, made the headlines in February of this year after deeming members of the London Assembly as “great supine protoplasmic invertebrate jellies” for failing to interrogate him over revisions to the £16.5 bn budget. The characteristic neologism merely capped his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nintendo’s Ethical Legacy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-18-nintendos-ethical-legacy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 21:26:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-18-nintendos-ethical-legacy/</guid>
        <description>Computing power is evolving at a relentless pace. The gaming industry moves in tandem with this tempo. Unfortunately (and for some, regrettably) its viability has waned in recent years having come under pressure from a burgeoning smartphone market and a reversion to the PC as the preferred platform …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Head to Head: Eoghan Totten on The Platonic Merits of a Religious Education
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-11-head-to-head-eoghan-totten-on-the-platonic-merits-of-a-religious-education/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 23:40:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-11-head-to-head-eoghan-totten-on-the-platonic-merits-of-a-religious-education/</guid>
        <description>Immanuel Kant, perennial philosopher of the 18th century, once made two key distinctions. Firstly, objects act in accordance with fixed rules. The latter distinction clarified that rational agents (you and I) formulate actions with flippant regard to mere conceptions of those rules. One would …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ed Miliband: Ethics Over Dogma?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-ed-miliband-ethics-over-dogma/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 00:46:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-ed-miliband-ethics-over-dogma/</guid>
        <description>This article was catalysed by the recent conference of The Conservative Party held in Manchester, where voluminous Government policy was proposed and discussed. The ‘Work for Benefits’ plan proved to be a topic of discussion as Chancellor, George Osborne, revised the criteria for Jobseeker’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘The Imperial Thing’: Why Comment Matters
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-the-imperial-thing-why-comment-matters/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 14:02:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-the-imperial-thing-why-comment-matters/</guid>
        <description>There are people out there that are highly critical of the ethos of Imperial College and its approach to academic pursuits. Some individuals from outside the institution find it ‘lacking’ in certain qualities. They often attempt to draw parallels between ourselves and the University of Oxford or the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Honour Before Pragmatism: What Lessons Can We Learn from The Fukushima Nuclear Debacle?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-5-honour-before-pragmatism-what-lessons-can-we-learn-from-the-fukushima-nuclear-debacle/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2013 18:40:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-5-honour-before-pragmatism-what-lessons-can-we-learn-from-the-fukushima-nuclear-debacle/</guid>
        <description>When I began to put this article together the recorded radiation levels around the storage tanks of the Fukushima Nuclear Plant stood at 1,800 millisieverts. By Tuesday a ground reading of 2,200 mSv, a 22% rise, was duly noted.
The Problem The plant incurred damage in the wake of the 2011 Japanese …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How can academic institutions prevent future scientific farce and outrage?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-8-28-how-can-academic-institutions-prevent-future-scientific-farce-and-outrage/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2013 08:52:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-8-28-how-can-academic-institutions-prevent-future-scientific-farce-and-outrage/</guid>
        <description>On August 20th 2013 Gary Bolton was dealt a seven year prison sentence for the sale of fake bomb detectors. His chief crime was classed as fraud, having pocketed up to £10,000 per unit.
His offence is dwarfed by the excesses of fellow Briton James McCormick, who globally distributed a similar …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College gains crucial ground in the National Student Survey
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-8-17-college-gains-crucial-ground-in-the-national-student-survey/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2013 18:33:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-8-17-college-gains-crucial-ground-in-the-national-student-survey/</guid>
        <description>On the 21st June I stated that students in third level education in the UK &amp;lsquo;feel undervalued, merely ushered through the system&amp;rsquo;. From National Student Survey results released on August 13th it would appear that recent graduates from Imperial College have broken free from this stigma. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2012 University Complaints (England &amp; Wales) in 2012
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-2012-university-complaints-england-wales-in-2012/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 16:30:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-2012-university-complaints-england-wales-in-2012/</guid>
        <description>I kid you not. The title highlights a rise of 25% in complaints lodged to the Office of the Independent Adjudicator from academic institutions in England and Wales.
Numerous academics, journalists and opinionated individuals ally this increase with the inaugural year of the £9,000 fee tariff. One …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial climbs league table
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-6-imperial-climbs-league-table/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 18:47:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-6-imperial-climbs-league-table/</guid>
        <description>A lacklustre performance in the NSS (National Student Survey) left Imperial College London trailing behind the University of Oxford and the University of Cambridge, the other two thirds of the ‘Big Three’ UK-based academic institutions, in the latest league table compiled by the Guardian. A score of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College London students to dominate Engineers Without Borders Finals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-30-imperial-college-london-students-to-dominate-engineers-without-borders-finals/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2013 12:26:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-30-imperial-college-london-students-to-dominate-engineers-without-borders-finals/</guid>
        <description>Three teams of prospective year two students dominated a 2,500 strong national field from thirteen Universities to secure a place in the Engineering Without Borders Challenge Finals taking place at Coventry University next month. The teams, consisting of individuals from multidisciplinary …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Virtuous Meritocracy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-the-virtuous-meritocracy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 23:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-the-virtuous-meritocracy/</guid>
        <description>A recent article in The Economist analysed social mobility (or rather a lack thereof) in the USA, focusing on education. Extensive discourse took place surrounding a modern phenomenon known as ‘virtuous meritocracy’. In basic terms, it has its origins in previous American governmental policy. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Medics in career limbo after marking mixup
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-medics-in-career-limbo-after-marking-mixup/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 01:22:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-medics-in-career-limbo-after-marking-mixup/</guid>
        <description>More than seven thousand final year medics nationwide have been left stunned and unsure of their future following the retraction of allocated Situational Judgement Test (SJT) results. The move, taken by the UK Foundation Programme Office (UKFPO) on 25 February, means that medics must undergo yet …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Royal Institution forced to sell home
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-royal-institution-forced-to-sell-home/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 21:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-royal-institution-forced-to-sell-home/</guid>
        <description>The Royal Institution (RI), one of the chief catalysts for the development of British science, has put its Mayfair residence on the market in an effort to overwrite mounting debts. Sir Richard Sykes, the current Chairman and former Rector of Imperial College London, has had to take swift action to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mud, mud, glorious mud!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-8-mud-mud-glorious-mud/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 00:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,Sophie Kirk,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-8-mud-mud-glorious-mud/</guid>
        <description>1000 runners, miles of mud and one epic after party can only mean one thing, BUCS Cross Country 2013!
This year saw the biggest team ever (44!) from Imperial travel to Leeds for what is the highlight of the Cross Country calendar. Imperial College achieved their strongest team finish in the British …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Looking into the gender balance
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-looking-into-the-gender-balance/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 22:43:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Proctor,Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-looking-into-the-gender-balance/</guid>
        <description> Male undergraduates continue to outnumber females by nearly two to one as revealed by the College Strategic Planning Division. Felix tries to make sense of it all.
The (unsurprising) revelation came to light after the department revealed that for the previous academic year a mere …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Summer Ball planners need you
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-summer-ball-planners-need-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2013 01:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-summer-ball-planners-need-you/</guid>
        <description>A meeting of the Ents Working Group, chaired by Stefan Nubert, Deputy President (Finance &amp;amp; Services), is due to be held on Friday 1 February at 12:30 – 1:30 pm. The group is set to convene in order to consolidate a budget for future events orchestrated by Ents, including the prospective 2013 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>International students want clearer information on fees and fee rises
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-17-international-students-want-clearer-information-on-fees-and-fee-rises/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 23:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-17-international-students-want-clearer-information-on-fees-and-fee-rises/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College fails to provide sufficient clarity on international student tariffs, as perceived by students. Imperial College Union intends to lobby the University amidst growing apprehension among overseas students.
Imperial College Union will lobby College to say how much the entire degree …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Should climate change be labelled?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-should-climate-change-be-labelled/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 21:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-should-climate-change-be-labelled/</guid>
        <description>I read over my last article and it seemed a bit too esoteric… and we’re all scientists after all, so I’ll try and keep to the facts this time.
There is a multitude of stigma attached to climate change. Some say we’re still on a positive temperature trend in the wake of an Ice Age ten millennia ago, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Needle in an environmental haystack
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-14-needle-in-an-environmental-haystack/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 00:39:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eoghan Totten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-14-needle-in-an-environmental-haystack/</guid>
        <description>London. A seething, writhing cacophony of activity by day and a place where simmering pulses of energy remain by night. If there’s one thing you can count on, it’s that in London, a light is always turned on somewhere.
Of course, this stands true for the monopoly of megacities pinned over the globe, …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
