<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/vbb08/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/vbb08/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>From wild wolves to top dogs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-from-wild-wolves-to-top-dogs/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 20:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Victoria Bignet,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-from-wild-wolves-to-top-dogs/</guid>
        <description>Although dogs are surely the first animals to be domesticated, the history and location of wolf-to-dog evolution has been controversial. Yet recent genetic evidence points to the Middle East. Most farmyard animals and the house cat were domesticated in the Middle Eastern area known as the Fertile …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>When the skies became green
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-when-the-skies-became-green/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 19:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Victoria Bignet,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-when-the-skies-became-green/</guid>
        <description>The Green Aviation Forum organised a one day international symposium at Imperial College on the 6th January 2011, in an attempt to link together many of the green aviation research activities ongoing at the College.
The Forum aimed to address the multiple environmental challenges faced by the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We are 7 billion
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-12-we-are-7-billion/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2010 13:48:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Victoria Bignet,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-12-we-are-7-billion/</guid>
        <description>Our population has tripled within less than one generation. The major reasons are the crash in death rates as a consequence of controlling infectious disease, higher life-expectancy and better quality of life. We are projected to add another 3 billion by 2050; that is more than Europe, Africa, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students with ‘Parasight’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-students-with-parasight/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2010 20:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Victoria Bignet,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-students-with-parasight/</guid>
        <description>MIT hosts an annual undergraduate Synthetic Biology competition called iGEM (International Genetically Engineered Machine), aiming for each university team to build biological systems and operate them in living cells. Imperial made an outstanding performance and landed fourth on the podium out of a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The retrovirus conundrum
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-the-retrovirus-conundrum/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 20:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Victoria Bignet,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-the-retrovirus-conundrum/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College researchers from the Department of Infectious Diseases have just succeeded in determining the mechanism of retroviral integration, using x-rays to analyse the key molecular structures involved in this process.
The Diamond synchrotron in Oxfordshire was the researchers’ main tool to …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
