<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Politics on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Politics on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/politics/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>A Decade of UK Politics</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-decade-of-uk-politics/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-decade-of-uk-politics/</guid>
        <description>As the clock ticked midnight on 1st January 2010, the nation celebrated the completion of an entire decade into the new millennium. At the time, 10 Downing Street was occupied by Gordon Brown, the Prime Minister who took the country through the global financial crash of 2008. Brown had been part of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix 2019 General Election Poll: Results</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-felix-general-election-poll-results-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-felix-general-election-poll-results-2019/</guid>
        <description></description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The End of a Decade: Spain</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-end-of-decade-spain/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-end-of-decade-spain/</guid>
        <description>The last decade has been a period of historical changes in Spain that have transformed its political culture and society forever. This historical phase is parallel to the European economic crisis and its aftermath, which were particularly intense in Southern European countries like Spain. Arguably, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Rise and Fall of Jo Swinson’s Liberal Democrats</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-rise-and-fall-of-jo-swinsons-liberal-democrats/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lloyd T James,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-rise-and-fall-of-jo-swinsons-liberal-democrats/</guid>
        <description>Six months ago, British politics seemed poised for upheaval. The Liberal Democrats, standing on an unambiguously pro-remain platform, secured a higher vote share than both Labour and the Conservatives in the EU elections. The overall victory however, had gone to the equally unambiguous Brexit Party. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“If you dare to struggle, you dare to win...”</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-dare-to-struggle-dare-to-win/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-dare-to-struggle-dare-to-win/</guid>
        <description>Before dawn on December 4th, 1969, Fred Hampton was murdered in his bed. He was killed in a police raid with the assent of local law enforcement, the state government’s prosecutor’s office, and the FBI. He was 21 years old.
Hampton was a member of the Black Panther Party. Established in 1966, the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oil Currencies: The Fight for Global Dominance</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-oil-currencies-fight-global-dominance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nehaal Pillai,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-oil-currencies-fight-global-dominance/</guid>
        <description>The United States of America has had a significant presence in the Middle East, a region so far away from it. Why? The reason is the preservation of the Petrodollar system, the currency in which most oil is traded. The demise of this system would bring about a colossal powershift from West to East: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Anger of an Exhausted Iraqi Youth Against a 16-year Old Corruptible Political System</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-anger-exhausted-iraqi-youth-against-16-year-old-corruptible-political-system/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mariam Shwea,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-anger-exhausted-iraqi-youth-against-16-year-old-corruptible-political-system/</guid>
        <description>Thousands of Iraqi youngsters, from central and southern cities and from all religious groups, have been taking the streets since October 1st against the worsening economic conditions, the divisive government policies, and widespread corruption that afflicts Iraq. The government has reacted …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UK Election Manifestos Review</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-uk-election-manifestos-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ansh Bhatnagar,James Thorne,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-uk-election-manifestos-review/</guid>
        <description>Labour
Brexit policy: negotiate a credible leave deal that protects jobs and living standards within three months, and put it to a referendum against remain in six months.
Titled “It’s time for real change”, the Labour manifesto certainly lives up to that promise. Labour have promised large spending …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Eritrean-Ethiopian Conflict And The Man Who Solved It</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-eritrean-ethiopian-conflict-man-who-solved-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-eritrean-ethiopian-conflict-man-who-solved-it/</guid>
        <description>In today’s world, where uncertainty and instability seem to always be on the surge, it is often relieving to witness the ability of men to repair the damages of their predecessors, to heal the cuts left open in the soul of an entire people. It is even more rewarding when such happenings involve a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Election Section: Spanish General Elections: the Rise of the Far-Right Wakes Up Left Parties</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-election-section-spanish-general-elections-rise-far-right-wakes-up-left-parties/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jorge Martínez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-election-section-spanish-general-elections-rise-far-right-wakes-up-left-parties/</guid>
        <description>This Sunday, Spain faced its second general election of the year, the country seeking a new government after President Pedro Sánchez failed to build a coalition after the last election in April.
At first glance, it seems that not much about Spanish politics has changed. Once more, the Socialist …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flag Patriotism: Vox in the November elections and the Rise of the Far Right in Spain</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-flag-patriotism-vox-november-elections-rise-far-right-spain/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-flag-patriotism-vox-november-elections-rise-far-right-spain/</guid>
        <description>Some political scientists argue that the far right comes in “waves”, and that Europe is currently being swept up by one of them. Most European countries have witnessed the rise (and sometimes fall) of parties representing this radical mindset in the last century; but Spain has been an exception, or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>EUphoria and the EU’s Role in the People’s Vote</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-euphoria-and-eu-role-in-peoples-vote/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-euphoria-and-eu-role-in-peoples-vote/</guid>
        <description>Brexit has been the main object of political attention for the past year, dividing UK’s population in half: pro-Brexit and pro-EU. The latter is interclass, constituted by voters mainly ranging from centre to left from all ages. In 2018, a pro-EU campaign group aiming to hold another referendum was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Election Section: Understanding the Spanish Election</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-election-section-understanding-spanish-election/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maeve Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-election-section-understanding-spanish-election/</guid>
        <description>Spain will be holding general elections yet again on the 10th of November, the second general election in six months and the fourth in four years.
In recent decades, the Spanish political landscape has been drastically reshaped by the new, younger politicians entering the scene and a surging number …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The State we’re in…</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-the-state-were-in/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-the-state-were-in/</guid>
        <description>In the previous article it was established that the state is a necessity for capitalism, as without a state private property rights could not be enforced. A state was defined by political economist Max Weber as “a political entity that maintains a monopoly on the use of violence”. We discussed how …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>General Election Time</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-general-election-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,Harvey Dolton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-general-election-time/</guid>
        <description>Above: General Election 2017 constituency map
It would be impossible to discuss any politics in the UK without stumbling upon Brexit. Brexit has been the key political issue of the last three years, a problem that successive governments have been unable to satisfactorily resolve.
The calling of this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Protests Sparked Over Political Stagnation in Chile</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-protests-sparked-political-stagnation-chile/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Harvey Dolton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-protests-sparked-political-stagnation-chile/</guid>
        <description>Over the past two weeks large scale protests have engulfed Chile’s capital, Santiago, and spread to neighbouring cities. Triggered by a now-suspended rise in the price of metro fares in Santiago, police brutality has sparked further resistance from the public. Felipe Hernandez, a law student who was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Quest for Supremacy in the Indian Ocean and its Victims: the Chagos Islands</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-quest-supremacy-indian-ocean-victims-chagos-islands/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-quest-supremacy-indian-ocean-victims-chagos-islands/</guid>
        <description>In the last few weeks the news cycle has been fixated on protests around the world, from Catalonia, to Chile and Hong Kong, to climate change and to Ecuador. All of these are processes which deal with the lives of countless people. These movements tend to make one reflect on the influence of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Understanding the 2019 Canadian Election</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-understanding-2019-canadian-election/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maeve Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-understanding-2019-canadian-election/</guid>
        <description>Last week Justin Trudeau managed to claw his way to a minority government in an election which saw him lose his 2015 sweeping majority and came after a term that had few clear wins and was marred by controversy. There was a clear regional divide in election results, with a complete loss of Liberal …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Election Section: Canada’s Trudeau Wins Minority Government</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-election-section-canadas-trudeau-wins-minority-government/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,Harvey Dolton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-election-section-canadas-trudeau-wins-minority-government/</guid>
        <description>When first elected as the Canadian Prime Minister in 2015, Justin Trudeau was a breath of fresh air for a country that for 9 years had been governed by the Conservative Stephen Harper. He was young, charismatic, progressive, and completely unlike the traditionally understated style of politics …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Highs and Lows: Parliamentary Votes Prolong Brexit Uncertainty</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-25-10-highs-lows-parliamentary-votes-prolong-brexit-uncertainty/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,Harvey Dolton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-25-10-highs-lows-parliamentary-votes-prolong-brexit-uncertainty/</guid>
        <description>Last week and Monday 21st October
Boris Johnson reaches a withdrawal agreement with the European Union, a 115 page Withdrawal Agreement Bill was published. The bill outlines the terms on which Britain will leave the EU and includes an exit fee, the price sum has not yet been established, to be paid …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Resurgence of Catalonian Separatist Violence</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-resurgence-catalonian-separatist-violence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jorge Martínez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-resurgence-catalonian-separatist-violence/</guid>
        <description>It’s 10pm in Barcelona. On a street corner, waste bins have been set alight, the noxious smell of burnt plastic penetrating the air. The piercing siren of a police van shatters the silence of the night as it speeds onto the scene. Running towards the van, a group of hooded people begin hurling …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Turkish Invasion of Syria</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-turkish-invasion-syria/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-turkish-invasion-syria/</guid>
        <description>Turkey has always occupied a strategically significant place in history. As the bastion for the Byzantine Empire, as the base for Ottoman dominance of the Middle East and as the gateway to the Crimea, Turkey has always been a valuable prize. More recently, Turkey’s membership of NATO was a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is Capitalism?, Part 2: Nobody Wants to Take your Toothbrush</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-what-is-capitalism-part-2-nobody-wants-take-toothbrush/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-what-is-capitalism-part-2-nobody-wants-take-toothbrush/</guid>
        <description>Last week we looked at wage labour and the class divide, where we assessed the capitalist class to be the minority that owns the means of production, such as land, a factory, or an office, and the working class to be the majority that are made to sell their labour power in exchange for a wage and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Graduate Work Visa Scheme will Benefit Current Students Graduating in or after Summer 2021</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-graduate-work-visa-scheme-benefit-current-students-graduating-2021/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Wang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-graduate-work-visa-scheme-benefit-current-students-graduating-2021/</guid>
        <description>Last month the government announced the Graduate visa scheme, through which non-EU/EEA students graduating from a UK university could be granted a 2-year work visa. This was seen as a reimplementation of the previous Post-Study Work visa, which was scrapped by the then-Home Secretary Theresa May …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Shaky Foundations: Unrest in Ecuador Offers Important Lessons for the Latin American Left</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-shaky-foundations-unrest-ecuador-offers-important-lessons-latin-american-left/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nicolás Manrique,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-shaky-foundations-unrest-ecuador-offers-important-lessons-latin-american-left/</guid>
        <description>If you’re not totally up to speed with the situation in which Ecuador currently finds itself, I think I can find it in my heart to forgive you – in a world which seems to be in a hurry to fall into crisis of late, it can be terribly hard to keep up with it all. In any case, let me lay it down for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>United States Supreme Court Weighs New LGBTQ&#43; Rights Cases</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-united-states-supreme-court-weighs-new-lgbtq-rights-cases/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Hodges,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-united-states-supreme-court-weighs-new-lgbtq-rights-cases/</guid>
        <description>Protection from dismissal on the grounds of sexual orientation or gender identity was up for debate before the US Supreme Court this week, in the first three LGBTQ rights cases of the last 2 years. The cases referenced Title VII of the Civil Rights Act, which bans discrimination in hiring, pay, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is Capitalism?, Part 1: Boss Makes a Dollar, I Make a Dime…</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-what-is-capitalism-part-1-boss-makes-dollar-i-make-dime/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-what-is-capitalism-part-1-boss-makes-dollar-i-make-dime/</guid>
        <description>Capitalism: in its modern form, it’s the way the world works, and has worked, for the last 200 years. It shapes more than just our economic life but encroaches on our politics, our climate, our culture, our very psychology. Although it dictates our lives, it can still remain a mystery to many of us, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brexit Developments: New PM Stance And Operation Yellowhammer</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-brexit-developments-new-pm-stance-operation-yellowhammer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-brexit-developments-new-pm-stance-operation-yellowhammer/</guid>
        <description>Several noteworthy events have recently occurred relating to an old subject: Brexit. Asking for a postponement is actually required by law, the Benn Act, which received Royal Assent by the Queen on 9th September. Johnson’s government confirmed last Friday that the Prime Minister will indeed ask for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>If You Don’t Already Know: Why an Impeachment Inquiry against Trump has Been Opened</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-if-you-dont-already-know-why-impeachment-against-trump-has-opened/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-if-you-dont-already-know-why-impeachment-against-trump-has-opened/</guid>
        <description>For months, Speaker of the House Nancy Pelosi has been resisting calls from progressive members of her party to open an impeachment inquiry into President Donald Trump. But within days of breaking news about a whistle-blower complaint about Trump, she has come out in support of it. On September …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Resistance, Resilience and Revolution</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-resistance-resilience-and-revolution/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-resistance-resilience-and-revolution/</guid>
        <description>For the first time ever in the lives of the Sudanese youth community, we get to see and experience a Sudan that isn’t ruled under Omar-Al-Bashir’s dictatorship. For the past 30 years, Sudan has seen Bashir’s rule take everything away from its people – everything except for the people’s resilience. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sudan Crisis: An Overview</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-sudan-crisis-an-overview/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Biyaser Abuelgasim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-sudan-crisis-an-overview/</guid>
        <description>On 19th December 2018, hundreds of people protested in Atbara and several other cities in Sudan against the rising costs of living and dramatic worsening of economic conditions. Even bread, a commodity we take for granted, tripled in price. The protests spread quickly to other cities, including the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Policy View of Abortion</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-a-policy-view-of-abortion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-a-policy-view-of-abortion/</guid>
        <description>Last week, the Alabama State legislature approved a bill that would limit a woman’s access to abortion at every stage of pregnancy and make it a criminal offence for doctors who provide the service. This measure has been the most drastic move by American pro-lifers to challenge a woman’s right to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Green New Deal: the less realistic the better</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-the-green-new-deal-the-less-realistic-the-better/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-the-green-new-deal-the-less-realistic-the-better/</guid>
        <description>A revolutionary set of policies called the New Deal was enacted by Franklin Roosevelt, in response to the Great Depression. The policies were incredibly successful in providing economic relief and financial reform through public work projects, laying the foundation for the upcoming era of Democratic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Spanish socialists win big in a fragmented parliament while the far-right gets representation for the first time</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-spanish-socialists-win-big-in-a-fragmented-parliament-while-the-far-right-gets-representation-for-the-first-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-spanish-socialists-win-big-in-a-fragmented-parliament-while-the-far-right-gets-representation-for-the-first-time/</guid>
        <description>Prime Minister Pedro Sánchez’s Spanish Socialist Workers Party (PSOE in Spanish) won a commanding victory in the general election held last Sunday in Spain. Despite being far from wining an absolute majority of seats, something that rarely happens due to the relatively proportional voting system and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mayhem in the Commons</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-mayhem-in-the-commons/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-mayhem-in-the-commons/</guid>
        <description>After significant pressure, Theresa May agreed to a series of votes this week to test the opinion of the House of Commons on Brexit. On Tuesday she put her deal to another vote after getting further minor concessions from the EU and still lost by 149 votes. This was a humiliating defeat. After …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Venezuela in crisis - the untold story</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-venezuela-in-crisis-the-untold-story/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Avirup Banerjee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-venezuela-in-crisis-the-untold-story/</guid>
        <description>War is a racket”, General Smedley Butler warned in 1935. Butler, who was the most decorated marine at the time of his death, was sent by his government to South America to establish one banana republic after another. The drums of war are at it again, this time in Venezuela, brought to you by the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>War, What Is It Good For? Absolutely Nothing!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-war-what-is-it-good-for-absolutely-nothing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Avirup Banerjee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-war-what-is-it-good-for-absolutely-nothing/</guid>
        <description>On 14th February 14, 40 Indian paramilitary soldiers were killed by a suicide bombing in Indian-Administered Kashmir. Whilst the bomber was born and raised in India (a fact ignored by the Indian media), he was funded and equipped by the Pakistan based terrorist organisation JeM, who have publicly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LSE Festival – An Exhibition of Policy and Social Science Research</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-lse-festival-an-exhibition-of-policy-and-social-science-research/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-lse-festival-an-exhibition-of-policy-and-social-science-research/</guid>
        <description>The LSE Festival, running from 25 February to 2 March, is a week-long series of events aimed at engaging the public with social science hot topics. This year’s theme is New World (Dis)Orders and focuses on the changing global situation: a new emergent world order where the US is no longer the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Labelling The Independent Group MPs “traitors” is exactly why they left</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-labelling-the-independent-group-mps-traitors-is-exactly-why-they-left/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-labelling-the-independent-group-mps-traitors-is-exactly-why-they-left/</guid>
        <description>When The Independent Group MPs left, they were in disgust at the state of their own parties. Let us consider the personal toll this must have taken. Many MPs grew up knowing that they wanted to be in politics, and what party they wanted to be a part of. They will have spent years working in small …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>VZ, Bernie, and Cohen on TV</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-vz-bernie-and-cohen-on-tv/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gritty,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-vz-bernie-and-cohen-on-tv/</guid>
        <description>The profligate son returns, crucified for calls to revolution and arisen after three days (and two months or so). Keeping with the theme – three independent stories from the past two weeks.
Venezuela. This is the classic American foreign policy pincher – place excruciating sanctions on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brexit to end the NHS: Hypochondria or the real deal?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-brexit-to-end-the-nhs-hypochondria-or-the-real-deal/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhiju Chatterjee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-brexit-to-end-the-nhs-hypochondria-or-the-real-deal/</guid>
        <description>Born in 1948, the NHS has survived through a lot. However, like many other 70 year olds, the NHS is facing multiple chronic issues that cannot be fixed with a simple operation. Patients are waiting longer and longer to see a doctor, both in GP practices and A&amp;amp;Es. This is due to a multitude of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Independent Group? No thanks</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-the-independent-group-no-thanks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-the-independent-group-no-thanks/</guid>
        <description>On Monday morning, a group of 7 Labour MPs took the unprecedented step of leaving the Labour Party and forming a new centrist “party”, taking the incredibly bland name of ‘The Independent Group’. Except it was not unprecedented at all – most of these MPs, such as their ringleader Chuka Umunna, have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Labour defections - a Tory perspective</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-the-labour-defections-a-tory-perspective/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-the-labour-defections-a-tory-perspective/</guid>
        <description>On Monday seven Labour MPs announced that they were leaving the Labour party in protest at Jeremy Corbyn’s leadership and his refusal to act on anti-Semitism present within the party. This has drawn inevitable comparisons with the Social Democrat Party, a group of four former ministers who resigned …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London is at knife’s edge: fatal stabbings at record high</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-london-is-at-knife-s-edge-fatal-stabbings-at-record-high/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aaron Hadley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-london-is-at-knife-s-edge-fatal-stabbings-at-record-high/</guid>
        <description>London has a knife problem. By the time of writing, ten people have died in 2019 from stab wounds. By the time you are reading this, that number will likely have increased by two or three. But people are not just numbers on a spreadsheet. Lives are being lost, and a blanket of fear is descending …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lefty YouTubers event draws large crowds </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-lefty-youtubers-event-draws-large-crowds/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-lefty-youtubers-event-draws-large-crowds/</guid>
        <description>Shout out to Something Awful forum poster SuperMechaGodzilla, who, in 2013, posted a Communist analysis of the film Prometheus, and basically radicalised me on the spot”. This was the answer of Harry Brewis (Hbomberguy) to the question on how he was introduced to leftism. With such a starting shot, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The World’s Largest Election in History - and no one is talking about it! </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-the-world-s-largest-election-in-history-and-no-one-is-talking-about-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Avirup Banerjee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-the-world-s-largest-election-in-history-and-no-one-is-talking-about-it/</guid>
        <description>The American election of 2020 is still 600 days away, yet even in the British press there is at least one article a day on any declared or even potential candidates to challenge Donald Trump. Yet very little focus has been given by the international press to the biggest election in human history …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Breaking Down Brexit: A Strong And Stable Analysis</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-breaking-down-brexit-a-strong-and-stable-analysis/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aaron Hadley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-breaking-down-brexit-a-strong-and-stable-analysis/</guid>
        <description>Theresa May is in trouble. More than that, the whole country is in trouble. Last week the government lost its vote to pass the withdrawal agreement, a 500-page legal document taking the UK out of the EU in an orderly fashion. She is to hold another vote on January the 29th (if she does not delay …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Donkey Kong became a trans icon</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-how-donkey-kong-became-a-trans-icon/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-how-donkey-kong-became-a-trans-icon/</guid>
        <description>First, a bit of background. Trans rights are a controversial topic in the UK currently with mainstream newspapers exhibiting some of the most toxic and transphobic headlines; The Telegraph recently ran a front-page story titled “Trans row as men get access to women’s NHS wards”. Not only does this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>May’s Brexit deal voted down by calamitous margin</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-may-s-brexit-deal-voted-down-by-calamitous-margin/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-may-s-brexit-deal-voted-down-by-calamitous-margin/</guid>
        <description>Theresa May lost the vote on her Withdrawal deal by 230 votes, and she only has herself to blame. This defeat was an inevitable consequence of the incompetent way she has handled Brexit.
Theresa May’s problems are profound and difficult to solve but she gave herself no chance at all by her approach …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nothing but Mayhem</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-nothing-but-mayhem/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-nothing-but-mayhem/</guid>
        <description>Theresa May’s survival ability is something to behold. She could be half-jokingly compared to the character of the Black Knight in Monty Python’s Holy Grail who kept fighting King Arthur even after losing his four limbs. In an ironic twist, her constant resilience mirrors that of Labour leader …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Now’s the time to tune back into US news</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-now-s-the-time-to-tune-back-into-us-news/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gritty,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-now-s-the-time-to-tune-back-into-us-news/</guid>
        <description>Merry Gritmas. Since Parliament voted to hold the government in contempt, I’ve been jerkin’ it constantly, and have released more “legal advice” than I knew my body could produce. Well, let’s get to it.
The Mueller probe is chugging along. Trump is now known to be “Individual 1” - the central focus …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sri Lankan Politics is in a sorry state of  Affairs</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-sri-lankan-politics-is-in-a-sorry-state-of-affairs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-sri-lankan-politics-is-in-a-sorry-state-of-affairs/</guid>
        <description>Over the last month there has been significant political turmoil in Sri Lanka which kicked off on the 26th October when the President of Sri Lanka, Sirisena, attempted to sack Wickremesinghe, the Prime Minister. Sirisena has tried to replace him with Rajapaksa, who was the sitting President Sirisena …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s been a slow week for American politics</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-it-s-been-a-slow-week-for-american-politics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gritty,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-it-s-been-a-slow-week-for-american-politics/</guid>
        <description>Grit went Brit this week.
We’ve been so busy with the recent collapse of the UK government that US news seemed to have been swept well under the rug. This is fine by me - no news is good news as far as America is concerned. There’s the odd morsel - Ivanka Trump’s emails; Nancy Pelosi being the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The midterms dust has settled; the races were rigged and we still live in a waking nightmare</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-the-midterms-dust-has-settled-the-races-were-rigged-and-we-still-live-in-a-waking-nightmare/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gritty,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-the-midterms-dust-has-settled-the-races-were-rigged-and-we-still-live-in-a-waking-nightmare/</guid>
        <description>When in times of trouble, Gritty comes to me, speaking words of wisdom - Trump’s pants are peed.
It’s been another week of abject hell in politics, but this time the chips are falling in the Dems’ favor. Turns out Florida and Georgia haven’t even counted all their ballots (Broward County, who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>American Midterms: Tactical Defeat, Strategic Victory for the Democrats</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-american-midterms-tactical-defeat-strategic-victory-for-the-democrats/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-american-midterms-tactical-defeat-strategic-victory-for-the-democrats/</guid>
        <description>Last Tuesday, Americans went to the poll to vote for a third of their Senators, all their Representatives, 36 governors and most state senators and state representatives in the country. The Felix readership probably knows the two main takeaways: while the Democrats were successful in their attempt …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gritty unwinds the American midterms</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-gritty-unwinds-the-american-midterms/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gritty,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-gritty-unwinds-the-american-midterms/</guid>
        <description>It the Grit. The midterms have come and gone, and the balance of power has shifted. Races have been won and lost. Pour a 40 out for my dudes Gillum, O’Rourke (3-point spread), Janz, and Abrams (~2 point spread). Good showing all.
The Dems picked up 34 seats in the House, clinching the majority. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>With Bolsonaro’s victory in the second round, Brazil goes down a tenebrous path</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-with-bolsonaro-s-victory-in-the-second-round-brazil-goes-down-a-tenebrous-path/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Avirup Banerjee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-with-bolsonaro-s-victory-in-the-second-round-brazil-goes-down-a-tenebrous-path/</guid>
        <description>In last week’s run-off election, Brazil’s fascist-in-chief Jair Bolsonaro won the presidency with 55% of the vote. Yes, fascist is the appropriate description, and let the record show that this was a far from a fair fight. From the 2016 impeachment of the former President Dilma Rouseff on flimsy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gritty’s Field Guide to the American Midterm Elections: It’s Gonna Be Rough, Folks</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-gritty-s-field-guide-to-the-american-midterm-elections-it-s-gonna-be-rough-folks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gritty,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-gritty-s-field-guide-to-the-american-midterm-elections-it-s-gonna-be-rough-folks/</guid>
        <description>Welcome one and all to the continuing shitshow saga that is the American political spectacle. When you last tuned in in 2016, the Ur-fascist narrowly beat out the neoliberal cancellation of the future, and we’ve been on a wild ride for the last two years as Republican majorities in Congress and a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to avoid a mess like Brexit: let’s adopt a new voting system</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-how-to-avoid-a-mess-like-brexit-let-s-adopt-a-new-voting-system/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-how-to-avoid-a-mess-like-brexit-let-s-adopt-a-new-voting-system/</guid>
        <description>Since the Brexit referendum we’ve seen Brexit come to dominate British politics. It has been incredibly divisive and has created more problems than it has solved. It has sent both of the major political parties into turmoil. We need to ask ourselves how we got here and more importantly how can we …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jamal, the Martyr</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-jamal-the-martyr/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-jamal-the-martyr/</guid>
        <description>In 1170, four English knights murdered the archbishop of Canterbury, Thomas Beckett, following the orders of king Henry II. The assassination of Beckett had ramifications that reached continental Europe, and less than two years after his death he was declared a saint by the Church. Henry had to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>War at the world</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-war-at-the-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-war-at-the-world/</guid>
        <description>What difference does half a degree make? It doesn’t seem like much, right? After all, you don’t notice if the water in your sink has gone from 35 ºC to 35.5 ºC when you are washing the dishes. But half a degree is much more important than what you may think. It is the difference between being able …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bolsonaro Wins the First Round: Brazil Goes Balls Up</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-15-bolsonaro-wins-the-first-round-brazil-goes-balls-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-15-bolsonaro-wins-the-first-round-brazil-goes-balls-up/</guid>
        <description>South American countries have usually been ignored by the Western media, with few exceptions. On the few occasions the continent was reported by our news organisations, its nations were painted as permanently failed states ravaged by civil war, dictators and death squads. This picture ignores the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Save the American Supreme Court from the Republicans</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-15-how-to-save-the-american-supreme-court-from-the-republicans/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Avirup Banerjee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-15-how-to-save-the-american-supreme-court-from-the-republicans/</guid>
        <description>After the election of 1800, who would become the third President of the American Republic was very much a mystery. With the electoral college tied at 73 between Thomas Jefferson and Aaron Burr, the decision was left to the House of Representatives with Jefferson only winning the Presidency after the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Demands for Safer Roads after Fatal Collision in Bangladesh</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-demands-for-safer-roads-after-fatal-collision-in-bangladesh/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tasneem Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-demands-for-safer-roads-after-fatal-collision-in-bangladesh/</guid>
        <description>The death on the 29th July of two school children, Diya Khanam Mim and Abdul Karim Rajib, after being run over by a speeding bus, sparked mass protests in Bangladesh’s capital, Dhaka. According to witnesses, the bus was racing with another bus to pick up passengers, before the driver lost control. A …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Visit to Labour Conference: Thoughts on the Government in Waiting</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-my-visit-to-labour-conference-thoughts-on-the-government-in-waiting/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-my-visit-to-labour-conference-thoughts-on-the-government-in-waiting/</guid>
        <description>Last week, I travelled along with three other Imperial students to the annual Labour Party Conference, this year held in the great city of Liverpool. After a long, difficult summer in the party, with lots of division between the two factional wings, I didn’t know if I should be looking forward to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Secret Tory: A Behind the Scenes Look at the Annual Tory Conference</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-the-secret-tory-a-behind-the-scenes-look-at-the-annual-tory-conference/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-the-secret-tory-a-behind-the-scenes-look-at-the-annual-tory-conference/</guid>
        <description>I will be frank – I am an undecided voter. I wanted to make an informed decision so I did the sane thing – I bought a media pass and packed my bags for the International Conference Centre (ICC) in Birmingham. The Conference was enlightening… it certainly changed my perspective of the Conservative …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s Been a Long Summer in British Politics </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-it-s-been-a-long-summer-in-british-politics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-it-s-been-a-long-summer-in-british-politics/</guid>
        <description>It’s been a crazy summer in the world of politics with both major political parties in major turmoil. The Conservative party and the Labour party have been in open warfare over Brexit with each other and within their own camps.
The start of the summer started well for Theresa May, she suffered no …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>May, you live in interesting times</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-may-you-live-in-interesting-times/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-may-you-live-in-interesting-times/</guid>
        <description>In 2015, David Cameron achieved by surprise what no other Conservative leader had accomplished since 1992: he returned to Westminster with a majority of six. The Tories had warned the electorate of a ‘coalition of chaos’ arising around Ed Miliband if voters returned again a hung parliament. Three …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Labour Party does not have a problem with Anti-Semitism</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-the-labour-party-does-not-have-a-problem-with-anti-semitism/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Avirup Banerjee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-the-labour-party-does-not-have-a-problem-with-anti-semitism/</guid>
        <description>The ancient Chinese had a curse: ‘may he live in interesting times’ – well these are interesting times when the president of the United States claims there are good people on the side of neo-Nazis and with the electoral success of far-right neo-Nazi political groups all over Europe and America. But …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Changing times...</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-changing-times/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-changing-times/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College isn’t the place it used to be. The student body is becoming less inward focussed, less tolerant of poor decision making on the part of the university, and less dismissive of things beyond the four walls of their degrees. We have a way to go yet, but the culture at our university is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In defence of the Syrian Democratic Forces</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-in-defence-of-the-syrian-democratic-forces/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-in-defence-of-the-syrian-democratic-forces/</guid>
        <description>Several weeks ago, I wrote a comment piece for this paper that advocated Western support to the organization known as SDF (Syrian Democratic Forces), a group I described as: “an organization which has an ideology that combines libertarian socialism, gender equality, respect for ethnic minorities, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s time to break the cycle of foreign interventions</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-it-s-time-to-break-the-cycle-of-foreign-interventions/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-it-s-time-to-break-the-cycle-of-foreign-interventions/</guid>
        <description>The olden days of warfare, of shrewd generals commanding their gallant troops into majestic battles, are long gone. The guerres du jour are served as drawn out, low-intensity meat grinders across land, sea, and air, augmented by a generous portion of ideological – and perhaps, one could say, memetic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bahá’í : a belief system suited to our troubled times?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-bah-a-belief-system-suited-to-our-troubled-times/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-bah-a-belief-system-suited-to-our-troubled-times/</guid>
        <description>The world has seen a resurgence of nationalism, fascism, and protectionism. These pose an existential threat to the world as we know it. Liberal democracies spreading wealth and freedom via free market capitalism have seen their support checked by the likes of Trump, Brexit and most recently the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The government’s handling of the Windrush scandal is a national disgrace</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-the-government-s-handling-of-the-windrush-scandal-is-a-national-disgrace/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-the-government-s-handling-of-the-windrush-scandal-is-a-national-disgrace/</guid>
        <description>The government’s past few years of immigration policy have been cruel and inhumane, as highlighted by the Windrush Scandal. The arbitrary target to cut immigration to the tens of thousands has spawned some nasty and unexpected consequences. The ‘hostile environment’ policy adopted whilst Theresa May …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>China’s House of Cards – The rise of Xi Jingping as China’s President for life </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-china-s-house-of-cards-the-rise-of-xi-jingping-as-china-s-president-for-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Avirup Banerjee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-china-s-house-of-cards-the-rise-of-xi-jingping-as-china-s-president-for-life/</guid>
        <description>In 1911, the Wuchang Uprising brought down the Qing Dynasty, thus bringing to an end the longest continuous imperial civilization of 8,000 years. One of the most powerful dogmas perpetrated by the ancient Mandarins that allowed the firm rule of the emperors was the idea that the emperors had a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brexit and Ireland: how can we solve the border crisis?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-brexit-and-ireland-how-can-we-solve-the-border-crisis/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-brexit-and-ireland-how-can-we-solve-the-border-crisis/</guid>
        <description>How do you solve a problem like the Irish border? This appears to be the biggest stumbling block in achieving a successful outcome for Brexit. It seems an impossible square to circle. Theresa May has committed to withdrawing from the customs union and single market, which would mean there would need …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Winter Olympic’s joint South &amp; North Korean delegation</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-the-winter-olympic-s-joint-south-north-korean-delegation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Avirup Banerjee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-the-winter-olympic-s-joint-south-north-korean-delegation/</guid>
        <description>One of the worst clichés trotted out during world sporting events, like the Olympics, is that sport should be above politics. Yet this couldn’t be further from the truth. Some of the most memorable moments in Olympic history have been steeped in politics: from Jesse Owens’ defying Adolf Hitler’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>No Olive Branch for Rojava – what happens after the Turkish intervention in Syria?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-no-olive-branch-for-rojava-what-happens-after-the-turkish-intervention-in-syria/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-no-olive-branch-for-rojava-what-happens-after-the-turkish-intervention-in-syria/</guid>
        <description>While Western audiences were being entertained by the latest Trump antics and the recent developments in the seemingly interminable process that is Brexit, the last three weeks saw the beginning of a new phase in the Syrian Civil War. Now ISIS has lost its territorial power base and has disappeared …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students need to support the strikes – here’s what you can do to help</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-students-need-to-support-the-strikes-here-s-what-you-can-do-to-help/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lloyd T James,Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-students-need-to-support-the-strikes-here-s-what-you-can-do-to-help/</guid>
        <description>After two months of failed negotiations, with university management proposing huge cuts to pensions, university staff will be taking the only action available to them: striking. The staff walkout will begin next Thursday, February 22nd, and will escalate over a four-week period.
You might be worried …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Poor use of statistics is undermining our faith in public institutions</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-poor-use-of-statistics-is-undermining-our-faith-in-public-institutions/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-poor-use-of-statistics-is-undermining-our-faith-in-public-institutions/</guid>
        <description>The rise of statistics has led to many benefits in everyday life: we use statistics in medical research to determine what the best treatment; they inform decisions from stock markets through to how many pop tarts Walmart stocks; and, perhaps most significantly, statistics shape decisions made by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The trial of Winston Churchill and the British Empire he helped to build</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-the-trial-of-winston-churchill-and-the-british-empire-he-helped-to-build/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Avirup Banerjee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-the-trial-of-winston-churchill-and-the-british-empire-he-helped-to-build/</guid>
        <description>Carthage must be destroyed, the Roman Senator Cato the Elder decried at the end of all his speeches, irrespective of the original topic at hand. As a result of the tenacity of the war-mongering Roman elite, a once mighty civilization was reduced to rubble. Thus, if history teaches us anything, it is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We are all Hadiza</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-we-are-all-hadiza/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theo Farah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-we-are-all-hadiza/</guid>
        <description>In the days following the successful appeal by the General Medical Council (GMC) to have Dr Hadiza Bawa-Garba struck off the medical register, meaning she is not able to return to practice for at least five years, a crowd-funding campaign has raised over £200, 000 to fund further legal counsel for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Innovation will save us from an economic death</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-innovation-will-save-us-from-an-economic-death/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Hall,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-innovation-will-save-us-from-an-economic-death/</guid>
        <description>The global economy is stalling because of a lack of innovation. Beyond computers, there is no longer a revolutionary mentality towards technology. You can see it in our psychology: we call ourselves the developed world, as if all great strides have already been made. Granted we depict our visions of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Palestine: apartheid, ethnic-cleansing &amp; discrimination </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-palestine-apartheid-ethnic-cleansing-discrimination/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>IC Friends of Palestine,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-palestine-apartheid-ethnic-cleansing-discrimination/</guid>
        <description>In today’s 140-character world, it’s all too easy to blur the line between fact and fiction, and apply false assumptions leading to fallacious beliefs”.
When we opened the Felix edition containing an article entitled “A response to those who criticise the Balfour Declaration”, we were eager to read …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The State of Israel</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-the-state-of-israel/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-the-state-of-israel/</guid>
        <description>In last week’s Felix, members of the Imperial College Friends of Palestine wrote an article entitled ‘Palestine: apartheid, ethnic-cleansing and discrimination’. It was a well-written piece, arguing against an earlier Felix article defending the Balfour declaration, itself a response to an earlier …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Theresa, what’s good? Our round up of the best (and worst) of what happened this year in politics</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-theresa-what-s-good-our-round-up-of-the-best-and-worst-of-what-happened-this-year-in-politics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-theresa-what-s-good-our-round-up-of-the-best-and-worst-of-what-happened-this-year-in-politics/</guid>
        <description>For most of humankind, 2017 has been an awful year for politics. For satirists and political commentators, it has been an absolute gift. Here are some of the best bits.
“Easiest [negotiations] in history” – Liam Fox, international trade secretary (Brexit)
Nine months have passed since Article 50 was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A New Hope: Zimbabwe’s new birth of freedom … or more of the same?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-a-new-hope-zimbabwe-s-new-birth-of-freedom-or-more-of-the-same/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dean Posthuma,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-a-new-hope-zimbabwe-s-new-birth-of-freedom-or-more-of-the-same/</guid>
        <description>After 37 years, Robert Mugabe is no longer the president of president of Zimbabwe. Many people, including myself (having lived there for the first year of my life), had stopped wondering if this day would ever come until events began to rapidly unfold last week. Almost overnight, the Zimbabwean …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Politics takes on the Autumn Budget</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-felix-politics-takes-on-the-autumn-budget/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-felix-politics-takes-on-the-autumn-budget/</guid>
        <description>This Wednesday, the Autumn Budget was delivered by the Chancellor of the Exchequer, Philip Hammond. It entails details about government spending and borrowing, and related policies, in advance of the next financial year. This sort of thing sounds horrendously dull, but it’s important to appreciate …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A response to those who criticise the Balfour Declaration</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-a-response-to-those-who-criticise-the-balfour-declaration/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saul Coleman,Daniel Moses,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-a-response-to-those-who-criticise-the-balfour-declaration/</guid>
        <description>In today’s 140-character world, it’s all too easy to blur the line between fact and fiction, and apply false assumptions leading to fallacious beliefs. When I opened last week’s edition of Felix, I was greeted by an article entitled “The Balfour Declaration: A Century On”. I was eager to read on: an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stop  and think about it – a defence of university tuition fees</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-stop-and-think-about-it-a-defence-of-university-tuition-fees/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shaul Rosten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-stop-and-think-about-it-a-defence-of-university-tuition-fees/</guid>
        <description>Early last week, I walked past a poster in the SAF building whose message so incensed me that I felt the time had come to vent my frustration in the therapeutic pages of Felix. The poster screams:
“NATIONAL DEMO - FREE EDUCATION NOW: TAX THE RICH”
Since the General Election of 2010 we have seen …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tuition fees are completely nonsensical: it’s time we scrapped them, for good</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-tuition-fees-are-completely-nonsensical-it-s-time-we-scrapped-them-for-good/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-tuition-fees-are-completely-nonsensical-it-s-time-we-scrapped-them-for-good/</guid>
        <description>There is no more obvious hot-button issue for UK students at the moment than tuition fees. Their trebling in the past few years was met with a wave of student anger, and Labour’s position at the last election – abolishing fees, though not cancelling past debt – doubtless helped them curry favour …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NHS Watchdog Reveals Crippling Mental Health Services</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-nhs-watchdog-reveals-crippling-mental-health-services/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lara Bailey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-nhs-watchdog-reveals-crippling-mental-health-services/</guid>
        <description>The government has been accused of ‘neglecting’ children’s mental health, following a report revealing some children were waiting up to 18 months for treatment.
The report, which was authored by the Care Quality Commission (CQC) – an independent regulator of health and social care services – showed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Balfour Declaration: a century on</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-the-balfour-declaration-a-century-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aida Manzano-Kharman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-the-balfour-declaration-a-century-on/</guid>
        <description>When people hear about Palestine and Israel, they usually know ‘something’s going on there’ but few seem to understand what exactly is happening, and most importantly how the conflict originated. There are many factors, but it is widely agreed that the Palestinian-Israeli conflict can be traced back …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Czech elections throw the country into political turmoil</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-czech-elections-throw-the-country-into-political-turmoil/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Veronika Šigutová,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-czech-elections-throw-the-country-into-political-turmoil/</guid>
        <description>Last week’s legislative elections in the Czech Republic were record-breaking in many ways – most candidates and parties standing; most fragmented Chamber of Deputies to date, with nine parties crossing the 5% mark; and the first time in the country’s history that neither Civic Democrats (ODS) nor …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UK Party Conferences 2017: Corbyn is confident, May is choking, and Johnson is out for blood</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-uk-party-conferences-2017-corbyn-is-confident-may-is-choking-and-johnson-is-out-for-blood/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ratan Gor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-uk-party-conferences-2017-corbyn-is-confident-may-is-choking-and-johnson-is-out-for-blood/</guid>
        <description>Taking place each autumn, political party conferences are essentially like festivals where loyal groupies go en masse to cheer on their favourite stateswomen and men. Politicians take to the stage to discuss the current state of the party, set out their ambitions for the following year, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Austria’s far-right achieves a landslide win in parliamentary elections</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-austria-s-far-right-achieves-a-landslide-win-in-parliamentary-elections/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Clemens Jakubec,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-austria-s-far-right-achieves-a-landslide-win-in-parliamentary-elections/</guid>
        <description>It was a long Sunday for those eagerly awaiting the outcome of Austria’s 26th parliamentary elections. When the results started to come in during early afternoon, the winner was clear: the right wing, above all Sebastian Kurz and his conservative Österreichische Volkspartei (ÖVP) with 31.5% of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Catalonia faces a uncertain future after an independence vote riddled with irregularities</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-catalonia-faces-a-uncertain-future-after-an-independence-vote-riddled-with-irregularities/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aida Manzano-Kharman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-catalonia-faces-a-uncertain-future-after-an-independence-vote-riddled-with-irregularities/</guid>
        <description>Do you want Cataluña to be an independent state in the form of a republic? This was the question posed to the 5,313,564 inhabitants of Cataluña, of which an overwhelming 90% voted “yes”, with a turnout of 42.3%.
While it is true that the right to self-determination is a fundamental human right, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Right-wing parties predicted success in upcoming Austrian election</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-right-wing-parties-predicted-success-in-upcoming-austrian-election/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Clemens Jakubec,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-right-wing-parties-predicted-success-in-upcoming-austrian-election/</guid>
        <description>In the wake of a controversial presidential election which saw independent candidate Alexander Van der Bellen assume power last January, Austria is holding a parliamentary election this Sunday. In spring the parliament unanimously decided to hold early elections, after the two governing parties, the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brexit: your wrap-up on all the issues you need to know</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-brexit-your-wrap-up-on-all-the-issues-you-need-to-know/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ratan Gor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-brexit-your-wrap-up-on-all-the-issues-you-need-to-know/</guid>
        <description>Brexit. With no background knowledge, the word seems innocuous enough – the latest breakfast cereal perhaps? However, this now-infamous word and all it represents have been the talk of the town for the past year and a half. This summer, you’ve used it to screen prospective suitors on a first date, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Interview with Mayor of London candidate George Galloway
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-7-5-an-interview-with-mayor-of-london-candidate-george-galloway/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 10:02:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Renken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-7-5-an-interview-with-mayor-of-london-candidate-george-galloway/</guid>
        <description>Born in Dundee, Galloway became involved in politics from a very young age and is now campaigning as RESPECT Party candidate for Mayor of London. Known as a political maverick and divisive figure in British politics, Galloway has been lauded for his lively rhetoric and impassioned debating style. …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
