<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welfare on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/welfare/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welfare on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/welfare/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>How to survive exams
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-how-to-survive-exams/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 09:25:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-how-to-survive-exams/</guid>
        <description>There is a lot to be stressed out about at exam time. Whether it is your first year or your last, it is difficult to balance the intense workload with other commitments, such as arranging accommodation for next year. First and foremost, if you feel you are struggling to cope, whether you have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Life after anorexia: IBS
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-life-after-anorexia-ibs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 12:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily-Jane Cramphorn,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-life-after-anorexia-ibs/</guid>
        <description>People often speak about the risks of anorexia and bulimia – how they can kill you, make your bones brittle and your hair fall out.
However, I want to talk about one very overlooked side effect, Irritable Bowel Syndrome (IBS). For many years I have starved and punished my body. I have abused …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reflecting on Mentality
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-reflecting-on-mentality/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 12:51:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily-Jane Cramphorn,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-reflecting-on-mentality/</guid>
        <description>After a successful campaign last academic year, Mentality has succeeded once again in capturing the interests of the staff and student body alike. On the 19th January 2016, Sir Anthony Seldon ‘headlined’ at Mentality’s most recent event, giving an honest and humbling talk about his personal …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Writing as a release
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-writing-as-a-release/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 09:43:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jawaad Farooq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-writing-as-a-release/</guid>
        <description>Off the back of the Met office announcement on Monday that the climate is about to pass the one-degree threshold for global warming, I sat at my desk trying to write a coherent piece about the subject. As I typed away on my laptop, making notes from articles and reading up on the subject I asked …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Self-care
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-self-care/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 11:36:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Noor Mulheron,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-self-care/</guid>
        <description> Self-care is a term that refers to anything you choose to do that is a step towards taking care of your physical, mental or emotional health. Practising self-care is a key aspect to keeping yourself productive, motivated and happy while on a busy schedule like the one typically present at uni. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>When Diversity Becomes Adversity
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-18-when-diversity-becomes-adversity/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2015 19:31:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pheerawat Ratnitisakul,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-18-when-diversity-becomes-adversity/</guid>
        <description> “London is a world-class international city with people coming from diverse cultures and backgrounds. This, I believe, will allow me to enhance my communicative skills and learn to adjust myself to different environments.”
This is the sentence I used in the personal statement for applying for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don’t keep it all bottled up
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-12-dont-keep-it-all-bottled-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2015 12:43:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chanon Wongsatayanont,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-12-dont-keep-it-all-bottled-up/</guid>
        <description>A few weeks ago, the results of a College-wide mental health survey was released on Felix.
At first glance, the numbers looked scary where 75% out of 1115 respondents said that they’d experienced unhealthy amounts of stress and mental health symptoms sometime during their time in Imperial.
It is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Concepts at a glance: Gender and Sexuality
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-4-concepts-at-a-glance-gender-and-sexuality/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2015 23:48:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vinothan Shankar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-4-concepts-at-a-glance-gender-and-sexuality/</guid>
        <description>When discussing gender, sexuality, and similar topics, there are a lot of terms and concepts that you might come across. This article will provide a brief introduction to these concepts, what they mean, and how to use the words correctly. Let’s start with concepts.
Sexuality
This is an intrinsic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to keep yourself safe on campus
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-how-to-keep-yourself-safe-on-campus/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 12:46:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Zahra Esbati,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-how-to-keep-yourself-safe-on-campus/</guid>
        <description>My name is Nigel Ward, and on 30th March 2015 I was employed by Imperial College as the Senior Security Officer, Crime. My role is to investigate all crime, deliver a gold standard of victim care, and implement prevention tactics and strategies to reduce crime and the number of victims. What I bring …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Support for the Supporters
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-support-for-the-supporters/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 12:52:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chanon Wongsatayanont,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-support-for-the-supporters/</guid>
        <description>This is the mental health awareness week and I’ll focus on a slightly different but related angle today. In welfare, mental health is a much discussed issue with ever-increasing helpful resources, but there is a group of people often left out from the media spotlight. These are the friends who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to live in an international flat
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-how-to-live-in-an-international-flat/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 19:29:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chanon Wongsatayanont,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-how-to-live-in-an-international-flat/</guid>
        <description>You’ve probably had a flat mate who’s from a different culture. For some of you, it might have gone like this. Day one, things were going well. Day seven, tensions began with unwashed dishes. Day twenty-five, both sides mobilized for war over a party that had turned the corridor into a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Recovering, One Day at a Time
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-20-recovering-one-day-at-a-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 16:37:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Zahra Esbati,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-20-recovering-one-day-at-a-time/</guid>
        <description>Depression sucks, there’s no getting around that. It’s awful and makes you feel like you’re not in control of your own emotions, sleep pattern, or motivation. But something that’s worth remembering is that it’s not unmanageable.
In my years of dealing with depression and anxiety, there have been a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Overcoming the Distance
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-overcoming-the-distance/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 13:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chanon Wongsatayanont,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-overcoming-the-distance/</guid>
        <description>The world is getting more globalised and people seem to end up all over the place, smattered here and there like dots of paint. Unfortunately, this also applies to couples, out of necessity or to chase after an opportunity elsewhere. Both sides mean well and they each want the best for each other, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What it means to be an international student
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-what-it-means-to-be-an-international-student/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 01:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mahima Razdan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-what-it-means-to-be-an-international-student/</guid>
        <description>Take a look around in your lecture hall. What do you see? Considering that all of you are studying at Imperial College, there will probably be people of different races, nationalities, ethnicities and socioeconomic backgrounds all packed into one room. Now take a closer look. I’ll wager that there …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s score a goal for equality
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-21-lets-score-a-goal-for-equality/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2015 11:54:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kyle Hellemans,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-21-lets-score-a-goal-for-equality/</guid>
        <description>In 1990, Justin Fashanu was the first English professional footballer to come out as gay. Throughout this, he faced abuse from his teammates, fellow players and even his manager. He committed suicide just eight years later.
Equality in sport has come a long way since Justin Fashanu’s death. From 23 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I’m sure you’ll do great!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-11-im-sure-youll-do-great/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 21:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chanon Wongsatayanont,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-11-im-sure-youll-do-great/</guid>
        <description>It’s that time of the term again. Well, for those of us unfortunate enough to have end-of-term exams anyway (e.g. me). As the days are getting shorter, colder and revision hours are ticking away like a time bomb, it’s hard to stay festive even with Christmas so close.
And for those with beginning of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A personal look at psychological abuse
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-a-personal-look-at-psychological-abuse/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 18:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-a-personal-look-at-psychological-abuse/</guid>
        <description>Αt a friend’s house party last week I met a couple that brought back a few memories I had hoped to keep locked up, and now, huddled next to the radiator in my otherwise arctic flat, I try to write this for what seems like the hundredth time. I want to write about emotional abuse, its warning signs, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Self-help tips and tricks
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-17-self-help-tips-and-tricks/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 18:21:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chanon Wongsatayanont,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-17-self-help-tips-and-tricks/</guid>
        <description>Now that we’ve gone through some kinds of mental illnesses, it’s time we talk about how to deal with them.
Friends, families and therapists can really help but they can sometimes feel inaccessible, especially during the height of an episode.
You might have told your friends and family before and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Big worries about small problems
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-big-worries-about-small-problems/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 22:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Zahra Esbati,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-big-worries-about-small-problems/</guid>
        <description>After all my preaching about de-stigmatising mental illness, I think it’s about time I talked about my own experiences in the hopes that it will help at least one person who is currently suffering and feels like they’re alone. I have struggled with anxiety for as long as I can remember. It is no …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London: a survival guide for international students
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-london-a-survival-guide-for-international-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 21:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Chio,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-london-a-survival-guide-for-international-students/</guid>
        <description>Do you remember what it was like when you first arrived in London? Did you find it challenging to live in a foreign country or did you find it difficult to communicate with people in English?
From my experience, moving into a foreign country can be challenging. It is, no doubt, a valuable experience …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>When colours fade away
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-when-colours-fade-away/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 20:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chanon Wongsatayanont,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-when-colours-fade-away/</guid>
        <description>This week, let’s move on from anxiety to the more cheerful topic of depression. To the sufferers, it is the worst feeling in the world. But for those who have never experienced it, it is hard to truly understand how unpleasant or disruptive it is, so this article will try to explain how it feels. …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
