<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ratangor/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ratangor/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>BBC’s Blue Planet II – A natural masterpiece</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-19-bbc-s-blue-planet-ii-a-natural-masterpiece/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ratan Gor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-19-bbc-s-blue-planet-ii-a-natural-masterpiece/</guid>
        <description>The BBC’s nature documentary series Blue Planet II comes 16 years after the original ground-breaking programme arrived on our television screens. Narrated by none other than Sir David Attenborough, scored by the Academy Award winning composer Hans Zimmer, and using the latest in camera technology, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UK Party Conferences 2017: Corbyn is confident, May is choking, and Johnson is out for blood</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-uk-party-conferences-2017-corbyn-is-confident-may-is-choking-and-johnson-is-out-for-blood/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ratan Gor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-uk-party-conferences-2017-corbyn-is-confident-may-is-choking-and-johnson-is-out-for-blood/</guid>
        <description>Taking place each autumn, political party conferences are essentially like festivals where loyal groupies go en masse to cheer on their favourite stateswomen and men. Politicians take to the stage to discuss the current state of the party, set out their ambitions for the following year, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brexit: your wrap-up on all the issues you need to know</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-brexit-your-wrap-up-on-all-the-issues-you-need-to-know/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ratan Gor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-brexit-your-wrap-up-on-all-the-issues-you-need-to-know/</guid>
        <description>Brexit. With no background knowledge, the word seems innocuous enough – the latest breakfast cereal perhaps? However, this now-infamous word and all it represents have been the talk of the town for the past year and a half. This summer, you’ve used it to screen prospective suitors on a first date, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who are the DUP?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-who-are-the-dup/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:41:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ratan Gor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-who-are-the-dup/</guid>
        <description>Last week’s general election marked a momentous occasion. The youth, generally considered docile and apathetic when it comes to politics and voting, went out in their droves to flex their muscle. The main battleground for the election was social media. The weapons of choice: memes and parody videos …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
