<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Investment on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/investment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Investment on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/investment/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Are we Headed for a New DotCom Bubble?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-are-we-headed-for-new-dotcom-bubble/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marios Papadopoulos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-are-we-headed-for-new-dotcom-bubble/</guid>
        <description>Above: Fig 1. Looking at around the year 1999, the NASDAQ leaped from below 3000 to the peak of 5048.62. It has taken 15 years for the NASDAQ to recover to that high. Will history repeat itself?
The entry of the new millennium was accompanied by a major stock market crash caused by a bubble known as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Finance vs. Old Finance</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-new-finance-vs-old-finance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marios Papadopoulos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-new-finance-vs-old-finance/</guid>
        <description>Non-traditional banks, such as Revolut and Starling, among many others, have disrupted the banking industry. Banking had traditionally been a difficult sector for startups due to the regulations that dictated the establishment and operation of a bank. Following the 2008 financial crisis, regulatory …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Private Equity vs. Venture Capital:  A Closer Look</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-private-equity-vs-venture-capital-a-closer-look/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavan Singh Gill,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-private-equity-vs-venture-capital-a-closer-look/</guid>
        <description>Private equity and venture capital both refer to investments by individuals or firms/institutions in companies. However, the scale of the investment and the stage of companies they invest in differ.
Private equity
You can think of it as equity that is held privately, either by wealthy individuals or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why Asset Diversification &amp; Hedging is Necessary</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-why-asset-diversification-hedging-necessary/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eugene Gwan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-why-asset-diversification-hedging-necessary/</guid>
        <description>The old adage “Do not place all your eggs in one basket” is probably one of the most important things to remember when investing. It is easy for beginner investors to see gains in a particular stock and have the urge to allocate more of their funds into it, hoping to generate even higher absolute …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Asset Management: A Closer Look</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-asset-management-a-closer-look/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Igor Fomenkov,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-asset-management-a-closer-look/</guid>
        <description>Above: Figure 1: How the buy-side and sell-side bridge the gap between corporates and investors
With such a huge focus on the sell-side nowadays (both in terms of career opportunities as well as industry-related news), the other part of the global financial industry, the buy-side, is oftentimes …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Investment Banks: A Closer Look</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-investment-banks-closer-look/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavan Singh Gill,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-investment-banks-closer-look/</guid>
        <description>Above: Figure 1: Your friend who recently scored a full-time offer is buying the next round at the Union
What are Investment banks and why should you care? Investment banks are financial institutions that provide two main services; brokerage and corporate advisory.
Corporate advisory
There are three …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Brief Introduction to Derivatives</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-brief-introduction-to-derivatives/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jinay Patel,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-brief-introduction-to-derivatives/</guid>
        <description>If you’ve flicked past all of the puzzles and literally every other section to get to Investments, well then I know you’re probably a banker w*****. All jokes asides, if any of you have read more than 3 articles on FT or spoke to a Business School student for 5 minutes, you’ve probably heard of a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dollar, Euro, Sterling and All their Friends: The Foreign Exchange Market</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-dollar-euro-sterling-all-friends-foreign-exchange-market/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivan Parmar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-dollar-euro-sterling-all-friends-foreign-exchange-market/</guid>
        <description>The Foreign Exchange market (Forex or FX) is an over-the-counter market in currency-pairs which is the largest and most liquid market in the world. An average of $5.1 trillion is traded every day, compared to $84 billion traded daily in equities’ markets. Like how you might trade in sterling for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What are Cryptocurrencies and what is Happening in this Space?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-what-cryptocurrencies-happening-in-space/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Issa Bqain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-what-cryptocurrencies-happening-in-space/</guid>
        <description>Cryptocurrencies are digital assets which are intended to be used as a medium of exchange. Traditionally, the supply currency can be controlled by a central bank or the government, however this is not the case with cryptocurrencies. Within this system, the safety solely lies in the hands of parties …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Story of Pork Belly: Overview of the Commodities Market</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-story-pork-belly-overview-commodities-market/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vanessa Tang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-story-pork-belly-overview-commodities-market/</guid>
        <description>Above: Figure 1: The increasing demand for pork belly has led to large gyrations in prices
Pork bellies – yes, the pork that comes from the belly of a pig, was an iconic commodity for the futures market’s representation in pop-culture.
While it might be surprising that the financial market involves …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Equity and Bonds: Two Different Ways of Raising Capital</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-equity-bonds-two-different-ways-raising-capital/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marios Papadopoulos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-equity-bonds-two-different-ways-raising-capital/</guid>
        <description>Raising capital is essential to the long-term health of every company and organisation.
Fresh capital is required for hiring more personnel, investing in new technologies, and expanding operations, among other purposes.
Equity constitutes one way of raising the sum of money necessary. In general, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Money and Capital Markets</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-money-capital-markets/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eugene Gwan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-money-capital-markets/</guid>
        <description>To many of us, a market is where we visit to purchase groceries. However, in the financial application, a financial market is where a transfer of capital from the people who supply it, to the people who demand it takes place.
Financial markets play 3 important roles. Firstly, they play an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Has MiFID II demolished the research industry?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-has-mifid-ii-demolished-the-research-industry/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-has-mifid-ii-demolished-the-research-industry/</guid>
        <description>At the beginning of last year MiFID II was introduced to make the financial industry more transparent. One key aspect of this is the move from bundled to unbundled products brokerage firms provide. Previously, a fund manager buying a security through a broker would pay a hefty commission. This would …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Which sector will prevail in the current market?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-which-sector-will-prevail-in-the-current-market/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Koh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-which-sector-will-prevail-in-the-current-market/</guid>
        <description>In an economically uncertain environment subject to policy-driven volatility, the underperformers would be high beta stocks such as the technology sector. The friction and tension surrounding the US-China trade war uncertainty has dampened the forecasted earnings of technology companies such as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Educational: Performing Absolute Evaluation</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-educational-performing-absolute-evaluation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Koh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-educational-performing-absolute-evaluation/</guid>
        <description>Investors are typically faced with the question of how much a stock (equity) is worth. To answer this question, there are two ways to value equities. The first method involves the use of ratios and comparison with other equities – relative valuation and the second method involves the use of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Big Daddy Oil outearns Apple and Google, wants more</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-big-daddy-oil-outearns-apple-and-google-wants-more/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xerxes Chong Xian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-big-daddy-oil-outearns-apple-and-google-wants-more/</guid>
        <description>The month of April marked a historic moment for the financial markets. The Saudi Arabian Oil Company (Saudi Aramco) had its debut international bond issuance. A titan in the world of oil and gas, whose pulse is closely monitored by financial markets as a proxy to the health of one the world’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are Uber’s bankers getting cold feet? </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-are-uber-s-bankers-getting-cold-feet/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-are-uber-s-bankers-getting-cold-feet/</guid>
        <description>The ride haling app has lowered its expectations from a rumoured IPO valuation of around $100 billion to between $80-90 billion. This would still be the largest public offering from Silicon Valley since Facebook, with the company pitching an initial price range of $44 to $55, even as many other …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Educational: Monetary and Fiscal Policy </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-01-educational-monetary-and-fiscal-policy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-01-educational-monetary-and-fiscal-policy/</guid>
        <description>Monetary and Fiscal Policy are the two most widely used tools governments and central banks use to control a nation’s economy. You may have read in FT about how the Federal Reserve, the US Central Bank has become “dovish”, due to its overly “hawkish” stance last year due to Trump’s fiscal policy. In …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An insight into consumer goods equities...</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-an-insight-into-consumer-goods-equities/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Megan Chen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-an-insight-into-consumer-goods-equities/</guid>
        <description>CG stocks tend to be low-innovation, mature companies that rely on big brands and timeless products and pay regular dividends. As defensive stocks, CG stocks are more likely to outperform in bear markets than in bull markets. In recent years, CG stocks have widely underperformed in the broader …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Do emerging markets matter?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-do-emerging-markets-matter/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Serkan Chakar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-do-emerging-markets-matter/</guid>
        <description>Globally, of all new bridges opened in the last five years, 50% was built in China. Chinese investment has also funded numerous engineering projects in Europe; from an engineering standpoint, China matters deeply. If your ambition is to design a bridge in the next ten years, work from Shanghai! At …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What are derivatives and how are they used? </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-what-are-derivatives-and-how-are-they-used/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-what-are-derivatives-and-how-are-they-used/</guid>
        <description>Warren Buffet has described them as “financial weapons of mass destruction”. Robert Kiyosaki said that the subprime Morgage Backed Security (MBS) disaster was a result of them “exploding in financial institutions such as AIG and Lehman Brothers”. So, what exactly are derivatives?
A derivative is a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sovereign debt: a tale of two dilemma’s</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-sovereign-debt-a-tale-of-two-dilemma-s/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-sovereign-debt-a-tale-of-two-dilemma-s/</guid>
        <description>At the beginning of the month, Beth Hammack, a senior Goldman Sachs banker and chair of the government advisory group know as the Treasury Bond Advisory Committee sent a letter to Steven Mnuchin, Treasury Secretary, warning that according to TBAC calculations, America will need to sell $12 trillion …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Debt and Equity: 2 sides of the same coin</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-debt-and-equity-2-sides-of-the-same-coin/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xerxes Chong Xian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-debt-and-equity-2-sides-of-the-same-coin/</guid>
        <description>Just as a plant needs water for growth, so does a business require capital to expand. Debt and equity are two sides of the same coin. A company may choose to finance itself with debt or equity or a combination of the two. The company approaches banks or investors for a loan and/or to sell a stake of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Insight into ETFs - The Future of Investing </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-an-insight-into-etfs-the-future-of-investing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Koh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-an-insight-into-etfs-the-future-of-investing/</guid>
        <description>Index funds refer to a mutual fund or Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) that track a specified basket of underlying securities (tradable financial assets). Moreover, ETFs are becoming an increasingly popular investment vehicle amongst both retail and institutional investors. More than 4,500 ETFs managed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Impact Investing in Africa</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-impact-investing-in-africa/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dike Dijemeni,Esuabom Dijemeni,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-impact-investing-in-africa/</guid>
        <description>According to The Global Impact Investing Network (GIIN), impact investment can be defined as investment made into companies, organisations, and funds with the intention to generate social and environmental impact alongside a financial return. Hence, impact investing in Africa is the deployment of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Electronic and Algorithmic Trading: Fixed Income Securities</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-electronic-and-algorithmic-trading-fixed-income-securities/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dike Dijemeni,Esuabom Dijemeni,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-electronic-and-algorithmic-trading-fixed-income-securities/</guid>
        <description>Electronic trading has become an increasingly important part of the fixed income market landscape in recent years. The rise of electronic trading has enabled a pickup of automated trading (including algorithmic and high-frequency trading) in fixed income futures and parts of cash bond markets. These …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Spy Who Went Public: Aston Martin lists on LSE</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-the-spy-who-went-public-aston-martin-lists-on-lse/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xerxes Chong Xian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-the-spy-who-went-public-aston-martin-lists-on-lse/</guid>
        <description>On 3rd October 2018, the iconic British marque synonymous with James Bond debuted on the London Stock Exchange, a milestone for the historically troubled carmaker, with a past marred by several bankruptcies. The shares were priced at £19, valuing the company at £4.3bn. While most IPOs are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Will the dollar determine markets in 2019?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-will-the-dollar-determine-markets-in-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-will-the-dollar-determine-markets-in-2019/</guid>
        <description>After a volatile end to 2018, investors are now looking at what the new year can bring. Despite rising 7% against a broad basket of currencies in 2018, many now deem the dollar overvalued. Drawing parallels from both physics and Forex trading, it is well known that whatever goes up must eventually …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bond Curve Yield Inversion </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-bond-curve-yield-inversion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Koh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-bond-curve-yield-inversion/</guid>
        <description>Yield curve inversions have traditionally been a foretelling sign of impending recessions. To explain the idea of a yield curve, one needs to understand what exactly a yield is. A yield to maturity, or simply bond yield has multiple interpretation, the simplest being – it is the return an investor …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Risk in Investment Management and Financial Services    Part 1 :Credit Risk</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-risk-in-investment-management-and-financial-services-part-1-credit-risk/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Esuabom Dijemeni,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-risk-in-investment-management-and-financial-services-part-1-credit-risk/</guid>
        <description>The objective of this series, Risk in Investment Management and Financial Services, is to provide a top-level introduction to risk in investment management and financial services. A broader and wider understanding of different types of risk faced in investment management and financial services is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Valuation of Medical Technology Start-Ups</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-valuation-of-medical-technology-start-ups/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dike Dijemeni,Esuabom Dijemeni,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-valuation-of-medical-technology-start-ups/</guid>
        <description>In the past, industry specific start-up “rules of thumb” may have been sufficient to serve as reasonable basis for any valuation concern. Combined with the unique market dynamics and regulatory environment associated with the medical technology industry, start-ups in this field present a unique set …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Scandals raises questions over Goldman Conduct</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-scandals-raises-questions-over-goldman-conduct/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-scandals-raises-questions-over-goldman-conduct/</guid>
        <description>Back in 2010, Goldman Sachs was sued by the US Securities and Exchange Commission over allegations that it had misled clients over the mortgage backed securities it had sold. Internal Goldman emails surfaced showing how arrogant self-interest bankers had left their clients out in the cold to save …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tech sell-off leads to market slump</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-tech-sell-off-leads-to-market-slump/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-tech-sell-off-leads-to-market-slump/</guid>
        <description>Turbulence in the global financial markets, particularly in the technology sector, saw equity sell offs, oil prices tumble, and dollar swings this week as concerns over the global economy intensified as investors fear growing trade tensions and weak corporate earnings. FAANG stocks, which had …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Crude oil enters bear market</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-crude-oil-enters-bear-market/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-crude-oil-enters-bear-market/</guid>
        <description>US crude oil prices entered a bear market [defined as a 20% drop from a recent high] on Thursday as concerns of tight global supplies eased. This follows Washington allowing eight countries to continue buying Iranian crude, softening the blow of new international sanctions on the nation. In addition …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why share buy backs are big on wall street now</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-why-share-buy-backs-are-big-on-wall-street-now/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Davide Vaccaro,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-why-share-buy-backs-are-big-on-wall-street-now/</guid>
        <description>The Economist has called them “an addiction to corporate cocaine.” Reuters has called them “self-cannibalization.” The Financial Times has called them “an overwhelming conflict of interest.” In an article that won the HBR McKinsey Award for the best article of the year, Harvard Business Review has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dark Pools: Evil place or a market place?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-dark-pools-evil-place-or-a-market-place/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xerxes Chong Xian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-dark-pools-evil-place-or-a-market-place/</guid>
        <description>Dark pools. The words invoke an atmosphere of secrecy and evil, harkening back to myths of murky waters and ancient terrors that lurk within. Throw in the modern element of trading and most imagine clandestine deals involving dubious characters straight out of The Godfather. The reality is less …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ESG investing, is it really worth it?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-esg-investing-is-it-really-worth-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-esg-investing-is-it-really-worth-it/</guid>
        <description>Global Warming. Corruption. War. Poverty. These are all problems every human on the face of the earth must deal with, and it is something everyone should be tackling. The financial industry has decided to combat these problems with Environmental, Social and Governance (ESG) Investing. It is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>From bad to worse for Puma Biotechnology</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-from-bad-to-worse-for-puma-biotechnology/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Peter Green,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-from-bad-to-worse-for-puma-biotechnology/</guid>
        <description>If you want a good example of how volatile biotechnology stocks can be, look no further than Puma Biotechnology Inc. This cancer-focused biotechnology company was founded 8 years ago and went public in 2012 with shares trading around $10 per share. In 2014 that share price rocketed to +$260 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Investment banks relish in hawkish environment</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-investment-banks-relish-in-hawkish-environment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-investment-banks-relish-in-hawkish-environment/</guid>
        <description>It is a well-known fact that when interest rates are hiked, investment banks increase their profitability due to their massive cash holdings. Increasing the interest rates directly increases the yield on the cash it holds, and the proceeds go directly into the income statement. Furthermore, interest …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rising Fed rates puts pressure on markets</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-rising-fed-rates-puts-pressure-on-markets/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-rising-fed-rates-puts-pressure-on-markets/</guid>
        <description>Since the fiscal stimulus of tax cuts that the Trump administration has implemented this year, the US economy on the surface has been doing great. It has notched a 4.1% annualized growth rate for Q2, which is considerably faster than the 2% growth rate that has been standard since 2001. Then in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Country’s Piggy Bank</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-a-country-s-piggy-bank/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xerxes Chong Xian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-a-country-s-piggy-bank/</guid>
        <description>We’ve all heard the age-old advice; save up for a rainy day, spend a little less, invest that money and have enough to retire. Your favourite car, that house in the countryside, that trip to the Maldives you’ve been planning since the days of eating lunch at your desk. The message is clear, invest …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Rise of Private Equity</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-the-rise-of-private-equity/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-the-rise-of-private-equity/</guid>
        <description>Before the financial crisis, private equity investors followed closely the “buyout” manual pioneered by Henry Kravis and George Roberts when they founded the firm KKR in the 1970’s. Essentially, they would acquire companies whole, then they would cut costs and load them with low interest rate debt. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Venture Capital &amp; Startups in Southeast Asia</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-venture-capital-startups-in-southeast-asia/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ryan Tham Ju Rong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-venture-capital-startups-in-southeast-asia/</guid>
        <description>As venture capital ecosystems go, Silicon Valley, Europe and China can be considered mature VC economies. Hence it makes sense for a VC firm to proceed to more underdeveloped, underserved markets to unearth and polish hidden gems that may, given time and guidance grow into the next Facebook or Uber. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Commercial Cannabis: Bitcoin Bubble?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-commercial-cannabis-bitcoin-bubble/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Alston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-commercial-cannabis-bitcoin-bubble/</guid>
        <description>On Tuesday 18th September, the US Drug Enforcement Agency gave the Canadian cannabis producer Tilray permission to export its cannabis to the United States for medical research. The next day Tilray Inc. shares were halted five times from trading in less than one hour as the market neared its close. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>U.S. Yield Curve Analysis </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-u-s-yield-curve-analysis/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pierre Moutounet-Cartan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-u-s-yield-curve-analysis/</guid>
        <description>A new analysis predicts that the U.S. Treasury two-year bond yield is set to overcome the U.S. Treasury ten-year bond yield between the beginning of November 2018 and the end of January 2019 - most likely in December 2018.
This analysis suggests that, with a 95% confidence interval using …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
