<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rnt11/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rnt11/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS album of the week: Alcest – Shelter
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-ams-album-of-the-week-alcest-shelter/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Robin N Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-ams-album-of-the-week-alcest-shelter/</guid>
        <description>Black metal has undoubtedly seen regeneration in recent years. Releases such as Deafheaven’s_ Sunbather _or Altar of Plagues’ Teethed Glory and Injury in 2013 were well received, provided you were looking for challenging music with power behind it. However, you’d be mistaken if it was purely “good …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS album of the week 20
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-ams-album-of-the-week-20/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 22:18:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Robin N Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-ams-album-of-the-week-20/</guid>
        <description>Ensemble Pearl is a thoroughly dark album featuring some big names in modern avant-garde metal. Steve O’Malley of Sunn O))) is the best known, but two members of Boris, the Japanese noise rock band, are also present (drummer Atsuo and live guitarist Michio Kurihara). Former bassist of Jesse Sykes …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS album of the Week 18
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-8-ams-album-of-the-week-18/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 20:12:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Robin N Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-8-ams-album-of-the-week-18/</guid>
        <description>Suspiciously named and sensibly abbreviated, ASIWYFA are a 4 piece who play instrumental rock. Their sound is probably best summarised by the title of their best known track, “Set Guitars To Kill” - hyperactive arena rock made to be heard from so close to the band that you can feel splinters flying …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS album of the Week 7
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-30-ams-album-of-the-week-7/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 13:32:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Robin N Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-30-ams-album-of-the-week-7/</guid>
        <description>You need a good reason to pay attention to an alternative rock band releasing their 7th album. Since their magnum opus, White Pony, Deftones have become a household name in making “straight forward” rock songs something bigger. They’re heavy, catchy, and they know just how to structure a good song – …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A realistic take on roguelikes
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-a-realistic-take-on-roguelikes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 16:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Robin N Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-a-realistic-take-on-roguelikes/</guid>
        <description>A popular mod on the PC gaming scene, as many of us will know, is DayZ, where you get one shot at survival on an island covered with zombies. It’s hailed for finally getting “survival” right, with atmosphere, realism and difficulty – and it’s the difficulty that interests me.
Games have been getting …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
