<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/disha_bandyopadhyay/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/disha_bandyopadhyay/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Dogfight</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-dogfight-when-camaraderie-and-debauchery-are-confused/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Disha Bandyopadhyay,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-dogfight-when-camaraderie-and-debauchery-are-confused/</guid>
        <description>It is intriguing how a musical with such a fierce name can be so gentle and sensitive. Amidst the brash soldiers and their swearing, Dogfight shines light on the importance of not being judgmental and accepting each others’ differences to work together. Dogfight, in a youth production by the British …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cinderella: sculpture of a fleeting magical moment</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-cinderella-sculpture-of-a-fleeting-magical-moment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Disha Bandyopadhyay,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-cinderella-sculpture-of-a-fleeting-magical-moment/</guid>
        <description>Christopher Weeldon creates magic right next to Imperial’s main campus at the Royal Albert Hall, in Cinderella, performed by the English National Ballet Philharmonic. A retelling of the Brothers Grimm fairy-tale, over ninety dancers and a live orchestra unfold a dream-like sequence with resplendent …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>INALA – Abundance of goodwill</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-inala-abundance-of-goodwill/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Disha Bandyopadhyay,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-inala-abundance-of-goodwill/</guid>
        <description>INALA is a fusion dance performance of Zulu ballet set to Zulu songs sung by the Soweto Gospel Choir, accompanied by western instrumentation. It celebrates the value of community and even the most mundane activities from the passage of life. Choreographed by Mark Baldwin, the show is about unity in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Great Gatsby: An Immersive Experience</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-the-great-gatsby-an-immersive-experience/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Disha Bandyopadhyay,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-the-great-gatsby-an-immersive-experience/</guid>
        <description>Not to brag, but I was seated personally by Jay Gatsby himself.
The Great Gatsby is a tragedy written by F. Scott Fitzgerald set in 1920s America where the wealthy squander their money, behaving recklessly, loving foolishly. The story centres around love triangles between a mysterious Jay Gatsby and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Way down, Hadestown: a story of love, loss and wonder</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-way-down-hadestown-a-story-of-love-loss-and-wonder/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Disha Bandyopadhyay,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-way-down-hadestown-a-story-of-love-loss-and-wonder/</guid>
        <description>Lights went off as soon as I took my seat. Jazzy Hermes filled the stage with snappy tunes and energy. He introduced Eurydice, Orpheus and the inevitable tragedy waiting to happen in Hadestown , the realm of Hades. A Greek myth transported to a post-apocalyptic Great Depression era setting, …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
