<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ykc111/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ykc111/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>“It’s time for you to get involved” – Student Volunteering Week 2015
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-20-its-time-for-you-to-get-involved-student-volunteering-week-2015/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 00:29:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Y K Chung,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-20-its-time-for-you-to-get-involved-student-volunteering-week-2015/</guid>
        <description>“Hiya! Do you have a few moments to volunteer for a good cause?“ “Ah sorry I’m in a hurry” This dialogue has occurred in the JCR for too long. And as students, who are stereotypically drunk 24&amp;frasl;7, it is time for us to stand up and change public perceptions.
The National Student Volunteering …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A few of our favourite things... - Mike&#39;s Take
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-2-a-few-of-our-favourite-things-mikes-take/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 13:12:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Y K Chung,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-2-a-few-of-our-favourite-things-mikes-take/</guid>
        <description> Okay, it’s not winter - but summer term is still a high-stress term here in Imperial, we’ll grant you that. Everyone’s got their own comfort foods/snacks (season be damned), favourite eateries, kitchen gadgets they’re biased towards. Even us as Food editors - we’re not going to pretend we don’t …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Future of urban agriculture?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-16-future-of-urban-agriculture/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 02:11:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Y K Chung,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-16-future-of-urban-agriculture/</guid>
        <description> Space is an issue in a metropolis like London. Roads crowded with cars and pedestrians, with more and more skyscrapers popping up around the capital. As the population in the UK grows, estimated around 70 million by 2028 - many of whom will be living in and around the capital and the major cities, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This week’s food for thought
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-this-weeks-food-for-thought/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 15:43:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Y K Chung,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-this-weeks-food-for-thought/</guid>
        <description>Procrastinating from work, I found myself looking at my Instagram stream, and I was quite surprised how many photos of food I had in my history. I’ve got to admit, not everything looked amazing, be it the colour reproduction of my phone (curry is not the most pleasant-looking dish ever), or just the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Examin-cake-sion
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-examin-cake-sion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 15:39:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Y K Chung,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-examin-cake-sion/</guid>
        <description>Who doesn’t like cake? Even Latvia’s entry to this year’s Eurovision was all about this sweet, fluffy and tasty food! It is a wide misconception to think cakes are hard to bake and it takes up a long time. But we are here to prove that wrong.
Yes, baking a beautiful cake might take patience and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bored of your meals?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-bored-of-your-meals/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 14:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Y K Chung,Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-bored-of-your-meals/</guid>
        <description> As students, our food budgets might be limited, but this does not mean our diets are boring! Eating out or ordering takeaway is neither cheap nor healthy most of the time, but not only can you control the cost and what goes into your food when you cook yourself, we guarantee you will find it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Keep Calm And Eat Chips
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-keep-calm-and-eat-chips/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 03:34:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Y K Chung,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-keep-calm-and-eat-chips/</guid>
        <description>Oh chips, glorious chips. The humble deep fried potato strips have been one of the most accessible and consumed foods across the world. It also provides a great subject for banter when stealing your friends’ chips becomes the top priority in the pub. As we near the end of the National Chip Week, it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where to go for a Taste of China
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-where-to-go-for-a-taste-of-china/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 04:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Y K Chung,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-where-to-go-for-a-taste-of-china/</guid>
        <description>If easy home cooking is not really for you, then you’re blessed that we are in one of the most culturally diversed cities in the world, but Chinatown is not your only option either! SCR &amp;amp; QTR
TasteImperial is serving Chinese specialities at their outlets on Friday. In SCR, the classic five spice …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>(Chinese New) Year of the Horse is here
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-chinese-new-year-of-the-horse-is-here/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 04:47:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Y K Chung,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-chinese-new-year-of-the-horse-is-here/</guid>
        <description>Kung Hei Fat Choi! The year of the horse has once again arrived and if you feel like having something festive, but find Chopstix slightly too greasy, here’s a healthy recipe for you! If people tell you Chinese food is hard to cook, they are lying to you. There is an Chinese idiom “People rank food …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are you drinking it right?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-are-you-drinking-it-right/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 11:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Y K Chung,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-are-you-drinking-it-right/</guid>
        <description>The coursework season has descended at Imperial - many of us are spending endless hours at the library. No matter if you are writing up your research project on rotor stator disk rim sealing, a model of the thermal structure of the North American lithosphere, or an essay answering the question “What …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Feed Yourself, Not Your Bin
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-feed-yourself-not-your-bin/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 01:04:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Y K Chung,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-feed-yourself-not-your-bin/</guid>
        <description>How much food do we throw away? Well, a quick survey in the EEE Level 5 labs shows that as students, we try to eat everything we buy in our shop. Unfortunately students only make up about 4% of the UK population, and Tesco has revealed earlier this week that it generated almost 30,000 tonnes of food …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The self-catering cheatsheet
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-the-self-catering-cheatsheet/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 19:55:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Y K Chung,Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-the-self-catering-cheatsheet/</guid>
        <description>Understandably everyone reading this article will have a different view or preference/budget when it comes to eating or food shopping. Even within Carol’s household, the boys prefer to bag everything from Sainsbury’s (everything’s in one location), whereas she doesn’t mind scouring the North End …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Emergency hangover cures
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-emergency-hangover-cures/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 15:39:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Y K Chung,Felix Food,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-emergency-hangover-cures/</guid>
        <description> Need something quick? Beans on toast with a twist The classic beans on toast is an awesome hangover cure. Not only do the beans contain high protein, it also releases energy slowly, so you feel better for the day! If you want to increase your appetite at the same time, why not add a can of tinned …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
