<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ohb09/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ohb09/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Oli Benton responds to &#34;Dri Night&#39;s Coverage does not whet the appetite&#34;
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-24-oli-benton-responds-to-dri-nights-coverage-does-not-whet-the-appetite/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2014 13:57:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Oliver Benton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-24-oli-benton-responds-to-dri-nights-coverage-does-not-whet-the-appetite/</guid>
        <description>Thanks for the response; I’m glad at least somebody, other than the Union staff and Sabbs that ‘checked over it’, actually read the article.
I feel that the article may have been slightly misinterpreted. While I can, but won’t, apologise for the puns that littered it, I do not feel that it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fire Alarm interrupts bar night again
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-24-fire-alarm-interrupts-bar-night-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2014 12:48:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Oliver Benton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-24-fire-alarm-interrupts-bar-night-again/</guid>
        <description>Hundreds of graduate students were looking forward to enjoying one last hurrah treading the sticky floors of Metric only for their revelry to be cut short by fire alarms and the early closing of the bars.
For the second time in two weeks the fire alarm forced people to leave the Union buildings. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Heston opens as the new home of sport
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-17-heston-opens-as-the-new-home-of-sport/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 15:12:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Oliver Benton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-17-heston-opens-as-the-new-home-of-sport/</guid>
        <description>Heston, the new home of Medic sport, was unveiled on Wednesday the 15th of October, to a nibbles and ‘BUCS’ fizz reception. Debra Humphris, Vice Provost (Education), launched the day with a short speech commenting on the “continued evolution of our sports facilities” and the revealing of a plaque …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lesson learnt: Never go in Dri
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-17-lesson-learnt-never-go-in-dri/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 15:07:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Oliver Benton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-17-lesson-learnt-never-go-in-dri/</guid>
        <description>The Union held its first ever alcohol free club night – “Dri” on Monday 13th. Unlucky for some; most likely the bar manager’s profit margins, and anyone who turned up. A full complement of security staff were on hand to deal with the rowdy non-crowd of non-drinkers, and with lime soda priced at 20p …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Uncommunicative University
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-uncommunicative-university/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 23:49:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Oliver Benton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-uncommunicative-university/</guid>
        <description>I wrote an article last month about how Imperial College is run like a business. This business doesn’t have the interests of the students or its academics at heart. The week after my article, a letter from Ian Howgate, hockey player and former Imperial College Union President, followed up on this. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An uncaring university
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-7-an-uncaring-university/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2013 19:17:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Oliver Benton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-7-an-uncaring-university/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College doesn’t care about its students and there’s nothing we can do to change it. The Sabbs are generally powerless and many of the Union’s decisions don’t seem to have our best interests at heart.
Much like a certain yeasty (and delicious) sandwich filling, those statements will either …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Netball’s season: highs lows and Funday!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-netballs-season-highs-lows-and-funday/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 22:07:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Oliver Benton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-netballs-season-highs-lows-and-funday/</guid>
        <description>Passionate about her sport, Nancy has led the netball club from strength to strength this year; with increased membership, more socials and coming so close to promotion. Despite the difficulties of a plague of injuries and sponsorship woes, ICUNC has had a good year even with potential wins at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC Rugby 1s Pipped to the post
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-ic-rugby-1s-pipped-to-the-post/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 00:26:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Oliver Benton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-ic-rugby-1s-pipped-to-the-post/</guid>
        <description>On a balmy Wednesday afternoon, ICURFC travelled to the all weather pitch at Maidenhead RFC for a double header match against Reading Uni.
Top of the league Reading were always going to be a tough physical match, and playing it on the plastic grass pitch was only going to add to the drama and pace …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
