<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/asad_raja/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/asad_raja/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Hip Hop: The Genre Of The Decade</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-hiphop-genre-of-decade/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-hiphop-genre-of-decade/</guid>
        <description>Undeniably, hip hop dominated this decade, having established itself as one of the most diverse yet hereditary forced in modern culutre. I asked Hip Hop Soc members to pick their top 20 albums of the decade. This pretty banging consensus list is the result:
20. Barter 6 - Young Thug (2015)
19. 4:44 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Top 10 Rap Albums of 2019</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-top-10-rap-albums-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-top-10-rap-albums-2019/</guid>
        <description>Straight up: the UK killed it this year. We’ve finally reached a point where the best outputs of the rap scene at home is legitimately comparable to the best of the US’s. Asides from the four banging albums that make this top 10 list, this year saw the release of great UK projects like Kojey …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Interview with Imperial’s very own Roy Juxon </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-interview-imperials-own-roy-juxon/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-interview-imperials-own-roy-juxon/</guid>
        <description>Felix: So when did this all start?
RJ: Still pretty recently actually. I only really got into it during my gap year. That’s when I did my Walland Hill EP, just before going travelling. But I hadn’t really done any music until January this year.
Felix: Really? Ever?
RJ: So, I used to produce drum and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Distortion of Orientalist Art</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-distortion-orientalist-art/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-distortion-orientalist-art/</guid>
        <description>2 stars
This tone is set by the very first piece in the exhibition, the Prayer. This painting by Frederick Arthur Bridgman, is supposed to capture two individuals in a mosque, engaged in the act of prayer (salat). The subject in the foreground stands with both hands outstretched at his sides, face …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Father of 4 does not Offset Migos’s solo album efforts</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-father-of-4-does-not-offset-migos-s-solo-album-efforts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-father-of-4-does-not-offset-migos-s-solo-album-efforts/</guid>
        <description>For the more devout Migos fans, and for Atlanta locals, Offset has consistently been seen as the stand out member, despite Quavo clearly becoming established as the head of the group since their mainstream breakthrough. More recently, Offset has experienced more widespread attention for reasons …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Psychodrama Review</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-psychodrama-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,Simran Kukran,Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-psychodrama-review/</guid>
        <description>1. Psycho
What a way to kick off the album. A truly building track, Dave and the instrumentation become one as the listener is guided through the three main psyches that Dave will expand on throughout the album. Not only does he switch up his flow, content and delivery with each transition, but he …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The wicked WIZRD of Sauce</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-the-wicked-wizrd-of-sauce/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-the-wicked-wizrd-of-sauce/</guid>
        <description>Future has always been a hit-making machine. Earlier in his career he adopted (and simultaneously established) a decidedly pimpish Atlanta trapper sound. Since then, Future has achieved ridiculous international recognition, the DJ Eskimo tags long gone. What set him apart from a Wacka Flaka or a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Riz Ahmed Is Synonymous With Brown Excellence</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-riz-ahmed-is-synonymous-with-brown-excellence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-riz-ahmed-is-synonymous-with-brown-excellence/</guid>
        <description>If you’re brown, woke (shut the fuck up it’s a meme to be woke) or from London, and especially if you’re all three, chances are you know Riz Ahmed to be a Desi messiah. Riz began his trajectory towards this status after appearing in 2010’s Four Lions, a now cult classic comedy following the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>With a new Chance the Rapper project supposedly on the way, let us revisit his iconic Acid Rap  mixtape</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-with-a-new-chance-the-rapper-project-supposedly-on-the-way-let-us-revisit-his-iconic-acid-rap-mixtape/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-with-a-new-chance-the-rapper-project-supposedly-on-the-way-let-us-revisit-his-iconic-acid-rap-mixtape/</guid>
        <description>In 2016, we witnessed Chance the Rapper’s spiritual rebirth as “lil Chano from 79th” on the prophetic ‘Ultralight Beam’; a moment that would formally introduce a more sober, sweet as Sunday Candy, family man of a gospel-rapper-Chano, who the mainstream would come to adore following the release of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to the pleasuredome</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-welcome-to-the-pleasuredome/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,Henry Eshbaugh,Asad Raja,Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-welcome-to-the-pleasuredome/</guid>
        <description>My friend Kunal from Singapore calls me the grime guy. I like the way that sounds so I don’t correct him. In truth, as far as grime or UK rap goes, I consider myself a semi-casual listener (you won’t catch me listening to anyone less niche than, like, Ghetts). Though I stay open to most genres, US …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>While you were away...</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-while-you-were-away/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,Henry Eshbaugh,Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-while-you-were-away/</guid>
        <description>Family of Aliens
The third full-length effort by this indie pop quartet packs all the wholesome family-friendly goodness that fans have come to expect, but not without a wicked sense of humour and a quirky, sci-fi inflected glaze. A new crisply produced electronic vibe replaces their traditionally …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kids See Ghosts is a return to form for Kanye West</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-kids-see-ghosts-is-a-return-to-form-for-kanye-west/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-kids-see-ghosts-is-a-return-to-form-for-kanye-west/</guid>
        <description>This self-titled release marks the first collaboration project from hip hop’s biggest contemporary influencers, Kid Cudi and Kanye West, who have dubbed themselves Kids See Ghosts. This moniker and album title, as well as the album art, which was the work of Takashi Murakami (who has previously …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>King Push reigns supreme on DAYTONA</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-king-push-reigns-supreme-on-daytona/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-king-push-reigns-supreme-on-daytona/</guid>
        <description>Pusha T is one of the few prominent rappers from the first decade of the 2000s to side-step any waning in his relevance since then. He’s achieved what a Lupe Fiasco or a 50 Cent were not able to by inhabiting a space somewhere in between – he raps about a street lifestyle with a heavily lyrical …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Naked, honest, and mildly disappointing</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-naked-honest-and-mildly-disappointing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-naked-honest-and-mildly-disappointing/</guid>
        <description>Three things I would like to clarify before I begin this review: I am a Kanye stan (albeit a realistic one); this album has grown on me immensely since my first listen; and I have decided to take everything on this album, especially the comments on mental health, as genuine. That’s not to say I’m …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ten projects from the past year that prove we still haven’t reached peak trap just quite yet</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-ten-projects-from-the-past-year-that-prove-we-still-haven-t-reached-peak-trap-just-quite-yet/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-ten-projects-from-the-past-year-that-prove-we-still-haven-t-reached-peak-trap-just-quite-yet/</guid>
        <description>Today’s release of Migos’ Culture II marks the start of, what will hopefully be, another year of refreshing and inventive mainstream trap projects. Last year was very content heavy for the genre, yielding more than a few projects that provided optimism in the sound’s longevity and continued …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
