<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/er208/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/er208/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Bank Holiday Boat BUCS
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-bank-holiday-boat-bucs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 16:46:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elizabeth Richards,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-bank-holiday-boat-bucs/</guid>
        <description>The annual three day BUCS regatta at Nottingham’s Holme Pierrepont is usually a test of endurance, both physical and mental, and this year was no exception. With competitors entered in multiple events on a single day and with weather ranging from pouring rain to brilliant sunshine, ICBC was put …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Blades of glory: a successful term for IC rowers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-blades-of-glory-a-successful-term-for-ic-rowers/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 20:37:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elizabeth Richards,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-blades-of-glory-a-successful-term-for-ic-rowers/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Boat Club has started the academic year with some incredible results. From the outset, Imperial students, both past and present, have shown strength in depth across the men’s and women’s squads and brought home the silverware to prove it.
The first race of the season was Pairs’ Head …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Boat Club bring in 111 BUCS points
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-boat-club-bring-in-111-bucs-points/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 20:06:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elizabeth Richards,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-boat-club-bring-in-111-bucs-points/</guid>
        <description>The River Nene has been kind to Imperial College Boat Club (ICBC) on occasions, and this year’s BUCS 4s and 8s Head was one of those as success after success was had over the weekend. Every crew entered were in the top ten of their event, 111 BUCS points were won from the club’s performance in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Injury and illness stalks rowing club at trials
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-injury-and-illness-stalks-rowing-club-at-trials/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 18:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elizabeth Richards,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-injury-and-illness-stalks-rowing-club-at-trials/</guid>
        <description>Last weekend, after the long four hour drive through the wind and rain from London to Boston, Lincolnshire (a mere 22 miles from the awesome seaside resort of Skegness), several of the Imperial College Boat Club (ICBC) contingent wondered “What the hell are we doing here?”; the answer – the GB …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
