<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/wsp10/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/wsp10/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Scrabble World Championships 2014: Grudge Match Against an 8 year-old
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-scrabble-world-championships-2014-grudge-match-against-an-8-year-old/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 13:05:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-scrabble-world-championships-2014-grudge-match-against-an-8-year-old/</guid>
        <description>Away from the top of the leader board, one of the most notable players here at tournament is New Zealand’s Lewis Hawkins. What sets him out from the rest of the crowd is that, being aged 8, he’s at least a decade younger than anyone else here. Learning from my failures in adopting the direct …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Scrabble World Championships: Prince Goes To Prague
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-scrabble-world-championships-prince-goes-to-prague/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 13:02:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-scrabble-world-championships-prince-goes-to-prague/</guid>
        <description>Prince goes to Prague
On December 6th at around midday, at least 55 games were taking place at the SCRABBLE Champions’ Tournament in Prague. 110 players from across the globe had convened in Prague for a tilt at the title of SCRABBLE World Champion and a share of the €25,000 prize pot. Players from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>50 Shades of Gre(noble)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-50-shades-of-grenoble/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 22:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-50-shades-of-grenoble/</guid>
        <description>It must be about midnight and I’m sitting on a sun lounger in a dress I bought from a supermarket several hours earlier with a puffer-jacket-clad security guard checking I don’t try and introduce myself to the pool. Luckily I’ve already learnt my lesson in this department, having tried to introduce …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Not for standing awkwardly in the corner
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-not-for-standing-awkwardly-in-the-corner/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 19:12:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-not-for-standing-awkwardly-in-the-corner/</guid>
        <description>One of the few enduring life lessons I learnt during my time in halls is that some guilty pleasures are more acceptable than others. Even in the relatively tolerant enclave of Imperial College, pulling an all-nighter in the kitchen with your mates playing StarCraft until dawn will still draw some …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Spilling all the beans
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-spilling-all-the-beans/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 19:41:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-spilling-all-the-beans/</guid>
        <description>I’m sat on a couch at The Beans Group head office, waiting to interview its founder, James Eder. I’ve been there only a matter of seconds and I’m already finding myself forced to adjust my expectations. The mental images evoked by the word ‘office’ certainly weren’t matching the scenes before my …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Go Hajj or Go Home
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-go-hajj-or-go-home/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 10:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-go-hajj-or-go-home/</guid>
        <description>I’d always thought writing opening paragraphs was hard. But no editorial challenge that faces us, here in the Felix office, comes anywhere close to the mammoth task taken on by the British Museum (or, more truthfully, by curator Venetia Porter) in its latest exhibition, Hajj: Journey to the Heart of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In the tweet of the moment
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-in-the-tweet-of-the-moment/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 21:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-in-the-tweet-of-the-moment/</guid>
        <description>Beyond being an interminable stream of the thoughts of Lethal Bizzle, Twitter for this reviewer had always been just another tool for procrastination. In 2006, many of the angel investors running their rule over the nascent microblogging site figured the same. To have said to them then that tweets …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A brave new molecular world
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-a-brave-new-molecular-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 20:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-a-brave-new-molecular-world/</guid>
        <description>Professor David Phillips, current president of the Royal Society of Chemistry, took to the lectern on November 8 for the latest Friends of Imperial College (FOIC) event.
In line with FOIC’s celebrations of the UN Year of Chemistry, the Imperial professor emeritus guided the audience with an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wraith the roof with DramSoc
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-wraith-the-roof-with-dramsoc/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 20:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-wraith-the-roof-with-dramsoc/</guid>
        <description>It’s been nearly eight years to the day since the final installment of the Lord of the Rings trilogy hit our screens - eight long years with little but over-sexed vampires and under-sexed boy wizards to fill the void. Clearly spotting an audience starved of orcs and elves, DramSoc’s latest …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Yerma-d not to see this!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-yerma-d-not-to-see-this/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 21:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-yerma-d-not-to-see-this/</guid>
        <description>I imagine all of us know a ‘Yerma’ character – that girl who arrives as an innocent and pure fresher only to then link up with a guy in the first few weeks. He ensnares her despite his inability to satisfy her physical needs and provide her with children, all the while using her own naivety to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can’t be artsed: Will and Eva consider
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-cant-be-artsed-will-and-eva-consider/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 21:39:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-cant-be-artsed-will-and-eva-consider/</guid>
        <description>It is always difficult, for unfathomable reasons, to make it to even the best of cultural events taking place in your own city. As a tourist, rushing around during a fleeting visit to the newest European cultural capital, visiting every museum in sight is merely second nature. But at home, with time …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Riverside Studios serve up a slice of the Deep South
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-riverside-studios-serve-up-a-slice-of-the-deep-south/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 22:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-riverside-studios-serve-up-a-slice-of-the-deep-south/</guid>
        <description>In the absence of any culinary skills, I’ve found that eating one’s dinner whilst watching MasterChef, can often make the experience a little more palatable. Through years of pretending that my toast was a main of spider crab thermidor accompanied with mussels, foraged sea vegetables and a side of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Want to get your Horne on?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-want-to-get-your-horne-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 11:47:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-want-to-get-your-horne-on/</guid>
        <description>Alex Horne is something of a mystery to me. He’s little known except by regular explorers of the comedy circuit and yet seems to have the phonebook of an A-list celebrity comedian. Here’s a man whose shows pull in the likes of Tim Minchin, Harry Hill and Jimmy Carr to name but a few, and yet who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Artists descend as Regent&#39;s Park Friezes over
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-artists-descend-as-regents-park-friezes-over/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 10:47:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-artists-descend-as-regents-park-friezes-over/</guid>
        <description>Frieze Art Fair – the 21st century’s answer to the Field of the Cloth of Gold – pitched up in Regent’s Park last week for its ninth year. Drawing galleries from not just the major art hubs but from the world over, they come to present the best of their wares – a shopping opportunity for a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bobby, what&#39;s the French for maths?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-bobby-whats-the-french-for-maths/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 10:31:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-bobby-whats-the-french-for-maths/</guid>
        <description>There ought to be a word for that moment when, as you’re reclined in blissful peace an arm’s reach from a trashy novel and an iced drink with the Mediterranean sun beating on your overworked, pasty body, you realize that you haven’t got any material for Felix next week. My best attempt has four …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Have a Ball at the RA’s Summer Exhibition
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-have-a-ball-at-the-ras-summer-exhibition/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 21:10:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-have-a-ball-at-the-ras-summer-exhibition/</guid>
        <description>Over the past three terms, I’ve made a habit of sitting on the fence when it comes to reviewing. I’ve never known quite why we don’t include ratings in the Arts section, but I suspect it might be due to the fact that it would just be a constant stream of three star reviews. Having said this, I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get Doon for Gogol at the Young Vic
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-get-doon-for-gogol-at-the-young-vic/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 21:05:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-get-doon-for-gogol-at-the-young-vic/</guid>
        <description>FIFA 2001 gave me unrealistic expectations in life. Never before had I realized that you could transfer Thierry Henry, Jimmy Floyd Hasselbaink and Fernando Hierro (to name but a few) to Leeds United and create a star-studded, world beating super team. In truth in reality, you couldn’t, but through …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Acid Test makes the grade
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-the-acid-test-makes-the-grade/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 19:41:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-the-acid-test-makes-the-grade/</guid>
        <description>I think seeing Mad Blud a few days before Anya Reiss’ new play at the Royal Court stood me in good stead. Who knows what sharp edged trouble I might have unwittingly meandered into on the walk from South Ken to Sloane Square? That said, any potential crossfire that was avoided on the journey down, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mad Blud does good
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-mad-blud-does-good/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 19:37:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-mad-blud-does-good/</guid>
        <description>So often in the media you hear directors and people of the arts talking of their desire to ‘transport’ the reader or viewer or listener, whatever it might be, away from their mundane reality. Whether the destination is Richmond, Rio or Ancient Rome, all too often you can find yourself back in that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Yamamoto’s fashionable life thus far
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-yamamotos-fashionable-life-thus-far/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 05:48:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-yamamotos-fashionable-life-thus-far/</guid>
        <description>You walk in and there is a huge hall of whiteness, just one single dazzling room, peopled throughout by the headless bodies of life-sized dolls dressed in couture clothing. Do not worry though, your £7 has got you more than just a roomful of mannequins, oh no, there is a whole audiovisual …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The ‘info-play’ strikes again
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-the-info-play-strikes-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 19:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-the-info-play-strikes-again/</guid>
        <description>Greenland is the National Theatre’s (NT) contribution to the eco-play wave that is washing ominously over London. And they do it unique NT style. Much in the same way as ENRON did a couple of years back for the financial crisis, the piece has dream-cum-documentary-like quality. By dressing science, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Modern British Sculpture
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-modern-british-sculpture/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 19:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-modern-british-sculpture/</guid>
        <description>On entering Modern British Sculpture, a vast trunk of stone stands before you. It fills the high-walled room almost up to its domed ceiling, making it more temple than art gallery. Smooth, cold, awesome in the most formidable sense, you have to lean back to see it as it ascends, narrowing in linear …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Do you believe in Science?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-do-you-believe-in-science/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 19:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-do-you-believe-in-science/</guid>
        <description>Personally, I thought Al Gore had flogged the climate change donkey for all it was worth. Most people recycle now, protesters have found new things to riot over and we have a Liberal Democrat as Minister for Climate Change – the war seemed, to all intents and purposes, won. Was I wrong? Is climate …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Less Than Kind, more than ordinary
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-less-than-kind-more-than-ordinary/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 19:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-less-than-kind-more-than-ordinary/</guid>
        <description>Everybody, it seems, loves Terrence Rattigan at the moment – or Terry, as the people who sat next to me during the Jermyn Street Theatre’s production of Less Than Kind, insisted on calling him. Last summer, After The Dance at the National Theatre paved the way for Terry’s centenary year in 2011 and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Waugh: What is it good for?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-12-waugh-what-is-it-good-for/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2010 17:07:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-12-waugh-what-is-it-good-for/</guid>
        <description>It’s in theatres like the Old Red Lion, that remind me why I review plays instead of just going to the see them. They want me to like them, and they have a bar – did I mention it was a pub-theatre? It’s a simple, yet highly effective equation. Regrettably though, it seems ORL had banked on the bar …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Notting Hill fabrication
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-the-notting-hill-fabrication/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 19:54:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-the-notting-hill-fabrication/</guid>
        <description>Often I find myself wondering why I don’t lead the life of a Felliniesque, care-free socialite, generally whilst carving the fossilized Crunchy Nut from my cereal bowl or in those few moments when confronted by the awful reality of capacitance problems. And whilst normally I painfully realize I have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Homework at Bethnal Green Working Men&#39;s Club
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-homework-at-bethnal-green-working-mens-club/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 20:12:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-homework-at-bethnal-green-working-mens-club/</guid>
        <description>Before anyone builds up a mental image of cockney miners drinking pints of bitter, let me set out a few facts. Whilst Bethnal Green Working Men’s Club at one point probably lived up to its name, those in charge now clearly don’t care for preserving history. Men in overalls and bingo nights have been …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Eccentric drama horrifies in Islington
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-eccentric-drama-horrifies-in-islington/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 19:15:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-eccentric-drama-horrifies-in-islington/</guid>
        <description>As one of the bigger names on the Edinburgh Fringe Festival scene, Pleasance has nearly 25 years experience in giving highly unconventional productions a stage. Halloween thriller The Insti2ute is no exception to the trend, being poles apart from your West End night out in both setting and, sadly, …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
