<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/js5913/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/js5913/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>We , the people | The Hamilton cast speak out
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-we-the-people-the-hamilton-cast-speak-out/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 14:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-we-the-people-the-hamilton-cast-speak-out/</guid>
        <description>By now, it’s a near certainty you’ll already have heard about Vice President-elect Mike Pence’s trip to Broadway’s hip-hop musical sensation, Hamilton. If you haven’t, it’s all rather simple: Pence went to the show, and following the curtain call, one of the cast stepped forward and addressed Pence …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The National Theatre gets its groove back with Amadeus
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-14-the-national-theatre-gets-its-groove-back-with-amadeus/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 14:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-14-the-national-theatre-gets-its-groove-back-with-amadeus/</guid>
        <description>The National’s new revival of its 1979 triumph is one tinged with sadness, doubly so on the evening of its opening. The playwright behind Amadeus, Peter Shaffer, sadly passed away earlier this year, and on the day of the opening the director Howard Davies, responsible for 30 shows at the National …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A premature follow up
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-a-premature-follow-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 16:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-a-premature-follow-up/</guid>
        <description>There is a depressing if predictable irony to the fact that, within hours of this article being completed, the Globe’s board went and pushed out their female artistic director. On Tuesday morning, it was announced that Emma Rice will be stepping down from her role in April 2018, following the close …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Casting women in male roles is not a gimmick
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-casting-women-in-male-roles-is-not-a-gimmick/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 16:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-casting-women-in-male-roles-is-not-a-gimmick/</guid>
        <description>Shakespeare. “Who owns Shakespeare? “. This is the idea Phyllida Lloyd and company set out to challenge with her all-female production of Julius Caesar at the Donmar Warehouse in 2012.
It’s easy to dismiss that move as a gimmick, a knock-off copy of the all-male Shakespeare productions that pop up …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Filibuster foils first aid – fair?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-27-filibuster-foils-first-aid-fair/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 14:22:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-27-filibuster-foils-first-aid-fair/</guid>
        <description>Last Friday, a group of Conservative MPs killed a bill intended to make first aid training compulsory in state-run secondary schools by “talking it to death.”
The thrillingly-named Compulsory Emergency First Aid Education (State-funded Secondary Schools) Bill – which tells you everything you need to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Yoga banned at Canadian university
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-27-yoga-banned-at-canadian-university/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 11:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-27-yoga-banned-at-canadian-university/</guid>
        <description>Yoga classes at the University of Ottawa have been cancelled by the university’s Student Federation (the Canadian student union equivalent) after apparent concerns over “cultural appropriation”.
Jennifer Scharf, an instructor who had been running free weekly yoga sessions at the university’s Centre …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>China overhauls one child policy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-30-china-overhauls-one-child-policy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 12:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-30-china-overhauls-one-child-policy/</guid>
        <description>China has scrapped its infamous one-child policy after more than three decades, it was revealed this week.
The ruling Communist Party issued a statement following a four-day summit in Beijing, revealing that couples will now be allowed to have up to two children.
This change in policy is intended to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The National wants you to watch
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-18-the-national-wants-you-to-watch/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2015 21:15:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-18-the-national-wants-you-to-watch/</guid>
        <description>Following on from Beyond Caring in the National’s Temporary Theatre, We Want You to Watch is the latest venture from producing trio RashDash, written together with Alice Birch.
Very little is available about the show – the synopsis is a collection of short, abrupt sentences that let you know “this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Summer of cinema
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-18-summer-of-cinema/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2015 20:28:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-18-summer-of-cinema/</guid>
        <description> With the summer upon us, it means the inevitable onslaught of blockbusters. By normal standards, 2015’s a pretty quiet year for the summer, with most of this year’s big hitters either already out, or landing towards Christmas time (Star Wars, I’m looking at you).
But don’t worry – once you’ve …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Still surviving... still thriving?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-18-still-surviving-still-thriving/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2015 19:42:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-18-still-surviving-still-thriving/</guid>
        <description>Another year, another season of Game of Thrones draws to a close.
This year marks a key milestone in the adaptation however, as with the end of season closer “Mother’s Mercy” the show has officially caught up with the books.
Despite adamant assurances from showrunners David Benioff and D. B. Weiss …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The wonderful world of film
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-12-the-wonderful-world-of-film/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2015 12:42:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-12-the-wonderful-world-of-film/</guid>
        <description>Sir Christopher Lee passes away
Veteran actor Sir Christopher Lee died aged 93, it was revealed on Thursday.
The star of many films, Lee passed away on Sunday at Chelsea and Westminster Hospital after being admitted with respiratory difficulties and heart failure.
Lee had an incredible career, with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Never Have I Ever”: The sexual adventures of Imperial students
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-4-never-have-i-ever-the-sexual-adventures-of-imperial-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2015 23:36:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-4-never-have-i-ever-the-sexual-adventures-of-imperial-students/</guid>
        <description>The perennially popular drinking game gets easier with the arrival of the sex survey. If you’re looking for an easy way to get people to drink, look no further than the old classics: fuck buddies, and one night stands.
53% of students have had a one night stand, with the males proving more likely to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brandon flowers on his own
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-brandon-flowers-on-his-own/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 12:19:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-brandon-flowers-on-his-own/</guid>
        <description>Brandon Flowers going solo has always been an interesting proposition, begging the question: when it comes to The Killers and everything they’ve done, how much of their sound is down to him?
First album Flamingo didn’t do much to help answer that question, with half of the album feeling like …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BBC doesn&#39;t mind the Buzzcocks
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-bbc-doesnt-mind-the-buzzcocks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 10:59:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-bbc-doesnt-mind-the-buzzcocks/</guid>
        <description> Comedy music panel show Never Mind the Buzzcocks was dropped by the BBC this week, after almost 20 years and nearly 270 episodes on air.
A 2014 revamp of the show failed to salvage falling ratings, likely leading to the show’s cancellation.
The show’s last run often struggled to hit 1 million …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dreaming of a better film
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-dreaming-of-a-better-film/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 10:42:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-dreaming-of-a-better-film/</guid>
        <description>Director: Brad Bird Screenplay: Damon Lindelof, Brad Bird, Jeff Jensen Cast: George Clooney, Hugh Laurie, Britt Robertson, Raffedy Cassidy, Tim McGraw
_Tomorrowland: A World Beyond _is in the running for year’s most pointless subtitle. It exists only for the UK, with every other territory simply …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Anti-Austerity Protests take place in Central London
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-anti-austerity-protests-take-place-in-central-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 01:10:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,Navid Nabijou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-anti-austerity-protests-take-place-in-central-london/</guid>
        <description>Anti-austerity protests took place in London on Wednesday, with demonstrators taking to the streets alongside the Queen’s Speech in the newly elected Parliament.
Organised by the People’s Assembly, the march covered large sections of central London, moving from outside Downing Street at around …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Zero-hours in an hour and a half
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-26-zero-hours-in-an-hour-and-a-half/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 14:10:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-26-zero-hours-in-an-hour-and-a-half/</guid>
        <description>The house lights don’t dim at the start of Beyond Caring. That’s the first thing that went through my head. That, rapidly followed by “hang on, have we even started?” It’s a unique and bold use of the Temporary Theatre, and an instantly striking re-opening for the National’s fourth theatre. Formerly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Coming down with a bad case of the Twits
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-26-coming-down-with-a-bad-case-of-the-twits/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 14:03:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-26-coming-down-with-a-bad-case-of-the-twits/</guid>
        <description>Roald Dahl’s made a bit of a resurgence of late, with _The Twits _representing the third adaptation of his works for the West End stage in four years. It follows on from Tim Minchin and Dennis Kelly’s musical adaptation of Matilda, and Sam Mendes delivery of _Charlie and the Chocolate Factory _in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Livin&#39; it large on Avenue Q
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-26-livin-it-large-on-avenue-q/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 13:52:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-26-livin-it-large-on-avenue-q/</guid>
        <description>There’s not a lot new that can be said about Avenue Q, on the face of it. It can be succinctly described as the unholy offspring of _The Muppets, Sesame Street _and the real world, blending classic Jim Henson-style puppetry with irreverent humour and adult themes.
 &amp;ldquo;Avenue Q sticks two fingers …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Do you really care about the NHS?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-26-do-you-really-care-about-the-nhs/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 13:41:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-26-do-you-really-care-about-the-nhs/</guid>
        <description>The title of Michael Wynne’s latest work, Who Cares, is both deliberately provocative and perfectly explanatory of what the audience entering the Royal Court have signed themselves up for. This production for the Jerwood Theatre Upstairs is less ‘state of the nation’ and more ‘state of the national …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A fractured take on a fractured world
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-26-a-fractured-take-on-a-fractured-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 13:30:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-26-a-fractured-take-on-a-fractured-world/</guid>
        <description>Simons Stephens ranks as one of Britain’s most prolific playwrights, which makes it no surprise that, fresh off the run of _Birdland_at the Royal Court last summer, he’s already back in the theatre with Carmen Disruption, a musing on life, love and loss in an unnamed European city.
As the title …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In Conversation: Ian MacNeil
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-26-in-conversation-ian-macneil/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 13:20:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-26-in-conversation-ian-macneil/</guid>
        <description>Ian MacNeil is the set designer for Everyman, currently on at the National Theatre. Directed by Rufus Norris, the new Director of the National, and starring Academy Award-winning Chiwetel Ejiofor, the play runs until 30th August. Ian’s previous work includes the likes of Billy Elliot: The Musical, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The RSC&#39;s Thoroughly Modern Miller
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-26-the-rscs-thoroughly-modern-miller/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 12:47:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-26-the-rscs-thoroughly-modern-miller/</guid>
        <description>With 2015 marking the centenary of Arthur Miller’s birth, it was inevitable that a fresh crop of revivals of the great American playwright’s works would spring up across the theatre world. Last year saw Yael Farber direct a production of The Crucible, staged in the round at the Old Vic and starring …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Avengers subtitles ‘too literal’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-21-avengers-subtitles-too-literal/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2015 23:22:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-21-avengers-subtitles-too-literal/</guid>
        <description>Age of Ultron is rapidly approaching a worldwide box office take of one billion US dollars (a touch under £650 million), but that doesn’t mean it hasn’t encountered its fair share of problems.
Joss Whedon’s latest contribution to the Marvel Cinematic Universe has just opened in China, a relative …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This week in Film: Terminator Genisys
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-this-week-in-film-terminator-genisys/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 12:10:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-this-week-in-film-terminator-genisys/</guid>
        <description>The marketing campaign for the latest reboot/revival of the Terminator series continues rolling, with a new batch of character posters hitting the web this week.
Posters for Terminator Genisys* have arrived, featuring looks at Arnold Schwarzenegger returning to one of the roles that made him famous, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Avengers: Age of Ultron subtitles &#39;too literal&#39;
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-14-avengers-age-of-ultron-subtitles-too-literal/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 21:47:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-14-avengers-age-of-ultron-subtitles-too-literal/</guid>
        <description>Age of Ultron is rapidly approaching a worldwide box office take of one billion US dollars (a touch under £650 million), but that doesn’t mean it hasn’t encountered its fair share of problems.
Joss Whedon’s latest contribution to the Marvel Cinematic Universe has just opened in China, a relative …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This week in Film: Suicide Squad
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-8-this-week-in-film-suicide-squad/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 12:50:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-8-this-week-in-film-suicide-squad/</guid>
        <description>In the face of Marvel’s continued success with their Cinematic Universe, DC have begun throwing out early glimpses of their upcoming slate, kicking off with a trailer for Batman vs Superman: Dawn of Justice*, and now the first image of the Suicide Squad all together.
David Ayer posted the group shot …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial’s local constituencies explained
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-1-imperials-local-constituencies-explained/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:24:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-1-imperials-local-constituencies-explained/</guid>
        <description>The majority of students at Imperial (especially those in halls) are concentrated in the four constituencies of Chelsea and Fulham, Kensington, Hammersmith, and Cities of London and Westminster. Felix takes a look at each of them below.
Hammersmith
Hammersmith is currently represented by the Labour …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Age of Ultron is upon us
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-4-23-the-age-of-ultron-is-upon-us/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2015 14:15:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-4-23-the-age-of-ultron-is-upon-us/</guid>
        <description>Director: Joss Whedon
Screenplay: Joss Whedon
Cast: Robert Downey Jr., Chris Evans, Jeremy Renner, Scarlett Johansson, Mark Ruffalo
Rating: 5&amp;frasl;5
There’s a lot to be said about sequels and their relationships to their predecessors, and it’s almost all been said before. So with the usual preamble …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tom Stoppard: Not so Hard After All
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-tom-stoppard-not-so-hard-after-all/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 12:56:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-tom-stoppard-not-so-hard-after-all/</guid>
        <description>Tom Stoppard’s latest play has been a long time coming. His last work to grace the stage was 2006’s _Rock and Roll _at The Royal Court – and his last work at the National Theatre was four years before that, with The Coast of Utopia in 2002. Nine years since his last play. To call expectations high …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Et in Arcadia Ego, Unfortunately
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-et-in-arcadia-ego-unfortunately/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 12:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-et-in-arcadia-ego-unfortunately/</guid>
        <description>A disclaimer, before this review goes any further. I have extraordinarily strong feelings and opinions about Arcadia. I studied the text for A-Level, and directed the show for DramSoc in the summer of my first year of university. It’s been a huge part of my life for the past few years, and it’s only …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Britain’s Greatest Living Playwright
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-britains-greatest-living-playwright/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 12:51:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-britains-greatest-living-playwright/</guid>
        <description>To call anyone “Britain’s greatest living playwright” is a bold claim. Competition for the title is fierce, and ever-growing – a simple glance at the work coming out of the likes of the Royal Court shows the strength of new talent.
But one name has been at the forefront of British drama since his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Favourite Play – The Importance of Being Earnest
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-6-my-favourite-play-the-importance-of-being-earnest/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 14:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-6-my-favourite-play-the-importance-of-being-earnest/</guid>
        <description>I have such an obvious fondness for Arcadia – and for Stoppard’s work in general – that my picking it as my favourite play seems like a foregone conclusion. So let’s side step that conversation by turning straight to my second-favourite play. Now comes the requirement to actually think about the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Everything is not awesome
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-everything-is-not-awesome/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 17:29:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-everything-is-not-awesome/</guid>
        <description> You might have noticed there’s been a bit of controversy about the Oscars. The LEGO Movie got completely snubbed for Best Animated Feature, and a lot of people got very angry, very, very quickly. The directors (Phil Lord and Chris Miller) responded in their typically wonderful style, with the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Once more unto the breach: Felix reviews Mockingjay, Part 1
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-once-more-unto-the-breach-felix-reviews-mockingjay-part-1/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 12:40:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-once-more-unto-the-breach-felix-reviews-mockingjay-part-1/</guid>
        <description>Mockingjay – Part 1
Director: Francis Lawrence
Screenplay: Peter Craig, Danny Strong, Suzanne Collins
Cast: Jennifer Lawrence, Josh Hutcherson, Liam Hemsworth, Woody Harrelson, Donald Sutherland, Julianne Moore
Rating: 4&amp;frasl;5
Katniss Everdeen is broken. Being thrown into the arena for the Hunger …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mankind’s next step will be our greatest
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-17-mankinds-next-step-will-be-our-greatest/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 18:12:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-17-mankinds-next-step-will-be-our-greatest/</guid>
        <description>INTERSTELLAR
Director: Christopoher Nolan
Screenplay: Christopher Nolan, Jonathan Nolan
Cast: Matthew McConaughey, Anne Hathaway, Michael Caine, Jessica Chastain, John Lithgow, Casey Affleck, Ellen Burstyn, Wes Bentley
Rating: 5&amp;frasl;5
Christopher Nolan has a back catalogue to die for. A Batman …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Creatures of the Night
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-creatures-of-the-night/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 21:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-creatures-of-the-night/</guid>
        <description>NIGHTCRAWLER
Director: Dan Gilroy
Screenplay: Dan Gilroy
Cast: Jake Gyllenhaal, Rene Russo, Bill Paxton
5&amp;frasl;5
Nightcrawler starts off innocently enough, with classic shots of the LA skyline at night, millions of lights fending off the darkness, before crashing down to a man cutting through a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The best X-Men film ever
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-2-the-best-x-men-film-ever/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 13:09:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-2-the-best-x-men-film-ever/</guid>
        <description>X-Men: Days of Future Past
Director: Bryan Singer
Writer: Simon Kinberg, Jane Goldman, Matthew Vaughn
Starring: Hugh Jackman, James McAvoy, Michael Fassbender, Patrick Stewart, Ian McKellen, Jennifer Lawrence, Ellen Page, Shawn Ashmore, Halle Berry, Nicholas Hoult, Peter Dinklage, Evan Peters, Omar …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You’re gonna hear me roar
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-23-youre-gonna-hear-me-roar/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 14:14:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-23-youre-gonna-hear-me-roar/</guid>
        <description>Godzilla
Director: Gareth Edwards
Writers: Max Borenstein, Dave Callaham
Starring: Aaron Taylor-Johnson, Elizabeth Olsen, Bryan Cranston, Ken Watanabe, Sally Hawkins, Juliette Binoche, David Strathairn
Runtime: 123 minutes
Certification: 12A
Rating: 4&amp;frasl;5
Godzilla has it all on paper. Provided …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wonders of the Marvel Cinematic Universe
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-23-wonders-of-the-marvel-cinematic-universe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 13:58:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-23-wonders-of-the-marvel-cinematic-universe/</guid>
        <description> With Captain America: The Winter Soldier still drifting around in cinemas almost two months after release, it’s clear that Marvel’s plan to dominate the world of (comic book) films continues to be a resounding success. But just what is that plan, and how has it been so successful?
Phase 1 Think …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Governator’s war on drugs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-19-the-governators-war-on-drugs/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2014 14:01:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-19-the-governators-war-on-drugs/</guid>
        <description>Sabotage
Director: David Ayer
Writers: Skip Woods, David Ayer
Starring: Arnold Schwarzenegger, Sam Worthington, Terrence Howard, Joe Manganiello, Josh Holloway, Max Martini, Mireille Enos, Olivia Williams
Runtime: 109 minutes
Certification: 15
Rating: 2&amp;frasl;5
The director of End of Watch (an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The big hit of Sundance 2014
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-19-the-big-hit-of-sundance-2014/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2014 14:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-19-the-big-hit-of-sundance-2014/</guid>
        <description>Frank
Director: Leonard Abrahamson
Writers: Jon Ronson, Peter Straughan
Starring: Michael Fassbender, Domnhall Gleeson, Maggie Gyllenhaal, Scoot McNairy, Tess Harper
Runtime: 95 minutes
Certification: 15
Rating: 3&amp;frasl;5
The opening lines of _Frank _are a mixture of odd noises and half-formed (and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bad boy bad boy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-19-bad-boy-bad-boy/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2014 13:59:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-19-bad-boy-bad-boy/</guid>
        <description>Bad Neighbours
Director: Nicholas Stoller
Writers: Andrew J. Cohen, Brendan O’Brien
Starring: Seth Rogen, Rose Byrne, Zac Efron, Dave Franco
Runtime: 96 minutes
Certification: 15
Rating: 4&amp;frasl;5
It’s comedy season again, and things are kicking off in the most family-unfriendly way possible (in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Locke’s collapse
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-19-lockes-collapse/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2014 13:57:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-19-lockes-collapse/</guid>
        <description>Locke
Director: Steven Knight
Writer: Steven Knight
Starring: Tom Hardy, Olivia Colman, Ruth Wilson
Runtime: 85 minutes
Certification: 15
Rating 4&amp;frasl;5
Locke is an intriguing premise. Set entirely in the cabin of a BMW (bar a few brief seconds of Locke climbing into his car at the very …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Calvary
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-calvary/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 01:22:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-calvary/</guid>
        <description>Calvary
Director: Marc Webb
Writer: John Michael McDonaugh
Starring: Brendan Gleeson, Chris O’Dowd, Kelly Reilly, Aidan Gillen
Runtime: 100 minutes
Certification: 15
Rating: 4&amp;frasl;5
Following on from their previous effort The Guard, director John Michael McDonagh (brother of Marty) have teamed up …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Amazing Spider-Man 2
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-the-amazing-spider-man-2/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 01:20:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-the-amazing-spider-man-2/</guid>
        <description>The Amazing Spider-Man 2
Director: Marc Webb
Writers: Alex Kurtzman, Roberto Orci, Jeff Pinker, James Vanderbilt
Starring: Andrew Garfield, Emma Stone, Dane DeHaan, Jamie Foxx, Sally Field, Paul Giamatti
Runtime: 142 minutes
Certification: 12A
Rating: 3&amp;frasl;5
The obvious point to be made here is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rio 2
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-rio-2/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 01:19:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-rio-2/</guid>
        <description>Rio 2
Director: Carlos Saldanha
Writers: Jenny Bicks, Carlos Saldanha, Yoni Brenner, Carlos Kotkin, Don Rhymer
Starring: (voices) Jesse Eisenberg, Anne Hathaway, Jamie Foxx, Bruno Mars
Runtime: 101 minutes
Certification: U
Rating: 2&amp;frasl;5
The original Rio (I’ve noticed the fact I seem to be using …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Noah: A Russell Crowe Epic
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-noah-a-russell-crowe-epic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 01:17:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-noah-a-russell-crowe-epic/</guid>
        <description>Noah
Director: Darren Aronofsky
Writers: Darren Aronofsky, Ari Handel
Starring: Russell Crowe, Jennifer Connelly, Emma Watson, Ray Winstone, Douglas Booth, Logan Lerman, Anthony Hopkins
Runtime: 138 minutes
Certification: 12A
Rating: 4&amp;frasl;5
The sweeping, captioned opening of Darren Aronofsky’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Divergent
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-divergent/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 01:15:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-divergent/</guid>
        <description>Divergent
Director: Neil Burger
Writers: Evan Daugherty, Vanessa Taylor, Veronica Roth (novel)
Starring: Shailene Woodley, Theo James, Kate Winslet
Runtime: 139 minutes
Certification: 12A
Rating: 3&amp;frasl;5
The quest to find the next Hunger Games finds it next entrant in Veronica Roth’s series of YA …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Muppets Most Wanted
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-muppets-most-wanted/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 01:12:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-muppets-most-wanted/</guid>
        <description>Muppets Most Wanted
Director: James Bobin
Writers: James Bobin, Nicholas Stoller
Starring: Ricky Gervais, Tina Fey, Ty Burrell, Steven Whitmire, Eric Jacobson, Dave Goelz, Bill Barretta, David Rudman
Runtime: 107 minutes
Certification: U
Rating: 3&amp;frasl;5
_Muppets Most Wanted_’s opening song, “We’re …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Raid 2
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-the-raid-2/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 01:11:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-the-raid-2/</guid>
        <description>The Raid 2
Director: Gareth Evans
Writer: Gareth Evans
Starring: Iko Uwais, Yayan Ruhian, Arifin Putra, Julie Estelle
Runtime: 150 minutes
Certification: 18
Rating: 5&amp;frasl;5
Subtitled _Berandal _in the US (much like the original was subtitled Redemption), The Raid 2 picks up …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Captain America: The Winter Soldier
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-captain-america-the-winter-soldier/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 01:07:47 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-captain-america-the-winter-soldier/</guid>
        <description>Captain America: The Winter Soldier
Directors: Anthony Russo, Joe Russo
Writers: Christopher Markus, Stephen McFeely, Ed Brubaker
Starring: Chris Evans, Scarlett Johansson, Samuel L. Jackson, Robert Redford, Sebastian Stan, Anthony Mackie, Cobie Smulders, Frank Grillo, Emily VanCamp
Runtime: 136 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Alien in Scotland
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-alien-in-scotland/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 13:47:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-alien-in-scotland/</guid>
        <description>Under the Skin
Director: Jonathan Glazer
Writers: Jonathan Glazer, Walter Campbell, Michel Faber (novel)
Starring: Scarlett Johansson, Jeremy McWilliams, Michael Moreland
Runtime: 108 minutes
Certification: 15
Rating: 4&amp;frasl;5
Grating noise over a blackout. A pinprick of light. The noise …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A 5-star hotel experience
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-a-5-star-hotel-experience/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 13:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-a-5-star-hotel-experience/</guid>
        <description>The Grand Budapest Hotel
Director: Wes Anderson
Writers: Wes Anderson, Hugo Guinness, Stefan Zweig (inspired by the works of)
Starring: Ralph Fiennes, F. Murray Abraham, Mathieu Amalric, Adrien Brody, Willem Dafoe, Jeff Goldblum, Harvey Keitel, Jude Law, Bill Murray, Edward Norton, Saoirse Ronan, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Crime has a new enemy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-17-crime-has-a-new-enemy/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 19:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-17-crime-has-a-new-enemy/</guid>
        <description>Robocop
Director: José Padilha
Writer: Joshua Zetumer
Starring: Joel Kinnaman, Gary Oldman, Michael Keaton, Abbie Cornish, Jackie Earle Haley
Runtime: 118 minutes
Certification: 12A
Rating: 4&amp;frasl;5
The original Robocop was – is – an undisputed classic, a masterpiece, quite possibly the best film …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Philadel...uhh...Dallas
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-17-philadeluhhdallas/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 19:29:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Martin,Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-17-philadeluhhdallas/</guid>
        <description>Michael S. Martin
Rating: 3&amp;frasl;5
Dallas Buyers Club is structured like the story of a self-made drug baron. Ron Woodroof (McConaughey) sees demand for an illegal product and goes through the trouble of importing and selling it, while trying to keep it away from the prying eyes of the law. But at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jack Steadman vs. Jack Ryan
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-jack-steadman-vs-jack-ryan/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 04:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-jack-steadman-vs-jack-ryan/</guid>
        <description>Jack Ryan: Shadow Recruit
Director: Kenneth Branagh Writers: Adam Cozad, David Koepp, Tom Clancy (characters) Starring: Chris Pine, Keira Knightley, Kevin Costner, Kenneth Branagh Runtime: 105 minutes Certification: 12A
The latest entry in the Jack Ryan franchise (a character who shares with James …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nebraska, Nebraska, I love you
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-nebraska-nebraska-i-love-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 03:58:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-nebraska-nebraska-i-love-you/</guid>
        <description>Nebraska
Director: Alexander Payne
Writer: Bob Nelson
Starring: Bruce Dern, Will Forte, June Squibb
Runtime: 115 minutes
Certification: 15
Following on from the Oscar-nominated The Descendants (featuring George Clooney’s best performance in years, and introducing the amazing Shailene Woodley – soon …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can Fassbender handle the truth?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-can-fassbender-handle-the-truth/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 16:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-can-fassbender-handle-the-truth/</guid>
        <description>The Counsellor
Director: Ridley Scott Writer: Cormac McCarthy Starring: Michael Fassbender, Penélope Cruz, Javier Bardem, Cameron Diaz, Brad Pitt Runtime: 117 minutes Certification: 18
On paper, The Counsellor should be perfect. Cormac McCarthy’s first original screenplay (a few of his other books …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Comic Success of Don Jon
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-the-comic-success-of-don-jon/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 01:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-the-comic-success-of-don-jon/</guid>
        <description>Joseph Gordon-Levitt’s directorial debut (which he also wrote and stars in – the classic triple threat) opens with a rather unsubtle montage that flicks between credits and the standard examples of society’s objectification of women. It makes a rather obvious point – objectification is everywhere – …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The return of the Australian Norse god
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-the-return-of-the-australian-norse-god/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 10:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-the-return-of-the-australian-norse-god/</guid>
        <description>Phase 2 of Marvel’s grand scheme to take over the world (sorry, “make really good movies”) continues apace with this, the second entry in the series about everyone’s second-favourite Norse god (if you’re about to tell me Loki isn’t your favourite, I’m going to stop you there and tell you you’re a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Revenge of the leftovers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-revenge-of-the-leftovers/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 09:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-revenge-of-the-leftovers/</guid>
        <description>The original Cloudy was a wacky, high-energy romp through the world of Flint Lockwood (Bill Hader), inventor extraordinaire (well, if you count rat birds and spray-on shoes as deserving of such a title) and his creation of the FLDSMDFR (no, I am not spelling out that acronym for you, go look it up), …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
