<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/gritty/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/gritty/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>VZ, Bernie, and Cohen on TV</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-vz-bernie-and-cohen-on-tv/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gritty,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-vz-bernie-and-cohen-on-tv/</guid>
        <description>The profligate son returns, crucified for calls to revolution and arisen after three days (and two months or so). Keeping with the theme – three independent stories from the past two weeks.
Venezuela. This is the classic American foreign policy pincher – place excruciating sanctions on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Now’s the time to tune back into US news</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-now-s-the-time-to-tune-back-into-us-news/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gritty,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-now-s-the-time-to-tune-back-into-us-news/</guid>
        <description>Merry Gritmas. Since Parliament voted to hold the government in contempt, I’ve been jerkin’ it constantly, and have released more “legal advice” than I knew my body could produce. Well, let’s get to it.
The Mueller probe is chugging along. Trump is now known to be “Individual 1” - the central focus …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>US news is moving like constipated bowels</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-us-news-is-moving-like-constipated-bowels/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gritty,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-us-news-is-moving-like-constipated-bowels/</guid>
        <description>Hey folks, welcome back to another instalment of your favourite politics comment column. Remember that Felix can be your voice if you email us by Monday; having more lefty voices would be pretty swanky. This column is gonna be short; Charlie’s stealing my page. Sorry for the terseness.
RIP to a real …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s been a slow week for American politics</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-it-s-been-a-slow-week-for-american-politics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gritty,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-it-s-been-a-slow-week-for-american-politics/</guid>
        <description>Grit went Brit this week.
We’ve been so busy with the recent collapse of the UK government that US news seemed to have been swept well under the rug. This is fine by me - no news is good news as far as America is concerned. There’s the odd morsel - Ivanka Trump’s emails; Nancy Pelosi being the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The midterms dust has settled; the races were rigged and we still live in a waking nightmare</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-the-midterms-dust-has-settled-the-races-were-rigged-and-we-still-live-in-a-waking-nightmare/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gritty,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-the-midterms-dust-has-settled-the-races-were-rigged-and-we-still-live-in-a-waking-nightmare/</guid>
        <description>When in times of trouble, Gritty comes to me, speaking words of wisdom - Trump’s pants are peed.
It’s been another week of abject hell in politics, but this time the chips are falling in the Dems’ favor. Turns out Florida and Georgia haven’t even counted all their ballots (Broward County, who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gritty unwinds the American midterms</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-gritty-unwinds-the-american-midterms/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gritty,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-gritty-unwinds-the-american-midterms/</guid>
        <description>It the Grit. The midterms have come and gone, and the balance of power has shifted. Races have been won and lost. Pour a 40 out for my dudes Gillum, O’Rourke (3-point spread), Janz, and Abrams (~2 point spread). Good showing all.
The Dems picked up 34 seats in the House, clinching the majority. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gritty’s Field Guide to the American Midterm Elections: It’s Gonna Be Rough, Folks</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-gritty-s-field-guide-to-the-american-midterm-elections-it-s-gonna-be-rough-folks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gritty,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-gritty-s-field-guide-to-the-american-midterm-elections-it-s-gonna-be-rough-folks/</guid>
        <description>Welcome one and all to the continuing shitshow saga that is the American political spectacle. When you last tuned in in 2016, the Ur-fascist narrowly beat out the neoliberal cancellation of the future, and we’ve been on a wild ride for the last two years as Republican majorities in Congress and a …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
