<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recipe on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/tags/recipe/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recipe on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/tags/recipe/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>On the eleventh day of Christmas, my true love gave to me… BRUSSELS SPROUTS</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-eleventh-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-brussels-sprouts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-eleventh-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-brussels-sprouts/</guid>
        <description>You will need&amp;hellip;
 1 kg Brussels sprouts 50 gr butter 4 tsp vegetable oil 20 gr almonds 400 ml double cream 5 tsp lemon juice 5 tbsp breadcrumbs freshly grated parmesan (the more, the better) a pinch of salt black pepper   Simmer salted water in a saucepan. Add the Brussels sprouts and boil them …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the seventh day of Christmas, my true love gave to me… CHRISTMAS ROAST PORK WITH RIB GRAVY AND APPLE BREAD SAUCE</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-seventh-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-christmas-roast-pork-with-rib-gravy-and-apple-bread-sauce/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-seventh-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-christmas-roast-pork-with-rib-gravy-and-apple-bread-sauce/</guid>
        <description>You will need&amp;hellip;
FOR THE ROAST - 2 kg pork belly (depending on how many people you plan to feed) - 3 tbsp salt
FOR THE GRAVY - 3 tbsp olive oil - 4 pork ribs - 2 onions, chopped - 2 carrots, chopped in big chunks - 1 litre chicken stock - 8 black peppercorns - fresh bay leaves - fresh thyme
FOR …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the sixth day of Christmas, my true love gave to me… GINGERBREAD MEN</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-sixth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-gingerbread-men/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-sixth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-gingerbread-men/</guid>
        <description>You will need&amp;hellip;
 400g plain flour 1 tsp bicarbonate of soda 2 tsp ground ginger 1 tsp ground cinnamon 125g butter (unsalted) 200g honey 2 eggs   Mix all the dry ingredients and then add in the butter. This step would be really easy if you have a food processor, but I imagine that, as a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the twelfth day of Christmas, my true love gave to me… SEA BASS WITH SWEET POTATO AND GREEN BEAN CURRY</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-twelfth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-sea-bass-with-sweet-potato-and-green-bean-curry/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-twelfth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-sea-bass-with-sweet-potato-and-green-bean-curry/</guid>
        <description>You will need&amp;hellip;
 2 large sweet potatoes 3 tbsp olive oil 1 onion, finely diced 3 garlic cloves, crushed 1 tbsp grated ginger 2 lime leaves (replaceable with 1 tsp lime juice) 1 tsp curry powder ½ tsp turmeric ½ masala ¼ tsp cinnamon 160 ml coconut cream 400 ml coconut milk 100 gr green beans 4 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Asian invasion</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-asian-invasion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chun Yuan Hii,Adrian Lua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-asian-invasion/</guid>
        <description>Felix Food has been sharing simple and quick recipes for the past few issues, and that’s great! Hopefully they’ve helped you to survive the term in some ways. But don’t you occasionally imagine yourself cooking a Michelin-starred dish, unleashing your inner chef, and it no longer mattering if you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Have a sweet tooth? We sure do...</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-have-a-sweet-tooth-we-sure-do/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chun Yuan Hii,Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-have-a-sweet-tooth-we-sure-do/</guid>
        <description>Admit it, we all need our sugary boost sometimes (though this might be heavily frowned upon by my friend who wrote on healthy eating last week&amp;hellip;) Maybe it’s just me, but occasionally, after a nine-to-five day full of labs and lectures, you just want to have something warm, sweet, and – most …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>From penne to puttanesca: an ode to pasta</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-from-penne-to-puttanesca-an-ode-to-pasta/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-from-penne-to-puttanesca-an-ode-to-pasta/</guid>
        <description>If there was ever an argument for the inherent goodness of humanity and the progress of mankind, it can be summed up in a single word: pasta. This humble staple of our diet is probably one of the best reasons to be alive on this earth. Whether it’s long, worm-like spaghetti drenched in a carbonara …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Healthy, mindful eating on a budget?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-healthy-mindful-eating-on-a-budget/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michelle Yeap,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-healthy-mindful-eating-on-a-budget/</guid>
        <description>One of my biggest struggles coming to university is living within a budget. I am sure many students, including myself, wonder whether it is possible to eat a healthy, balanced diet while also living on a shoestring.
For me, the supermarket is none other than the place for distraction and …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
