<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/eva_tadros/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/eva_tadros/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>7 Must-See Destinations for Under £70</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-seven-must-see-destinations-under-70/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-seven-must-see-destinations-under-70/</guid>
        <description>Above: Copenhagen, Denmark
Student life is hard enough as it is, but travelling on a tight budget is a whole other struggle. Finding the perfect getaway only for your bank balance to shatter all your dreams is top two most heart-breaking feelings, and hint – it’s not number two. That’s why for our …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How is Brexit Going to Affect My Next Holiday?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-how-brexit-affect-holiday/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-how-brexit-affect-holiday/</guid>
        <description>I know what you’re thinking - another day, another Brexit article. But if you’re anything like us and have the travel bug, then you’re going to want to read this one. With Brexit being delayed once again to January at the soonest, there’s no better time to grab a bargain and finally book flights to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Small Place, Big Adventures</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-small-place-big-adventures/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-small-place-big-adventures/</guid>
        <description>As one of the world’s smallest countries, Singapore has gained popularity as Asia’s corporate capital, but there’s so much more than business on offer when visiting this South East Asian country. Singapore is also one of the safest places you could possibly visit - so whether you’re embarking on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Top 6 Cities You Should Visit in the UK</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-top-6-cities-you-should-visit-in-UK/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-top-6-cities-you-should-visit-in-UK/</guid>
        <description>You might’ve just moved to London and are already missing home and looking for something to do to help distract you – be it camping in the countryside, or lunch on the seaside, England has so much to offer, and London is only the tip of the iceberg, Make the most of your time here and make it a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Resistance, Resilience and Revolution</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-resistance-resilience-and-revolution/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-resistance-resilience-and-revolution/</guid>
        <description>For the first time ever in the lives of the Sudanese youth community, we get to see and experience a Sudan that isn’t ruled under Omar-Al-Bashir’s dictatorship. For the past 30 years, Sudan has seen Bashir’s rule take everything away from its people – everything except for the people’s resilience. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Spice Up Your Summer in 3 Recipes</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-spice-up-your-summer-in-3-recipes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-spice-up-your-summer-in-3-recipes/</guid>
        <description>Exams are nearly over, the sun is out (thanks, global warming), and you can almost taste the sweet, sweet freedom that comes with summer; what better way to relax and refresh than by savouring some of the season’s finest produce in easy-to-follow, simple recipes?
Here are Felix’s top three recipes: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Cookie Dough: everything you never knew you needed in your life!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-my-cookie-dough-everything-you-never-knew-you-needed-in-your-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,Julia Dabrowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-my-cookie-dough-everything-you-never-knew-you-needed-in-your-life/</guid>
        <description>After reviewing Naked Dough last month, when we got the chance to try out another cookie dough place, My Cookie Dough, the excitement was real. Although both serve cookie dough, this place adds a completely different twist onto what we thought we were expecting, replacing raw cookie dough with baked …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mumbai Mix: a comprehensive review of the best Indian food on campus</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-mumbai-mix-a-comprehensive-review-of-the-best-indian-food-on-campus/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-mumbai-mix-a-comprehensive-review-of-the-best-indian-food-on-campus/</guid>
        <description>You’ve had Indian food, sure, but we guarantee you haven’t had anything that tastes close to what Mumbai Mix has to offer. If you spend a lot of time on campus, chances are you’ve probably heard of Mumbai Mix – the only authentic Indian food stall at the Farmers Market on Tuesdays. If you haven’t, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Naked Dough: the good, the bad and the ugly</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-naked-dough-the-good-the-bad-and-the-ugly/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Julia Dabrowska,Eva Tadros,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-naked-dough-the-good-the-bad-and-the-ugly/</guid>
        <description>Remember that cute little stand that sells big tubs filled with mouthwatering cookie dough that we told you about in the “2 Girls, 1 Dessert” article earlier this year? Well, we felt like we just had to go back and satisfy our cravings, so we bring you the ultimate guide to (almost) every single …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cheap clean eats</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-cheap-clean-eats/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-cheap-clean-eats/</guid>
        <description>Now that the new year has started, how many of those “new year, new me” posts have you seen floating around? It’s nice to think we can have a fresh start as soon as the year begins, but those first few days up until term restarts are so much of a limbo, it’s pretty much impossible to send any form …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Taste of Italy in (only)1,572km²: 5 of London’s favourite Italian spots</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-a-taste-of-italy-in-only-1-572km-5-of-london-s-favourite-italian-spots/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-a-taste-of-italy-in-only-1-572km-5-of-london-s-favourite-italian-spots/</guid>
        <description>We’ve all had our classic “Eat, Pray, Love” moment where it just seems like we desperately need to sit there and stare at a massive plate of pasta before we absolutely devour it. Unfortunately, whilst getting on the next flight to Italy might seem mouth-wateringly tempting, recreating that moment …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Low-fat, reduced fat and fat-free foods: a healthy choice or a myth?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-low-fat-reduced-fat-and-fat-free-foods-a-healthy-choice-or-a-myth/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,Julia Dabrowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-low-fat-reduced-fat-and-fat-free-foods-a-healthy-choice-or-a-myth/</guid>
        <description>Hey, could you please grab a Greek yoghurt when you’re in Tesco? Just make sure it’s the low-fat one - thanks!”
Sound familiar? Nowadays, we’re constantly surrounded by a myriad of fat-free, low-fat and reduced fat products as the food industry’s attempt to maximise profits gains momentum – taking a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2 Girls, 1 Dessert</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-2-girls-1-dessert/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,Julia Dabrowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-2-girls-1-dessert/</guid>
        <description>Watching all those Food Insider videos on Facebook on a mundane afternoon undoubtedly leaves us all drooling, daydreaming about those Instagram-worthy desserts – just think of the food envy your friends will experience when they see a boomerang of that food! So naturally, you tag your friends …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>101 Ways to eat Pasta</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-101-ways-to-eat-pasta/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,Julia Dabrowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-101-ways-to-eat-pasta/</guid>
        <description>So you’ve got through your first week of uni madness - the wild balance of parties, events, and socials with possible introductory lectures or just straight up normal classes. Food this week has probably just been frozen pizza, toast, and of course all the sweets from Freshers’ Fair because who has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Freshers’ 10 under £10</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-20-freshers-10-under-10/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,Julia Dabrowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-20-freshers-10-under-10/</guid>
        <description>Freshers is upon us and you know what that means – time for our bank accounts to hate us. So you keep tapping that contactless on every night out – if you don’t see the money leaving, it’s not really gone, right? If only it worked like that. It can be quite tempting to splash out during freshers and …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
