<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/marena_gray/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/marena_gray/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Fame the Musical</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-fame-the-musical/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marena Gray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-fame-the-musical/</guid>
        <description>Who doesn’t want to be famous? Fame the Musical is all about that desire to be recognised, to be known, to not fade out of existence when death takes hold. While based on a film from the 1980s, that desire is just as relevant today. “I’m Gonna Live Forever” is the refrain of our protagonists - …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rosmersholm</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-rosmersholm/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marena Gray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-rosmersholm/</guid>
        <description>Ibsen wrote Rosmersholm (pronounced Ros-mers-home) in 1886, and it is considered to be his masterpiece, over The Wild Duck and A Doll’s House. Yet it is rarely staged. The day I saw Rosmersholm was ironically the day of the European Elections, and the parallels were astonishing, regardless of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>She Persisted</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-she-persisted/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marena Gray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-she-persisted/</guid>
        <description>Following the acclaimed She Said in 2016, English National Ballet’s director Tamara Rojo continues with She Persisted, another triple bill showcasing women’s work offering a revival, a premiere and one of the greats. The name comes from the feminist movement “Nevertheless, she persisted” in 2017 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>True West: Engaging, absurd</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-true-west-engaging-absurd/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marena Gray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-true-west-engaging-absurd/</guid>
        <description>The West End debut of the 1980 play is the first major revival of Sam Shepherd’s work since his death last year. The two main leads provide a meaty role for any actor, with talents such as John Malkovich and Gary Sinise, Philip Seymour Hoffman and John C Reilly, and Mark Rylance alternating the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
