<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sk2214/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sk2214/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Gauguin Portraits</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-gauguin-portraits/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-gauguin-portraits/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
As you enter the exhibition, the first room is filled with self-portraits of Gauguin. To walk into any room of self-portraits would give the impression of a self-centred creator, but Gauguin’s portraits strike one as particularly narcissistic, given there are several oil paintings where he …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Man Booker Prize 2019 Shortlist: The Testaments</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-man-booker-prize-2019-shortlist-testaments/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-man-booker-prize-2019-shortlist-testaments/</guid>
        <description>The Testaments is a sequel to Margaret Atwood’s 1985 dystopian novel, The Handmaid’s Tale. It is set 15 years after the first, in the same totalitarian state of Gilead, where a fertility crisis and patriarchal fundamentalism have come together to foster a society where women are legally subordinate, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Psychodrama Review</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-psychodrama-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,Simran Kukran,Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-psychodrama-review/</guid>
        <description>1. Psycho
What a way to kick off the album. A truly building track, Dave and the instrumentation become one as the listener is guided through the three main psyches that Dave will expand on throughout the album. Not only does he switch up his flow, content and delivery with each transition, but he …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Review: Tobacco Road at the Vaults</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-review-tobacco-road-at-the-vaults/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-review-tobacco-road-at-the-vaults/</guid>
        <description>Tobacco Road begins with a standoff, a gang cornered in a shootout, directly facing the audience. The gang of 1920s ne’er do wells address the audience. “We should tell them how we got here” gesturing at us. “We’ll have to start all the way at the beginning”. The cast run through the years …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Biff’s Jack Shack: turning jackfruit into fast food is not just for the vegans</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-biff-s-jack-shack-turning-jackfruit-into-fast-food-is-not-just-for-the-vegans/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhidian Thomas,Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-biff-s-jack-shack-turning-jackfruit-into-fast-food-is-not-just-for-the-vegans/</guid>
        <description>The past 12 months have been more vegan inspired than ever; in fact, 2018 was the year of the vegan. Last year saw sales of meat-free food increase by a staggering 987%, with everyone from Beyonce to Benedict Cumberbatch getting in on the action. Like it or not, plant based (read: vegan) food is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flamboyant family fun with Aladdin the Panto</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-flamboyant-family-fun-with-aladdin-the-panto/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-flamboyant-family-fun-with-aladdin-the-panto/</guid>
        <description>This production of Aladdin was a 20th year celebration of pantomime at the Hackney Empire. Panto tends to deviate from set plot lines, but this performance uses Aladdin as a vague guideline rather than a script. There are several layers of narration, starting with an impressive 10ft trapped puppet …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get the strap! 50 Cent storms O2 arena</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-get-the-strap-50-cent-storms-o2-arena/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-get-the-strap-50-cent-storms-o2-arena/</guid>
        <description>The crowd who turn out to see the O2 arena stop of 50 Cent’s Get Rich or Die Tryin’ 15th anniversary tour is probably the most diverse I have ever seen at a show. Aside from the Power theme tune or 50’s Instagram feed, I’ve been largely out of touch with his work for about a decade. Despite this, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to the pleasuredome</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-welcome-to-the-pleasuredome/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,Henry Eshbaugh,Asad Raja,Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-welcome-to-the-pleasuredome/</guid>
        <description>My friend Kunal from Singapore calls me the grime guy. I like the way that sounds so I don’t correct him. In truth, as far as grime or UK rap goes, I consider myself a semi-casual listener (you won’t catch me listening to anyone less niche than, like, Ghetts). Though I stay open to most genres, US …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Frida Kahlo: making an icon into a caricature?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-15-frida-kahlo-making-an-icon-into-a-caricature/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-15-frida-kahlo-making-an-icon-into-a-caricature/</guid>
        <description>Frida Kahlo’s is a feminist icon. Her eyebrows, jewellery, and clothes are distinctly recognisable through her self-portraits, and Kahlo is revered for challenging gender norms and rejecting colonial influences as a proud Mexican communist. This is the first time the artwork, medication, clothing, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The queen of summertime sadness continues her reign</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-the-queen-of-summertime-sadness-continues-her-reign/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-the-queen-of-summertime-sadness-continues-her-reign/</guid>
        <description>Lykke Li’s 4th studio album, so sad so sexy is her first in four years. During this break, she grappled with the artistic block she experienced as she had a child and mourned the loss of her mother. Youth Novel, Wounded Rhymes, and I Never Learn were a trilogy; exploring the trials and tribulations …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ballet Black: glorious and achingly beautiful</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-ballet-black-glorious-and-achingly-beautiful/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-ballet-black-glorious-and-achingly-beautiful/</guid>
        <description>This March, Ballet Black, the company consisting entirely of BAME performers, returned to the Barbican with a double bill. Their offering was a show in two halves; neither of these were traditional performances, but rather a showcase of the power of modern ballet.
The first half, choreographed by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello darkness, my old friend: First Aid Kit’s Ruins</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-hello-darkness-my-old-friend-first-aid-kit-s-ruins/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-hello-darkness-my-old-friend-first-aid-kit-s-ruins/</guid>
        <description>The sad Swedish sisters are back with their fourth album, ten songs of crooning harmony and synth. Ruins is a breakup album so pure and candid it’ll have you crying into your ice cream about heartache that hasn’t even happened yet. The work is anything but stripped back – as with any of First Aid …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Royal Academy shows the links between two titans</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-royal-academy-shows-the-links-between-two-titans/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-royal-academy-shows-the-links-between-two-titans/</guid>
        <description>Salvador Dali and Marcel Duchamp are both regarded as two of the twentieth century’s most influential artists, but are often seen as polar opposites. Although their personal and professional lives have been studied extensively in literature, this exhibition at the Royal Academy is the first to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Little Simz Welcome to Wonderland: The Experience
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-little-simz-welcome-to-wonderland-the-experience/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 14:45:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-little-simz-welcome-to-wonderland-the-experience/</guid>
        <description>Little Simz, real name Simbi Ajikawo, returned to the Roundhouse Rising show, having performed a headline set in 2014. This year, she headlined and curated a varied line-up of emerging talent. An art installation accompanied the show, with the Wonderland theme in focus throughout. An animation …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Shappi Khorsandi – Oh My Country!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-25-shappi-khorsandi-oh-my-country/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 22:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-25-shappi-khorsandi-oh-my-country/</guid>
        <description>As a Middle Eastern girl from Ealing whose life resembles a sitcom, there’s no other comedian I can relate to as much as Iranian-born Shappi Khorsandi, whose performances deliver a refreshing take on the world around us. Her new show, “Oh My Country!” is focused on “reclaiming patriotism” in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Vigil held at Iranian Embasssy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-vigil-held-at-iranian-embasssy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 14:52:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-vigil-held-at-iranian-embasssy/</guid>
        <description>A candle-lit vigil was held outside the Iranian embassy on Monday for Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe, a British-Iranian Thompson-Reuters charity worker. Organised by Amnesty International, supporters including Imperial students gathered on Princes’ Gate calling for Nazanin’s release from Evin prison in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Giggs at O2 Forum Kentish Town
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-giggs-at-o2-forum-kentish-town/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 15:43:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-giggs-at-o2-forum-kentish-town/</guid>
        <description>This is Peckham rapper Nathaniel Thompson’s first London headline show, despite over 10 years making music. He says he can’t believe this is finally here after all the aggro; it’s been a long time coming. Commonly known as Giggs, his accolades include BET best hip hop artist UK, and his latest album …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>So Long Forever – Palace
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-so-long-forever-palace/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 18:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-so-long-forever-palace/</guid>
        <description>So Long Forever is Palace’s eagerly anticipated debut album. The group have been releasing singles and EPs from 2012, turning heads and building up a loyal fan base. Wah-wah guitars compliment frontman Wyndam’s distinctive woozy voice, delivering emotionally charged, repetitive lyrics. Track one, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>felix feminist power playlist
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-felix-feminist-power-playlist/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 23:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Simran Kukran,Abigael Bamgboye,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-felix-feminist-power-playlist/</guid>
        <description> 1 | Christina Aquilera Can&amp;rsquo;t Hold Us Down Listen to this when: you want to refute someone’s ‘witty’ remark. As females, there’s no doubt that we’ve all experienced some kind of sexism. Sometimes, it feels easier to ignore the stupidity after a long day. However, we have to tackle the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to survive exams
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-how-to-survive-exams/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 09:25:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-how-to-survive-exams/</guid>
        <description>There is a lot to be stressed out about at exam time. Whether it is your first year or your last, it is difficult to balance the intense workload with other commitments, such as arranging accommodation for next year. First and foremost, if you feel you are struggling to cope, whether you have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Check your privilege
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-check-your-privilege/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:10:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-check-your-privilege/</guid>
        <description>This piece is something of a sequel – the aftermath of a Women@Imperial week interview in FELIX about a month ago. I spoke about my experience at Imperial as a woman of colour, my reaction to sexist comments that were made as “jokes”, as well as the issue of gendered insults, particularly when it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Poppies are not a source of pride
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-poppies-are-not-a-source-of-pride/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 13:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-poppies-are-not-a-source-of-pride/</guid>
        <description>Wednesday 11th November marks 97 years since the armistice of the First World War. Across the UK, the poppy will be worn this month as a symbol of commemoration for all the lives lost and affected by conflict.
Every year the appeal is criticised for seeming to glorify war: the parade by the Royal …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can we ignore human rights abuses in China?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-can-we-ignore-human-rights-abuses-in-china/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 11:58:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-can-we-ignore-human-rights-abuses-in-china/</guid>
        <description>According to the College website, we are the UK’s number one research partner with China. In a speech welcoming Xi Jinping, Professor Alice Gast, president of the university, said “brilliant students and academic collaborations are making both the UK and China stronger, more prosperous and ready to …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
