<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Postgraduate on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/postgraduate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Postgraduate on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/postgraduate/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>5 Steps To Improve Your Emotional Intelligence</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-five-steps-improve-emotional-intelligence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sara Hendricks,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-five-steps-improve-emotional-intelligence/</guid>
        <description>Emotional Intelligence is the one life skill that many great leaders possess. Someone with a high emotional IQ can navigate the waters of all life situations. Emotional intelligence is the ability to manage your emotions as well as those around you. People often forget how important their emotional …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Silwood: Imperial’s Green Cupboard </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-silwood-imperial-s-green-cupboard/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jessica-Lee Cole,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-silwood-imperial-s-green-cupboard/</guid>
        <description>Did you know that Imperial College has postgraduate campus (read: farm) way out in the countryside? It’s a whopping 20 miles from South Kensington. It is easily the most remote campus, but also the most beautiful (suck it SK). I like to call it Imperial’s green cupboard. This is because, for me, it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Union’s promises towards PG are good. Sticking to these promises would be better.</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-the-union-s-promises-towards-pg-are-good-sticking-to-these-promises-would-be-better/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ute Thiermann,Hannah Jones,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-the-union-s-promises-towards-pg-are-good-sticking-to-these-promises-would-be-better/</guid>
        <description>In the beginning of my period as GSU President, I had frequent meetings with the Union’s Managing Director, Jarlath O’Hara, and some of the Officer Trustees, particularly Rob Tomkies [Union President] and Alejandro Luy [Deputy President (Education)]. Damn, we had really good plans! For the first …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Best Supervision meant to Imperial College PG Students this year?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-what-best-supervision-meant-to-imperial-college-pg-students-this-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ute Thiermann,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-what-best-supervision-meant-to-imperial-college-pg-students-this-year/</guid>
        <description>&amp;ldquo;I would like to nominate Professor Dominik Weiss from the Earth Science and Engineering department for the best supervision award. He is just a great guy and I am lucky to have him as my supervisor! I am coming towards the end of my PhD and I couldn’t have done it without him.
Dominik has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Black girl in STEM</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-a-black-girl-in-stem/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-a-black-girl-in-stem/</guid>
        <description>Where I’m from, the colour of my skin didn’t make me “the minority”, nor did being a female determine my academic success. Where I’m from, it was quite commonly joked about that the girls were smarter and more mature than the boys because, after all, “behind every successful man is a strong woman …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Rainbow Chemist at Imperial</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-a-rainbow-chemist-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Simeon Draganov,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-a-rainbow-chemist-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>I often find myself faced with questions from friends and colleagues such as “What is it like to be a gay man at uni?” or “How do others perceive you once they find out that you are gay?”. I used to ask the same questions during my undergraduate studies at UCL, prior to starting my MRes+PhD course …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Supervision Story </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-my-supervision-story/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ute Thiermann,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-my-supervision-story/</guid>
        <description>My objective to improve supervision at Imperial College has turned out to be a real conundrum. I hear endless stories of PG research students being unhappy with their level of supervision, the behaviour of their supervisors and precarious lab situations. Being aware of the sensitivity of these …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PhD Survival Tip: Mindfulness Through Art</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-phd-survival-tip-mindfulness-through-art/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Iman Ibrahim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-phd-survival-tip-mindfulness-through-art/</guid>
        <description>Undertaking PhD research can be a daunting experience. Not only does it challenge you intellectually, but it can put a strain on your mental wellbeing. A study published last year revealed that one in two PhD researchers experience psychological distress, while one in three is at risk of a common …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Super-talents need super-food – a PG perspective on h-bar cuts</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-super-talents-need-super-food-a-pg-perspective-on-h-bar-cuts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ute Thiermann,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-super-talents-need-super-food-a-pg-perspective-on-h-bar-cuts/</guid>
        <description>Life is our best teacher about how the biggest crises can be turned into the most fundamental opportunities for change. If there is one good thing about the h-bar food-cut tragedy, then it is the chance to take a step back and rethink how we provide and procure food at Imperial in general. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Supervision Story</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-supervision-story/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-supervision-story/</guid>
        <description>The PhD student – supervisor relationship is a strange one; it is rare that in a workplace you would have a single boss for three to four years or have the flexibility to come into work at 11am and have the freedom to take three hours for lunch if you so wish. Then again, a PhD isn’t a normal job; …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>That Awkward Silence</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-that-awkward-silence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emma Couves,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-that-awkward-silence/</guid>
        <description>Mental health provision, awareness and destigmatisation is as much a College issue as it is a national one; yet we still find it uncomfortable or difficult to talk about.
Recently I attended a workshop from the Royal Society of Chemistry on Wellbeing and Resilience; though it was not exactly what I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Supervision Story - February </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-supervision-story-1/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-supervision-story-1/</guid>
        <description>Dialogue. I believe that in the thorough yet enjoyable experience that the PhD can be, we all go through times of self-doubt and questioning. Not only about the research itself, but about our own capabilities and the, sometimes, fearful prospect of having to finish. I am glad to have a supportive …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is GSU Connect?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-what-is-gsu-connect/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Clare Chan,Hannah Jones,Sam Yu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-what-is-gsu-connect/</guid>
        <description>You are a scientist and have an entrepreneurship idea? Confused about how to make a business proposal or get the idea off the ground? Or, do you want to learn how you could turn your expertise and knowledge into a kick-starter that could change the world?!
If you think you have what it takes to: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Women in STEM: Report from a conference</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-women-in-stem-report-from-a-conference/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-women-in-stem-report-from-a-conference/</guid>
        <description>I was at a conference and a guy from a research centre approached me. Initially our conversation was on research but then he asked if I would like to go to a bar with him after the gala dinner. He looked at me in an erotic way that made me feel very uncomfortable. I told him that I couldn’t go with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A new PhD community? Yes, please.</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-a-new-phd-community-yes-please/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emma Couves,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-a-new-phd-community-yes-please/</guid>
        <description>Despite having been at Imperial for three years, adjusting to PhD life brought its own new challenges, both academic and in terms of maintaining work-life balance, managing my motivation and mental health and finding time to devote to exercise. At the start, when I knew literally no one, I wished I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Meet your GSU Committee!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-meet-your-gsu-committee/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Graduate Students&#39; Union,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-meet-your-gsu-committee/</guid>
        <description>The Graduate Students’ Union (GSU) is the representative body within the Imperial College Union for the postgraduate community across all Imperial campuses. The GSU works alongside the Imperial College Union President to ensure that the requirements of postgraduate students are catered for. The GSU …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why “Supervision Stories”?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-why-supervision-stories/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ute Thiermann,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-why-supervision-stories/</guid>
        <description>On 7th December 2018, we published our first supervision story (together with the first ever postgraduate focused content in Felix!). The reaction from students and staff at the College was polarised, spanning from enthusiastic support to harsh criticism. While one brave ex-Imperial student took the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Graduate Students’ Union hosts Hammersmith Event</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-graduate-students-union-hosts-hammersmith-event/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Clare Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-graduate-students-union-hosts-hammersmith-event/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday 21st November, Imperial College Union and the Graduate Students’ Union (GSU) teamed up with Feast Bar, located close to the Hammersmith and White City campuses of Imperial College to throw a fabulous social for postgraduate students located in the area. The event itself lured students …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Share your PhD supervision story - anonymous and impactful</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-share-your-phd-supervision-story-anonymous-and-impactful/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ute Thiermann,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-share-your-phd-supervision-story-anonymous-and-impactful/</guid>
        <description>The quality of PhD supervision is becoming a hot topic, not only at Imperial College but across the whole UK. Decision-makers across Imperial College are becoming increasingly aware that the quality of supervision is the major predictor of satisfaction and wellbeing of any PhD student. Together with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Supervision Story - December</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-supervision-story-december/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-supervision-story-december/</guid>
        <description>My experience as a postgraduate research student at Imperial was in complete contrast to my expectations.
A diligent and hardworking student, I was accustomed to high-level problem solving, difficult tasks, proposing and defending arguments and manipulating complex data and ideas. Eager for the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
