<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/gep07/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/gep07/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Famous last words
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-28-famous-last-words/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 11:21:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gregory Power,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-28-famous-last-words/</guid>
        <description>Dear Friend: it would appear that we are approaching the end. We’ve had some laughs, we’ve shed some tears. I think overall we had a pretty damn good time, wouldn’t you say?
I’ve very much enjoyed being one of the Music Editors for Felix this year. It’s one of those things that got me through the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Future sounds at BONED
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-11-future-sounds-at-boned/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2011 17:35:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gregory Power,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-11-future-sounds-at-boned/</guid>
        <description>Toby Ridler, A.K.A. Becoming Real, is one of the most promising young producers around today, giving birth to strange new music that tends to melt faces and scar minds. It also turns out he’s a really nice dude. He answered a few questions of mine in anticipation of his headlining set at BONED, the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BONED at Metric
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-boned-at-metric/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 19:56:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gregory Power,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-boned-at-metric/</guid>
        <description>Felix is throwing another rocking party at Imperial College Union’s live music venue and all around super-club, Metric, on Saturday 11th June.
Following the success of the first Felix Music Night - 19.02 - we bring you the most anticipated sequel of the Summer: BONED. Come gaze in awe at our …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Inescapable Fate are bringing the noise to BONED...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-inescapable-fate-are-bringing-the-noise-to-boned/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 19:51:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gregory Power,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-inescapable-fate-are-bringing-the-noise-to-boned/</guid>
        <description>If you have ever strolled into Imperial Union on a Jazz n’ Rock jam night, chances are you’ve been paralyzed by the sight of Inescapable Fate’s members tearing shit up with an admirable disregard for authorized decibel levels. Inescapable Fate (IF) is Imperial’s foremost death metal band, and they …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tin Can 44s release first EP
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-tin-can-44s-release-first-ep/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 19:03:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gregory Power,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-tin-can-44s-release-first-ep/</guid>
        <description>Imperial’s own blues maestros, The Tin Can 44s, have released their first studio recording: a five-track gem called The Speak Easy EP. Everyone who attended the first Felix Music Night on the 19th of February will remember The Tin Cans as “that wild bunch of whiskey-swiggers” that kept us grooving …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Album of the Week: Goblin
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-album-of-the-week-goblin/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 18:57:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gregory Power,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-album-of-the-week-goblin/</guid>
        <description>By now Odd Future are pretty much the biggest new thing in music, having just finished their first full-fledged European tour. They incited a bit of a riot at the Camden Crawl, where they outshined every other band present, and have an established and dedicated fanbase that just keeps on growing. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Odd Future killed them all
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-odd-future-killed-them-all/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 20:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gregory Power,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-odd-future-killed-them-all/</guid>
        <description>If you are even remotely interested in music, and regardless of your stylistic preferences, then there is a strong chance you have heard of Odd Future Wolf Gang Kill Them All by now (Odd Future for the lazy). If you have not, then you must be living under a rock somewhere with no wi-fi, phone or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>19.02: Felix Music Night
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-1902-felix-music-night/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 21:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gregory Power,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-1902-felix-music-night/</guid>
        <description>This one goes out to all the cool cats and saucy mamas who turned up for the first ever Felix Music Night on Saturday 19th February. I hope all 250 people who were there that night had a great time, and from the looks on people’s faces as they left Metric when the event was over, I believe it was a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bow before your alien overlord, puny Earthlings!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-bow-before-your-alien-overlord-puny-earthlings/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 20:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gregory Power,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-bow-before-your-alien-overlord-puny-earthlings/</guid>
        <description>After years of scouring through the Necronomicon and the Dead Sea Scrolls searching for proof of the existence of the mythical extraterrestrial pharaoh known as Raath-Mon-Tet, a friend suggested I should Google him.
I had not thought of that. I guess I just did not expect to find one of the most …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tin Cans talkin’ Blues
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-tin-cans-talkin-blues/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 20:09:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gregory Power,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-tin-cans-talkin-blues/</guid>
        <description>Sometimes life just kicks you square in the balls. It sucks, but it is an intrinsic part of Mother Nature’s menstrual cycle.Yeah I know it hurts because it turns out that chick you liked is actually a total slag. And that guy you thought was giving you the eye? He happens to be a sex offender. Life …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>19.02: Fun-loving funk
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-1902-fun-loving-funk/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 19:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gregory Power,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-1902-fun-loving-funk/</guid>
        <description>Some people take music way too seriously. Praise Jeebus then for bands like The Eleven 37s. Mixing the fun vibes of funk with the raw energy of rock, they play party music of the best breed, sure to get you dancing and leaving you with a smile on your face.
We spoke about crazy dancing, gig size to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bye, bye, White Stripes
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-bye-bye-white-stripes/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 19:12:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gregory Power,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-bye-bye-white-stripes/</guid>
        <description>Sad news for rock fans across the world: The White Stripes are no more.
I remember hearing “Fell In Love With A Girl” for the first time like it was yesterday. The year was 2002, nu-metal was in its dying days and like many other teenagers back then my reference points were more “Hybrid Theory” and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Balls out rock at 19.02
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-balls-out-rock-at-1902/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 20:38:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gregory Power,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-balls-out-rock-at-1902/</guid>
        <description>It’s tough being a guitar band in 2011. Only three guitar-based tunes were featured in the UK’s top 100 best-selling songs of 2010. It gets even more depressing when you realise that half of the top 40 songs featured were by David Guetta, Black Eyed Peas or Rihanna.
I still believe there is hope yet …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Music Night coming to Metric on Saturday 19th February!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-felix-music-night-coming-to-metric-on-saturday-19th-february/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 20:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gregory Power,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-felix-music-night-coming-to-metric-on-saturday-19th-february/</guid>
        <description>Students of Imperial College, UNITE! Sorry, I’ve always wanted to say that.
We’re throwing a party at Imperial College’s very own Union live music venue and all around super-club, Metric, on Saturday 19th February. It will feature a showcase of Imperial’s musical talent, featuring three live bands …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Dillinger Escape Plan are goddamn terrifying... and terrific
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-the-dillinger-escape-plan-are-goddamn-terrifying-and-terrific/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2010 20:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gregory Power,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-the-dillinger-escape-plan-are-goddamn-terrifying-and-terrific/</guid>
        <description>Dillinger have been one of my favorite bands ever since I first heard “Calculating Infinity”. I distinctly recall a spasm-inducing epiphany. Since then they’ve changed a fair amount: guitar virtuoso Ben Weinman is the only remaining original member of the band and their music, though firmly rooted …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brave New World
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-brave-new-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 21:19:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gregory Power,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-brave-new-world/</guid>
        <description>Something crazy is going on with this internet thing. Oh sure, there’s always some kind of weird video of people shooting a bear and doing ungodly things over it afterwards, but I’m not talking about that. I mean a social media revolution, involving music in particular. Social media is Youtube, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial’s own DJ Physics returns
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-imperials-own-dj-physics-returns/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 19:38:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gregory Power,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-imperials-own-dj-physics-returns/</guid>
        <description>I’ve always regretted the absence of coverage of the ‘Imperial Music Scene’ by Felix. As Music Editor I’ve made it my duty to find the brightest young musicians at Imperial and extract juicy musical knowledge from their souls.
Who better to start with then but Martin Archer, an Imperial Physics …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
