<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Imported on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/tags/imported/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Imported on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/tags/imported/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Colour and Light: Degas&#39; mastery of pastels
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-25-colour-and-light-degas-mastery-of-pastels/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 12:41:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-25-colour-and-light-degas-mastery-of-pastels/</guid>
        <description>Glasgow’s Burrell Collection, which was amassed by shipping magnate William Burrell, is closed until 2020 for refurbishment; a loss, perhaps, for Glasgow, but a boon for Londoners, who are able to view the Collection’s celebrated Degas works, which have never travelled before as a group. It is these …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Getting to the truth of Jasper Johns
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-22-getting-to-the-truth-of-jasper-johns/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 18:56:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-22-getting-to-the-truth-of-jasper-johns/</guid>
        <description>On the way out of the press viewing of the Royal Academy&amp;rsquo;s latest exhibition, Jasper Johns: ‘Something Resembling Truth’, an immense monograph of the titan of 20th century American art, I overhear a fragment of a conversation: “and when did he die?”
Johns is still going strong, but it is an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cassini bids farewell in its Grand Finale
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-15-cassini-bids-farewell-in-its-grand-finale/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 12:09:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kenza Tazi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-15-cassini-bids-farewell-in-its-grand-finale/</guid>
        <description>Before 1:00 PM (GMT) today, the Cassini spacecraft will bid us a final farewell. We will take a closer look at this mission, the furthest orbiting space operation from Earth, and what we can expect in the last moments of Cassini’s life.
On October 15th 1997, Cassini was launched from Cape Canaveral, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial drops nine places in the QS World Graduate Employability Rankings
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-14-imperial-drops-nine-places-in-the-qs-world-graduate-employability-rankings/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 15:24:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-14-imperial-drops-nine-places-in-the-qs-world-graduate-employability-rankings/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London has dropped nine places in the QS Graduate Employability Rankings, which were released earlier this week, putting it at 29th place.
The rankings, which are “arguably the most extensive attempt to make a global comparison of the employability outcomes achieved by higher …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Waiting for Godot has its definitive homecoming at the Arts Theatre
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-12-waiting-for-godot-has-its-definitive-homecoming-at-the-arts-theatre/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 09:25:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-12-waiting-for-godot-has-its-definitive-homecoming-at-the-arts-theatre/</guid>
        <description>Billed as its “definitive homecoming” Samuel Beckett’s tragicomedy Waiting for Godot returns to the Arts Theatre after the first English-language production premiered there in 1955.
Nick Devlin and Patrick O’Donnell are delightfully childish and mercurial as vagabonds Didi and Gogo, who seem to love …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Government to implement crackdown on high pay in universities
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-11-government-to-implement-crackdown-on-high-pay-in-universities/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 15:41:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-11-government-to-implement-crackdown-on-high-pay-in-universities/</guid>
        <description>Universities will have to justify the salaries of their highest earners or face fines, in new governmental plans unveiled last week.
Jo Johnson, the Minister of State for Universities, Science, Research and Innovation, used a speech to the annual Universities UK (UUK) conference to highlight the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial maintains its place in the Times Higher Education global rankings
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-7-imperial-maintains-its-place-in-the-times-higher-education-global-rankings/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 15:52:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-7-imperial-maintains-its-place-in-the-times-higher-education-global-rankings/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London has maintained its ranking in the Times Higher Education (THE) World Rankings, placing 8th for the third consecutive year.
Imperial was one of three universities to make it into the top ten, alongside Oxford and Cambridge Universities, who came first and second, respectively. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Medical school cancels resit at the last minute after security breach
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-5-medical-school-cancels-resit-at-the-last-minute-after-security-breach/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 09:51:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-5-medical-school-cancels-resit-at-the-last-minute-after-security-breach/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College School of Medicine (ICSM) were forced to cancel a resit for final year medical students last week less than 12 hours before it was due, citing an “exam security breach”.
The resit of the Practical Assessment of Clinical Examination Skills (PACES) was scheduled to take place in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Xenia Hall&#39;s management to be taken over by Salvation Army Housing Association
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-1-xenia-halls-management-to-be-taken-over-by-salvation-army-housing-association/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 09:14:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-1-xenia-halls-management-to-be-taken-over-by-salvation-army-housing-association/</guid>
        <description>Chapter 1, the charity that owns and manages Xenia hall, is to be merged with the Salvation Army Housing Association (Saha) at the end of September.
The hall, which is located in Waterloo, accommodates 149 Imperial students. Saha, “a leading provider of residential centres for single and homeless …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brainsnatchers: Microbes that change the way we behave
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-31-brainsnatchers-microbes-that-change-the-way-we-behave/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 10:57:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maya Kaushik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-31-brainsnatchers-microbes-that-change-the-way-we-behave/</guid>
        <description>Friday night, work finally done, I sit down in my favourite pub and order a pint. I’m tired, maybe a bit grumpy. A couple of pints in and I’m happy, my energy levels are up, I’m chatting to everyone vibrantly. A couple more pints and I’m dragging myself home somewhat stupefied.
Alcohol is just one …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cooked breakfast removed from SCR menu amid wide-ranging changes to campus services
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-26-cooked-breakfast-removed-from-scr-menu-amid-wide-ranging-changes-to-campus-services/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2017 14:02:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-26-cooked-breakfast-removed-from-scr-menu-amid-wide-ranging-changes-to-campus-services/</guid>
        <description> On the 31st July, the Senior Common Room (SCR) served its last cooked breakfast to Imperial College London staff and students. From the 1st August, the SCR has removed cooked breakfasts from its menu as part of a wide-ranging series of changes to campus services, affecting a number of areas.
As …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>National Student Survey results reveal wide ranges in student satisfaction
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-25-national-student-survey-results-reveal-wide-ranges-in-student-satisfaction/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 10:26:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-25-national-student-survey-results-reveal-wide-ranges-in-student-satisfaction/</guid>
        <description> The results from the National Student Survey (NSS), which saw a number of universities omitted following a boycott, show a divide among Imperial students, with a wide range in satisfaction rates between undergraduate courses.
The survey, which is given to all final-year undergraduates, showed that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Against | A necessary exploration of violence and religion in the modern world
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-22-against-a-necessary-exploration-of-violence-and-religion-in-the-modern-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 21:09:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henrietta Blohm,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-22-against-a-necessary-exploration-of-violence-and-religion-in-the-modern-world/</guid>
        <description>A small shrine of flowers, candles, soft animals and religious memorabilia, a sight most usually attributed to the aftermath of acts of terrorism or massacres, lay at the bottom of the stage. Serving as a visceral reminder of the extended, emotional damage of acts of violence, the stage design …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your Name: Freaky Friday by way of Kierkegaard
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-20-your-name-freaky-friday-by-way-of-kierkegaard/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 18:26:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-20-your-name-freaky-friday-by-way-of-kierkegaard/</guid>
        <description>In his latest amine film Your Name, which has broken box-office records in Japan and beyond, director Makoto Shinkai chooses a plot-line which has a long pedigree: body swapping. Shuffling characters’ consciousnesses around is a trope that stretches back to the 19th Century and beyond. In Your Name, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial student halls fail fire safety tests on cladding
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-9-imperial-student-halls-fail-fire-safety-tests-on-cladding/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 09:48:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-9-imperial-student-halls-fail-fire-safety-tests-on-cladding/</guid>
        <description>The cladding system used in Woodward Buildings, one of Imperial College London’s newly-built student halls, has failed governmental fire safety testing. Sources from inside the hall also report multiple failures to adhere to fire safety policy, Felix can reveal.
The results of the tests were …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Eurovision Song Contest: The pop and the politics*
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-7-eurovision-song-contest-the-pop-and-the-politics/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 08:55:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-7-eurovision-song-contest-the-pop-and-the-politics/</guid>
        <description> I once had the misfortune of watching Eurovision with only an Argentinian, a Mexican, and a Lebanese for company. If you’re not European (or Australian, apparently), Eurovision seems to be very confusing and completely un-understandable. For us Europeans, either on the mainland or stuck on little …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Words can help us understand this
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-7-words-can-help-us-understand-this/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 08:44:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-7-words-can-help-us-understand-this/</guid>
        <description>Under the strain of thousands of people seeking refuge in Europe, several countries including Germany began to restrict their borders, after decades of free travel within the continent and the Schengen Area.
As a result, my well­ planned and advance booked night train from Vienna to Munich, being a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cyclists don’t follow the same rules
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-7-cyclists-dont-follow-the-same-rules/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 08:41:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-7-cyclists-dont-follow-the-same-rules/</guid>
        <description>New year, new you; the only time of the year when there’s a dramatic increase in the number of cyclists on the roads – with the exception of during tube strikes, that is. As a cyclist, there’s a definite sense of safety in numbers, and more people taking up this underrated method of getting around …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LFF: Manchester by the Sea
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-5-lff-manchester-by-the-sea/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 20:37:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Stephens,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-5-lff-manchester-by-the-sea/</guid>
        <description>If you were to rely on the list of previous winners of the Best Actor Oscar as a definitive list of cinema history’s greatest performances, you would probably have one clear go-to when thinking of acting techniques for a sure-fire win (apart from being white): shouting. It has seemed throughout the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LFF: La La Land
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-5-lff-la-la-land/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 20:30:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Stephens,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-5-lff-la-la-land/</guid>
        <description>It turns out Ryan Gosling is as roguishly charming and wonderful in person as we all hoped he would be. I was lucky enough to see La La Land for the first time at a London Film Festival screening, after which he appeared to a hurricane of cheers and thrown roses/knickers for a Q&amp;amp;A. When asked …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LFF: A Monster Calls
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-5-lff-a-monster-calls/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 20:27:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Meryl Chittethazhathu Anil,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-5-lff-a-monster-calls/</guid>
        <description>Storytellers are a threat,” wrote Chinua Achebe, “they threaten all champions of control, usurpers of the right-to-freedom of the human spirit”. It is this power, that of a simple story well-told, that director J. A. Bayona is trying to tap with his latest feature A Monster Calls, an adaptation of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LFF: Certain Women | Postcards from the edge of solitude
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-5-lff-certain-women-postcards-from-the-edge-of-solitude/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 20:22:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Meryl Chittethazhathu Anil,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-5-lff-certain-women-postcards-from-the-edge-of-solitude/</guid>
        <description>Certain Women, American director Kelly Reichardt’s sixth film, begins with a shot that serves as a statement of intent: a rusting old train slowly drags itself across the Montana landscape, framed by snowy mountain peaks; stoic in its solitude, it chuffs and puffs along the track, determined to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cat on a Hot Tin Roof | Jack O&#39;Connell shines in the Tennessee Williams classic
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-2-cat-on-a-hot-tin-roof-jack-oconnell-shines-in-the-tennessee-williams-classic/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 12:37:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-2-cat-on-a-hot-tin-roof-jack-oconnell-shines-in-the-tennessee-williams-classic/</guid>
        <description>In arguably what is Tennessee William’s most famous play, yearning and desperation boil over in the oppressive heat of the Mississippi delta. Brick Politt, the indulged youngest son, a onetime all-star athlete sinks into alcoholism to appease his gnawing guilt. His wife Maggie is driven to the edge …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Andrada’s trans-European culinary summer adventure
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-andradas-trans-european-culinary-summer-adventure/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 17:12:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-andradas-trans-european-culinary-summer-adventure/</guid>
        <description>Believe it or not, this is the last food tip of the year – and it makes me feel both sad and relieved. Because there is no dish that’s really good enough to celebrate the end of the year, the promise of summer and freedom, I decided to create the perfect trans-European food itinerary for you.
If you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>XU | the brainchild of BAO is a beautiful addition to the London food scene
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-xu-the-brainchild-of-bao-is-a-beautiful-addition-to-the-london-food-scene/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 17:10:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-xu-the-brainchild-of-bao-is-a-beautiful-addition-to-the-london-food-scene/</guid>
        <description>Two years into this half-university-student-half-food-blogger life of mine and I already have a lifetime’s worth of cringe worthy moments – mostly encountered during blogger events and restaurant invites. Imagine: turning up to the door of a launch event to know that my name had never been added to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The imperfect ending
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-imperfect-ending/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 17:06:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-imperfect-ending/</guid>
        <description>Gaming isn’t all fun and games perhaps ironically. In fact gamers are often pressed for time, having to juggle life admin and professional obligations on top of their gaming habit. It’s fair to say we rarely have the time to complete many games, and if we do, more often than not we’re ‘rewarded’ …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>E3 2017 | Follow up
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-e3-2017-follow-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 17:06:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Qasim Mahmood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-e3-2017-follow-up/</guid>
        <description>Microsoft had a few more reveals, including PlayerUnknown’s Battlegrounds, State of Decay 2, Minecraft in 4K and DragonBall FighterZ. They then proceeded to an extended look at Sea of Thieves, Rare’s open-world pirate game, which featured treasure hunting, riddle solving and a large-scale naval …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Lives of Others | Master of None S2
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-lives-of-others-master-of-none-s2/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 17:03:24 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-lives-of-others-master-of-none-s2/</guid>
        <description>Two years ago, comedian Aziz Ansari debuted his Netflix original series, Master of None. The show proved to be a critical darling, charming viewers with its mix of insightfulness, comedy, and genuineness. After its stellar first season, the series took a one year break; only recently did it return …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Swet Shop Boys | Rap heroes of our time
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-swet-shop-boys-rap-heroes-of-our-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 17:01:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-swet-shop-boys-rap-heroes-of-our-time/</guid>
        <description>On the first of June, midway through his set, Riz Ahmed signalled for the sold-out crowd at Scala to quiet down. Leaning in close, unaccompanied by music, he rapped his 2011 single Sour Times; “Please allow me to vouch for mine…/ losing my religion to tomorrow’s headlines”. It had been exactly a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Fellwanderers Easter Tour
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-imperial-fellwanderers-easter-tour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:59:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Emma McCracken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-imperial-fellwanderers-easter-tour/</guid>
        <description>Following an early flight at 7am from Gatwick to Aberdeen, we arrived in the scenic village Braemar in the Cairngorms national park at around 1pm. Kate, the provider of Rucksacks accommodation, greeted us as we sleepily got off the bus. Luckily Braemar was the end of the line, as otherwise we …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Three years after my roommate’s death I’m ready to move on
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-three-years-after-my-roommates-death-im-ready-to-move-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:56:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonathan Masters,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-three-years-after-my-roommates-death-im-ready-to-move-on/</guid>
        <description>A few weeks ago I finally came to the end of my three year course at Imperial, and although it is a cliché, the time has simply flown by. As I handed in the final final final draft of my undergraduate dissertation into turnitin, I suddenly burst into tears. Now it could have been a combination of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nutt talks at Psychedelics Studies Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-nutt-talks-at-psychedelics-studies-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:50:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-nutt-talks-at-psychedelics-studies-imperial/</guid>
        <description>The psychedelic renaissance is here. Psychedelic Studies Imperial launched their venture last Wednesday with a mind-expanding talk by Professor David Nutt.
Despite initially being told that psychedelics was too niche a subject to form a society around, the PSI has sprung into life with the aim of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College gets collection points for Grenfell Tower fire victims
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-college-gets-collection-points-for-grenfell-tower-fire-victims/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:49:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-college-gets-collection-points-for-grenfell-tower-fire-victims/</guid>
        <description>Following the fire that engulfed Grenfell Tower in the early hours last Wednesday, claiming 17 lives and injuring many more, some critically, Imperial College set up clothes and bedding donation points at the main entrance to the South Kensington campus and in White City at the Gradpad Wood Lane …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sport to be reshuffled next year
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-sport-to-be-reshuffled-next-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abigail E de Bruin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-sport-to-be-reshuffled-next-year/</guid>
        <description>Since about January, there have been rumblings in the Union of a big sports shake-up. We got in touch with James Cox, current Deputy President (Clubs and Societies) to see what’s happening now that things are pretty much ready to be openly discussed. It appears we are set to go into a full year of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Abuse is not a valid comment
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-abuse-is-not-a-valid-comment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:45:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-abuse-is-not-a-valid-comment/</guid>
        <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been writing and editing Comment for felix for years, and it’s my strongly held opinion that a student newspaper without opinion is not a student newspaper worth having. University is a time when we’re all growing up, finding ourselves and forming our beliefs, and a huge part of this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Writing mental illness off as a personality quirk is dangerous</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-writing-mental-illness-off-as-a-personality-quirk-is-dangerous/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:44:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-writing-mental-illness-off-as-a-personality-quirk-is-dangerous/</guid>
        <description>Two weeks ago, I read an article in felix posing the question: “Are we medicalising personality?” The author argues that self-diagnosis of a mental health problem can be risky. I agree. They argue that convincing yourself you have a mental illness when you don’t, can make you miserable. I agree. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It doesn&#39;t matter if you&#39;re queer or not, you need to support Gay Pride
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-it-doesnt-matter-if-youre-queer-or-not-you-need-to-support-gay-pride/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:43:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-it-doesnt-matter-if-youre-queer-or-not-you-need-to-support-gay-pride/</guid>
        <description>It doesn’t matter if you’re queer or not. You need to support Gay Pride.
It’s that rainbow month of the year again, when queers all around the world take to the streets to celebrate being alive and every bigoted dickhead gets the opportunity to rant about how they “don’t mind The Gays but do they …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The failings of the Conservatives
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-failings-of-the-conservatives/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:42:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-failings-of-the-conservatives/</guid>
        <description>Theresa May went for a power grab. She wanted to wipe out Labour while her party was polling with almost 20 points ahead of them. With a fragmented opposition and Corbyn’s poor approval ratings, everyone assumed it was going to be a landslide election. So how did this all backfire and end up in a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who are the DUP?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-who-are-the-dup/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:41:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ratan Gor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-who-are-the-dup/</guid>
        <description>Last week’s general election marked a momentous occasion. The youth, generally considered docile and apathetic when it comes to politics and voting, went out in their droves to flex their muscle. The main battleground for the election was social media. The weapons of choice: memes and parody videos …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>So long... and thank you for all the fish
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-so-long-and-thank-you-for-all-the-fish/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:25:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-so-long-and-thank-you-for-all-the-fish/</guid>
        <description>It’s the final issue. I’ve ranted for some 28 editions now and you guys have taken it like champs. In my last editorial I’d like to say one final thing before I fade into irrelevance. I want to talk about complaining.
I’m a great complainer. I bitch and moan about everything. I quit an online …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What a week
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-what-a-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:21:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-what-a-week/</guid>
        <description>What a week. Since last Friday, shit has hit the fan. Much like an evil mastermind in a superhero movie, Donald Trump has announced to the world his evil plan to fuck over the planet: quitting the Paris Agreement. The only differences are that he’s as thick (but slightly more orange) as mustard, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>(1) 666 number of the beast
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-1-666-number-of-the-beast/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:19:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-1-666-number-of-the-beast/</guid>
        <description>Fun fact: we originally had big plans for issue 1666. We were gonna do a ‘pagan issue’ dedicated to religion, with a graphic illustration of the Devil splashed across the front cover. But then in April, May announced a snap general election and we were like ‘God damn’. We forfeited the pagan issue …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Summer lovin’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-summer-lovin/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:15:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-summer-lovin/</guid>
        <description>Summer is officially here. You can tell by the hoards of panting students waiting to get served at FiveSixEight. You can also tell because felix has succumbed to society’s pressures and has dropped to half its original weight in preparation for the beach. For real though yesterday was so hot I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is news?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-what-is-news/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:13:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-what-is-news/</guid>
        <description>In fact let’s go deeper. What is a newspaper? If it’s a publication propelled by the propagation of news to its readers, then let me tell you; you’re in for a treat because this is the newsiest, newspaper we’ve ever made. I’m obviously referring to the twelve page (centrefold included) sex survey …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Divest this
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-divest-this/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:10:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-divest-this/</guid>
        <description>Is Imperial morally bankrupt? I first asked myself this question in 2011 when I started my Biology undergraduate. My department had just sacked most, if not all of its plant scientists. There was no money in the field. Have I come close to an answer since? Maybe. Sometimes I’ve looked at Imperial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We’re back. Pitches?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-were-back-pitches/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:06:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-were-back-pitches/</guid>
        <description>Yay! The Easter break is over! Yay&amp;hellip;”
Lef suddenly stopped typing, an overwhelming feeling of sadness taking over him. He thought of all those hours he’d idly spent in bed, no stupid print deadlines, no stupid paper distribution cutting his sleep short. He thought of all that nutritious …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>k bye.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-k-bye/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-k-bye/</guid>
        <description>Finally, the last issue (of term). I have been waiting for this moment for too long. While I’m going to miss putting together this wonderful publication for the next few weeks, I’ll be honest with you, I’m super excited to lay back and relax, maybe get a massage, definitely re-balance my sleep and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Memememememememe
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-memememememememe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:57:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-memememememememe/</guid>
        <description>Chill. Happy thoughts. Breathe in, breathe out. This issue is about self-care, which ideally would have involved me taking a holiday and getting my tan on, maybe on a small, secluded beach in the Canary Islands. But obviously I can’t just leave you guys hanging. How are you supposed to do the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My manifesto
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-my-manifesto/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:55:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-my-manifesto/</guid>
        <description>Hello everyone. My name is Lef. Some of you might know me from my reign of terror as felix editor. Others might have spotted me making short sustenance runs to the union or the JCR (dem buns tho&amp;hellip;) and might have admired my luscious locks or strong eye-liner game. Regardless of your …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Elections should be fun
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-elections-should-be-fun/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:52:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-elections-should-be-fun/</guid>
        <description>Let’s be honest. Everything we do, we do in the name of fun. Sure you can use fancy lingo, such as pleasure, satisfaction, gratification, joy, and even gusto if you’re that kind of person, but at the end of the day, fun does the trick just fine.
The reason we make babies is because sex is fun. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Going green is hard
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-going-green-is-hard/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:50:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-going-green-is-hard/</guid>
        <description>Oh my god this issue is so green. SO GREEN I TELL YOU. Just reading it will make you healthier and add at least one year to your sad, Imperial-stunted life. You might wonder why. You might even vocally ask me on the off chance you spot me outdoors “why are you doing a Green Issue Lef? Caring about …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Love is love
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-love-is-love/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:47:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-love-is-love/</guid>
        <description>February is LGBT history month (yes, I know – I only just found out too) and my heart is filled with joy because for the first time ever I’m actually clued up. I also feel more a part of the queer community than I’ve ever felt before. I can’t really explain why, but it is what it is and I’m glad, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Feeeeeeeeeed meeeeeeee
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-feeeeeeeeeed-meeeeeeee/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:45:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-feeeeeeeeeed-meeeeeeee/</guid>
        <description>This issue is quite clearly dedicated to food. Whether you eat it, throw it up, get high on it, or get down and dirty with it (hey, we don’t judge) food is a fundamental part of the human existence. We carefully selected this week to talk about food, because Eating Disorder Awareness Week is coming …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Resistance is not futile. We think.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-resistance-is-not-futile-we-think/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:40:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-resistance-is-not-futile-we-think/</guid>
        <description>Well we honestly tried – you know, taking a break from the doom and gloom. With the end of 2016, we were eager to turn over a new leaf, start anew with starry eyes full of hope for the future. But since Trump’s inauguration last Friday, it’s just been an onslaught of bad news, dumb news, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hang in there kitties
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-hang-in-there-kitties/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:35:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-hang-in-there-kitties/</guid>
        <description>Blue Monday, alternatively known as the most depressing day of the year, came and went this week (Blue like hands without gloves flaunted at passing strangers on the street. Wait what?). By now you’ve come to terms with the fact that you probably spent way too much money over Christmas. You’ve also …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The post new year’s blues
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-post-new-years-blues/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:29:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-post-new-years-blues/</guid>
        <description>One of my friends recently pointed out I’m going through a quarter-life crisis, that we (our group of friends) all are. And I can see where he’s coming from. We’re all in our mid-twenties and we seem to permanently be at a crossroads. Transcending from adolescence into adulthood (it’s… a process) – …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>felix navidad
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-felix-navidad/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:24:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-felix-navidad/</guid>
        <description>It’s beginning to look a lot like Christmas. The tube is packed, the streets are clogged, shopping is a nightmare, and you keep embarrassing yourself, blurting out family secrets at dinners, to people you barely know.
Meanwhile, there are all these fake gifts everywhere: stupid, empty, gift-wrapped …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My head hurts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-my-head-hurts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:21:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-my-head-hurts/</guid>
        <description>This is a very special editorial, a very special issue even. Partly because I started writing it after smacking my head on the cold, hard asphalt just past Kensington Gardens (I know it looks cool to have your flowy hair trailing behind you as you cycle, but don’t do it kids. Don’t cycle without a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We’re almost there
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-were-almost-there/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:18:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-were-almost-there/</guid>
        <description>Another week, another quality paper. The holidays are fast approaching, and let me tell you I cannot wait. For a glorious three weeks I will not have to work like a madman and I can catch up on all the Westworld I’ve missed, and go through my inbox, print all my unread mail, put it in little …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The lady doth protest too much
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-lady-doth-protest-too-much/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:16:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-lady-doth-protest-too-much/</guid>
        <description>Warning: I’m really tired, I have a million things to do including packing a suitcase for a weekend escape (yay me), and this editorial has been a pain in the butt to write. So prepare yourself for some really wishy washy stuff, cause I’m on course to work 54 hours this week and at this point I just …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We’ve all got daddy issues
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-weve-all-got-daddy-issues/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:13:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-weve-all-got-daddy-issues/</guid>
        <description>Change is in the air. Imperial College has taken up recommendations to improve student satisfaction made by the Union, the Higher Education and Research Bill has just been amended, an education demo is taking place in London this weekend, and Donald Trump’s backtracking behaviour has captured the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It happened
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-it-happened/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:11:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-it-happened/</guid>
        <description>The dreaded day has come and gone. The world has changed. Donald Trump is a democratically elected world leader. I don’t think I’ve processed the tangible reality of the above sentence quite yet (and what a sentence: four years, eight years, or life?).
The man who inflamed an already polarised …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I’ve had it
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-ive-had-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 14:49:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-ive-had-it/</guid>
        <description>Three weeks in and I have nearly had it. Don’t get me wrong, editing a major cough newspaper is fun but it is exhausting. On Wednesday, I got an email from the printers at 19:51, ten minutes before leaving the office which wrote: “Hi Lef, If you run into trouble tonight pls call my home number on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Post freshers’ blues
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-post-freshers-blues/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 14:46:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-post-freshers-blues/</guid>
        <description>So. Here we are once again, two weeks in a row. One more week and it will have become an unhealthy habit, like smoking, binge-watching Netflix, or reassuming the leadership of UKIP.
This week everything sucks. For starters we’ve all got freshers’ flu, passing it on like a joint at a house party (the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Soul of a Nation | A searing portrait of the Civil Rights Era
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-23-soul-of-a-nation-a-searing-portrait-of-the-civil-rights-era/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 12:13:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-23-soul-of-a-nation-a-searing-portrait-of-the-civil-rights-era/</guid>
        <description>“Is there a black aesthetic, and if there is, what form does it take?” is the question that concerns the artists assembled for Soul of a Nation. For some, like the Spiral collective, the answer lay in monochrome paintings with a strong political message. In Norman Lewis’ America the Beautiful, a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Swet Shop Boys | Rap heroes for our time
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-15-swet-shop-boys-rap-heroes-for-our-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 17:13:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-15-swet-shop-boys-rap-heroes-for-our-time/</guid>
        <description>On the first of June, midway through his set, Riz Ahmed signalled for the sold-out crowd at Scala to quieten down. Leaning in close, unaccompanied by music, he rapped his 2011 single Sour Times; “Please allow me to vouch for mine…/ losing my religion to tomorrow’s headlines”. It had been exactly a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Queer British Art (1861-1967) | Ostracised, criminalised, but never conquered
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-15-queer-british-art-1861-1967-ostracised-criminalised-but-never-conquered/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 15:59:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-15-queer-british-art-1861-1967-ostracised-criminalised-but-never-conquered/</guid>
        <description>Little rainbows have been popping up everywhere lately - on Facebook, in Skittles adverts, soon they’ll arriving on London’s streets. In fact, the rainbow flag has been flying over Tate Britain for some months now. The gallery will be kicking off the London Pride celebrations next Saturday with a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Anatomy of a Suicide | Alice Birch weaves a story of three women bound together by mental illness
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-15-anatomy-of-a-suicide-alice-birch-weaves-a-story-of-three-women-bound-together-by-mental-illness/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 15:32:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-15-anatomy-of-a-suicide-alice-birch-weaves-a-story-of-three-women-bound-together-by-mental-illness/</guid>
        <description>Anatomy of a Suicide follows the stories of three generations of women of the same family, linked together not only by their genetic heritage, but also by the same emotions and struggles as they battle with mental illness. Carol is a 1970s housewife, struggling to find reasons to stay in the world. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Summer Exhibition at the Royal Academy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-15-the-summer-exhibition-at-the-royal-academy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 15:17:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-15-the-summer-exhibition-at-the-royal-academy/</guid>
        <description>There aren’t many galleries in which you might expect to see a multimillion pound creation by a Turner prize winning artist exhibited on equal footing with an oil by Joe Bloggs from Surrey, but that is exactly what the Royal Academy’s Summer Exhibition offers. Each year, tens of thousands of works …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to dump someone (you met in Metric and subsequently fell in love with)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-how-to-dump-someone-you-met-in-metric-and-subsequently-fell-in-love-with/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 16:16:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Theresa Davey,Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-how-to-dump-someone-you-met-in-metric-and-subsequently-fell-in-love-with/</guid>
        <description> You were weak. Despite our foolproof guides on how to have a one night stand (in Metric), ‘How to have a one night stand (in Metric)’, and how not to fall in love with someone (from Metric), ‘How not to fall in love with someone (from Metric)’, you went ahead and fell in love with someone (from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Keeping Track of Imperial’s Cross Country &amp; Athletics Club
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-keeping-track-of-imperials-cross-country-athletics-club/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:42:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-keeping-track-of-imperials-cross-country-athletics-club/</guid>
        <description>Saturday the 27th of May saw the final event in the London Universities and Colleges Athletics (LUCA) outdoors championship take place. The series of three athletics meets between the London universities had previously visited St. Mary’s and Woodford athletics tracks, and the destination for the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lazy food edition | Chilled rice pudding with berry compote
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-lazy-food-edition-chilled-rice-pudding-with-berry-compote/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:39:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-lazy-food-edition-chilled-rice-pudding-with-berry-compote/</guid>
        <description> I’m back you fools and to celebrate let me share a story from my childhood.
When I was in elementary school, our teacher used to teach us different ‘life hacks’ based on science – she said. One of the most memorable things she ever said was that it’s better to drink a hot drink (hot tea) when it’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We’re all a bunch of boozy drug addicts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-were-all-a-bunch-of-boozy-drug-addicts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:34:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theo Farah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-were-all-a-bunch-of-boozy-drug-addicts/</guid>
        <description>Every single one of us has as some point been lectured about the dangers of cocaine, Adderall, and heroin. Take them once and it might not be long before you’re finding an excuse to take them again. Regardless of whether it’s the oh-so-good high or a few too many nights out one week, you can easily …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>E3 2017 | What to expect
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-e3-2017-what-to-expect/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:30:47 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Qasim Mahmood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-e3-2017-what-to-expect/</guid>
        <description>The biggest gaming event of the year is right around the corner; all the biggest gaming companies will be taking the stage to announce their plans for the upcoming year and showcase brand new games and consoles.
First up of the big three is Microsoft, and they are in the most interesting position of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The great age of the 3DS
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-the-great-age-of-the-3ds/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:25:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-the-great-age-of-the-3ds/</guid>
        <description> The 3DS has been the go-to portable games machine of its time, testified by the sales of over 65 million units, and is a shining example of how to make a perfect handheld console. Its only other portable rival, the Playstation Vita is as good as dead these days, and mobile games don’t even come …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Ode to Sense8
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-an-ode-to-sense8/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:11:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-an-ode-to-sense8/</guid>
        <description>Three weeks ago I embarked on an emotional binge-watch of the 2015 Netflix original Sense8. Within two weeks I’d managed to watch the 23 near hour-long episodes of the first two seasons. Then a week later it was announced that sense8 would not be getting renewed, that episode 23 would be the last …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Death in Dreamland | Archer S8
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-death-in-dreamland-archer-s8/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:08:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-death-in-dreamland-archer-s8/</guid>
        <description>The ever popular action-spy-office-whatever comedy returns for yet another season; one that again opts to change the show’s setting altogether. Given the show’s relatively niche premise, and its ever-falling viewership, it’s quite impressive that it has made it this far. It has even managed to be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Bionic Skin’ could give robots the sense of touch
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-bionic-skin-could-give-robots-the-sense-of-touch/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:03:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sophie Protheroe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-bionic-skin-could-give-robots-the-sense-of-touch/</guid>
        <description>As we are entering an age where robots are becoming more human, so are humans becoming increasingly attached to technology. Scientists have created a 3D printed ‘bionic skin’ which could give robots the sense of touch. This is a major step towards printing electronics onto human skin. Cyborgs, part …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ice, Ice Baby
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-ice-ice-baby/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:02:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aran Shaunak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-ice-ice-baby/</guid>
        <description>Fact: Hot water freezes faster than cold water.
Once upon a time, Erasto Mpemba was making ice cream in his cookery class. The sign of a good scientist? He noticed that the mix froze faster if it was hot, rather than just eating it.
First observed in the 1960s, this experiment has been repeated many …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Diesel pollution poses serious risk for asthma sufferers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-diesel-pollution-poses-serious-risk-for-asthma-sufferers/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:00:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Rachel Baxter,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-diesel-pollution-poses-serious-risk-for-asthma-sufferers/</guid>
        <description>Forty million British people are living in cities and towns with illegally high air pollution levels. This alarming statistic is in part due to diesel exhaust, which according to new research can directly affect our lungs and make respiratory conditions worse.
An international team of scientists led …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An ode to Shepherd&#39;s Bush
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-an-ode-to-shepherds-bush/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 14:59:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-an-ode-to-shepherds-bush/</guid>
        <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve lived in various places all over London over the last eight years, but I always come back to Shepherd’s Bush. It&amp;rsquo;s not the geographical convenience or the relative cheapness that keeps me there, it’s the fact that Shepherd’s Bush feels like home.
I feel at home on the Green, with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s not rational to be scared of terrorism
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-its-not-rational-to-be-scared-of-terrorism/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 14:57:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-its-not-rational-to-be-scared-of-terrorism/</guid>
        <description>Every time there’s a terrorist attack, the more skittish of my friends set about panicking. Marking themselves safe on Facebook, making dramatic social media posts, and generally creating the hysteria and alarm that follows a terrorist attack.
If a chemical weapon had been used, or if the numbers …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Trump can&#39;t ruin the environment by himself (even if he is trying)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-trump-cant-ruin-the-environment-by-himself-even-if-he-is-trying/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 14:56:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sara Hamilton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-trump-cant-ruin-the-environment-by-himself-even-if-he-is-trying/</guid>
        <description>There’s a lot one can say against Donald Trump, but thus far he has stuck to his word (or tried to a least). After doing his best to rid the US of ‘bad hombres’, last Thursday he proceeded to attack another of his enemies – the environment – by announcing the withdrawal of the US from the Paris …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Defeating ISIS is impossible. Dealing with them is not
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-defeating-isis-is-impossible-dealing-with-them-is-not/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 14:53:24 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-defeating-isis-is-impossible-dealing-with-them-is-not/</guid>
        <description>The UK has been subjected to a number of terrorist acts. At this point in time it is appropriate to mourn and honour the dead and remember that nothing can justify these acts. At the same time, it is important to look at this topic with nuance if we as a nation wish to solve this problem. Two …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union awards ceremony honours volunteers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-union-awards-ceremony-honours-volunteers/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 14:51:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-union-awards-ceremony-honours-volunteers/</guid>
        <description>Monday saw the Union thank its volunteers at the annual Union Awards.
During the event, which is meant to showcase the best of Imperial College Union and its membership, 69 (wink) students were awarded colours, a further 19 were awarded outstanding service and a final five students were given …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Consent Matters pilot launched
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-consent-matters-pilot-launched/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 14:49:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-consent-matters-pilot-launched/</guid>
        <description>Two terms since consent training became a subject of contention amongst Imperial students, the Consent Matters pilot has finally been launched. Consent Matters is an interactive course aiming at educating students on areas of sexual consent, communication and relationships, and bystander …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial academics on Trump and climate
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-imperial-academics-on-trump-and-climate/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 14:48:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-imperial-academics-on-trump-and-climate/</guid>
        <description>Last week Trump declared to the world that he’d be pulling the US out of the Paris Agreement. Within hours, Elon Musk resigned from the President’s Board of Advisors, American states such as California went rogue and protested the move, vouching to uphold their commitment anyway, and world leaders …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>&#34;Feverish Progress&#34; | Giacometti at the Tate Modern is comprehensive retrospective on a man with man
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-7-feverish-progress-giacometti-at-the-tate-modern-is-comprehensive-retrospective-on-a-man-with-man/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 08:14:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lizzie E Riach,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-7-feverish-progress-giacometti-at-the-tate-modern-is-comprehensive-retrospective-on-a-man-with-man/</guid>
        <description>Alberto Giacometti’s work has always been close to my heart. He was central to the wider body of artwork that inspired me to do art for GCSE and A level, and I&amp;rsquo;ve based countless of my own pieces on his. Despite being known more for his extremely thinly sculpted figures, it was actually his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The election and the NHS
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-the-election-and-the-nhs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 14:25:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Dan Faehndrich,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-the-election-and-the-nhs/</guid>
        <description>Since the surprise of 7th May 2015, the NHS has fallen into its darkest times since its inception. As a medical student, seeing my colleagues here and across the whole medical profession has, frankly, made becoming a doctor look the least appealing it’s looked since 14 year-old me decided it was the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why I’m voting Labour
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-why-im-voting-labour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 14:16:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-why-im-voting-labour/</guid>
        <description>Soft on security, denying the deficit, and incapable of addressing concerns over immigration. These sound like the sort of accusations the Conservatives levelled at the last Labour government not too long ago, and yet after seven years in government, these are all areas in which the Conservative …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why I’m voting Conservative
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-why-im-voting-conservative/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 14:14:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip N N Kurukgy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-why-im-voting-conservative/</guid>
        <description>Anyone who thinks that this election is not about Brexit, is out of touch with the reality of the task ahead. Brexit will be looked upon as a turning point in this country’s relationship with its neighbours. Some argued that this was the worst political choice this country has ever made. For a long …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Manifesto breakdowns
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-manifesto-breakdowns/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:59:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,Cale E Tilford,Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-manifesto-breakdowns/</guid>
        <description> This piece aims to break down the main party manifestos and summarise a few key policies. This is by no means a full and in-depth analysis of each party. Mainly because the manifestos are long and complex, and it’s exam season. [Insert tinfoil hat theory that the timing of the election coincides …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An idiot’s guide to the UK general election
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-an-idiots-guide-to-the-uk-general-election/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:57:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-an-idiots-guide-to-the-uk-general-election/</guid>
        <description>Ding ding ding, it’s election time again. No, you haven’t woken up from that nap in 2020, they’ve called an early election. Do you have no idea who you’re voting for? Well, you’re in luck my friend, because we’ve got a whole pull-out complete with manifesto breakdowns, and personal views on who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The near-peg experience
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-the-near-peg-experience/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:53:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-the-near-peg-experience/</guid>
        <description>I went home last week for a few days over the bank holiday. As always when I go home, I opened up Tinder and began to swipe. I mostly use it as a way to keep track of who from school is single, but sometimes use it to shark on hot students and locals.
I swiped right on a few people before I ran out …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Party candidates come to Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-party-candidates-come-to-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:50:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-party-candidates-come-to-imperial/</guid>
        <description>A hustings of local parliamentary candidates was held yesterday in Blackett which saw Victoria Borwick (Conservatives), Cllr Alan De’Ath (Labour), Bridget Fox (LibDems), Richard Braine (UKIP), and finally Bill Cashmore (Green), engaging in a debate on Education, Public Health and Brexit.
Borwick, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Atomic funding pours into Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-atomic-funding-pours-into-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:49:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-atomic-funding-pours-into-imperial/</guid>
        <description>The Atomic Weapons Establishment (AWE) has long been responsible for the UK’s nuclear deterrence programme. In addition to providing the nuclear warheads for each of the Vanguard submarines that make up Trident, the AWE contributes significant amounts to the coffers of Imperial.
Imperial is one of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Afterhours sessions in the Central Library
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-afterhours-sessions-in-the-central-library/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:29:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-afterhours-sessions-in-the-central-library/</guid>
        <description>How does one end up in the Library past midnight? Maybe you had a paper to submit tomorrow. You thought you had everything under control. You were halfway there but you made the mistake of taking a break and committing to an episode of the Great British Bake Off. Six hours later you get a text from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In defence of being flaky
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-in-defence-of-being-flaky/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:25:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-in-defence-of-being-flaky/</guid>
        <description>Be honest, we all have that friend who’s a complete flake. You know, you make plans with them only to have them cancel at the last minute. Maybe this happens repeatedly. They’re really fucking annoying, right? Maybe you don’t even want to bother to reschedule. Maybe they’re so flaky that you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dealing with escapism
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-dealing-with-escapism/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:22:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-dealing-with-escapism/</guid>
        <description>It should come as no surprise to anyone that life is a cruel mistress, especially if you’re in uni. With deadlines, exams and project work, it can quickly get overwhelming. Things can also be insanely frustrating (when for example, you put all your heart and soul into revising for a course but you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Course Correction | Doctor Who
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-course-correction-doctor-who/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:21:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-course-correction-doctor-who/</guid>
        <description>Halfway into the latest season of Doctor Who, set to be Peter Capaldi and showrunner Steven Moffat’s last, we have yet to be disappointed. After a rocky few seasons, the show began to show signs of recovery with last Christmas’ delightful, superhero themed fix. The first six episodes of series ten …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
