<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ml2909/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ml2909/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Is Feminism a Toxic Word? – Response
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-is-feminism-a-toxic-word-response/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 13:13:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marissa Lewis,Kirstin Hay,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-is-feminism-a-toxic-word-response/</guid>
        <description>I’ve been calling myself a feminist for about 10 years, and I started doing so for a simple reason – I believe women and men should be treated equally. I was not going to pretend not to be something because it might make others around me more comfortable.
Just to be sure, I looked up ‘feminism’ in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Higher Education Fees Debate - Graduate Tax
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-6-higher-education-fees-debate-graduate-tax/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 02:43:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marissa Lewis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-6-higher-education-fees-debate-graduate-tax/</guid>
        <description>Graduate Tax is a model of higher education funding that shockingly involves students paying a tax in line with their income after graduation. Some models of graduate tax involve graduates paying a rate of tax until retirement, or for a certain number of years after graduation or until the cost of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Helping friends with depression
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-helping-friends-with-depression/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 00:59:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marissa Lewis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-helping-friends-with-depression/</guid>
        <description>In the last Wellbeing section, I wrote about my experience with recovering from depression. Maybe it’s because I don’t make a habit of talking about my mental illness but I was genuinely surprised at the positive reception it received from friends, acquaintances and even complete strangers. As a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Recovering from depression
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-recovering-from-depression/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 04:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marissa Lewis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-recovering-from-depression/</guid>
        <description>There’s been a movement in the last couple of years to get people talking about their experiences with mental health, whether it’s on a national scale such as Mind’s Time to Talk campaign or Imperial’s own OpenMinds campaign. There’s also been a move to try and explain life with a mental illness to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Lobbies Lords For Our International Students
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-imperial-lobbies-lords-for-our-international-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 12:24:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marissa Lewis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-imperial-lobbies-lords-for-our-international-students/</guid>
        <description>There are two proposals in the Immigration Bill in particular which affect international students – the first is the introduction of an NHS fee of up to £200 per year of study, paid before entry into the country. For doctoral research students with families, this could add up to £3000 to their costs …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Evidence for sexism in the Union?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-evidence-for-sexism-in-the-union/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 22:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Osborne,Marissa Lewis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-evidence-for-sexism-in-the-union/</guid>
        <description>Inequality irritates me, particularly as it is so prevalent within our society. Women are oppressed on many different levels; here at Imperial the most recent evidence for this is the refusal by the NCC (New Clubs Committee) of a Gender Equality Society. The reasoning of the Union is as follows: we …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
