<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/pavan_inguva/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/pavan_inguva/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>A trip down memory lane: two mini reviews</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-a-trip-down-memory-lane-two-mini-reviews/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavan Inguva,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-a-trip-down-memory-lane-two-mini-reviews/</guid>
        <description>Before starting at Imperial, I took a short holiday to India to visit friends and family. For those of you who don’t know, India is an amazing place to buy books. You can get original prints of many books for a fraction of the price compared to any western country. Obviously I took this chance to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Of Missed Opportunities and Vanity: Books from the Balkans</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-of-missed-opportunities-and-vanity-books-from-the-balkans/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavan Inguva,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-of-missed-opportunities-and-vanity-books-from-the-balkans/</guid>
        <description>Normally, I would start off by sharing how I serendipitously came across a beautiful bookstore or an author, or book, related to the country I am travelling to. This isn’t one of those occasions. The two books I write about here came to me in a far more dubious manner. The first book was stuck in my …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Japanese literature through the ages</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-japanese-literature-through-the-ages/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavan Inguva,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-japanese-literature-through-the-ages/</guid>
        <description>I have become quite partial to Japanese literature as a literary category. Most examples share overarching similarities in aesthetic flavour, such as the notion of impermanence of being, which derive from both cultural and religious developments throughout Japanese history. These sensitivities, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix recommends Valentine&#39;s reads… or the books to help you to forget about romance</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-felix-recommends-valentine-s-reads-or-the-books-to-help-you-to-forget-about-romance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,Alice Peberdy,Indira Mallik,Pavan Inguva,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-felix-recommends-valentine-s-reads-or-the-books-to-help-you-to-forget-about-romance/</guid>
        <description> Written on the Body by Jeanette Winterson
 The first question is, who is the narrator? She or he is never named, and their gender never revealed. &amp;ldquo;Why is the measure of love loss?&amp;rdquo; asks the opening sentence, and throughout the book we are taken through the narrator’s clandestine …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Contemplating troubled pasts in the City of Literature</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-contemplating-troubled-pasts-in-the-city-of-literature/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavan Inguva,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-contemplating-troubled-pasts-in-the-city-of-literature/</guid>
        <description>The seeds of this article were sowed over December break, during a weekend I spent in Hamburg, Germany and a visit to Lubeck (Birthplace of Thomas Mann), followed by a week in Poland.
I only found out when in Krakow, that it is designated a UNESCO city of literature. This made more sense after …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>From high-school comedies to dark police dystopias – an anime for all seasons</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-from-high-school-comedies-to-dark-police-dystopias-an-anime-for-all-seasons/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavan Inguva,Mingrou Xie,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-from-high-school-comedies-to-dark-police-dystopias-an-anime-for-all-seasons/</guid>
        <description>Japanese manga and anime has something for everyone: enchanting soundtracks, remarkable aesthetics and animation, nuanced and thought-provoking storylines, and more. As a media form, it has always been bold and refreshing, pushing the boundary on plots, character development, and artistic styles to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Seeing the world through literature – so many books, so little time</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-seeing-the-world-through-literature-so-many-books-so-little-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavan Inguva,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-seeing-the-world-through-literature-so-many-books-so-little-time/</guid>
        <description>Seeing another part of the world is quite an exciting prospect for anyone: different foods, culture, history, and – most importantly – visiting beautiful bookstores and discovering authors you would not have heard of otherwise. Picking up a book, albeit translated to English, by a local author has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Immerse yourself in the tumultuous sea of this 20th century historical drama</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-immerse-yourself-in-the-tumultuous-sea-of-this-20th-century-historical-drama/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavan Inguva,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-immerse-yourself-in-the-tumultuous-sea-of-this-20th-century-historical-drama/</guid>
        <description>A lot of great literature has served as excellent snapshots into the culture and attitudes of the society that the author describes. Yukio Mishima’s Sea of Fertility Tetralogy is a perfect example of that. The tetralogy consists of Spring Snow, Runaway Horses, The Temple of Dawn, and The Decay of …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
