<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ch1810/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ch1810/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Using carbon dioxide to fight global warming
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-using-carbon-dioxide-to-fight-global-warming/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 19:57:47 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Harvey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-using-carbon-dioxide-to-fight-global-warming/</guid>
        <description>It was on a cool, clear autumn day in northern Minnesota when two scientists, driving towards a fieldwork station, stopped for gas. It was at this petrol station that Martin Saar and Jimmy Randolph had a flash of inspiration that could one day help in the fight against climate change.
Road journeys …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kermit-ted to helping out
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-12-kermit-ted-to-helping-out/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 15:46:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Harvey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-12-kermit-ted-to-helping-out/</guid>
        <description>Scientists at Queen’s University Belfast have discovered proteins in frog skins that could be used to treat cancer, diabetes, stroke and transplant patients by regulating the growth of blood vessels.
The research identified two proteins that can be used in a controlled and targeted way to regulate …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Attack from Within
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-attack-from-within/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 20:31:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Harvey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-attack-from-within/</guid>
        <description>The sound of the radio was not loud enough to drown out the cries from upstairs. Sophie continued with her routine, putting the shopping away, unloading the dishes; making sure everything was in its rightful place. She paused, just briefly, to adjust the old radio, which seemed to be getting quieter …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Back to the Past
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-back-to-the-past/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 18:33:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Harvey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-back-to-the-past/</guid>
        <description>X-rays could help us peer back in time to see the origins of life on Earth. Fossils, the indelible mark of ancient life, have been a vital piece of evidence for Darwin’s theory of evolution. Most, however, are from a time millions of years after life started. The evidence of life’s origin has been, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Top banana fights fungal infection
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-top-banana-fights-fungal-infection/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 19:13:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Harvey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-top-banana-fights-fungal-infection/</guid>
        <description>For the past 30 years, the humble banana has been under attack from a fungal invader. Black sigatoga disease, caused by the fungus Mycosphaerella fijiensis, decimates fruit yields and reduces profit yields for some of the poorest farmers in East Africa.
Help is at hand, however, from a new …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Alcohol consumption linked to gene
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-alcohol-consumption-linked-to-gene/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 08:13:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Harvey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-alcohol-consumption-linked-to-gene/</guid>
        <description>A gene associated with increased alcohol drinking behaviour has been identified, and may lead to a better understanding of the biological mechanisms that control drinking.
The research, published in the journal PNAS, identified the gene known as autism susceptibility candidate 2 (AUTS2) as the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Beauty is not in the eye of the beholder
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-beauty-is-not-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 08:09:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Harvey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-beauty-is-not-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</guid>
        <description>Yes, maybe it’s true that there are differing opinions on who we think of as attractive. Indeed, some people think Simon Cowell is good looking; still can’t get my head around that one, but I digress. Yes, people have their own personal prefernces – blonde or brunette, brainy or brawny, etc. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Scientific foundations of Tōhoku quake
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-scientific-foundations-of-thoku-quake/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 20:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thea Cunningham,Charles Harvey,Kelly Oakes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-scientific-foundations-of-thoku-quake/</guid>
        <description>Like all large earthquakes, the Japanese quake occurred in what is known as a subduction zone. In these zones – which are common in the Pacific – large slabs of solid rock called tectonic plates move towards each other. When they collide, the less dense plate will ride over the denser plate, which …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Deep voice sign of shallow personality
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-deep-voice-sign-of-shallow-personality/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 20:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Harvey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-deep-voice-sign-of-shallow-personality/</guid>
        <description>Men with deep and manly voices are more likely to be judged as unfaithful by woman, compared to those with a higher vocal register – good news, perhaps, for Joe Pasquale.
The research, published in the journal Evolutionary Psychology, also found that women viewed the deeper voices as more sexually …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Probing the depths
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-probing-the-depths/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 16:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Oakes,Charles Harvey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-probing-the-depths/</guid>
        <description>Ever since man has been able to think of clichés, he has dreamed of heading to the stars. The staff and students at Imperial College London are no exception, and have been involved in numerous missions to explore our solar system. Here, we take a look at just some of the missions Imperial is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Genetically engineered vaccination
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-genetically-engineered-vaccination/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 20:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Harvey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-genetically-engineered-vaccination/</guid>
        <description>A new type of vaccine for pneumonia based on genetically engineered bacteria has been developed, and may help in the fight against many other infectious diseases.
The vaccine, which protects against a virulent form of the bacterium Streptococcus pnuemoniae, works by introducing a modifed form of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial science blog star up for award
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-imperial-science-blog-star-up-for-award/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Harvey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-imperial-science-blog-star-up-for-award/</guid>
        <description>David Robertson is the small town blogger done good. In only 2 years he has converted his own little personal website into one of the globe’s most eminent science blogs (davidpj.wordpress.com). Just this month, it has been nominated for the 2011 Weblog Awards Best Science Blog. Felix Science caught …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Drug-resistant bacteria mapped
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-drug-resistant-bacteria-mapped/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 19:57:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Harvey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-drug-resistant-bacteria-mapped/</guid>
        <description>The genomes of hundreds of bacterial strains that cause pneumonia have been sequenced and may lead to new antibiotics and vaccines.
240 lineages of multidrug resistant Streptococcus pneumoniae were collected from around the world and their genomes sequenced in order to understand how the bacteria …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
