<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/dmw08/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/dmw08/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Rugby : 1st XV edge out Chichester
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-rugby-1st-xv-edge-out-chichester/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 22:29:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>David Wilson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-rugby-1st-xv-edge-out-chichester/</guid>
        <description>Rugby
Men’s 1st XV – 28
Chichester 1st – 24
Travelling the long distance to Chichester and producing a convincing performance against a physical minded team is not an easy feat and as a result this fixtures has, in recent years, been a tight affair. Unsurprisingly, the most recent clash was no …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Men’s Rugby 1s get off to a winning start over Portsmouth
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-mens-rugby-1s-get-off-to-a-winning-start-over-portsmouth/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 22:41:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>David Wilson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-mens-rugby-1s-get-off-to-a-winning-start-over-portsmouth/</guid>
        <description>Rugby: Imperial 22 - 20 Portsmouth
Imperial’s 1st XV got their season off to a positive start with a narrow win over Portsmouth at Harlington. On a day where the weather conditions were unusually favorable, Imperial made it difficult to overcome their stubborn opposition.
Despite the close full time …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2nd annual ARCS awards celebrate sports at Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-2nd-annual-arcs-awards-celebrate-sports-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 21:21:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>David Wilson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-2nd-annual-arcs-awards-celebrate-sports-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Last Friday, Sport Imperial hosted the second annual Imperial ARCS (Appreciate, Recognise and Celebrate Sport) award ceremony championing those who have contributed to sport at Imperial College over the past year. The event was attented by over 140 guests including nominees for awards, supporting …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reading stun lacklustre Imperial at the death
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-reading-stun-lacklustre-imperial-at-the-death/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 08:23:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>David Wilson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-reading-stun-lacklustre-imperial-at-the-death/</guid>
        <description>Reading staged a second half fightback to stun Imperial and dash their hopes of topping their league table this season.
Reading started the match playing with the wind in their favour and used it to their advantage, pinning Imperial within their half for the first few stages of the game. With the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rugby: First XV put 50 past St Mary’s
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-rugby-first-xv-put-50-past-st-marys/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 20:01:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>David Wilson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-rugby-first-xv-put-50-past-st-marys/</guid>
        <description>Following the fifteen’s crushing victory over Portsmouth the previous week, Imperial again showed impressive away from, turning over St Mary’s seconds by a massive score.
The game was played in atrocious conditions with rain showering down on an already sodden pitch. Imperial were not to be deterred …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>RSM regain The Bottle in emphatic style
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-rsm-regain-the-bottle-in-emphatic-style/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 19:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>David Wilson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-rsm-regain-the-bottle-in-emphatic-style/</guid>
        <description>The Bottle Match was the decisive game for the Royal School of Mines. Win and R.S.M. would boast a 5-3 victory over their bitter rivals Camborne School of Mines following wins in golf, netball, squash and women’s hockey. Lose and the weekend of fixtures would be drawn at four apiece. None of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>1st XV overrun Portsmouth
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-1st-xv-overrun-portsmouth/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 20:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>David Wilson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-1st-xv-overrun-portsmouth/</guid>
        <description>The 1st XV travelled down to Portsmouth on Wednesday eager to maintain their challenge for promotion against a side that are extremely difficult to beat at home.
The match began with fly half James Hayward rocked by three late hits by the Portsmouth openside in sequential plays. Portsmouth’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rugby: 1st XV record stylish victory
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-rugby-1st-xv-record-stylish-victory/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 19:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>David Wilson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-rugby-1st-xv-record-stylish-victory/</guid>
        <description>The fifteen recorded a well-deserved victory and impressive victory over RUMS in their first match back after Christmas. The disruption caused by the inclement weather towards the end of the Christmas term meant that this was the first game that the 1st XV were playing for nearly two months. This …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
