<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/alessio_incitti/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/alessio_incitti/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Here’s what I’m up to at the moment!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-here-s-what-i-m-up-to-at-the-moment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alessio Incitti,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-here-s-what-i-m-up-to-at-the-moment/</guid>
        <description>As part of LGBT History Month, IQ (Imperial College LGBT+) and I are running a series of events throughout February.
This weekend you can join IQ at the National Student Pride, one of the biggest student events of the year, featuring Courtney Act.
If you would like to learn more about LGBT history, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LGBT History Month: Why is it important?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-lgbt-history-month-why-is-it-important/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alessio Incitti,Sophie Quinn,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-lgbt-history-month-why-is-it-important/</guid>
        <description>If you’ve wondered why the Queen’s Tower is lit up in rainbow colours, it’s because Imperial is currently celebrating LGBT (Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, Transgender) History Month – an annual observance of the history and experiences of LGBT people that aims to promote acceptance and raise awareness of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Here’s what I’m up to at the moment!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-here-s-what-i-m-up-to-at-the-moment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alessio Incitti,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-here-s-what-i-m-up-to-at-the-moment/</guid>
        <description>My number one priority for this year is to ensure Imperial becomes a more safe, welcoming, and inclusive space for transgender &amp;amp; gender-variant students. In the last few months I’ve been working to secure lasting advances for the Imperial trans community. Action I’m taking includes:
 Bringing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Here’s what cis people can do to protect trans folks</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-here-s-what-cis-people-can-do-to-protect-trans-folks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alessio Incitti,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-here-s-what-cis-people-can-do-to-protect-trans-folks/</guid>
        <description>20th November marked Transgender Day of Remembrance, an annual memorialisation of those who lost their lives as a result of transphobic violence in the last year. A vigil was held in London, among many other cities, where the trans community and their allies paused to remember Paola, who was stabbed …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
