<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/dmm04/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/dmm04/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Documentary corner: A Riot of our Own
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-documentary-corner-a-riot-of-our-own/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 09:16:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Diogo M Geraldes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-documentary-corner-a-riot-of-our-own/</guid>
        <description>No Nazis. No dark metal. Live acts seven days a week. These simple admission criteria meant that gigs could be booked in the same day, regardless of band size or experience, to play in front of the music-loving crowd who religiously converged on the 12 Bar Club, hidden in Denmark Street.
What made …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A dangerous step backwards
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-a-dangerous-step-backwards/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 22:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Diogo M Geraldes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-a-dangerous-step-backwards/</guid>
        <description>In 1615, Galileo was tried and convicted by the Italian inquisition for his unorthodox views on the heliocentrism of our solar system. His denial to comply and bend over before the established power threw him into house arrest until the end of his life. However, it also sparked a scientific …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Leslie Feist at the Royal Albert Hall
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-leslie-feist-at-the-royal-albert-hall/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 17:56:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Diogo M Geraldes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-leslie-feist-at-the-royal-albert-hall/</guid>
        <description>The Royal Albert Hall was ready to welcome back the queen of Broken Social Scene for a truly magical end of 2012’s spring equinox weekend after M. Ward played a very pleasant stripped down version of his repertoire and David Bowie’s ‘Let’s Dance’.
Leslie Feist set the tone for the following …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Tallest Man On Earth
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-the-tallest-man-on-earth/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 20:38:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Diogo M Geraldes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-the-tallest-man-on-earth/</guid>
        <description>A packed, expectant Electric Ballroom welcomed on stage Idiot Wind’s deep enchanting voice. The simultaneously life partner and support act for Kristian Matsson comfortably slipped into the big shoes any act with a Dylan reference in its name has to walk on. Amanda Bergman’s stunningly sweet and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Janelle Monáe is here to stay
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-janelle-mone-is-here-to-stay/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 20:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Diogo M Geraldes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-janelle-mone-is-here-to-stay/</guid>
        <description>Creator of “ArchAndroid”, the 2010 R&amp;amp;B reinventing masterpiece soon to be omnipresent in all the end of year top albums lists Janelle Monáe has been much hyped since her destruction of SXSW 2009. Destruction indeed was what the 2000-strong audience witnessed at the Shepherd Bush Empire. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ready for War? Ready for Love!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-ready-for-war-ready-for-love/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 18:35:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Diogo M Geraldes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-ready-for-war-ready-for-love/</guid>
        <description>I knew these girls were good. I knew they were hyped. I knew they could put on a great live performance. But still, I wasn’t expecting a sold out Scala only two days after they released their first album!
2:54 opened the night with their “pre-pubescent Garbage”-like songs led by a extremely foxy …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
