<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ks607/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ks607/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Time to rest my bones
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-time-to-rest-my-bones/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 11:51:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-time-to-rest-my-bones/</guid>
        <description>The last day was bliss. My parents had driven down to Cornwall and had taken the bags off our bikes; after two weeks, we finally had a support car. With the weight removed from my beleaguered back wheel, the tandem was a dream. I sped up the hills, my now mutant thighs making short work of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kadhim’s Last Totally Hot Album of the Week
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-22-kadhims-last-totally-hot-album-of-the-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 17:01:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-22-kadhims-last-totally-hot-album-of-the-week/</guid>
        <description>So, this exists&amp;hellip; By ‘this’ I mean haha im sorry, Kitty Pryde’s debut mixtape. Words truly fail me – ok, well maybe not entirely, but let’s not get meta here. Let’s imagine, for a horrifying moment, that you teamed a tumblr tween up with the guys behind Main Attrakionz. You’d end up with lazy, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kadhim&#39;s Totally Hot Album of the Week #20
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-15-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-20/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 07:50:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-15-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-20/</guid>
        <description>I fell in love last week. I was standing in the Now Wave tent at Parklife Festival in Manchester, when all of a sudden Cupid’s Arrow pierced my ears. I turned to my friend beside me, and pointed towards the stage with my right hand, and said, “That is the coolest man I have ever seen or heard.” The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sun Glitters flies over for the Felix Music Night
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-7-sun-glitters-flies-over-for-the-felix-music-night/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 22:29:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-7-sun-glitters-flies-over-for-the-felix-music-night/</guid>
        <description>Tell us a bit about yourself. Did you grow up in a musical household? What kind of music did you listen to growing up?
My name is Victor Ferreira and I compose and perform under the moniker, Sun Glitters. I was born in Luxembourg in 1973 and sadly I didn’t really grow in a musical household…
I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>XVI Records take over Metric
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-7-xvi-records-take-over-metric/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 22:22:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-7-xvi-records-take-over-metric/</guid>
        <description>Hey Josh, how are you doing?
Very well thanks mate, how about you?
Not bad, just listening to some Patchwork Pirates so things could be worse.
Nice, I’m Fleetwood Mac’ing it.
Haha. Let’s start with the easy stuff, what does XVI stand for? I keep saying X-V-I in my head.
It is indeed XVI, it stands …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kadhim&#39;s totally hot album of the week #19
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-7-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-19/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 22:18:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-7-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-19/</guid>
        <description>Some of you may remember 2009. Those who don’t may want to put their thinking caps on for a moment (and maybe lay off the bath salts for a few face-chewing minutes). 2009 was the earth-shattering year in which the painfully mediocre band Ash decided the album was dead. They went on to prove that the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kadhim&#39;s Totally Hot Revision Playlist
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-kadhims-totally-hot-revision-playlist/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 21:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-kadhims-totally-hot-revision-playlist/</guid>
        <description>Listen to the playlist here: http://spoti.fi/FelixRevision
_Nine _weeks until final year exams; boom, let’s get down to revision. Samiyam, play me in with ‘Cushion’ – the bass means business, my new pen and ‘revision folder’ mean business too.
That’s how revision plans start: with vigour. But things …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kadhim&#39;s Totally Hot Album of the Week #18
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-9-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-18/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 13:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-9-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-18/</guid>
        <description>Do you know anyone who says, “Music is crap nowadays?” Let’s be honest: those people are the most boring people you know. In fact, you’re not even sure why you know them anymore. Everytime you hang out with them you find your brain warning you, with fundamentalist zeal, “Get the fuck out of here …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kadhim’s totally hot album of the week #17
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-17/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 23:05:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-17/</guid>
        <description>I saw Perfume Genius in November 2010; I hated him. “Whoa there!”, I hear you cry – hot coffee spitting from your mouths in shock. Don’t be too hasty, don’t turn the page, don’t ‘Command + T’ away: there’s redemption at the end of this article.
He was playing at the beautiful Cecil Sharp House in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kadhim’s totally hot album of the week #16
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-16/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 20:57:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-16/</guid>
        <description>On Monday, Azealia Banks will play at Heaven. Sadly, I will not be there. Those damned academic commitments trumped my desire to go see the hottest female rapper since Missy Elliott said she wanted to search around in my trousers for Lord knows what (well, I assume she was talking to me, but one can …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Simply the Bestival?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-simply-the-bestival/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 21:47:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-simply-the-bestival/</guid>
        <description>Dressing up: probably the reason I love going to Bestival every year. In 2010, a pair of twins I know dressed as colonial-era hunters and chased the other festival-goers who had so foolishly dressed as characters from The Fantastic Mr Fox. (Last year, well, a picture speaks a 1000 words [see …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kadhim’s totally hot album of the week #15
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-15/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 21:38:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-15/</guid>
        <description>Oh, errors of judgement. How I know you well! Last term, just as we were heading off for Christmas, I wrote, in a throwaway comment that I’d now like to dispose of properly, that the Black Keys’ latest album El Camino is a ‘dud’. Well, it is time to make amends. Using all the powers of apology that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kadhim’s totally hot album of the week #14
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-14/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 22:23:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-14/</guid>
        <description>I’m bAAAAAck! Terribly sorry about last week; unfortunately my ghostwriter was on holiday, so doing my column was a bit trickier than expected. But now that he’s taken his leave for the next 12 years, we can continue on as normal. Django Django’s Django Django [Spotify] is this week’s Totally Hot …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kadhim&#39;s Totally Hot Album of the Week #13
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-27-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-13/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 09:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-27-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-13/</guid>
        <description>The most irritating thing about Tim Westwood is this: he’s actually 100% credible. He’s been supporting UK hip-hop since the 80s and, by all fair metrics, has earned the right to ram obnoxious horns and gunshot sounds up the backside of every track he plays on his radio show. I, on the other hand, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kadhim’s totally hot album of the week #12
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-12/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 20:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-12/</guid>
        <description>The scientifically-dubious ‘most depressing day of the year’ has past us by without running aground, and unless you’re Maggie Dallman, you’ll probably make it to the end of the month without being publicly humiliated. Let’s shake off these January blues and start living again. Ernest Gonzales, let …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kadhim&#39;s totally hot album of the week #11
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-11/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 22:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-11/</guid>
        <description>My New Year’s Resolution was to stop using food metaphors in my writing, but as you will see, this album has left me a bit drunk and I’ve succumbed to the lurid appeal of Pot Noodle once again.
Broken resolutions aside, 2012 is still young and the green shoots of new albums are yet to appear. So I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kadhim&#39;s Totally Hot Xmas Playlist
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-21-kadhims-totally-hot-xmas-playlist/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2011 01:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-21-kadhims-totally-hot-xmas-playlist/</guid>
        <description>Christmas has come early! (Kind of). Through the miraculous luxuries the 21st century has brought us, I&amp;rsquo;ve compiled the artists from last term&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Totally Hot Album of the Week&amp;rsquo; column into a Spotify playlist. It starts off with a bit of a toe-tapper from Slow Club, slides …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kadhim&#39;s totally hot album of the week #10
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-10/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 21:09:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-10/</guid>
        <description>And so this is Christmas. The season of merriment, mulled wine, and all-too-predictable disappointment. You were probably expecting the album of the week, given that it is the season of cheer, to be Michael Bublé’s Christmas; if so, I’m sorry to disappoint. You may have expected it to be The Black …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kadhim’s totally hot album of the week #9
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-9/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 21:04:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-9/</guid>
        <description>On Sunday, I was at a friend-of-a-friend’s flat; it was almost completely burnt out. The TV had caught fire and the ensuing blaze had torn up the walls and slithered around the rooms, turning home into hell. Some things had survived: a coating of soot was all the happy family photos had to endure. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Give yourself over to absolute pleasure
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-give-yourself-over-to-absolute-pleasure/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 22:47:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-give-yourself-over-to-absolute-pleasure/</guid>
        <description>I’m a Rocky Horror Picture Show virgin. Or, at least, I was a Rocky Horror Picture Show virgin until last Thursday, when my innocence was taken from me in a flash of lingerie, transvestitism, and hilarious heckling. Musical Theatre Society provided the girls, guys, and the pizazz, while iCU Cinema …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Devil May Blair
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-devil-may-blair/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 22:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-devil-may-blair/</guid>
        <description>Those of us born around the end of the 80s and the start of the 90s have a lot to chew over. Too young to remember a time before Blair but old enough to recall a precious year or two before Bush fucked the world – sorry, “took office” – we not only grew up in an era where wars were fought against …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kadhim’s totally hot album of the week #8
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-8/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 22:23:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-8/</guid>
        <description>Searching out new music is not a lone pursuit and cannot be meaningfully automated. You can’t hope to get past the tripe on mainstream radio or last.fm’s “1+1 = U2” algorithm without a friend giving you a nudge and saying, “we literally won’t be friends anymore if you don’t love this band”.
There’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kadhim’s totally hot album of the week #7
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-7/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 21:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-7/</guid>
        <description>I recently told my friend that I couldn’t understand the hype surrounding A$AP Rocky. In a completely unrelated incident, I was called “a fucking codpiece” on Twitter by Felix Music Night headliner Mikill Pane (we’ve since patched things up). He didn’t think any of my questions in an email interview …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reports from a sick night in Metric... no, seriously
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-reports-from-a-sick-night-in-metric-no-seriously/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 21:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-reports-from-a-sick-night-in-metric-no-seriously/</guid>
        <description>See photos of the night here
Don’t let anyone convince you to put on a music event. It’ll stress you out, distract you from your degree, and worst of all, when it comes off, the feeling of satisfaction will make you forget all the shit and make you think about doing it all again.
Last Saturday was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Be sure not to miss...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-be-sure-not-to-miss/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 20:39:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-be-sure-not-to-miss/</guid>
        <description>In 2009, I received a copy of Tru Thoughts’ Tenth Anniversary album and although I was slightly embarrassed at the fact that it took me ten years to notice them, it was musically one of the best things that’s ever happened to me.
Tru Thoughts is a gem of a label, nestled down in Brighton on the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kadhim&#39;s totally hot album of the week #6
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-6/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 20:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-6/</guid>
        <description>It was cold this morning, wasn’t it? Like most students, myself included, you’re probably a bit suspicious of the thermostat and slightly paranoid that if you turn the heating on your next gas bill will be enough to bankrupt you. (I’m not talking about you, “1%” students; you know who you are…)
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mikill Pane does not exist... survived by hate of hip-hop
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-mikill-pane-does-not-exist-survived-by-hate-of-hip-hop/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 20:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-mikill-pane-does-not-exist-survived-by-hate-of-hip-hop/</guid>
        <description>Kadhim Shubber: Your website says you’re “non-existent”; what happened, can we help?
Mikill Pane: I’m just a figment of Justin Smith Uzomba’s vivid imagination and nope, you can’t help. I’ve got all the assistance I need, thanks. Unless you know anyone who’s letting go of a better body than the one …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kadhim’s totally hot album of the week #5
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-5/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 20:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-5/</guid>
        <description>You know those music writers who twist meaningless metaphor around meaningless metaphor in a futile attempt to recreate the music on paper? Wander/Wonder is basically that kind of reviewer’s wet dream. But it also a bear-trap for anyone who thinks they’re going to slide along without using the word …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Music Night: KABLAAM
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-28-felix-music-night-kablaam/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 10:30:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Inigo Martinez de Rituerto,Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-28-felix-music-night-kablaam/</guid>
        <description>Imperial’s music scene is certainly underground. The bright morning sunshine rarely reaches its dark recesses and its artists receive little attention. The Felix Music Nights are our way of celebrating this under-appreciated scene and also fostering it; bringing more students into the tent and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kadhim&#39;s totally hot album of the week #4
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-28-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-4/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 10:05:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-28-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-4/</guid>
        <description>Of all the shit stage-names artists have given themselves in the history of music, ‘Bono’ has got to be the worst. But ‘Young God’, one-half of Seattle-based Blue Sky Black Death (BSBD), is definitely a close second. In fact, if BSBD weren’t so damn fantastic, I’d say he was an arrogant so-and-so …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kadhim&#39;s totally hot album of the week #3
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-3/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 11:23:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-3/</guid>
        <description>When it comes to Twitter, musicians usually have one of two personalities:
1) No personality – SINGLE OUT NOW!!! yawn 2) Uber-kick-ass insight into their awesome psyche – “DEAR LORD RYAN GOSLING GETT ON MY FACE”.
Slow Club’s Rebecca Taylor falls into the latter category (indeed, the second example …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The economics of occupation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-the-economics-of-occupation/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 21:43:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-the-economics-of-occupation/</guid>
        <description>As we picked our way through the tents outside St Paul’s Cathedral this Monday one thing was clear: anarchists are not an easy bunch to organise. Not a surprise, perhaps, but add to this a passionate belief in not telling others what to do, and suddenly you find yourself voting about whether to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kadhim&#39;s totally hot album of the week #2
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-2/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 23:40:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-2/</guid>
        <description>Girls Father, Son, Holy Ghost 2011
Girls’ frontman Christopher Owen is an opiate-addicted former cult-member: have I got your attention? Good. Father, Son, Holy Ghost is the richest indie-rock album that anyone has made in a long time. It’s as rich as a warm chocolate brownie with artery-clogging …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kadhim&#39;s totally hot album of the week #1
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-1/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 13:28:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-kadhims-totally-hot-album-of-the-week-1/</guid>
        <description>Clams Casino Instrumental Mixtape 2011
Instrumental hip-hop is officially ‘it’. You can’t go more than a few hours in the day without some producer deciding that hip-hop would be infinitely better without an ex-parole officer pretending to be gangster over his beloved beats. Remove the distracting, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Summer Ball suffers £100,000 loss
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-7-15-summer-ball-suffers-100000-loss/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2011 16:49:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-7-15-summer-ball-suffers-100000-loss/</guid>
        <description>Management accounts from Imperial College Union show that this year’s Summer Ball made an estimated loss of £100,000.
The accounts, which cover the period from April to June 2011, show that the event made an overall loss of £122,123. Taking into consideration a donation of £20,000 from the College, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Try harder next week’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-try-harder-next-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 20:41:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-try-harder-next-week/</guid>
        <description>I hope that you will excuse me for writing in the first person. This is the last article I will ever write as Editor of this publication and, as such, it is quite a significant moment for me.
When I first came to Imperial in 2007 to study Physics, I would not have believed it possible that one could …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Physics lectures in SAF?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-physics-lectures-in-saf/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 19:10:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-physics-lectures-in-saf/</guid>
        <description>The College has announced an initiative to “implement a College-wide timetabling project” that could see departments sharing major lecture theatres and potentially reduce the need to build new lecture theatres.
The proposal comes out of work done by Professor Robin Leatherbarrow and his team and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Disappointing Summer Ball turnout
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-disappointing-summer-ball-turnout/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 19:08:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-disappointing-summer-ball-turnout/</guid>
        <description>The Union were forced to hold the Summer Ball two weeks before the end of term this year, instead of the usual one week, because the clash with Glastonbury meant that “acts and equipment” would have been too difficult to hire. Union President Alex Kendall explained that the difficulty in having the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London Student vs. Felix: Day Nineteen – A song from your favorite album
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-17-london-student-vs-felix-day-nineteen-a-song-from-your-favorite-album/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2011 12:51:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-17-london-student-vs-felix-day-nineteen-a-song-from-your-favorite-album/</guid>
        <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if My Beautiful Dark Twisted Fantasy is my favourite album (it&amp;rsquo;s probably close) but since Pitchfork officially rated it &amp;lsquo;perfect&amp;rsquo;, it&amp;rsquo;s probably as good a choice as any.
The London Student and Felix are currently fighting an epic war. Like, tweet, or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London Student vs. Felix: Day Fifteen – A song that describes you
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-17-london-student-vs-felix-day-fifteen-a-song-that-describes-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2011 12:37:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-17-london-student-vs-felix-day-fifteen-a-song-that-describes-you/</guid>
        <description>There&amp;rsquo;s always going to be something pretentious about choosing a song that &amp;lsquo;describes&amp;rsquo; you, but the line &amp;ldquo;I just want to worry about those sunshine girls&amp;rdquo; sums up my outlook whenever I&amp;rsquo;m feeling a little unmotivated about doing Felix.
_The London Student and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London Student vs. Felix: Day Nine – A song that you can dance to
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-17-london-student-vs-felix-day-nine-a-song-that-you-can-dance-to/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2011 12:28:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-17-london-student-vs-felix-day-nine-a-song-that-you-can-dance-to/</guid>
        <description>You may have noticed that this is the second Star Slinger tune so far. (He&amp;rsquo;s basically my favourite artist in recent memory.) The beat on this refix makes it the most danceable music that I have ever heard.
The London Student and Felix are currently fighting an epic war. Like, tweet, or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London Student vs. Felix: Day Eight – A song that you all the words to
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-17-london-student-vs-felix-day-eight-a-song-that-you-all-the-words-to/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2011 12:21:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-17-london-student-vs-felix-day-eight-a-song-that-you-all-the-words-to/</guid>
        <description>My favourite line in this song is: &amp;ldquo;We got food everywhere as if the party was catered.&amp;rdquo; If there is so much food (high-quality no doubt) at the party, such that the impression is given that someone has hired a catering company, but in fact it&amp;rsquo;s not catered, then where the hell is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London Student vs. Felix: Day Seven – A song that reminds you of a certain event
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-17-london-student-vs-felix-day-seven-a-song-that-reminds-you-of-a-certain-event/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2011 12:11:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-17-london-student-vs-felix-day-seven-a-song-that-reminds-you-of-a-certain-event/</guid>
        <description>The album that this song is off was played almost on loop throughout the week of The Daily Felix. The rolling bass kept me calm and saved me from near certain insanity.
_The London Student and Felix are currently fighting an epic war. Like, tweet, or comment on this page to help us win today&amp;rsquo;s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Tooth Fairy’s Palace
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-the-tooth-fairys-palace/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 19:36:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-the-tooth-fairys-palace/</guid>
        <description>It almost sounds like something straight from a children’s fairytale: using the milk teeth of children to build a palace. But this is no tooth-fairy-gone-rogue story, rather it’s the inventive collaboration of Imperial’s Professor Sara Rankin and artist Gina Czarnecki. The pair aim to move the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Management Board took decision to leave CaSE
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-management-board-took-decision-to-leave-case/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 19:08:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-management-board-took-decision-to-leave-case/</guid>
        <description>It has emerged that the decision to cut Imperial’s £3,000 per year membership of the Campaign for Science and Engineering (CaSE) was made by the College’s Management Board.
A trusted source, who wished to remain anonymous, told Felix that the Board felt that Imperial could lobby effectively by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union Court clears President
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-union-court-clears-president/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 19:00:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-union-court-clears-president/</guid>
        <description>The Union Court has ruled that Union President Alex Kendall did not act inappropriately when, during the central Union elections when he was Returning Officer, he told a student to withdraw his nomination for the position of Community Action Group (CAG) Chair. The Court also ruled that Kendall had …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union forced to clarify future of Summer Ball
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-union-forced-to-clarify-future-of-summer-ball/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 18:45:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,Ben Scally,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-union-forced-to-clarify-future-of-summer-ball/</guid>
        <description>The Union has been forced to clarify that no plans for the future of the Summer Ball have been set in stone after several Deputy Presidents raised concerns following last week’s Felix article. Union President Alex Kendall said that the statement given to Felix regarding plans for the future of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Preview of stop-motion video
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-14-preview-of-stop-motion-video/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 15:05:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonathan Kim,Kadhim Shubber,Christopher Walmsley,Slobodan Radosavljevic,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-14-preview-of-stop-motion-video/</guid>
        <description>
</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Musharraf cancels talk
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-musharraf-cancels-talk/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 21:16:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-musharraf-cancels-talk/</guid>
        <description>Former Pakistani President Pervez Musharraf has pulled out from a talk scheduled for this Sunday. The College had approved the talk, after initially rejecting an earlier date, but imposed severe restrictions, including only allowing College members to attend and preventing online publicity, except …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Humanities staff attack College day proposals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-humanities-staff-attack-college-day-proposals/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 21:14:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-humanities-staff-attack-college-day-proposals/</guid>
        <description>Staff from the Humanities Department have attacked the proposed changes to the College day, saying that there are “serious reasons why [the proposals] will not work” and suggesting that they marginalise and devalue humanities courses.
The letter, signed ‘Staff of the Humanities Department’, argues …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An eloquent spokesperson for science
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-an-eloquent-spokesperson-for-science/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 21:07:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-an-eloquent-spokesperson-for-science/</guid>
        <description>I’m standing outside the offices for the Campaign for Science and Engineering (CaSE) on Gordon Square, near Euston Square tube station, trying to stop sweating (summer showers tricked me into wearing a coat&amp;hellip;) when I notice something. While our university recently took the controversial, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union could join CaSE
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-union-could-join-case/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 20:55:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-union-could-join-case/</guid>
        <description>The Union has criticised the College’s decision to cut ties with the science lobby group CaSE, calling the decision “cynical” and suggesting that the Union itself could affiliate with the group independently.
In a statement to Felix, later posted online, Union President Alex Kendall praised the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Untitled
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-untitled/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 18:05:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-untitled/</guid>
        <description>Who’s hiding in the trees? Who’s watching me through dark leaves, as I run through Battersea Park at 5 minutes to midnight?
Why aren’t they at home? What will they gain from the sight of hot breath on cold air and soft shoes on coarse gravel?
Are they listening? To my breathless monologues about …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mum, I need a doctor
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-mum-i-need-a-doctor/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 17:53:47 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-mum-i-need-a-doctor/</guid>
        <description>In my house, down in the dark there&amp;rsquo;s a door. It&amp;rsquo;s always kept locked and behind it I store A wretched, disfigured, maniacal beast.
It screams and it howls. Its anguish reverberates Along empty corridors into my bedroom where I curl shivering on my bed, ears aching.
I can hear it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cricket coalition come close second
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-cricket-coalition-come-close-second/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 20:34:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-cricket-coalition-come-close-second/</guid>
        <description>Cricket, cupcakes and comedy – who could ask for more on a glorious Bank Holiday? For those of you weren’t chained to your desks revising, you’ll remember that Good Friday was like the perfect English summer’s day. With the clear blue skies, sun beating down and public deciding ‘less is more’ when …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Field of Dreams
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-field-of-dreams/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 20:03:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-field-of-dreams/</guid>
        <description>I have been trying to pin down what is truly appealing about festivals. What makes them so hellishly fun and why do we go to them? Of course there can’t be just one answer. Part of the fun is getting away from ‘civilisation’ and going a bit mad for a few days; but after a while you can’t help but …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College await police advice on Musharraf talk
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-college-await-police-advice-on-musharraf-talk/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 18:21:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-college-await-police-advice-on-musharraf-talk/</guid>
        <description>The College has denied permission for a high-profile talk by former Pakistani President Pervez Musharraf on Sunday 5th June, saying that they were not given enough notice. The talk, which may go ahead on the following Sunday, was organised by the Pakistan Society and was to focus on ‘Unity, Faith …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial cuts ties with CaSE
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-imperial-cuts-ties-with-case/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 18:02:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-imperial-cuts-ties-with-case/</guid>
        <description>Imperial has ended its subscription to influential science lobby group the Campaign for Science and Engineering (CaSE). The decision, which CaSE director Imran Khan called “puzzling”, means that Imperial is now one of only two Russell Group institutions, the other being the LSE, that is not …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London Student vs. Felix: Day Thirteen – A song that is a guilty pleasure
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-1-london-student-vs-felix-day-thirteen-a-song-that-is-a-guilty-pleasure/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 14:39:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-1-london-student-vs-felix-day-thirteen-a-song-that-is-a-guilty-pleasure/</guid>
        <description>Ok I have a confession to make: I absolutely love trashy RnB and Hip-hop from around the millenium. As well as listening to metronomic dance tunes on print day, the Sports Editor David Wilson and I also spend a significant amount of time listening to Nelly, G-Unit, and sometimes even a little Usher. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London Student vs. Felix: Day Twelve – A song from a band you hate
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-31-london-student-vs-felix-day-twelve-a-song-from-a-band-you-hate/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 11:03:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-31-london-student-vs-felix-day-twelve-a-song-from-a-band-you-hate/</guid>
        <description>This song reminds Science Editor Thea Cunningham of the worst of Radio 1. Which is a fair shout really.
The London Student and Felix are currently fighting an epic war. Like, tweet, or comment on this page to help us win today&amp;rsquo;s battle. Tomorrow is &amp;lsquo;A song that is a guilty …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London Student vs. Felix: Day Eleven – A song from your favourite band
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-30-london-student-vs-felix-day-eleven-a-song-from-your-favourite-band/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 10:40:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-30-london-student-vs-felix-day-eleven-a-song-from-your-favourite-band/</guid>
        <description>Ok so this unsigned instrumental hip-hop producer from California isn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily my favourite musician of all time. I&amp;rsquo;m not really sure that I could choose just one artist anyway. However, he is my favourite musician as of 10:27 this morning when former Science Editor Katya-yani Vyas …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London Student vs. Felix: Day Ten – A song that makes you fall asleep
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-29-london-student-vs-felix-day-ten-a-song-that-makes-you-fall-asleep/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 11:04:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-29-london-student-vs-felix-day-ten-a-song-that-makes-you-fall-asleep/</guid>
        <description>Ok, so I may have missed a couple of days. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if there&amp;rsquo;s much to say about this song. It&amp;rsquo;s from a great album, Gemini, and is the perfect companion for drifting gently off to sleep. (Unfortunately Wild Nothing are terrible live&amp;hellip;)
The London Student and Felix are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Animal Collective in Eastbourne. Wait, what?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-animal-collective-in-eastbourne-wait-what/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 19:52:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-animal-collective-in-eastbourne-wait-what/</guid>
        <description>It would probably be the first, and last time that the sheltered residents of Eastbourne would see the word ‘Supreme’ with the word ‘chicken’ preceding it. Yes, a sizeable crowd of hipsters had made the perilous journey out of London and Brighton to the mundane streets of my elderly hometown – also …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Star Slinger
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-star-slinger/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 19:37:47 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-star-slinger/</guid>
        <description>It’s the 1st of May and Star Slinger is playing Camden Rock at the Camden Crawl. The room is rather sparsely populated and despite the best efforts of this “one man beat machine”, as he was described by Pitchfork, the sound system just isn’t playing nice this evening. At the end of his set a crowd …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Two hour lunchtime could be abolished
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-two-hour-lunchtime-could-be-abolished/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 18:42:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-two-hour-lunchtime-could-be-abolished/</guid>
        <description>The current two-hour lunch break could be abolished to allow departments more flexibility in scheduling classes, according to proposals from the College Day Working Party. The Chair of the working party, Professor Dorothy Griffiths, said that departments would still be expected to schedule a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reduction in subwarden numbers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-reduction-in-subwarden-numbers/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 18:39:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-reduction-in-subwarden-numbers/</guid>
        <description>A review into the wardening system has recommended reducing the number of sub-wardens by around 15%. The reductions, which will occur through the normal turnover of contracts, are aimed at rebalancing the College’s welfare provision towards counselling and disability services.
The recommendations …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rector’s Awards announced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-rectors-awards-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 18:32:24 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-rectors-awards-announced/</guid>
        <description>The recipients of the annual Rector’s Awards for Excellence in Teaching and in Research Supervision have been announced this week. The staff honoured range across departments and faculties and include two academics who were affected by the Life Sciences restructure.
The teaching awards are presented …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lessons from the Mechanical Engineering building refurbishment
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-lessons-from-the-mechanical-engineering-building-refurbishment/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 18:29:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-lessons-from-the-mechanical-engineering-building-refurbishment/</guid>
        <description>The renovation of the Mechanical Engineering Department has not run smoothly, to put it mildly. As Felix has reported in previousweeks, it has seen delays, hiccups, and errors that have caused snorts of derision around campus. With this in mind, we suggested to the College and the Department that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Life Sciences Teaching Review proposals approved
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-life-sciences-teaching-review-proposals-approved/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 18:17:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-life-sciences-teaching-review-proposals-approved/</guid>
        <description>The Science Studies Committee has approved the recommendations of the Life Sciences Teaching Review, after initially rejecting them last week. The committee were satisfied that the department had addressed their concerns and that “its requirements for the academic quality of degree programmes had …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London Student vs. Felix: Day Six – A song that reminds you of somewhere
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-25-london-student-vs-felix-day-six-a-song-that-reminds-you-of-somewhere/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 11:14:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-25-london-student-vs-felix-day-six-a-song-that-reminds-you-of-somewhere/</guid>
        <description>This song will forever remind me of being in the Felix office on a Thursday with Chief Copy Editor Lizzy Griffiths, with an hour or two left until the print deadline. The metronomic shake of the beat, along with the ominous thudding opening, has helped it become our copy-editing anthem (yes, I am …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London Student vs. Felix: Day Five – A song that reminds you of someone
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-24-london-student-vs-felix-day-five-a-song-that-reminds-you-of-someone/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 13:14:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-24-london-student-vs-felix-day-five-a-song-that-reminds-you-of-someone/</guid>
        <description>Felix&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;witty&amp;rsquo; Science Editor Charlie Harvey, upon being asked, suggested this song for today because it reminded him of my mum&amp;hellip; Hey Charlie, fuck you!
The London Student and Felix are currently fighting an epic war. Like, tweet, or comment on this page to help us …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London Student vs. Felix: Day Four – A song that makes you sad
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-23-london-student-vs-felix-day-four-a-song-that-makes-you-sad/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2011 11:03:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-23-london-student-vs-felix-day-four-a-song-that-makes-you-sad/</guid>
        <description>Thanks to David from yesterday for this suggestion. Whichever way you interpret this song, it undoubtedly has the power to take you to that dark place where ex-girl/boyfriends, old friends, and missed opportunities reside.
The London Student and Felix are currently fighting an epic war. Like, tweet, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New research centre in Shoreditch
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-22-new-research-centre-in-shoreditch/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2011 13:02:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-22-new-research-centre-in-shoreditch/</guid>
        <description>In a speech made to the 2011 Google Zeitgeist conference, Chancellor George Osborne announced that Imperial, in collaboration with UCL, are developing plans for a new Research and Innovation Centre in Shoreditch. The project is part of the Government’s ‘Tech City’ initiative that aims to create a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Glimpses of the past – the Imperial Institute
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-22-glimpses-of-the-past-the-imperial-institute/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2011 12:23:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,Gilead Amit,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-22-glimpses-of-the-past-the-imperial-institute/</guid>
        <description>When construction began on the grand Imperial Institute in 1887, fears were already being expressed that it would turn into a wasteful white elephant. Barely a year later, in fact, Thomas Henry Huxley had already pronounced the monumental project ‘a failure’. But when Rector Sir Patrick Linstead …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London Student vs. Felix: Day Three – A song that makes you happy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-22-london-student-vs-felix-day-three-a-song-that-makes-you-happy/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2011 10:19:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-22-london-student-vs-felix-day-three-a-song-that-makes-you-happy/</guid>
        <description>The reaction when I play someone this Star Slinger song is always the same: &amp;ldquo;Holy shit that&amp;rsquo;s awesome!&amp;rdquo; they say in not so many words. The song (and its video) makes me happy for two reasons:
 It&amp;rsquo;s full of summery cheer and makes you want to jump out of bed and run around in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London Student vs. Felix: Day One – Felix&#39;s Favourite Song
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-london-student-vs-felix-day-one-felixs-favourite-song/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 10:42:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-london-student-vs-felix-day-one-felixs-favourite-song/</guid>
        <description>Felix Travel Editor Chris Richardson demanded that we listen to the Jamie xx/Gil Scott-Heron remix album in the office when it was released way back in February, but his orders fell on deaf ears; when I finally got around to it a few weeks ago, I felt quite the fool&amp;hellip;
The London Student and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Further details emerge on Mechanical Engineering refurbishment
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-further-details-emerge-on-mechanical-engineering-refurbishment/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 15:42:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-further-details-emerge-on-mechanical-engineering-refurbishment/</guid>
        <description>New information about the delayed refurbishment of the Mechanical Engineering department has come to light in the past week; showing the effect of the disruption on PhD students and implying that the College was unhappy with the way the project was being managed and that the error with the £3 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Blunder in Mechanical Engineering Department
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-5-blunder-in-mechanical-engineering-department/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 23:40:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-5-blunder-in-mechanical-engineering-department/</guid>
        <description>A team of technical experts is currently investigating how a £3 million exhaust system, in the Mechanical Engineering building, came to be built with galvanised, instead of stainless steel. The College were reluctant to reveal the cost of fixing the error, saying only that it was less than half of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Scaled-down Science Challenge launches
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-5-scaled-down-science-challenge-launches/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 23:35:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-5-scaled-down-science-challenge-launches/</guid>
        <description>The Royal College of Science Union (RCSU) Science Challenge finally launched last week. The essay writing competition offers cash prizes of up to £2,000 and is open to Imperial students and students from schools in the UK. However, the competition this year is vastly scaled-down in comparison with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Football team fined after ULU Cup fight
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-5-football-team-fined-after-ulu-cup-fight/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 23:32:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-5-football-team-fined-after-ulu-cup-fight/</guid>
        <description>The football team has been fined £100 by the Amateur Football Association (AFA) after a fight broke out at the 19th of March ULU Cup Final with UCL. The club was charged with failing to control its supporters, to which they pleaded guilty, and one individual, whose case has yet to be heard, has been …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Financial Emergencies
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-18-financial-emergencies/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 08:58:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-18-financial-emergencies/</guid>
        <description>If you suddenly find yourself in financial hardship, for example finding that you&amp;rsquo;re unable to pay your rent for that month, the College can help you and may give you money (which you don&amp;rsquo;t have to pay back). As well as the processes described below, they will also provide emergency …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The next Medic President?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-the-next-medic-president/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 19:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-the-next-medic-president/</guid>
        <description>Read Suzie&amp;rsquo;s, and other manifestos, here, at comparethemedic.com
Voting opens on Monday 21st
This is your second time running. What do you think that says about you? I think it probably shows how much I want the position. Obviously I’ve had to rethink it this year and it’s quite a weird …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union launches Welfare and long-awaited Halls Surveys
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-union-launches-welfare-and-long-awaited-halls-surveys/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 19:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-union-launches-welfare-and-long-awaited-halls-surveys/</guid>
        <description>The Union’s delayed survey on hall rents has launched this week. It comes after weeks of debate about the value of the halls Amenities fund, which subsidises social events and is paid into by all students in halls. The survey asks a range of questions including whether or not students think that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lecturers to strike
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-lecturers-to-strike/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 19:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,Haralambos Dayantis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-lecturers-to-strike/</guid>
        <description>The University and College Union (UCU) has scheduled strikes over changes to pension schemes of university staff, with English universities due to be affected on the 22nd and 24th of March. Falling in the last week of term, the strikes could have a damaging effect on lecture courses across many …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>There’s no need to fear robots
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-theres-no-need-to-fear-robots/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 18:59:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-theres-no-need-to-fear-robots/</guid>
        <description>The Polish restaurant on Exhibition Road, Ognisko, seems to be out of its time. The décor and atmosphere would seem to suggest that mink-ensconced flappers and mustachioed airmen could come swooping into the dining hall at any moment. It’s in these surroundings that I have the pleasure to sit beside …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Break-ins reported in EEE building
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-break-ins-reported-in-eee-building/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 05:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-break-ins-reported-in-eee-building/</guid>
        <description>Lockers in the Electronic and Electrical Engineering (EEE) building were broken into on Tuesday night. The theft is the second in the building in as many weeks. The College is calling on students and staff to remain vigilant to reduce opportunities for “walk-in thieves”.
A laptop was stolen during …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sir Keith pied as RAG revive tradition
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-sir-keith-pied-as-rag-revive-tradition/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 19:52:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-sir-keith-pied-as-rag-revive-tradition/</guid>
        <description>See more photos of the Rector getting pied here
Finally! A Rector who isn&amp;rsquo;t afraid to take a pie to the face! The annual pieing of the Rector, a tradition that was discontinued during the reign of Sir Roy Anderson (whether that&amp;rsquo;s because he objected or due to lack of organisation is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Interview with President Alex Kendall
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-interview-with-president-alex-kendall/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 19:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-interview-with-president-alex-kendall/</guid>
        <description>Life Sciences cuts and Student Protests
Would you say that you have been an activist this year? Yes, I have, but not in the general sense. I don’t just jump on any bandwagon because it happens to be something other people are getting excited about. I’d like to think the Union is quite good at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cash-strapped libraries threaten to end journal subscription deals over rising costs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-cash-strapped-libraries-threaten-to-end-journal-subscription-deals-over-rising-costs/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 18:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-cash-strapped-libraries-threaten-to-end-journal-subscription-deals-over-rising-costs/</guid>
        <description>Intimidating isn’t the first word that springs to mind when you first meet Deborah Shorley, Director of the Imperial College London Library. A short, erudite librarian, one would not imagine such a character to be leading a fight against two of the largest publishers in the UK: Elsevier and Wiley …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>If laughter be the food of love, hear here
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-11-if-laughter-be-the-food-of-love-hear-here/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 06:46:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-11-if-laughter-be-the-food-of-love-hear-here/</guid>
        <description>I shall be open here, I’m not sure how to review a comedian. Does it suffice to say that Alun Cochrane was hilarious? Do I have any hope of conveying the humour of his jokes by retelling them here? The answer, I suspect, to both these questions is no, so I shall give it a go. He’s a Yorkshire …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Magic show success open to Copenhagan interpretation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-magic-show-success-open-to-copenhagan-interpretation/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 20:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-magic-show-success-open-to-copenhagan-interpretation/</guid>
        <description>It is somewhat topsy-turvy to say that there are no mysteries in magic, but plenty in physics. But as Dr Nic Harrigan, our Master of Ceremonies for the evening (complete with magician’s attire), explained: all magic tricks are explicable, but not all physics is yet understood. And no area of physics …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Complaint to Rector leads to radio shutdown
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-complaint-to-rector-leads-to-radio-shutdown/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 19:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-complaint-to-rector-leads-to-radio-shutdown/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Radio (IC Radio) was shut down by the Union last Tuesday evening after a “member of the public” complained to the Rector about the use of racially offensive language during a broadcast. A non-Imperial guest on an IC Radio show referred to a close friend as a “Paki”, which the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Major flooding shuts Biochemistry
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-major-flooding-shuts-biochemistry/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 19:37:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-major-flooding-shuts-biochemistry/</guid>
        <description>The Biochemistry building has been hit with two serious floods this past week. A failure of a pipe connection to a rooftop water tank is believed to have caused the flood on Thursday morning while a suspected valve failure, or pump malfunction, caused a 6ft flood of water in the sub-basement during …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ladies have a hot first term
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-ladies-have-a-hot-first-term/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 20:52:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-ladies-have-a-hot-first-term/</guid>
        <description>The Imperial Womens team are back and we are stronger than ever! After a frustrating couple of years trying to drum up interest amongst our female players, finally things have clicked into place. Nan and I were back after some busy times (we combined to win the BUCS Womens doubles bronze medal in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Does Imperial have a drinking problem?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-does-imperial-have-a-drinking-problem/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 21:11:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew N Colvin,Aemun Reza,Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-does-imperial-have-a-drinking-problem/</guid>
        <description>Following the controversial exposure of the drunken antics of Imperial medical students at the Reynolds Bar earlier this month, action has been taken to clamp down on the excessive drinking of “a minority of students”. However, as Felix found this week, many students have shrugged off concerns about …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New postgraduate halls at Clapham Junction
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-new-postgraduate-halls-at-clapham-junction/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 21:47:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-new-postgraduate-halls-at-clapham-junction/</guid>
        <description>New halls in Clapham Junction are set to open to postgraduates in the next academic year. Griffon Studios, which charges £235 per week for high-quality studio apartments, is the product of a joint venture between the Imperial College Fund and the property developer Berkeley First. The halls on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Uncertain future for Evelyn Gardens
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-uncertain-future-for-evelyn-gardens/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 21:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-uncertain-future-for-evelyn-gardens/</guid>
        <description>The long-term future of student accommodation in the Evelyn Gardens area is currently under review, with the high cost of necessary refurbishment likely to mean the closure of halls such as Fisher. The uncertainty comes as Imperial is reviewing all areas of its accommodation provision including the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Disappointment as Senate sides with Life Sciences cuts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-15-disappointment-as-senate-sides-with-life-sciences-cuts/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2010 17:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-15-disappointment-as-senate-sides-with-life-sciences-cuts/</guid>
        <description>The movement to stop the Life Sciences cuts suffered a setback today as Imperial College Senate rejected the Imperial College Union paper that called for a halt to the restructure. The Senate, which is made up of senior members of College management, including the Rector, failed to support the paper …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Opposition to Life Sciences cuts grows
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-11-opposition-to-life-sciences-cuts-grows/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2010 15:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-11-opposition-to-life-sciences-cuts-grows/</guid>
        <description>The Department of Life Sciences came under further pressure as the Director of the influential John Innes Centre (JIC), a plant science and microbiology research institute, called the changes &amp;ldquo;misguided&amp;rdquo;. It also been revealed that the College&amp;rsquo;s annual surplus, or the profit, has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I really don&#39;t know if I&#39;m going to stay at Imperial now...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-i-really-dont-know-if-im-going-to-stay-at-imperial-now/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 21:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-i-really-dont-know-if-im-going-to-stay-at-imperial-now/</guid>
        <description>What do you do?
I’m a self-funded PhD student from Russia. I am investigating the effect of synaptic proteins on neural circuits. I was a BioChem undergraduate at Imperial and let me say this, Dr Jane Saffell and Prof. Yuri Ushkaryov’s final year modules are irreplaceable. Their teaching was …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
