<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/tesni_haddon/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/tesni_haddon/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Meet Me at Dawn: Stun Me at Dusk</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-meet-me-at-dawn-stun-me-at-dusk/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tesni Haddon-Mcmillan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-meet-me-at-dawn-stun-me-at-dusk/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
According to Greek myth, Orpheus loses his lover, Eurydice, and laments so painfully for her that the gods themselves weep and help him on the terrible quest to reclaim Eurydice from the underworld.
This tale of longing and devastation was the source of inspiration for playwright, Zinnie …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The beauty behind the monster of Frankenstein</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-the-beauty-behind-the-monster-of-frankenstein/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tesni Haddon-Mcmillan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-the-beauty-behind-the-monster-of-frankenstein/</guid>
        <description>Frankenstein has long borne the false title of a frightening and twisted tale. However, the focus of this story is really on the loneliness of Frankenstein’s Creature, and its cravings for the affections of his master.
Upon the loss of his mother in child-birth, Victor Frankenstein succumbs to a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dark Laughs from ‘Pinter 7’</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-dark-laughs-from-pinter-7/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tesni Haddon-Mcmillan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-dark-laughs-from-pinter-7/</guid>
        <description>I write these first words at 10pm, having just made it back from Pinter 7. It seems that I’d have to at least make a start on my article now, not for issues of time but to capture feeling while it is still strong, for what is the point of art if not to inspire feeling?
I’ve left with a sense of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Love That Dare Not Speak Its Name</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-the-love-that-dare-not-speak-its-name/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tesni Haddon-Mcmillan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-the-love-that-dare-not-speak-its-name/</guid>
        <description>Love is perhaps the most integral and celebrated part of the human condition. People have been known to try to express and capture it since 800BC when the oldest recorded love poem was created in Mesopotamia. It is without question that love is a unique experience for all, and so countless artists …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Outlying Islands: A Dark Exploration of  Isolation</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-outlying-islands-a-dark-exploration-of-isolation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tesni Haddon-Mcmillan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-outlying-islands-a-dark-exploration-of-isolation/</guid>
        <description>The King’s Head Theatre is a charming location in Islington fronted by an eccentric-looking, cosy pub. Walking past the bar- after collecting an essential beverage- takes you to the small and intimate theatre, already full of tipsy patrons; this jovial atmosphere was truly a highlight of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Small Place and a Big Message</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-a-small-place-and-a-big-message/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tesni Haddon-Mcmillan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-a-small-place-and-a-big-message/</guid>
        <description>Once you enter the Gate Theatre, you are brought into a room lined with rows of chairs and scattered with seemingly out-of-place objects. Looking around, you see that there is no stage and you realise that the ‘show’ you believed you were coming to see is far closer to a private meeting. With no …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
