<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sph109/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sph109/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Dancing the Grim Fandango
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-dancing-the-grim-fandango/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 21:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Horti,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-dancing-the-grim-fandango/</guid>
        <description>I have come to realise that there is one thing that gamers crave above all else in their video games: uniqueness. It&amp;rsquo;s something that we only seem to see fleeting glances of in the modern day. Where did all the innovation and inspiration go? Well, a lot of it was spent in 1998 with the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let’s talk about Ron Paul
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-lets-talk-about-ron-paul/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 21:20:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Horti,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-lets-talk-about-ron-paul/</guid>
        <description>If you’ve been paying attention to the goings on in America in the lead up to next year’s presidential elections, you will no doubt have heard many political commentators expressing the view that Ron Paul is the man that everyone has been waiting for. The hero that America needs. What is especially …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sex, Drugs and Video Games
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-sex-drugs-and-video-games/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 20:55:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Horti,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-sex-drugs-and-video-games/</guid>
        <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve all been there. We&amp;rsquo;ve all played games that we are unable to put down, and the responsibility comes down to others to crowbar the controller – or mouse and keyboard if you&amp;rsquo;re so inclined – out of our hands. We&amp;rsquo;ve all got up early before school to spend a few golden …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Interview: William Lane Craig
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-interview-william-lane-craig/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 21:41:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Horti,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-interview-william-lane-craig/</guid>
        <description>Watch the interview in full below – with thanks to STOIC TV
Firstly, Dr Craig, thanks very much for coming along to speak to us, we appreciate you taking the time to enrich the Imperial College students.
Dr Craig: My pleasure.
I just want to get a little of your personal background and ask: when did …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Hell of Heaven
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-the-hell-of-heaven/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 22:11:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Horti,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-the-hell-of-heaven/</guid>
        <description>The question of what happens to us after we die is one that has troubled us as a species for thousands of years, and to this day many among us still wrestle daily with our own doubt and confusion over the matter. The posthumously themed wonderings of religious movements and philosophers alike have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A True Dichotomy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-a-true-dichotomy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 10:11:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Horti,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-a-true-dichotomy/</guid>
        <description>When facing a dichotomy, it often takes only a small amount of creative thinking to find a secret, third option. Some people will use this tactic unknowingly when their religious beliefs are called into question, especially when the question posed is: “Are you a theist or an atheist?” The secret, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mass deception
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-11-mass-deception/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2011 17:23:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Horti,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-11-mass-deception/</guid>
        <description>The news that the Belgian victims of abuse at the hands of Catholic priests are attempting to sue the Vatican should not surprise any of us. There have been various attempts over the years demanding that the church tries to put right the hideous crimes performed by its members, including a high …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Make your mind up, Clegg
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-make-your-mind-up-clegg/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 23:46:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Horti,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-make-your-mind-up-clegg/</guid>
        <description>Last week I offered my thoughts on why I believe Nick Clegg’s stance on the tuition fee policy was requisite, citing the essential maintenance of government stability. This week, we have seen the Lib Dem leader chance his arm on the other side, and I think he will find out that the grass is …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
