<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/czb11/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/czb11/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Shoes: Pleasure and Pain
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-18-shoes-pleasure-and-pain/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2015 21:01:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecile Borkhataria,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-18-shoes-pleasure-and-pain/</guid>
        <description>The V&amp;amp;A’s latest fashion exhibition takes a look at the extremes of footwear from around the world, ranging from Cinderella’s glass slippers featured in the recent Disney live action movie, to tiny lotus shoes used to bind women’s feet in 19th century China. The exhibition focuses on the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Life on Foot’: Discovering Spanish shoe brand Camper
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-life-on-foot-discovering-spanish-shoe-brand-camper/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 12:54:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecile Borkhataria,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-life-on-foot-discovering-spanish-shoe-brand-camper/</guid>
        <description>After arriving at the Design Museum soaking wet from London’s pelting rain, I joined a group of journalists ready to be guided through the Museum’s latest exhibition entitled Life on Foot: Camper at the Design Museum. The exhibition marks the 40th anniversary of the Spanish footwear Brand Camper, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Fitting Legacy: Nick Waplington/Alexander McQueen – Working Process
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-a-fitting-legacy-nick-waplingtonalexander-mcqueen-working-process/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 13:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecile Borkhataria,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-a-fitting-legacy-nick-waplingtonalexander-mcqueen-working-process/</guid>
        <description>Last week, Nick Waplington’s photography exhibition of legendary fashion designer Alexander McQueen’s final collection opened at Pimlico’s Tate Britain. The exhibition, based on Nick Waplington’s book entitled Alexander McQueen: Working Process, features photographs of McQueen’s Fall 2009 collection …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Music’s biggest night: the best and worst outfits of the 2015 Grammy’s
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-musics-biggest-night-the-best-and-worst-outfits-of-the-2015-grammys/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 23:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecile Borkhataria,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-musics-biggest-night-the-best-and-worst-outfits-of-the-2015-grammys/</guid>
        <description>Beyoncé killed it in this all black Proenza Schouler dress at Sunday’s Grammy’s. She wore an equally beautiful white dress on stage whilst performing Take My Hand, Precious Lord, which featured in the popular movie Selma about the civil rights movement in the United States. Her performance was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chanel haute couture spring/summer 2015: the luxe rebirth of the beanie
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-chanel-haute-couture-springsummer-2015-the-luxe-rebirth-of-the-beanie/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 13:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecile Borkhataria,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-chanel-haute-couture-springsummer-2015-the-luxe-rebirth-of-the-beanie/</guid>
        <description>On Tuesday, Karl Lagerfeld pushed the boundaries of haute couture fashion yet again at the Chanel haute couture fashion show. The exclusive catwalk event was held at the Grand Palais in Paris, with attendees ranging from the likes of Hollywood starlets like Kristen Stewart, to French femme fatales …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ASOS CEO Nick Robertson talks about his sucesses to crowd of hundreds
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-asos-ceo-nick-robertson-talks-about-his-sucesses-to-crowd-of-hundreds/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 01:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecile Borkhataria,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-asos-ceo-nick-robertson-talks-about-his-sucesses-to-crowd-of-hundreds/</guid>
        <description>On Monday, an event hosted by the Imperial Entrepreneurs society (IE) saw Huxley flooded with students hoping to see ASOS co-founder and CEO, Nick Robertson, give his insight into the success of his company. As the queue of hopeful students extended onto the Sherfield walkway, members of IE handed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Victoria’s Secret fashion show – landing on home turf
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-11-the-victorias-secret-fashion-show-landing-on-home-turf/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 21:33:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecile Borkhataria,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-11-the-victorias-secret-fashion-show-landing-on-home-turf/</guid>
        <description>Angel: Alessandra Ambrosio
The Fantasy Bra
This year, Alessandra Ambrosio and Adriana Lima had the honour of modeling a Fantasy Bra this year. Normally, only one angel wears a fantasy bra each year, but for this year’s show, two were made for the angels who have been modelling for Victoria’s Secret …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial raises £54.2 million from donations
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-9-imperial-raises-542-million-from-donations/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2014 13:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecile Borkhataria,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-9-imperial-raises-542-million-from-donations/</guid>
        <description>On the 25th of November, Imperial College London hosted a Thank You Reception in celebration of the record-breaking number of donations made to the College during 2013-2014. Part of the donations, which totalled £54.2 million, went towards funding 110 undergraduate scholarships through the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>World News: 47 killed by a suicide bomb in Nigeria
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-world-news-47-killed-by-a-suicide-bomb-in-nigeria/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 20:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecile Borkhataria,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-world-news-47-killed-by-a-suicide-bomb-in-nigeria/</guid>
        <description>On the morning of Monday 13th November, an explosion detonated by a female suicide bomber killed 47 people and injured 79 others in Yobe, Niberia. The attack took place at a local school, and the suicide bomber entered the school undetected, wearing a school uniform and carrying explosive materials …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial professor to lead Ebola vaccine trial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-imperial-professor-to-lead-ebola-vaccine-trial/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 22:52:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecile Borkhataria,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-imperial-professor-to-lead-ebola-vaccine-trial/</guid>
        <description>The current Ebola outbreak in West Africa, which began in March 2014, has afflicted Guinea, Sierra Leone, Liberia, Nigeria, and recently, Senegal.
The death toll has now surpassed 2800, with the total number of cases numbering 5864. The severity of this outbreak is unprecedented; the virus first …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wedding Dresses: An Exhibition at the V&amp;A
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-wedding-dresses-an-exhibition-at-the-va/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 20:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecile Borkhataria,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-wedding-dresses-an-exhibition-at-the-va/</guid>
        <description>Today, brides of many faiths and nationalities wear white to celebrate their marriages, even in countres where it is not traditional to do so. The globalisation phenomenon and the influence and strength of the wedding industry have contributed to this homogenisation in wedding trends. The white …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Best Dressed Stars of the 2014 Met Gala: Beyond Fashion
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-the-best-dressed-stars-of-the-2014-met-gala-beyond-fashion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 15:03:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecile Borkhataria,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-the-best-dressed-stars-of-the-2014-met-gala-beyond-fashion/</guid>
        <description>On Monday night the most exclusive fashion event of the year took place in New York City, and its famous guests wowed us with their style.
This years Met Gala theme, Charles James: Beyond Fashion, gave guests the opportunity to dress over the top! From Lupita Nyong’o’s flapper girl Prada ensemble to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The cutest spring 2014 trends
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-the-cutest-spring-2014-trends/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 01:35:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecile Borkhataria,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-the-cutest-spring-2014-trends/</guid>
        <description>Spring is slowly starting to set in in London, and although we’re not feeling the mini-skirt wearing heat yet, these trends work for the transiton stage between winter and summer. On a cooler day, carry around a chunky knit sweater to ward off the occasional chills of the British spring time, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Quite the ‘best’ exotic marigold hotel
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-quite-the-best-exotic-marigold-hotel/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 18:16:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cecile Borkhataria,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-quite-the-best-exotic-marigold-hotel/</guid>
        <description>The Best Exotic Marigold Hotel
Director John Madden Screenwriters Ol Parker, Deborah Moggach (novel) Cast Bill Nighy, Judi Dench, Maggie Smith, Dev Patel, Tom Wilkinson, Penelope Wilton, Celia Imrie, Ronal Pickup
John Madden’s uplifting dramatic comedy offers a perfect blend of laughter, tears and …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
