<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/extuser0/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/extuser0/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Finding Out What Makes JOHN Tick....
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-18-finding-out-what-makes-john-tick/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 15:53:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-18-finding-out-what-makes-john-tick/</guid>
        <description>“The normality of life is just to have someone you can express stuff with.”
Devised by DV8 Physical Theatre, a contemporary dance company known for their original and controversial work, the atmosphere surrounding the press night of JOHN was electric.
The production was devised following a series of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Top 5 Memberships in London
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-18-top-5-memberships-in-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 15:38:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-18-top-5-memberships-in-london/</guid>
        <description>There are a good number of reasons why you may want to join one or more of the plethora of membership schemes offered across the capital. Do you want to show off to everyone how cultured you are? Maybe you simply can’t stand to queue. Perhaps you relish going to members-only areas. Hopefully though, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A personal look at psychological abuse
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-a-personal-look-at-psychological-abuse/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 18:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-a-personal-look-at-psychological-abuse/</guid>
        <description>Αt a friend’s house party last week I met a couple that brought back a few memories I had hoped to keep locked up, and now, huddled next to the radiator in my otherwise arctic flat, I try to write this for what seems like the hundredth time. I want to write about emotional abuse, its warning signs, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Should non-participants be forced to subsidise events?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-should-non-participants-be-forced-to-subsidise-events/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 18:06:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-should-non-participants-be-forced-to-subsidise-events/</guid>
        <description>Oh how trendy it is to decry the College for their financial decisions! Mind you, short of stating parallels with ‘Butcher of the Somme’, we can settle for glorifying an ambiguous term such as ‘student experience’ – nails in the coffin, I tell you! But do we try to view this topic from a rational …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is feminism a toxic word?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-is-feminism-a-toxic-word/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 13:12:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-is-feminism-a-toxic-word/</guid>
        <description>I first remember coming across the word ‘feminism’ when I was about 9, and asking my mum what it meant. “It’s the principle”, she replied, without even glancing up from her newspaper, “that girls and boys should be treated in exactly the same way”. I remember thinking it bizarre that such an obvious …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pirates: A Review With Scientists
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-20-pirates-a-review-with-scientists/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2014 16:13:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-20-pirates-a-review-with-scientists/</guid>
        <description>Without making so bold a claim so as to say that we’ve never watched porn, it’s fair to say that neither of us are connoisseurs of the cinematographic genre. However, the 2005 feature-length Pirates, with its million-dollar budget, was the most expensive pornographic film ever made at the time, a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Berlin: A Night Life Review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-berlin-a-night-life-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 04:53:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-berlin-a-night-life-review/</guid>
        <description>People are always on the hunt for a place to party, a place to have a blast, for it to be a hoot. Maybe, if luck will have it, you manage to make love sideways to the rhythm of Mandy and Stella Artoorhys in Dalston or Metric. But sadly, London can be a bit of a ‘les incompetents’ in this department. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Election Anonymity - What’s the Point?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-17-election-anonymity-whats-the-point/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 17:25:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-17-election-anonymity-whats-the-point/</guid>
        <description>This year the Union Election process has significantly changed; there is no longer a list of candidates standing for each position and instead the complete list will be announced once nominations are complete.
According to the Deputy Returning Officers this change has been brought about to make the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>3am Mocaine with an Ex-Banker
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-17-3am-mocaine-with-an-ex-banker/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 17:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-17-3am-mocaine-with-an-ex-banker/</guid>
        <description>This is a story of caution. A story of naivety, intense highs and bad judgement. Try to find value in it, if you can.
2am, Wednesday morning. Insomniac me, wakes up; I am hungry. Needless to say, a quick venture into the kitchen yields no results: the fridge is void. Void like my mental state as I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>When is it Wrong to Enjoy Art?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-17-when-is-it-wrong-to-enjoy-art/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 17:22:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-17-when-is-it-wrong-to-enjoy-art/</guid>
        <description>Woody Allen’s confusing and highly questionable private life has once again been thrust into the open with Dylan Farrow’s accusation of being molested by him when she was seven. Whilst I was shocked, but not surprised by the recent happenings, I am not going to use this space to pass comment on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I’m SINGLE. What should I do today?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-16-im-single-what-should-i-do-today/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 12:18:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-16-im-single-what-should-i-do-today/</guid>
        <description>Today, for all intents and purposes, is Friday the 14th of February, 2014 A.D. Many people are divided over embracing a modern fad called St. Valentine’s Day, with those favoured by Cupid’s Arrows largely choosing to play along and pander to the irrational significance attributed to this day, while …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On age and respect for your elders
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-on-age-and-respect-for-your-elders/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 05:07:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-on-age-and-respect-for-your-elders/</guid>
        <description>Respect your elders” is a mantra that I always felt was redundant. You would give someone due respect if they were reasonable and polite to you, as anyone should be, or you would give them special consideration, such as offering your seat on the bus, if they were physically infirm, not just because …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The last samurai movie PLEASE
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-the-last-samurai-movie-please/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 03:59:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-the-last-samurai-movie-please/</guid>
        <description>There is no doubt that 47 Ronin was Universal Studio’s hope-child given its vast budget of $175-million. However, unlike The Last Samurai in whose footsteps this movie obviously attempted to follow, the difference between their respective results is stark; in fact, rather akin to that between a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Virtual Reality
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-virtual-reality/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 17:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-virtual-reality/</guid>
        <description>Ah, what a powerful feeling!
I manipulate Red Man and Green.
My thumbs are in full control,
I order leaps, dashes and sprints across the screen.
I am the virtual boss,
Haha! I click at buttons A and B,
Every problem you could ever think of, I can solve,
Brave is what I am, staring into the face of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science Challenge’s Original Aim Exposed
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-science-challenges-original-aim-exposed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 03:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-science-challenges-original-aim-exposed/</guid>
        <description>Every year the RCSU issues the Science Challenge, which has evolved into an essay competition with very acceptable prizes. However the original motivation for the challenge was only known to a select few – now it can be revealed.
Some years ago a curious old RCS alumnus found he had insufficient …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Opinion: h-bar – Revisiting the Holland Club
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-opinion-h-bar-revisiting-the-holland-club/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 03:47:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-opinion-h-bar-revisiting-the-holland-club/</guid>
        <description>The Holland Club was so popular because it was a unique facility within the College offering a traditional ‘local’ pub ambience for staff and postgraduates to relax and socialise in. The bar was carpeted and comfortably furnished, the lighting sympathetic, the atmosphere warm and friendly. The new …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>And may the odds be ever in your favour...again
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-and-may-the-odds-be-ever-in-your-favouragain/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 22:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-and-may-the-odds-be-ever-in-your-favouragain/</guid>
        <description>The Hunger Games: Catching Fire
Director: Francis Lawrence Writers: Simon Beaufoy, Michael Arndt, Suzanne Collins (novel) Starring: Jennifer Lawrence, Josh Hutcherson, Liam Hemsworth, Woody Harrelson Runtime: 146 minutes Certification: 12A
So it’s been about a year since the first Hunger Games film …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-supercalifragilisticexpialidocious/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 22:18:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-supercalifragilisticexpialidocious/</guid>
        <description>Saving Mr Banks
Director: John Lee Hancock Writers: Kelly Marcel, Sue Smith Starring: Tom Hanks, Emma Thompson, Ruth Wilson, Colin Farrell, Paul Giamatti, Bradley Whitford, Jason Schwartzman, Rachel Griffiths Runtime: 125 minutes Certification: PG
If the single word that makes up this article’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Depression – ­My Story
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-depression-my-story/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 15:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-depression-my-story/</guid>
        <description>I was diagnosed with clinical depression when I was 17. For me, the diagnosis helped. It helped to give a name to the bizarre way that I had been feeling for over a year. I was always tired and always sad. The worst feeling was that of isolation, and feeling disjointed from the world, and I felt …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Depression – Taboo or Not Taboo?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-depression-taboo-or-not-taboo/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 15:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-depression-taboo-or-not-taboo/</guid>
        <description>Imperial, welcome to the OpenMinds campaign! Our aim is to increase understanding of mental health conditions and remove some of the stigma with which they are associated. 1 in 4 people suffer from a mental health condition, yet there is a severe lack of awareness and the subject is, too often, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College Chess Congress 2013
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-24-imperial-college-chess-congress-2013/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 23:35:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-24-imperial-college-chess-congress-2013/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College has had a long tradition of hosting prestigious chess events in London, starting several decades ago with the Kensington Congress – this fell by the wayside somewhat in the early 2000’s but was revived by Imperial College alumnus John Sargent in 2011 with the help of IC Chess Club’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A dream of liquid light
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-a-dream-of-liquid-light/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 21:00:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-a-dream-of-liquid-light/</guid>
        <description>By Cristina Ferraz Rigo
“To them, I said, the truth would be literally nothing but the shadows of the images.” Socrates dialogue with Glauco, Plato, The Republic
The allegory of the cavern is one of the most inspiring readings to get acquainted with design semiotics. In this beautiful metaphor, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The importance of funded scholarships
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-7-the-importance-of-funded-scholarships/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 19:50:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-7-the-importance-of-funded-scholarships/</guid>
        <description>Like an excitable kid on Christmas morning, A-level results day saw me up before dawn, frantically refreshing the beloved UCAS track page to see whether or not I’d cut the mustard. Unfortunately, I had to be up and at work early that morning, so couldn’t make it in to school to find out my exact …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who is Silvio?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-6-who-is-silvio/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2011 11:34:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-6-who-is-silvio/</guid>
        <description>Who is Silvio? What is he, That all our swines commend him? Wholly full of vice is he; The seven such place did lend him, That he might removed be.
Is he blind to his hair? For arrogance lives with blindness. Sloth doth to his mind repair, To help him of his spineless, And being helped, inhabits …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The next iteration of Android’s future
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-the-next-iteration-of-androids-future/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 18:21:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-the-next-iteration-of-androids-future/</guid>
        <description>A fortnight ago saw Google team up with Samsung for the much anticipated launch of the latest iteration of Android, its popular smartphone OS, alongside the Galaxy Nexus, the latest and greatest Google branded hardware to run it on. Held in Hong Kong, the keynote swiftly began with Samsung taking to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Punk Planet
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-punk-planet/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 11:30:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-punk-planet/</guid>
        <description>There’s nothing more hardcore punk than having a creed to live by. The straight-edge subculture – an abstention from drugs, promiscuous sex, and often hair – was a creed of sorts, inspired by the anti-hedonistic stance of 1980s bands such as Minor Threat, and many bands have adopted the stance of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fabulous Fusion arrives in London
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-fabulous-fusion-arrives-in-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 11:08:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-fabulous-fusion-arrives-in-london/</guid>
        <description>Imperial is no stranger to big events; you’d have to have had your head in the sand to not know what East Meets West is. Now an Imperial postgraduate hopes to bring her experiences from her previous university to break the mould with a spectacle that goes above and beyond anything that has come …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Founder Stories: Storify and MinuteBox
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-founder-stories-storify-and-minutebox/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 22:52:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-founder-stories-storify-and-minutebox/</guid>
        <description>Last Friday, as part of the Imperial Entrepreneurs speaker series programme, the founders of Storify, Xavier Damman, and MinuteBox, Josh Liu, came to the Imperial Business School.
The evening kicked off with a presentation from Imperial Entrepreneurs about what they do and the set of events planned …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Economy in History
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-the-economy-in-history/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 22:46:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-the-economy-in-history/</guid>
        <description>Legend has it that, as for all faithful Muslims, the day came when the good King Musa of Mali announced to his people that he would be leaving Mali for the Hajj, the pilgrimage to Mecca. The announcement, though praised by the wise and respected by all his subjects, came with fear, as the trip from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>QE, or not QE, that is the question
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-qe-or-not-qe-that-is-the-question/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 22:35:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-qe-or-not-qe-that-is-the-question/</guid>
        <description>There was a global economic meltdown in 2008. World governments have since spent their time running through plans A-Z to try and reboot economies, but so far any recovery has been wiped out by other problems such as the crisis in the Eurozone. The problem of what to do with the levels of debt has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gazing into the soul of the 99%
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-gazing-into-the-soul-of-the-99/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 21:52:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-gazing-into-the-soul-of-the-99/</guid>
        <description>Saturday saw a global day of occupation and protest in 951 cities across 82 countries, making this day one of the most widespread days of resistance ever seen. Apart from Rome, they were also entirely peaceful. This was no random event but part of a global tide of uprising that began in the Arab …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dennis Ritchie – An Unsung Hero
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-dennis-ritchie-an-unsung-hero/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 21:34:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-dennis-ritchie-an-unsung-hero/</guid>
        <description>The world has lost two giants of technology in as many weeks. The news that Dennis Ritchie died on 12 October, aged 70, after enduring cancer and heart disease for several years, elicited a quieter response than that for Steve Jobs. Ritchie was the creator of the C programming language and one of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Punk planet
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-16-punk-planet/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2011 15:11:24 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-16-punk-planet/</guid>
        <description>Sicily: land of citrus fruit, olive oil, Cosa Nostra, and Uzeda, a band hailing from the foothills of smoking Mt. Etna. Three of their five albums were recorded by Steve Albini, the pixie of punk rock himself, and released on the Touch &amp;amp; Go label. Albini’s instantly recognizable sound on 4 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Armitage Here?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-16-armitage-here/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2011 14:42:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-16-armitage-here/</guid>
        <description>Karole Armitage’s limited run of performances at the Southbank Center were billed as science inspired punk-ballet. On the basis of that description alone I realised that my attendance was inevitable. Nothing however could have prepared me for the breathtakingly energetic, shockingly beautiful dance …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fast times for charity
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-8-fast-times-for-charity/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2011 18:12:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-8-fast-times-for-charity/</guid>
        <description>The 18th century French philosopher Denis Diderot once said ‘Only passions, great passions, can elevate the soul to great things.’
I have never been one to attach much importance to helping others. Being an only child, I never had the time to think whether life was treating others as fairly as it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rivers of London
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-rivers-of-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 10:25:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-rivers-of-london/</guid>
        <description>A deft mix of police procedural and urban fantasy, Aaronovitch&amp;rsquo;s Rivers of London follows Peter Grant, police constable in central London and all round nice guy. After coming across a voluble witness to a murder (who himself is already dead), Grant is plunged into the magical and twisted …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Simple, lazy, great
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-9-30-simple-lazy-great/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2011 12:40:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-9-30-simple-lazy-great/</guid>
        <description>The Americans are really good at it. American Pie, Dude, Where’s My Car?, Bill &amp;amp; Ted’s Excellent Adventure. The Brits tried it once – Kevin &amp;amp; Perry Go Large. And then four pubescent, awkward, goofy, and weird teenagers popped onto the scene to deliver the summer’s funniest movie.
Just like …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don&#39;t Scare the Hare
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-4-28-dont-scare-the-hare/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2011 13:43:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-4-28-dont-scare-the-hare/</guid>
        <description>“Thanks for coming at such short notice.”
“Oh, no, always a pleasure.”
“Not today, not after last night’s ratings.”
Dave had to agree, Sunday at the BBC commission office sat in front of the commissions chief himself wasn’t going to be the best place to find yourself when your show has just bombed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Festive antics in Amsterdam
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-festive-antics-in-amsterdam/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 20:43:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (non-IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-festive-antics-in-amsterdam/</guid>
        <description>Amsterdam: when the word is spoken bells immediately begin to ring. It’s one of those places that’s on everyone’s to-do list, whether the intentions be noble or otherwise. Following a whimsical conversation many sleepy Sundays ago we decided that it would be the perfect pre-Christmas destination, a …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
