<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/tags/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/tags/books/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Contemplating troubled pasts in the City of Literature</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-contemplating-troubled-pasts-in-the-city-of-literature/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavan Inguva,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-contemplating-troubled-pasts-in-the-city-of-literature/</guid>
        <description>The seeds of this article were sowed over December break, during a weekend I spent in Hamburg, Germany and a visit to Lubeck (Birthplace of Thomas Mann), followed by a week in Poland.
I only found out when in Krakow, that it is designated a UNESCO city of literature. This made more sense after …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“What would you have done?”</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02--what-would-you-have-done/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bayan Al Balushi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02--what-would-you-have-done/</guid>
        <description>The Reader is one of those books that one can discuss at length and would make a good choice for a book club, but I’ll try to keep it short though I have much to say.
The story is told from the first person perspective of Michael Berg and begins with him having contracted hepatitis at the age of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Debut novel challenges traditions of the Arab world</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-debut-novel-challenges-traditions-of-the-arab-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bayan Al Balushi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-debut-novel-challenges-traditions-of-the-arab-world/</guid>
        <description>The first time I heard of this book was when I watched the author being interviewed on an Arab channel. Not having watched the interview from the beginning, I didn’t know what the novel was about, but I was intrigued by their discussion of Arab culture and traditions. When I learnt that the book …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Strong contenders for 2017 T. S. Eliot Prize for poetry</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-strong-contenders-for-2017-t-s-eliot-prize-for-poetry/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-strong-contenders-for-2017-t-s-eliot-prize-for-poetry/</guid>
        <description>The T. S. Eliot Prize, awarded by the Poetry Book Society, is arguably one of the most prestigious poetry prizes in the world. Awarded every year to a poetry collection in English first published in the UK or Ireland, it has seen many household names winning in the past, including Ted Hughes, Carol …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2017 roundup: the best books of the year</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-2017-roundup-the-best-books-of-the-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Alice Peberdy,Katie Cook,Clemens Jakubec,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-2017-roundup-the-best-books-of-the-year/</guid>
        <description>What was the best thing you read this year? Four of our Books Writers give their thoughts:
Morning and Evening, by Jon Fosse
Jon Fosse to tell the story of the Norwegian fisherman Johannes in only a hundred pages. To be exact, we only learn about the two most significant events in his life: his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kazuo Ishiguro, winner of 2017 Nobel Prize in Literature, is master of words and the heart</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-kazuo-ishiguro-winner-of-2017-nobel-prize-in-literature-is-master-of-words-and-the-heart/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-kazuo-ishiguro-winner-of-2017-nobel-prize-in-literature-is-master-of-words-and-the-heart/</guid>
        <description>I first encountered Kazuo Ishiguro’s writing back in high school, in the form of his short story collection Nocturnes. I had won some book vouchers, and was browsing the local bookstore for something worth buying when I came across this slim volume. Five Stories of Music and Nightfall, it read, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Literature should not just be about ‘dead white men’</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-literature-should-not-just-be-about-dead-white-men/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-literature-should-not-just-be-about-dead-white-men/</guid>
        <description>Much has been written so far about ‘decolonising’ the English Literature curriculum, after Cambridge University’s English undergraduate Lola Olufemi wrote an open letter imploring her faculty to broaden their curriculum to include non-white writers. The letter, signed by around 150 students, called …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Tis the season to be reading</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08--tis-the-season-to-be-reading/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,Alice Peberdy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08--tis-the-season-to-be-reading/</guid>
        <description>Got a family member you need to get a last-minute gift for? Why not get them a book – at least it&amp;rsquo;s easy to wrap!
This is Going To Hurt, by Adam Kay
Have a healthcare professional among your family and friends? Even if you don’t, they are sure to enjoy this hilarious journal by ex-doctor, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Seeing the world through literature – so many books, so little time</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-seeing-the-world-through-literature-so-many-books-so-little-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavan Inguva,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-seeing-the-world-through-literature-so-many-books-so-little-time/</guid>
        <description>Seeing another part of the world is quite an exciting prospect for anyone: different foods, culture, history, and – most importantly – visiting beautiful bookstores and discovering authors you would not have heard of otherwise. Picking up a book, albeit translated to English, by a local author has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Decolonising the canon: Felix recommends</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-decolonising-the-canon-felix-recommends/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-decolonising-the-canon-felix-recommends/</guid>
        <description>Trumpet, by Jackie Kay
Kay’s only novel Trumpet is in a class of its own, and one of the most unconventional books I’ve ever read. Joss Moody is a renowned jazz musician whose death sparks a frantic seeking of truth by his son and the public about his ‘true’ identity and gender. It explores the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A women’s alternative to the Booker</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-a-women-s-alternative-to-the-booker/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katie Cook,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-a-women-s-alternative-to-the-booker/</guid>
        <description>If you’re only going to read the winner of one fiction prize each year, the Women’s Prize for Fiction will always be your best bet. Each year the prize honours one female author whose novel has made the greatest impact on the literary world in the past year. The prize began when in 1991 it was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hollywood has brought Atwood’s dystopia to the screen, and now into reality</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-hollywood-has-brought-atwood-s-dystopia-to-the-screen-and-now-into-reality/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Peberdy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-hollywood-has-brought-atwood-s-dystopia-to-the-screen-and-now-into-reality/</guid>
        <description>It seems the morning news is scarcely without another allegation of sexual assault these days. Harvey Weinstein has inspired many stars, mostly women, to share their stories of abuse by people with power. Finally, these hard-hitting topics may finally be discussed at a meaningful level through their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In the relentless tread of time, a man searches for the greater miracle of life </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-in-the-relentless-tread-of-time-a-man-searches-for-the-greater-miracle-of-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Clemens Jakubec,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-in-the-relentless-tread-of-time-a-man-searches-for-the-greater-miracle-of-life/</guid>
        <description>Freedom – a word as awe-inspiring as it is undefined. There are many ways of tackling the issue of what freedom means on a general as well as on a personal level. In his 2013 novel The Greater Miracle Thomas Glavinic sheds light on the problem of freedom from a very personal perspective.
The novel …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In the words of a young poet finding her feet</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-in-the-words-of-a-young-poet-finding-her-feet/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-in-the-words-of-a-young-poet-finding-her-feet/</guid>
        <description>What do we know of someone else’s life, besides what they choose to reveal to us? What more of a life that was tragically cut short, and has remained an enigma since?
In a newly-published tome of never-before-seen letters by 20th-century poet Sylvia Plath, we steal glimpses of a young, gifted poet …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The koala bear as a metaphor for life, death, and the struggle to survive </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-the-koala-bear-as-a-metaphor-for-life-death-and-the-struggle-to-survive/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Clemens Jakubec,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-the-koala-bear-as-a-metaphor-for-life-death-and-the-struggle-to-survive/</guid>
        <description>The animal was not black. It was not strong. It was lazy and had furry ears, a creature, that people laughed about. The best one could say about the animal was, that it was cute.” The koala is usually not an animal that people tend to spend a lot of time thinking about. Nevertheless, swiss author …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Immerse yourself in the tumultuous sea of this 20th century historical drama</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-immerse-yourself-in-the-tumultuous-sea-of-this-20th-century-historical-drama/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Pavan Inguva,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-immerse-yourself-in-the-tumultuous-sea-of-this-20th-century-historical-drama/</guid>
        <description>A lot of great literature has served as excellent snapshots into the culture and attitudes of the society that the author describes. Yukio Mishima’s Sea of Fertility Tetralogy is a perfect example of that. The tetralogy consists of Spring Snow, Runaway Horses, The Temple of Dawn, and The Decay of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In defence of ‘difficult’ books</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-in-defence-of-difficult-books/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ned Summers,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-in-defence-of-difficult-books/</guid>
        <description>There is no criticism more widely levelled against book and author than that of difficulty. I was prompted to write this article because of a one-star Goodreads review of Thomas Pynchon’s The Crying of Lot 49. It began:
“A classic English majors only book, aka people like talking about this book and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ali Smith’s Autumn is more than just a post-Brexit manifesto</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-ali-smith-s-autumn-is-more-than-just-a-post-brexit-manifesto/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Peberdy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-ali-smith-s-autumn-is-more-than-just-a-post-brexit-manifesto/</guid>
        <description>Books which lack speech marks always scare me. It can seem like they’re trying too hard just to break a rule and look contemporary. But I should never have doubted Ali Smith, in whose new book, Autumn, it feels entirely appropriate. It freed the author to skip between characters and to entwine her …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hope amid darkness in Philip Pullman’s new series</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-hope-amid-darkness-in-philip-pullman-s-new-series/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Natasha Manuelpillai,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-hope-amid-darkness-in-philip-pullman-s-new-series/</guid>
        <description>Known for his trilogy His Dark Materials, a fixture of many of our teenage bookshelves, Pullman is no stranger to the best-seller charts. La Belle Sauvage is the much-anticipated first volume of The Book of Dust, which Pullman discussed with BBC broadcaster and fellow author Cerys Matthews at a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Words of migratory flight</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-words-of-migratory-flight/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-words-of-migratory-flight/</guid>
        <description>The world is a fleeting glory”, reads Asha Lul Mohamud Yusuf’s poem, The Scab. To the more than 110,000 Somali-born immigrants living in the UK, many of whom fled the Somali Civil War as refugees, this cannot be more true. Stability is an illusion when one has to witness one’s own country torn apart …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An evening discussion with the Booker Prize nominees</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-an-evening-discussion-with-the-booker-prize-nominees/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-an-evening-discussion-with-the-booker-prize-nominees/</guid>
        <description>It was the night before the announcement of the 2017 Man Booker Prize winner, and it was the first time the shortlisted writers had all come together in the same space. In the Royal Festival Hall, where all six shortlisted writers sat next to each other on stage, the anticipation was palpable amid …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How a terrible beauty is born</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-how-a-terrible-beauty-is-born/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Astrid Zong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-how-a-terrible-beauty-is-born/</guid>
        <description>Be-monster not thy feature,” says Albany to Goneril; “proper deformity seems not in the fiend so horrid as in woman.” In King Lear, what renders Goneril’s ruthlessness particularly chilling is the juxtaposing presence of inhumanity – or, in Albany’s Elizabethan conception, unfemininity – in someone …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On Kazuo Ishiguro</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-on-kazuo-ishiguro/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Gracie Holt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-on-kazuo-ishiguro/</guid>
        <description>There was a time when, as an adult, I did not read books. Then one evening, when I lay awake overthinking and analysing, I realised what this meant. If I continued at my current rate of reading 0.75 books a year on holiday, then I would likely die not having read 100 books. I was then suddenly aware …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All the best books coming out this term</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-all-the-best-books-coming-out-this-term/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-all-the-best-books-coming-out-this-term/</guid>
        <description>The Floating World, by C. Morgan Babst (October 17th)
Normally I don’t find this kind of books fascinating – I sometimes add them to my to-be-read (TBR) list, but they just stay there forever. However, this book has something… probably the parents who abandon their daughter in the middle of a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Saunders explores the limbo between life and death in debut novel</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-saunders-explores-the-limbo-between-life-and-death-in-debut-novel/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Bennie,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-saunders-explores-the-limbo-between-life-and-death-in-debut-novel/</guid>
        <description>I was fearful when I heard about Lincoln in the Bardo almost a decade ago. I’m not a fan of historical novels and was aware of the difficulties that come with moving from short stories to novels. My fears were unfounded, George Saunders’ first novel is a triumph. To even call it a historical novel …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Timeless’ recommendations for Autumn reading...</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13--timeless-recommendations-for-autumn-reading/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13--timeless-recommendations-for-autumn-reading/</guid>
        <description>Adulthood is a Myth, by Sarah Andersen
I know you are stuck in between two assignments and three textbooks to read, so you definitely don’t have a lot of time to lose reading ‘for pleasure’, but I think that you can find five minutes here and there to realise that you are not the only one who has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gaiman’s London is never where you think it is</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-gaiman-s-london-is-never-where-you-think-it-is/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-gaiman-s-london-is-never-where-you-think-it-is/</guid>
        <description>Neil Gaiman has an uncanny knack for picking out the essence of a place.
In American Gods, Gaiman weaved the battle between ancient gods and modern greed into an epic tale of contemporary America. Neverwhere, in my opinion, should be read by everyone who lives in London. Richard, the protagonist, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>H.G. Wells’ little-known South Ken connection</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-h-g-wells-little-known-south-ken-connection/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Peberdy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-h-g-wells-little-known-south-ken-connection/</guid>
        <description>Imagine the Imperial freshers of the past; ponder where their college career led them. Research is probably first to mind – medicine, teaching, banking… Arts? We’re scientists, not robots! Great academics are often churned out, but our university also produced one of the fathers of science fiction, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ken Kesey – Author, revolutionary, and counter-cultural icon of the 1960s</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-ken-kesey-author-revolutionary-and-counter-cultural-icon-of-the-1960s/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Purdy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-ken-kesey-author-revolutionary-and-counter-cultural-icon-of-the-1960s/</guid>
        <description>As Cold War tension and paranoia reached its height in the mid-1950s, the American government entered into the most obscure stretch of the arms race – development of a weapon that could be used as means of mass mind control. During this search psychedelics drugs such as LSD were discovered and …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
