<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mp1710/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mp1710/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Miners Mourn Medic Defeat
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-miners-mourn-medic-defeat/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 22:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Margot Pikovsky,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-miners-mourn-medic-defeat/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday 14 November, ICSM Ladies’ 2s faced off with the RSM 1s at their Osterley home ground. The afternoon was glorious: the sun overhead and no-leggings-necessary heat a stark contrast from the last time these two teams met back in March, an event that will long stay in the memory of both …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A call to remembrance
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-a-call-to-remembrance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 11:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Margot Pikovsky,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-a-call-to-remembrance/</guid>
        <description>Anybody who has ever seen The History Boys, whether on stage or on screen, will remember the moment when Irwin, that world-wise and world-weary teacher, turns round to his pupils observing a monument to fallen soldiers and says: “All this mourning has veiled the truth. Because you should …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bromance of the renaissance men
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-bromance-of-the-renaissance-men/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 03:05:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Margot Pikovsky,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-bromance-of-the-renaissance-men/</guid>
        <description>The year is 1848. Railways are being deposited left, right and centre; the Industrial Revolution is in full swing; and next year, Darwin will publish his infamous ‘Origin of Species’. It is no surprise, then, that today, in the 21st century, we always look back on this period as a time of incredible …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>WitTank spoons out hilarity at King’s Place
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-25-wittank-spoons-out-hilarity-at-kings-place/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 18:30:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Margot Pikovsky,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-25-wittank-spoons-out-hilarity-at-kings-place/</guid>
        <description>Having first seen comedy group WitTank two years ago at the Edinburgh Fringe on the recommendation of a friend, I’ve been coming back for more at every opportunity. These are the guys who compete against some other 2500 shows for an audience at the Fringe every year and still manage to pack the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Take a gawk on the wild side
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-take-a-gawk-on-the-wild-side/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 22:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Margot Pikovsky,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-take-a-gawk-on-the-wild-side/</guid>
        <description>If labs and essay deadlines have so far prevented you from paying a visit to the Natural History Museum and you’re looking for an excuse to get out of the library: forget the dinosaurs, forget the massive blue whale and forget the Kobe earthquake room, because if there’s one exhibition that you …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
