<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/pnk14/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/pnk14/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Why I’m voting Conservative
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-why-im-voting-conservative/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 14:14:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip N N Kurukgy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-why-im-voting-conservative/</guid>
        <description>Anyone who thinks that this election is not about Brexit, is out of touch with the reality of the task ahead. Brexit will be looked upon as a turning point in this country’s relationship with its neighbours. Some argued that this was the worst political choice this country has ever made. For a long …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A thousand people can&#39;t be wrong
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-a-thousand-people-cant-be-wrong/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 08:46:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip N N Kurukgy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-a-thousand-people-cant-be-wrong/</guid>
        <description>An expected outbreak of support for Felix’s campaign for air conditioning in the library has seriously raised questions about the role of the union in delivering student demands.
Imperial provides great facilities to study in and world class labs, but falls short in the central library.
From …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is Crossrail 2 coming to Kensington?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-is-crossrail-2-coming-to-kensington/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 08:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Philip N N Kurukgy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-is-crossrail-2-coming-to-kensington/</guid>
        <description>Bosses of organisations around West London, including Imperial College Union’s managing director, have signed an open letter to the Evening Standard announcing their support for a Crossrail station on the King’s Road.
The proposed station would be part of the £30 billion infrastructure project by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Shadow chancellor praises Imperial on visit
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-27-shadow-chancellor-praises-imperial-on-visit/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 11:49:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip N N Kurukgy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-27-shadow-chancellor-praises-imperial-on-visit/</guid>
        <description>MP and shadow chancellor, John McDonnell, visited Imperial this week, where he gave a speech acclaiming Imperial’s role in science and innovation. This visit comes only two weeks after George Osborne, the chancellor of the exchequer, visited Imperial’s White City campus, where he said Imperial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The modern way of dealing with crises
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-19-the-modern-way-of-dealing-with-crises/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2015 22:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip N N Kurukgy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-19-the-modern-way-of-dealing-with-crises/</guid>
        <description>In the deadliest attack on French soil since WWII, panic and chaos unfolded in the French capital this week. Many people were left worried that their relatives, family and friends had been amongst those murdered or injured.
In what initially was a welcome move, Facebook launched the ‘I’m safe’ …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial’s halls solution is a travesty
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-imperials-halls-solution-is-a-travesty/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 14:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip N N Kurukgy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-imperials-halls-solution-is-a-travesty/</guid>
        <description>For the past five years, when it comes to handling accommodation issues, Imperial has been following the mantra that two wrongs make a right and fixing problems by creating new ones. Last year prices were hiked in the South Kensington halls by 10% to compensate for the low rents in Woodward, since …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New observatory keeps any eye on big data
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-new-observatory-keeps-any-eye-on-big-data/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 14:21:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip N N Kurukgy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-new-observatory-keeps-any-eye-on-big-data/</guid>
        <description>Last week, the KPMG Data Observatory was launched as part of Imperial’s Data Science Institute. The purpose of the observatory is to enable the analysis and visualisation of data, particularly useful for large corporations that collect massive amounts of it.
This new observatory, which is part of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We talk to the mega fans who camped out on Prince Consort Road for the Bond premiere
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-26-we-talk-to-the-mega-fans-who-camped-out-on-prince-consort-road-for-the-bond-premiere/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2015 13:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip N N Kurukgy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-26-we-talk-to-the-mega-fans-who-camped-out-on-prince-consort-road-for-the-bond-premiere/</guid>
        <description>You might well be skiving lectures this afternoon to catch a glimpse of national treasure Daniel Craig and a handful of royals as they attend tonight’s Spectre premiere. That’s nothing compared to these fans, who have been camping out on Prince Consort Road for three days to secure a place right at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Two Imperial Professors receive awards from the Royal Society of Chemistry
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-21-two-imperial-professors-receive-awards-from-the-royal-society-of-chemistry/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2015 20:15:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip N N Kurukgy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-21-two-imperial-professors-receive-awards-from-the-royal-society-of-chemistry/</guid>
        <description>The Royal Society of Chemistry has recognised two Imperial professors for their world-leading research. Professor Sergei Kazarian from the Department of Chemical Engineering and Professor Elaine Holmes from the Department of Surgery and Cancer have received the awards in the light of new discoveries …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial top University for employment prospects
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-8-imperial-top-university-for-employment-prospects/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 00:13:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip N N Kurukgy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-8-imperial-top-university-for-employment-prospects/</guid>
        <description>In the latest University ranking table study produced by The Complete University Guide, Imperial took the top spot, being declared the best University for postgraduate employment prospects.
The College surpassed St George’s (University of London), the University of Oxford, the University of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Universities dismiss Miliband’s Tuition Fee Policy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-5-universities-dismiss-milibands-tuition-fee-policy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2015 23:43:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philip N N Kurukgy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-5-universities-dismiss-milibands-tuition-fee-policy/</guid>
        <description>Ed Milliband, Labour party leader, has promised to decrease tuition fees to £6,000. However vice-chancellors of the Russell group universities have said this is “implausible” as it would leave a £10 billion hole in University Revenue and could lead to “cuts to universities that would damage the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
