<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/aidan_chan/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/aidan_chan/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Avengers: Endgame</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-avengers-endgame/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aidan Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-avengers-endgame/</guid>
        <description>Once again directed by Joe &amp;amp; Anthony Russo, starring Robert Downey Jr., Chris Evans, Chris Hemsworth, Mark Ruffalo, Scarlett Johansson and Jeremy Renner as the original Avengers, Paul Rudd as Ant-Man and Josh Brolin as Thanos, mega-blockbuster Avengers: Endgame is the direct sequel of Avengers: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Captain Marvel:Review</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-captain-marvel-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aidan Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-captain-marvel-review/</guid>
        <description>Directed by Anna Boden and Ryan Fleck, starring Brie Larson, Samuel L. Jackson and Jude Law, Captain Marvel is the first female-led superhero film produced by Marvel Studios. Politics and social agenda aside, Captain Marvel is an entertaining, though not fully satisfying, chapter of the Marvel …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Memory Loss, Chopping off fingers, and Erotic musical numbers: A Perfect Valentine Trio</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-memory-loss-chopping-off-fingers-and-erotic-musical-numbers-a-perfect-valentine-trio/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aidan Chan,Sung Soo Moon,Mikhail Demtchenko,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-memory-loss-chopping-off-fingers-and-erotic-musical-numbers-a-perfect-valentine-trio/</guid>
        <description>Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind
Tis the season of romance! Whether you’re looking for a film for your next night in with your significant other, or to drown the bitter feeling of rejection, Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind is surely the answer. It’s a film that’s suitable for all couples, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s a Wonderful Felix Film Christmas: The Lowdown of Must Watch Christmas Films this Holiday Season </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-it-s-a-wonderful-felix-film-christmas-the-lowdown-of-must-watch-christmas-films-this-holiday-season/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mikhail Demtchenko,Aidan Chan,Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-it-s-a-wonderful-felix-film-christmas-the-lowdown-of-must-watch-christmas-films-this-holiday-season/</guid>
        <description>The Nightmare Before Christmas
Less of a nightmare, more of a dream for a Christmas movie choice
Sick of the Jingle Bells and the Christmas lights? Tired of fake white beards and elven tights? Well you are in luck my mates, for The Nightmare Before Christmas awaits. From the inexplicable mind of Tim …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fantastic Beasts: The Crimes of Bad Storytelling</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-fantastic-beasts-the-crimes-of-bad-storytelling/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aidan Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-fantastic-beasts-the-crimes-of-bad-storytelling/</guid>
        <description>I walked into the cinema with mild apprehension. I knew that the critical reception was particularly unfavorable, yet I had hoped that this would be a Pirates of the Caribbean: Dead Man’s Chest scenario, where the film would still be immensely fun to watch. After two hours of sitting and hoping for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Man: Review</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-first-man-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aidan Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-first-man-review/</guid>
        <description>Directed by Damien Chazelle and starring Ryan Gosling and Claire Foy (as Neil and Janet Armstrong respectively), First Man is an impressive depiction of the moon landing. Damien Chazelle opted for a very realistic and grounded approach when tackling this groundbreaking event. Using nearly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Go Watch The Wife, If Only for Glenn Close</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-go-watch-the-wife-if-only-for-glenn-close/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aidan Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-go-watch-the-wife-if-only-for-glenn-close/</guid>
        <description>The Wife, directed by Björn Runge and starring Glenn Close and Jonathan Pryce, is a story about Joan Archer, the wife of Nobel Prize in Literature recipient Joseph Castleman (Jonathan Pryce). Glenn Close, as the eponymous “Wife” proves to be the most stunning and transcendent feature of the film.
As …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>American Animals and the Hazards of Adaptation</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-american-animals-and-the-hazards-of-adaptation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aidan Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-american-animals-and-the-hazards-of-adaptation/</guid>
        <description>American Animals, directed by Bart Layton, is about the real-life story of 4 young adults, Spencer (Barry Keoghan), Warren (Evan Peters), Eric (Jared Abrahamson) and Chas (Blake Jenner) who decided to steal several books of extremly high value, including The Birds of America and On the Origin of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Film’s Student Essentials</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-felix-film-s-student-essentials/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sung Soo Moon,Aidan Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-felix-film-s-student-essentials/</guid>
        <description>Y TU MAMA TAMBIEN
DIR: Alfonso Cuaron
SCRIPT: Alfonso Cuaron, Carlos Cuaron
Literally translating to “And Your Mother Too”, Y Tu Mama Tambien is a coming-of-age film set in Mexico about two young men and an older woman searching for an invented beach called “la Boca del Cielo”, or “Heaven’s Mouth”. …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
