<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/cw3414/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/cw3414/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Don’t keep it all bottled up
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-12-dont-keep-it-all-bottled-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2015 12:43:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chanon Wongsatayanont,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-12-dont-keep-it-all-bottled-up/</guid>
        <description>A few weeks ago, the results of a College-wide mental health survey was released on Felix.
At first glance, the numbers looked scary where 75% out of 1115 respondents said that they’d experienced unhealthy amounts of stress and mental health symptoms sometime during their time in Imperial.
It is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Support for the Supporters
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-support-for-the-supporters/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 12:52:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chanon Wongsatayanont,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-support-for-the-supporters/</guid>
        <description>This is the mental health awareness week and I’ll focus on a slightly different but related angle today. In welfare, mental health is a much discussed issue with ever-increasing helpful resources, but there is a group of people often left out from the media spotlight. These are the friends who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to live in an international flat
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-how-to-live-in-an-international-flat/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 19:29:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chanon Wongsatayanont,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-how-to-live-in-an-international-flat/</guid>
        <description>You’ve probably had a flat mate who’s from a different culture. For some of you, it might have gone like this. Day one, things were going well. Day seven, tensions began with unwashed dishes. Day twenty-five, both sides mobilized for war over a party that had turned the corridor into a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Overcoming the Distance
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-overcoming-the-distance/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 13:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chanon Wongsatayanont,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-overcoming-the-distance/</guid>
        <description>The world is getting more globalised and people seem to end up all over the place, smattered here and there like dots of paint. Unfortunately, this also applies to couples, out of necessity or to chase after an opportunity elsewhere. Both sides mean well and they each want the best for each other, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I’m sure you’ll do great!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-11-im-sure-youll-do-great/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 21:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chanon Wongsatayanont,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-11-im-sure-youll-do-great/</guid>
        <description>It’s that time of the term again. Well, for those of us unfortunate enough to have end-of-term exams anyway (e.g. me). As the days are getting shorter, colder and revision hours are ticking away like a time bomb, it’s hard to stay festive even with Christmas so close.
And for those with beginning of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Self-help tips and tricks
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-17-self-help-tips-and-tricks/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 18:21:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chanon Wongsatayanont,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-17-self-help-tips-and-tricks/</guid>
        <description>Now that we’ve gone through some kinds of mental illnesses, it’s time we talk about how to deal with them.
Friends, families and therapists can really help but they can sometimes feel inaccessible, especially during the height of an episode.
You might have told your friends and family before and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>When colours fade away
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-when-colours-fade-away/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 20:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chanon Wongsatayanont,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-when-colours-fade-away/</guid>
        <description>This week, let’s move on from anxiety to the more cheerful topic of depression. To the sufferers, it is the worst feeling in the world. But for those who have never experienced it, it is hard to truly understand how unpleasant or disruptive it is, so this article will try to explain how it feels. …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
