<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/frh10/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/frh10/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Does sitting down on sofas give you cancer?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-does-sitting-down-on-sofas-give-you-cancer/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 14:49:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fiona Hartley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-does-sitting-down-on-sofas-give-you-cancer/</guid>
        <description>People who spend more time sitting are more at risk of getting cancer than people who don’t, a new study reveals.
We already knew that sitting is linked to diabetes and heart disease, but our sedentary lifestyles are now even more dangerous than we thought.
Scientists looked at thousands of cancer …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Epigenetics implicated in type 2 diabetes
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-7-epigenetics-implicated-in-type-2-diabetes/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 12:58:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fiona Hartley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-7-epigenetics-implicated-in-type-2-diabetes/</guid>
        <description>H
ow can the body change how a gene acts without changing the DNA sequence of said gene? Part of the answer lies with epigenetics: alterations to a genome that don’t happen by messing with the nucleotide sequence of DNA but by changing how the gene is expressed.
Common changes include DNA …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mars MAVEN mission launches
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-mars-maven-mission-launches/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 16:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fiona Hartley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-mars-maven-mission-launches/</guid>
        <description>This week the latest US mission to Mars launched successfully; NASA called the launch “flawless”. The rocket carrying the Mars Atmosphere and Volatile EvolutioN (MAVEN) spacecraft left the Earth on Monday from Cape Canaveral Air Force Station in Florida, the site of many previous NASA mission …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The launch of a challenger, RCSU prepares for the next Science Challenge
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-the-launch-of-a-challenger-rcsu-prepares-for-the-next-science-challenge/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 15:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fiona Hartley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-the-launch-of-a-challenger-rcsu-prepares-for-the-next-science-challenge/</guid>
        <description>It’s less than two weeks until the RCSU Science Challenge 2014 launch event, on Tuesday December 3rd. Come along to find out what prizes will be on offer and to hear the judges speak about science communication and reveal their questions for this year’s Challenge. You can book your free place now …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Natural History Museum Skate &amp; Drink Review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-natural-history-museum-skate-drink-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 15:54:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fiona Hartley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-natural-history-museum-skate-drink-review/</guid>
        <description>There’s currently a student skating offer on at the Natural History Museum’s ice rink. All day Mondays and Tuesdays until December 3, students can skate for £8.50 with a free drink at the Café Bar. If you present your student ID when booking tickets at the box office and then save your ticket, you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>RCSU’s Interview with Dr Jad Marrouche
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-rcsus-interview-with-dr-jad-marrouche/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 11:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fiona Hartley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-rcsus-interview-with-dr-jad-marrouche/</guid>
        <description>RCSU’s annual Science Challenge is launching for this year on December 3rd. Previous years have included a tour of CERN as a prize for the overall winner. This tour of CERN was offered by past RCSU President &amp;amp; Science Challenge Chair Dr Jad Marrouche. Dr Marrouche is the man responsible for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>RCSU Science Challenge
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-rcsu-science-challenge/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 09:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fiona Hartley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-rcsu-science-challenge/</guid>
        <description>Meet Professor Lord Robert Winston. Attend a grand final in a prestigious location. Win a slice of a prize pot of over £4000. These chances have one factor in common: this year’s RCSU Science Challenge. It’s big and it’s back, launching on December 3 in SAF. You should come to the launch event and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Apparently money does grow on trees
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-apparently-money-does-grow-on-trees/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 09:45:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fiona Hartley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-apparently-money-does-grow-on-trees/</guid>
        <description>Money doesn’t grow on trees, said every person ever, but it turns out that isn’t entirely accurate. There’s gold in them thar hills, or rather, in them thar trees. Scientists have struck gold – surprisingly in the leaves, twigs and bark of eucalyptus trees in Western Australia.
A group of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jet lag resistance in mice
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-18-jet-lag-resistance-in-mice/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 21:16:47 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fiona Hartley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-18-jet-lag-resistance-in-mice/</guid>
        <description>Jet lag is one of those annoyances that stems from living in the modern era. Anyone who has flown to Asia or come home to the UK after an American holiday recognises its unpleasantness. You just have to wait for your body to adjust to the new time zone. When evolution was working on humans, it had …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hartley Science: Attack of the Hornets
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-11-hartley-science-attack-of-the-hornets/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 23:24:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fiona Hartley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-11-hartley-science-attack-of-the-hornets/</guid>
        <description>Here we are at the end of the first proper week and here’s a new spread of science to educate and hopefully entertain you. Philippa introduced me as a ‘bubbling biologist’ last week, which is an exaggeration, but true to form this week’s news story that has struck me is a biological one.
I strongly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Blood, snot and students
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-blood-snot-and-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 00:30:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fiona Hartley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-blood-snot-and-students/</guid>
        <description>I’m sure several of you are suffering with freshers’ flu by now, as I am, because sharing your germs via sniffling and/or coughing on your unfortunate peers in lectures is akin to physical intimacy here at Imperial. You’d rather be healthy, or at least in bed, as you sip your Lemsip Max and wish …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tired or drunk? You might be feeling quite creative
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-tired-or-drunk-you-might-be-feeling-quite-creative/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 14:05:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fiona Hartley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-tired-or-drunk-you-might-be-feeling-quite-creative/</guid>
        <description> Imagine: it’s 9am and you enter the lecture theatre that will be your home for the next year. Maybe you went out to Ministry or you had a few too many pints in Metric. Perhaps you just stayed up late getting to know new people in halls or from your course. Either way you’re knackered. Maybe you’re …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The epic genetics (or epigenetics) of invasive species
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-the-epic-genetics-or-epigenetics-of-invasive-species/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 00:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fiona Hartley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-the-epic-genetics-or-epigenetics-of-invasive-species/</guid>
        <description>Even at Imperial I doubt you’d find biology students wearing T-shirts referring to Lamarckism, but you especially wouldn’t find them wearing shirts that deride, “Inhindsight, pretty ridiculous”. Jean-Baptiste Lamarck’s evolutionary theories are remembered for suggesting that offspring could inherit …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Looking Beyond Binary
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-looking-beyond-binary/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 01:26:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fiona Hartley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-looking-beyond-binary/</guid>
        <description>Speculative fiction, that hard-to-define genre that encompasses everything from science fiction to alternate histories, is all about the fantastical, the what-ifs. It is all about imagination. It’s a genre that challenges the reality that we live in, dreaming of and exploring new ideas about …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Iskander Malaysia – as green as they say?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-iskander-malaysia-as-green-as-they-say/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 23:20:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fiona Hartley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-iskander-malaysia-as-green-as-they-say/</guid>
        <description>You don’t have to be an urban planner or an environmentalist to recognise that continued urbanisation alongside green living is the future of the planet. I’m certainly not. So we might as well do it right by considering the environmental implications of new urban development projects, and any scheme …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>From stem cells to sex cells
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-from-stem-cells-to-sex-cells/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 20:51:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fiona Hartley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-from-stem-cells-to-sex-cells/</guid>
        <description>Japanese researchers have created viable eggs in mice from skin stem cells which produced healthy fertile offspring that successfully had their own progeny. This breakthrough could hopefully lead to treatments for human infertility in the distant future.
Stem cells give rise to all specialised cells …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brainy gene
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-brainy-gene/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 11:18:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fiona Hartley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-brainy-gene/</guid>
        <description>A recent study published in the journal Cell has identified a major genetic component of human brain development, with implications for research into autism and schizophrenia. Scientists at The Scripps Research Institute have found that the gene SRGAP2, the protein product of which is responsible …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Honey bees seek thrills just like us
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-honey-bees-seek-thrills-just-like-us/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 19:53:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fiona Hartley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-honey-bees-seek-thrills-just-like-us/</guid>
        <description>Honey bee scouts are at the forefront of bee exploration, seeking out new sources of food for the hungry hive and finding suitable nest sites for the colony when it outgrows its current home. These bees differ from their fellow foragers. They do not wait to be told where to go or what to do, but …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
