<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Multi Author on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/tags/multi-author/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Multi Author on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/tags/multi-author/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>National Student Survey results reveal wide ranges in student satisfaction
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-25-national-student-survey-results-reveal-wide-ranges-in-student-satisfaction/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 10:26:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-25-national-student-survey-results-reveal-wide-ranges-in-student-satisfaction/</guid>
        <description> The results from the National Student Survey (NSS), which saw a number of universities omitted following a boycott, show a divide among Imperial students, with a wide range in satisfaction rates between undergraduate courses.
The survey, which is given to all final-year undergraduates, showed that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Fellwanderers Easter Tour
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-imperial-fellwanderers-easter-tour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:59:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Emma McCracken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-imperial-fellwanderers-easter-tour/</guid>
        <description>Following an early flight at 7am from Gatwick to Aberdeen, we arrived in the scenic village Braemar in the Cairngorms national park at around 1pm. Kate, the provider of Rucksacks accommodation, greeted us as we sleepily got off the bus. Luckily Braemar was the end of the line, as otherwise we …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Writing mental illness off as a personality quirk is dangerous</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-writing-mental-illness-off-as-a-personality-quirk-is-dangerous/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:44:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-writing-mental-illness-off-as-a-personality-quirk-is-dangerous/</guid>
        <description>Two weeks ago, I read an article in felix posing the question: “Are we medicalising personality?” The author argues that self-diagnosis of a mental health problem can be risky. I agree. They argue that convincing yourself you have a mental illness when you don’t, can make you miserable. I agree. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The failings of the Conservatives
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-failings-of-the-conservatives/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:42:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-failings-of-the-conservatives/</guid>
        <description>Theresa May went for a power grab. She wanted to wipe out Labour while her party was polling with almost 20 points ahead of them. With a fragmented opposition and Corbyn’s poor approval ratings, everyone assumed it was going to be a landslide election. So how did this all backfire and end up in a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to dump someone (you met in Metric and subsequently fell in love with)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-how-to-dump-someone-you-met-in-metric-and-subsequently-fell-in-love-with/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 16:16:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Theresa Davey,Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-how-to-dump-someone-you-met-in-metric-and-subsequently-fell-in-love-with/</guid>
        <description> You were weak. Despite our foolproof guides on how to have a one night stand (in Metric), ‘How to have a one night stand (in Metric)’, and how not to fall in love with someone (from Metric), ‘How not to fall in love with someone (from Metric)’, you went ahead and fell in love with someone (from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Keeping Track of Imperial’s Cross Country &amp; Athletics Club
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-keeping-track-of-imperials-cross-country-athletics-club/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:42:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-keeping-track-of-imperials-cross-country-athletics-club/</guid>
        <description>Saturday the 27th of May saw the final event in the London Universities and Colleges Athletics (LUCA) outdoors championship take place. The series of three athletics meets between the London universities had previously visited St. Mary’s and Woodford athletics tracks, and the destination for the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Diesel pollution poses serious risk for asthma sufferers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-diesel-pollution-poses-serious-risk-for-asthma-sufferers/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:00:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Rachel Baxter,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-diesel-pollution-poses-serious-risk-for-asthma-sufferers/</guid>
        <description>Forty million British people are living in cities and towns with illegally high air pollution levels. This alarming statistic is in part due to diesel exhaust, which according to new research can directly affect our lungs and make respiratory conditions worse.
An international team of scientists led …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The election and the NHS
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-the-election-and-the-nhs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 14:25:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Dan Faehndrich,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-the-election-and-the-nhs/</guid>
        <description>Since the surprise of 7th May 2015, the NHS has fallen into its darkest times since its inception. As a medical student, seeing my colleagues here and across the whole medical profession has, frankly, made becoming a doctor look the least appealing it’s looked since 14 year-old me decided it was the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why I’m voting Labour
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-why-im-voting-labour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 14:16:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-why-im-voting-labour/</guid>
        <description>Soft on security, denying the deficit, and incapable of addressing concerns over immigration. These sound like the sort of accusations the Conservatives levelled at the last Labour government not too long ago, and yet after seven years in government, these are all areas in which the Conservative …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Manifesto breakdowns
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-manifesto-breakdowns/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:59:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,Cale E Tilford,Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-manifesto-breakdowns/</guid>
        <description> This piece aims to break down the main party manifestos and summarise a few key policies. This is by no means a full and in-depth analysis of each party. Mainly because the manifestos are long and complex, and it’s exam season. [Insert tinfoil hat theory that the timing of the election coincides …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Party candidates come to Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-party-candidates-come-to-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:50:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-party-candidates-come-to-imperial/</guid>
        <description>A hustings of local parliamentary candidates was held yesterday in Blackett which saw Victoria Borwick (Conservatives), Cllr Alan De’Ath (Labour), Bridget Fox (LibDems), Richard Braine (UKIP), and finally Bill Cashmore (Green), engaging in a debate on Education, Public Health and Brexit.
Borwick, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Afterhours sessions in the Central Library
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-afterhours-sessions-in-the-central-library/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:29:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-afterhours-sessions-in-the-central-library/</guid>
        <description>How does one end up in the Library past midnight? Maybe you had a paper to submit tomorrow. You thought you had everything under control. You were halfway there but you made the mistake of taking a break and committing to an episode of the Great British Bake Off. Six hours later you get a text from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fuelling the resistance
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-19-fuelling-the-resistance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 15:03:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Naomi Pratt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-19-fuelling-the-resistance/</guid>
        <description>The greatest obstacle to action on climate change is the one most often missing from discourse: the fossil fuel industry. Since comprehension of anthropogenic global warming began, the fossil fuel industry has been ignored in negotiations and subsidised by governments. Much time and energy has been …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Xavier Dolan | In praise of popular art
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-xavier-dolan-in-praise-of-popular-art/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 17:21:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Leo Diaz,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-xavier-dolan-in-praise-of-popular-art/</guid>
        <description>Xavier Dolan is not your average director. What first sets him apart is that he is extremely young: 28 at the time of writing, he’s already released six full-length features. He directed his first, I Killed My Mother, when he was just 20, and his 2014 Mommy received the Jury Prize at Cannes, along …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College&#39;s white vision for White City
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-imperial-colleges-white-vision-for-white-city/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 16:02:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Chaundri,Kieran Ryan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-imperial-colleges-white-vision-for-white-city/</guid>
        <description>At the end of last term I attended a Union Council meeting. Before the meeting could commence there was an extensive powerpoint presentation about the college’s development in White City, Imperial West, given by Professor Neil Alford (Imperial White City Syndicate).
As someone who has lived in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The case for divestment at Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-the-case-for-divestment-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 16:00:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Sarah Barfield Marks,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-the-case-for-divestment-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Here at Imperial, any mention of divestment from fossil fuels is largely met with one of two responses. The first is a supportive but disheartened reply along the lines of, “yeah, it’s a nice idea but it will never happen”. The second offers a complete aversion to the subject entirely, by changing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Divestment has worked before, and will work again
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-divestment-has-worked-before-and-will-work-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 15:57:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Conor O&#39;Riordan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-divestment-has-worked-before-and-will-work-again/</guid>
        <description>As the threat of climate change continues to loom large over society, activists are turning to more creative methods to encourage the large-scale change that we urgently need. Where traditional political methods have failed, divestment is now making serious progress on university campuses, in city …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is so bad about fossil fuel companies, anyway?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-what-is-so-bad-about-fossil-fuel-companies-anyway/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 15:55:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhidian Thomas,Max Moynan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-what-is-so-bad-about-fossil-fuel-companies-anyway/</guid>
        <description>Divest Imperial are calling on College to remove its investments from fossil fuel companies, but what exactly is so bad about fossil fuel companies, anyway? Most attention is given to their impact on the climate through their carbon emissions, but fossil fuel companies often make headlines (or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>SPA awards shortlist announced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-spa-awards-shortlist-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 16:28:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-spa-awards-shortlist-announced/</guid>
        <description>UPDATE: We didn&amp;rsquo;t win anything, there is no god, and everything sucks
April saw felix getting shortlisted for four Student Publication Association Awards last month, with Editor Lef Apostolakis and Comment Editor/Millennials Queen/felix Vice Chair/Office Legend Tessa Davey each garnering two …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Could 2017 be the year of indie?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-could-2017-be-the-year-of-indie/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 17:06:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Joseph O&#39; Connell-Dannes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-could-2017-be-the-year-of-indie/</guid>
        <description>Last year, was almost unquestionably the year of hip-hop; the genre saw a huge influx of new artists and the drop of some absolutely massive albums from established names (From Chance the Rapper’s Colouring Book and A Tribe Called Quest’s We Got It From Here… Thank You 4 Your Service to Kendrick …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>There&#39;s no place at Imperial for elitist &#39;secret&#39; clubs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-theres-no-place-at-imperial-for-elitist-secret-clubs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 17:01:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Andrew D Olson Gallardo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-theres-no-place-at-imperial-for-elitist-secret-clubs/</guid>
        <description>Everyone studying at Imperial is aware that this place is not perfect. Yes, there are problems with student engagement, mental health, even sexism. But despite these issues, I feel it is the place which has mainly contributed at making me who I am today; the fantastic wardening team in my halls in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial to get HEFCE Funding
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-imperial-to-get-hefce-funding/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 13:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Abigail E de Bruin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-imperial-to-get-hefce-funding/</guid>
        <description>Imperial has been selected as one of 64 institutions to receive up to £50,000 of HEFCE Catalyst funding from the Student Safeguarding fund. This is part of the £2.45 million released by HEFCE for projects addressing sexual harassment on campus following the report from Universities UK’s Harassment …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The felix sex survey 2017 #callmedaddy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-16-the-felix-sex-survey-2017-callmedaddy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2017 19:22:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,Felix Editor,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-16-the-felix-sex-survey-2017-callmedaddy/</guid>
        <description>The 2017 felix sex survey is now LIVE! Fill it out here
</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>KenDO or KenDONT ? You be the judge
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-kendo-or-kendont-you-be-the-judge/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 14:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Gabriel Ng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-kendo-or-kendont-you-be-the-judge/</guid>
        <description>Last weekend on the 4th and 5th of March, the annual UK Kendo University Championships took place in Cambridge, where Imperial College took home several awards, including winning the kyu grade team competition.
Kendo is a Japanese martial art, similar to European fencing, where the objective in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The 2017 IC Cinema Spring All-Nighter
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-the-2017-ic-cinema-spring-all-nighter/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 14:37:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Sophie Sagawe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-the-2017-ic-cinema-spring-all-nighter/</guid>
        <description>This year’s Spring All-Nighter will take place on Tuesday the 21st of March at 6pm, ending at approximately 7.45am the next day. For those who are inexplicably out of the loop with this beloved Imperial College tradition: it’s a whole night of films, shown back to back, on a screen 8 meters wide, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let’s talk about Drugs #realtalk
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-lets-talk-about-drugs-realtalk/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 14:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,David Charchoglyan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-lets-talk-about-drugs-realtalk/</guid>
        <description>Do you know why some drugs are called ‘Drugs’ with a capital D? Or why your school was so eager to drill into you that some things are bad no-questions-asked-because-I-said-so during those insufferable PSHE lessons? Why some substances are kept completely out of our reach and have a seven year …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ugly Lies the Bone | VR therapy and emotional trauma
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-ugly-lies-the-bone-vr-therapy-and-emotional-trauma/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 13:43:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-ugly-lies-the-bone-vr-therapy-and-emotional-trauma/</guid>
        <description>Ugly Lies the Bone follows the story of Jess, a young woman returning home following 3 tours in Afghanistan, which have left her with severe burns after an IED. Struggling to fit back into her old life in her declining Florida home town, and struggling to cope with her disability and chronic pain, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LFF: Certain Women | Postcards from the edge of solitude
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-lff-certain-women-postcards-from-the-edge-of-solitude/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 13:37:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Meryl Chittethazhathu Anil,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-lff-certain-women-postcards-from-the-edge-of-solitude/</guid>
        <description>Certain Women, American director Kelly Reichardt’s sixth film, begins with a shot that serves as a statement of intent: a rusting old train slowly drags itself across the Montana landscape, framed by snowy mountain peaks; stoic in its solitude, it chuffs and puffs along the track, determined to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC American Football | Divison champs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-ic-american-football-divison-champs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 16:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Gatis Ogle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-ic-american-football-divison-champs/</guid>
        <description>After a season-long fight, it all boiled down to the last Sunday of the regular season. To be or not to be, it’s now or never: all three play-off qualifiers (Imperial Immortals, Cambridge Pythons and Kent Falcons) could come out top of the division if the day went their way.
While our play-off …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Trump&#39;s cabinet is cleverer than you think
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-trumps-cabinet-is-cleverer-than-you-think/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 14:41:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Alexander Luisi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-trumps-cabinet-is-cleverer-than-you-think/</guid>
        <description>The language of the Trump administration fascinates me. The daily barrage of comments, tweets and press conferences reveals something quite fundamental about the way that the government is operating, and how it will operate. It’s hard to believe that the administration is not in utter chaos, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Confused Nursery exhibition
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-the-confused-nursery-exhibition/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 15:34:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Tom Mutimer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-the-confused-nursery-exhibition/</guid>
        <description>Friday of last week, I had the pleasure of attending the Blyth gallery for the opening of a joint exhibition between Leonardo Fine Arts and PhotoSoc, titled ‘Confused Nursery’.
The space is a time machine that will take you back to days you hardly remember and juvenile feelings that you forgot …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ten of the best</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-ten-of-the-best/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 15:23:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-ten-of-the-best/</guid>
        <description> 1 | Dirty Bones Shoreditch Fried chicken on waffles for brunch? Definitely. Hit up Dirty Bones for their boozy brunch menu with mac ‘n’ cheese burgers, short rib crumpets and more heart attack-worthy dishes!
   Christy Lam   2 | Café Loren Looking for a homey, warming breakfast? Café Loren in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My eating disorder
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-my-eating-disorder/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 13:48:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Conchi Hermida Sánchez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-my-eating-disorder/</guid>
        <description>As part of Eating Disorders Awareness Week, I would like to share my personal experience and hopefully help someone out there.
“You are going to get fat.” ”Don’t let yourself go as I did.” “Remember: a moment on the lips is a lifetime on the hips”. These are all expressions I have been hearing at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial rugby down RUM(s)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-imperial-rugby-down-rums/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 16:22:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,David Nielson-Scot,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-imperial-rugby-down-rums/</guid>
        <description>Still buzzing after their triumph last week, Imperial were roaring to get at a UCL Medical School (RUMS) side which had evaded defeat in the past five meetings, including a 49-10 drubbing earlier this season. With RUMS 2nd top and IC 2nd from bottom in our league, the scene was set for a tough …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Love is the drug you can’t get enough of
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-love-is-the-drug-you-cant-get-enough-of/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-love-is-the-drug-you-cant-get-enough-of/</guid>
        <description> Let’s be real. Love is a drug. It inhibits our ability to think clearly, turns us into terrible people, and makes us do stupid things. Face it, it’s far more harmful than a few hours gurning at the weekend. But just like with drugs, there are different kinds of highs, and so now, in honour of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hit me up, homeslice
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-hit-me-up-homeslice/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Alice Davage,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-hit-me-up-homeslice/</guid>
        <description>The hipster revolution is upon us. No food is safe. The humble burger has been embellished with a bright green avocado bun. If you haven’t tried kale or quinoa (pronounced “keen-wah”, trust me, I have been corrected multiple times), frankly, where have you been? Although the occasional twists on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are we killing the planet in style | Sustainable Fashion
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-are-we-killing-the-planet-in-style-sustainable-fashion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:47:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Eloise Hunt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-are-we-killing-the-planet-in-style-sustainable-fashion/</guid>
        <description>At the thought of pollution, we imagine raw sewage pumped into rivers, open-caste mines and oil spills. We don’t often think of our fluffy unicorn slippers or plaid shirts. But the overall impact the fashion industry has on our planet is shocking. The production of clothing has been estimated to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Romeo and Juliet | Updated and abridged
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-romeo-and-juliet-updated-and-abridged/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Helen Money-Kyrle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-romeo-and-juliet-updated-and-abridged/</guid>
        <description>Regardless of whether you&amp;rsquo;re madly in love, or frankly you&amp;rsquo;ve had enough of it this week, there&amp;rsquo;s still something inherently appealing about the tragic tale of Romeo and Juliet.
Squeezed into a running time of just one hour, the National Theatre’s interpretation sets a shortened …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Helping out a bee in need
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-helping-out-a-bee-in-need/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Olivia Barber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-helping-out-a-bee-in-need/</guid>
        <description>Over the past few years, discussion of the rapid decline of bee populations has intensified. Every week there seems to be another alarming headline implying that honeybee population decline is something we should care about. Do bees truly impact the world as we know it? Wouldn’t we do just fine …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The challenges facing early career sustainable scientists
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-the-challenges-facing-early-career-sustainable-scientists/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Alexandra Hicken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-the-challenges-facing-early-career-sustainable-scientists/</guid>
        <description>As a director on the executive board of the Network of Sustainable Scientists and Engineers (NESSE) and a PhD student in the Chemistry Department funded via the Grantham Institute, it may appear as though my future career path in sustainable science is all but decided. This, however, is far from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Being Black and Muslim in the UK
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-being-black-and-muslim-in-the-uk/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 14:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Omer G Mohamed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-being-black-and-muslim-in-the-uk/</guid>
        <description>The US is what most of us think of when we think of Black Civil Rights, which is where the movement was the most prominent, but seldom do we realise or remember what people in our own communities go through. The recent race row at Oxford University, in which students received an email from staff …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Query your consumerism
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-query-your-consumerism/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 14:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Valerie Wischott,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-query-your-consumerism/</guid>
        <description>I buy these flip-flops from H&amp;amp;M for every summer – after one year, they’re broken. But it doesn’t matter, they’re only €7.” “I already booked my journey back home for Christmas holidays – got a flight for €10!” All of you have probably said something along these lines at some point. These quotes …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You have no excuse for not recycling
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-you-have-no-excuse-for-not-recycling/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 14:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Giulia Costa,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-you-have-no-excuse-for-not-recycling/</guid>
        <description>Have you ever spent a long time staring at the coloured bins wondering where your everything should go? Wondering if someone is judging your bin choice? Well good, because recycling is important.
The global population is rapidly increasing and our lifestyles generate huge amounts of waste. In the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Climate change is a political problem
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-climate-change-is-a-political-problem/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 14:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Rhidian Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-climate-change-is-a-political-problem/</guid>
        <description>As political descriptors go, the humble watermelon is perhaps predictably an unconventional one: it is not wheeled out too often as a way of making a point. It’s a charge often levelled at politicians like Caroline Lucas, who are accused of being green on the outside but red (that is, socialist) on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Talk dirty to me | Banana Tree
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-talk-dirty-to-me-banana-tree/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 16:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Shanzeh Khurshid,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-talk-dirty-to-me-banana-tree/</guid>
        <description> Where to go On their way to the Royal Albert Hall, my friends and I caught up in Banana Tree in Bayswater. I suggested the restaurant because it’s about 30 minutes walking distance from campus, and only 20 minutes from Wilson House and Pembridge. Ever since she went on a yoga trip to Vietnam, one …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s a queer gal to do/see/watch/listen to? Our guide to your gal-pal culture fix
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-whats-a-queer-gal-to-doseewatchlisten-to-our-guide-to-your-gal-pal-culture-fix/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 15:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-whats-a-queer-gal-to-doseewatchlisten-to-our-guide-to-your-gal-pal-culture-fix/</guid>
        <description> Film Appropriate Behaviour
Desiree Akhavan directs and stars in this comedy about an American-Iranian bisexual going through a breakup. It’ll make you feel worse about your recent breakup but then, strangely, better. It’s pretty funny and feels quite real. The protagonist also struggles with coming …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fuck Valentine’s Day | Asexual and aromantic
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-fuck-valentines-day-asexual-and-aromantic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 14:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-fuck-valentines-day-asexual-and-aromantic/</guid>
        <description>The first two weeks in February are an infernal nightmare of constant bombardment with advertisements for jewellery, chocolates, and lingerie – all for that ‘special someone’. People in relationships presumably don’t mind. Single people complain incessantly about it. For aromantics however, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science won’t be Trumped
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-science-wont-be-trumped/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 14:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Agnes Donnelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-science-wont-be-trumped/</guid>
        <description>The past three weeks have meant that the previously enjoyable activity of looking at Facebook has instead become a daily battle of emotions as I brace myself to learn of another Trump shocker. A travel ban on 7 countries, banning organizations from speaking to the public and a petty fight over who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Romanian protests are an unlikely beacon of democracy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-the-romanian-protests-are-an-unlikely-beacon-of-democracy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 13:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Claudia Mihai,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-the-romanian-protests-are-an-unlikely-beacon-of-democracy/</guid>
        <description>A brief glance at the main headlines and you can see that the past month has been filled with protests, discontent, and outrage. While the world is watching the United States, Eastern Europe is facing its own demons as formerly communist country Romania is seeing its largest protest since the fall …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The LGBT community is a dichotomy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-the-lgbt-community-is-a-dichotomy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 13:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Elizabeth Windo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-the-lgbt-community-is-a-dichotomy/</guid>
        <description> I found a home in the LGBT community The LGBT community is the first place that I found people like me. For so many years of my life, I lived in a state of confusion. To finally discover people that shared the same interests and passions was incredible. I’ve been able to make the lifelong friends …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You&#39;re misrepresenting the facts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-youre-misrepresenting-the-facts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 13:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Saul Coleman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-youre-misrepresenting-the-facts/</guid>
        <description>Opening last week’s issue of felix, I was greeted on page three by an article entitled “Israeli ambassador’s secret visit to Imperial”. And I’m pleased to say that, on the whole, the article was a very balanced read, just as the event was very civil. The sensitive nature of the discussion had …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial students launch campaign to make medical curriculum LGBT-inclusive
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-imperial-students-launch-campaign-to-make-medical-curriculum-lgbt-inclusive/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 13:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Michael Wilkinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-imperial-students-launch-campaign-to-make-medical-curriculum-lgbt-inclusive/</guid>
        <description>The founding principles of the NHS were that it should meet the needs of everyone, be free at the point of delivery, and be based on clinical need, not ability to pay. Those of us watching BBC’s Hospital last week, were reminded of the importance of these values, as we witnessed overseas patients …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I heard you like... food?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-i-heard-you-like-food/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 18:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,B. C. Maile,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-i-heard-you-like-food/</guid>
        <description> Have you ever found yourself aroused by the thought of having a cream pie pushed into your face or cracking eggs over someone’s chest? Of course you have. Well, you’re not alone. This fringe phenomenon is called ‘Wet and Messy Fetishism’, often abbreviated to WAM or simply called sploshing. Fans of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All hail the sublime starch, the chieftan of cuisine, the triumphant tuber | the potato
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-all-hail-the-sublime-starch-the-chieftan-of-cuisine-the-triumphant-tuber-the-potato/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 17:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanjay Bhattacharya,Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-all-hail-the-sublime-starch-the-chieftan-of-cuisine-the-triumphant-tuber-the-potato/</guid>
        <description> The humble spud. Where to start? How many foodstuffs can compare to the tuber that brought a whole nation to its knees – and I’m not talking about the Irish potato famine, but rather the introduction of potatoes to haute cuisine. People had been searching for a starch that was affordable yet …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bake sale
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-bake-sale/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 17:07:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Harry Wilkinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-bake-sale/</guid>
        <description>Among other smaller, less internationally important incidents, it seems to me that 2016 will be remembered primarily as the year that the BBC lost the Great British Bake Off to Channel 4. In what is ostensibly just a show about people making cakes, you find a lot of what British culture is all …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Percolate | Mind Fundraiser
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-percolate-mind-fundraiser/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 17:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Philipp Antonas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-percolate-mind-fundraiser/</guid>
        <description>Any excuse to visit one of my favourite venues in London is welcomed by me, so much more the better when that excuse is me donating to an amazing charity and getting a great, music-heavy evening in return.
The Oval Space is small and intimate, overlooking an industrial side of the city which adds to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ghost in the Shell
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-ghost-in-the-shell/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 16:52:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Peter Shatwell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-ghost-in-the-shell/</guid>
        <description>If you wish to dive into the world of Japanese animation, you cannot miss Mamoru Oshii’s profound 1995 cyberpunk film Ghost in the Shell. It stands as a science-fiction classic and has gone on to inspire other films such as The Matrix, Surrogates, and Avatar. But why am I talking now about a film …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Denial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-denial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 16:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Theo Farah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-denial/</guid>
        <description>In a political climate increasingly described with the neologism ‘post-factual’, director Mick Jackson’s latest film Denial is sharply relevant. Centering around the libel case of British Holocaust-denier David Irving against American historian Deborah Lipstadt – a case that was often referred to as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I turned vegan four months ago – am I allowed to preach yet?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-i-turned-vegan-four-months-ago-am-i-allowed-to-preach-yet/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 15:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Alex Chaundri,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-i-turned-vegan-four-months-ago-am-i-allowed-to-preach-yet/</guid>
        <description>A year ago, after mostly avoiding meat for several months, I decided to make the commitment to being fully vegetarian. My decision for this was mostly driven by a concern for the planet. The Food and Agriculture Organisation of the UN estimates that 14.5% of global greenhouse gas emissions come from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Leave Trident alone
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-leave-trident-alone/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 15:54:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-leave-trident-alone/</guid>
        <description>Trident was announced as the UK’s new deterrent back in 1980, and patrols with the missile began in 1994. The renewal of trident was debated in July 2016, to replace the current submarines with the newer Dreadnought Class by 2028. The estimated cost of the upgraded weapons system is around £31 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Zero tolerance policy gets scrapped
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-zero-tolerance-policy-gets-scrapped/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 15:04:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Matt Rego,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-zero-tolerance-policy-gets-scrapped/</guid>
        <description>Last Tuesday, during Union Council, Student Deputy President of Education, Luke McCrone announced a repeal to the university’s zero-tolerance late submission policy.
According to McCrone’s report given at the meeting, the zero tolerance policy will be replaced by a new policy, allowing grades capped …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Terrains of the Body is a bold but beguiling show
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-terrains-of-the-body-is-a-bold-but-beguiling-show/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 17:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-terrains-of-the-body-is-a-bold-but-beguiling-show/</guid>
        <description>Hellen van Meene’s works combine this unsteady storyline with a heady mix of sensual textures and colours. Her works are celebrations of surface, with Vermeer-light like dappling across her subjects, bringing an incredible sense of tactility. Janaina Tschape’s work shares this obsession with tone, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hallelujah Money
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-hallelujah-money/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 16:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Sam Wood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-hallelujah-money/</guid>
        <description>Gorillaz are back – and this time they are as political as they are whacky. Having teased a new album through Instagram and SoundCloud releases over the past few months, Gorillaz released the brand new track Hallelujah Money (ft. Benjamin Clementine) on the eve of Trump’s inauguration. The Damon …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Protesting Trump | The Women’s March through the eyes of Imperial students
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-protesting-trump-the-womens-march-through-the-eyes-of-imperial-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 14:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-protesting-trump-the-womens-march-through-the-eyes-of-imperial-students/</guid>
        <description>    Indira Mallik   Ana Villanueva | felix reader I asked myself a question the first time I heard about the Women’s March: Is it necessary? The answer is yes. I joined tens of thousands of people because I needed to share a message too. It was not a complaint. We advocated tolerance and respect for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How not to fall in love with someone (from Metric)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-how-not-to-fall-in-love-with-someone-from-metric/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Theresa Davey,Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-how-not-to-fall-in-love-with-someone-from-metric/</guid>
        <description> This is a follow up to our piece ‘How to have a one night stand (in Metric)’. For those of you who somehow missed it, we provided a tried-and-tested plan of action designed to get you laid after a night in Metric. This plan was meant to get you in and out without leaving any trace. But expectedly, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cunts in conversation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-cunts-in-conversation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lucille Calmon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-cunts-in-conversation/</guid>
        <description>I bet you&amp;rsquo;re worried. I was worried. I was worried about vaginas. I was worried about what we think about vaginas, and even more worried that we don&amp;rsquo;t think about them” wrote Eve Ensler in the introduction of The Vagina Monologues, a compilation of over 200 women’s feelings about their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Taking a leaf out of Tove Jansson&#39;s book
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-taking-a-leaf-out-of-tove-janssons-book/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:28:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Jenny Shelley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-taking-a-leaf-out-of-tove-janssons-book/</guid>
        <description>For many, the Moomins hold nothing more than the nostalgia of childhood. While some have no idea what they are, for others the word conjures up a vague image of a hippo-esque creature that adorns cutesy bottles and notepads. There is no particular reason to go any deeper than these associations, but …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bro do you even lift?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-bro-do-you-even-lift/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:08:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Aran Shaunak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-bro-do-you-even-lift/</guid>
        <description>Fact: The strongest living thing on the planet is gonorrhea.
Neisseria gonorrhoeae (the bacterium that causes gonorrhea) is a force to be reckoned with, given it can pull with a force over 100,000 times its own body weight. For a human to compete, you’d have to shift over ten million kilos, which …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is it stupid to take smart drugs?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-is-it-stupid-to-take-smart-drugs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Anjeline Joegi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-is-it-stupid-to-take-smart-drugs/</guid>
        <description> It’s the night before the final exam, but you haven’t studied. If you had a small white pill which promised greater focus and productivity would you take it? The Tab website conducted a survey of 2000 UK university students and discovered that 1 in 5 have taken the drug ‘Modafinil’. Many students …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Head of Sport Imperial resigns
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-head-of-sport-imperial-resigns/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 14:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-head-of-sport-imperial-resigns/</guid>
        <description>Grant Danskine, Head of Sport Imperial, has resigned amidst resurfaced criticism of the organisation’s treatment of female athletes. Although the criticism – which resurfaced after Imperial published its institutional culture report – is unrelated to Danskine’s direction of Sport Imperial, it did …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Central Library to get air con
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-central-library-to-get-air-con/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 14:54:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-central-library-to-get-air-con/</guid>
        <description>Happy days. Imperial College will finally be taking steps to solve issues with temperature regulation at the Central Library. Probably.
According to a teasing announcement from Library Services just before Christmas, “early indications are that a project to improve the temperature at Central Library …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial to face LSE at City Varsity
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-imperial-to-face-lse-at-city-varsity/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 14:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-imperial-to-face-lse-at-city-varsity/</guid>
        <description>Imperial will be taking on LSE this year during a showcase event to take place in March. The event, christened the City Varsity, will mark the first time in a long time that Imperial plays against another University. (Though earlier last year the first e-sports varsity was launched at Gfinity Arena …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The university meme page revolution
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-the-university-meme-page-revolution/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 15:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,Paul Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-the-university-meme-page-revolution/</guid>
        <description>T his strange world of memes which we currently find ourselves in – one where a president can be catapulted to the White House with the help of online fascists and Pepe the Frog – is terrifying. There was an undercurrent of darkness in the memes that defined 2016: we celebrated Harambe’s death as if …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Silence
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-silence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Theo Farah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-silence/</guid>
        <description>Following on from the messy hedonism of The Wolf of Wall Street – a three hour orgy of casual violence, over-sexualisation, and easy profanity – it is clear that Martin Scorsese is searching for a kind of ‘mea culpa’ with Silence, a mix of asceticism, endurance, and proselytism. It’s a hard pill to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Monster Calls
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-a-monster-calls/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Fred S Fyles,Meryl Chittethazhathu Anil,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-a-monster-calls/</guid>
        <description>Storytellers are a threat,” wrote Chinua Achebe, “they threaten all champions of control, usurpers of the right-to-freedom of the human spirit”. It is this power, that of a simple story well-told, that director J. A. Bayona is trying to tap with his latest feature A Monster Calls, an adaptation of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Southern Rail need to get their shit together
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-southern-rail-need-to-get-their-shit-together/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-southern-rail-need-to-get-their-shit-together/</guid>
        <description>There were train strikes this week, you might have heard. No, not the tube strikes, they happen like once a year; you can take a bus for a day, get over yourself, no one cares. I’m talking about Southern Rail, whose staff are on strike for three days this week, causing a genuine total shutdown of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rhodes must stay
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-rhodes-must-stay/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 13:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-rhodes-must-stay/</guid>
        <description>In recent months, the ‘Rhodes Must Fall’ campaign has gained significant traction not only at Oriel college, Oxford but at several institutions in the UK and abroad. The campaign has attempted to have the statue of Cecil Rhodes removed due to his strong support for the apartheid movement in South …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Prayer room refurbishment completed
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-prayer-room-refurbishment-completed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 13:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-prayer-room-refurbishment-completed/</guid>
        <description>The Brother’s Prayer Room was successfully refurbished over the winter break. Earlier last year, felix revealed many maintenance issues that had plagued the IC Islamic Society managed prayer room for six years. The issues included a dirty carpet emitting a strong smell, damp on the walls, peeling …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Firefighters swarm the Science Museum
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-firefighters-swarm-the-science-museum/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 13:52:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-firefighters-swarm-the-science-museum/</guid>
        <description>Just before noon last Wedensday, hundreds of visitors were evacuated from the Science Museum. As the visitors collected outside the museum on Exhibition Road, three firefighter squads arrived and created a perimeter around the historical building, amounting to a total of seven fire engines with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>National Student Survey open for 2017
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-national-student-survey-open-for-2017/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 13:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-national-student-survey-open-for-2017/</guid>
        <description>It’s that time of year again when final year students across the country are invited to fill in the National Student Survey (NSS), also known as Imperial’s bane of existence. Last year’s remarkably low student satisfaction scores saw Imperial dropping in ranking from number ten to 21 out of 24 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jiu Jitsu advances to the next level in style
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-jiu-jitsu-advances-to-the-next-level-in-style/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 16:26:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Cloe Fradin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-jiu-jitsu-advances-to-the-next-level-in-style/</guid>
        <description>Last Saturday saw London host the Jiu Jitsu grading. If competitions are scary, then gradings are a halloween movie marathon with the lights off and the creepy neighbour wearing his Freddy Krueger outfit staring through the window.
A grading is the opportunity for any member of a Jitsu club (from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICSM Netball get crafty
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-icsm-netball-get-crafty/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 16:23:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Ifrah Hussain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-icsm-netball-get-crafty/</guid>
        <description>The start of the summer saw planning and preparations for the upcoming academic year get underway at ICSM Netball. With an ever-expanding club, we decided to shift some focus to the development of the club off-court whilst maintaining team progression on-court. One particular area of focus was club …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A seat at the (culture) roundtable
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-a-seat-at-the-culture-roundtable/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 15:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-a-seat-at-the-culture-roundtable/</guid>
        <description>During the American election cycle on his comedy show Last Week Tonight, John Oliver had a running gag – “look up,” he’d say “that faint glimmer in the distance? That’s rock bottom.” So it has seemed for most of 2016; in almost every sphere, particularly in politics, bad news has been followed by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Crowning Glory | The Crown
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-crowning-glory-the-crown/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 15:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-crowning-glory-the-crown/</guid>
        <description>The Crown isn’t just one of the most anticipated shows of the year, but if the rumors of its budget of £100 million an episode are true, it’s also one of the most expensive. This is Netflix’s attempt at trying out something more traditional yet different (at least by Netflix standards) at the same …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>4 Your Eyez Only J Cole review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-4-your-eyez-only-j-cole-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 14:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-4-your-eyez-only-j-cole-review/</guid>
        <description>JCole’s last album release, 2014 Forest Hills Drive, received critical acclaim and was met with exceptional commercial success, making it the first LP in 25 years to sell over a million copies without a guest appearance. On November 27th 2015, J. Cole and Kendrick Lamar raised fans’ hopes of finally …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Andy’s Top 10 hip-hop albums of 2016
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-andys-top-10-hip-hop-albums-of-2016/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 14:57:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-andys-top-10-hip-hop-albums-of-2016/</guid>
        <description> 10. Kendrick Lamar | “Untitled Unmastered” In March Kendrick surprised fans with a compilation of unused demos recorded during the making of 2015’s To Pimp a Butterfly, his 3rd studio album. Kendrick previewed three of the tracks on late night talk shows throughout 2015 and during his performance …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Through the Wall
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-through-the-wall/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 14:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lawrence Good,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-through-the-wall/</guid>
        <description>I’m tired of being alone – I just want to love, and to be loved” laments Michal (Noa Kooler), voicing a complaint that many Imperial students share. Yet instead of just drowning her sorrows like the rest of us, Michal resolves to marry in 22 days’ time, trusting in God to find her a husband. From …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Harnessing bacterial defences to disrupt infectious biofilms
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-harnessing-bacterial-defences-to-disrupt-infectious-biofilms/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 14:34:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Rachel Gillespie,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-harnessing-bacterial-defences-to-disrupt-infectious-biofilms/</guid>
        <description>Pseudomonas aeruginosa is a bacterium of considerable medical importance. It is the archetypal “multi-drug resistant (MDR) pathogen”, known for its extreme antibiotic resistance, broad host range, and an association with serious illnesses including sepsis and hospital-acquired infections, prominent …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The real disgrace of executive pay
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-the-real-disgrace-of-executive-pay/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 14:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Shaul Rosten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-the-real-disgrace-of-executive-pay/</guid>
        <description>Theresa May announced this week that she intends to force companies to “justify” executive pay in response to reports that, at times, executives earn 140 times more than the average worker. High executive pay has been thrust into the headlines recently amidst the furore of the BHS collapse, and the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Report sheds light on Imperial culture
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-report-sheds-light-on-imperial-culture/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 23:46:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-report-sheds-light-on-imperial-culture/</guid>
        <description>Results of a report investigating Imperial’s institutional culture were recently released to the public, revealing a troubling picture behind the shining facade of academic excellence. The report was commissioned after felix brought to the public’s attention a series of incidents that took place …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Transphobic incident in Reynolds Bar
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-transphobic-incident-in-reynolds-bar/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 23:45:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-transphobic-incident-in-reynolds-bar/</guid>
        <description>A transphobic incident reportedly took place last week at the women’s restroom of the Reynolds Bar at Charing Cross Hospital, against a member of women’s rugby.
The trans student involved was grabbed by the arms in an attempt to forcefully eject them from the women’s restroom. Thankfully one of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Evelyn Gardens | Halls from hell?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-evelyn-gardens-halls-from-hell/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 23:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-evelyn-gardens-halls-from-hell/</guid>
        <description>Several students currently housed at Evelyn Gardens are reporting being unhappy with the quality of the accommodation they are receiving, with complaints coming in ranging from issues with pest control, to problems with plumbing and electrical works.
The recently refurbished residencies of Holbein, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Islamic Society Charity Week success
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-islamic-society-charity-week-success/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 23:41:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-islamic-society-charity-week-success/</guid>
        <description>For the first time, this year’s Charity Week hit and smashed through the £1,000,000 ceiling, as students from around the globe managed to collectively raise a total of £1,057,220.12 in donations.
The initiative which traditionally takes place over the final week of October sees students in London …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Arts Interviews | Edie Edmundson
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-arts-interviews-edie-edmundson/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 15:59:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ezra Kitson,Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-arts-interviews-edie-edmundson/</guid>
        <description>The Little Matchgirl is a show populated by people and puppets, of which the eponymous character, masterfully operated by Edie Edmundson, is one. Our writer, Ezra Kitson, was fortunate enough to speak with her after the performance.
Edmundson was drawn to puppetry by a National Theatre production of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Unknown Girl ties everything up in the end
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-the-unknown-girl-ties-everything-up-in-the-end/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 15:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Steve Bohnel,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-the-unknown-girl-ties-everything-up-in-the-end/</guid>
        <description>For about the first 90 minutes of The Unknown Girl, I sat rather unimpressed in my leather chair in one of the small theaters at Soho Screening Rooms. Then, as the last half hour unfolded, directors Jean-Pierre and Luc Dardenne tied together multiple plot lines like a beautiful bow on a Christmas …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Documentary Corner | Citizenfour
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-documentary-corner-citizenfour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 15:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-documentary-corner-citizenfour/</guid>
        <description>Sometimes a perfect opportunity can just present itself to a director. Citizenfour is a film whose mere existence is incredible. Based on the drama of Edward Snowden’s whistleblowing on the mass surveillance being performed by the NSA in America, Citizenfour is the final film in director Laura …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A year of Shazams and this is what I found
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-a-year-of-shazams-and-this-is-what-i-found/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 15:43:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-a-year-of-shazams-and-this-is-what-i-found/</guid>
        <description>So it’s Sunday; I’m tending to some life admin, such as paying rent, doing laundry, binge-watching Gilmore Girls, you know, the usual. All of a sudden an amazing cover of I Drove All Night (originally by legendary Céline Dion) comes up on the radio and I just have to know who it’s by. So I whip out …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>felix talks NSS and Imperial’s teaching strategy plans with VP for Education
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-felix-talks-nss-and-imperials-teaching-strategy-plans-with-vp-for-education/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 15:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-felix-talks-nss-and-imperials-teaching-strategy-plans-with-vp-for-education/</guid>
        <description>So I guess we should probably start by welcoming you to Imperial. How are you finding it so far?
It’s amazing, I’m having a great time. It’s the best job I’ve had ever I think, at least that’s what it feels like right now, it’s only been four months. There’s a lot that needs to be done, which of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cosmic dust in your backyard
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-cosmic-dust-in-your-backyard/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 12:09:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,Ipsita Herlekar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-cosmic-dust-in-your-backyard/</guid>
        <description>Of the many things you might have been sweeping off your balconies and terraces, cosmic dust particles could have found their way in your dust pan. Cosmic dust grains are minute particles measuring around 0.01 millimetres in size and are remnants from the time our solar system was born. They contain …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Does this look burnt?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-does-this-look-burnt/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 12:08:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,Alexandra Lim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-does-this-look-burnt/</guid>
        <description>The perennial question. You notice that slightly-too-blackened edge of your fried chicken thigh during a friend’s thanksgiving dinner, and hesitate just a little, but eat it anyway because nothing can take that peri-peri pleasure away from you. I guess it’s common knowledge that burnt foods can be …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
