<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jrp08/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jrp08/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Fencing men&#39;s 2nd team start off season with a win
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-fencing-mens-2nd-team-start-off-season-with-a-win/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 10:13:24 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Patten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-fencing-mens-2nd-team-start-off-season-with-a-win/</guid>
        <description>The fencing season opened this year at Ethos, with the men’s second team fencing against Surrey University’s first team. After a delayed start, the foilists got things going. Matthew Carney drew first blood with a neat parry-riposte, and continued on to win the bout against the opposition’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fencers comprehensively beat Manchester to make it to BUCS semi-finals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-fencers-comprehensively-beat-manchester-to-make-it-to-bucs-semi-finals/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 21:23:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Patten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-fencers-comprehensively-beat-manchester-to-make-it-to-bucs-semi-finals/</guid>
        <description>The scene, Wednesday lunchtime, Ethos; enter, the Women’s first Fencing team, they start preparing for the quarterfinal match of the BUCS championships against Manchester’s firsts. Feeling very confident of advancing, thanks to previous form, everyone was ready to win. The match opened well with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fencers return from Malta with most of their gold
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-fencers-return-from-malta-with-most-of-their-gold/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 18:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Patten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-fencers-return-from-malta-with-most-of-their-gold/</guid>
        <description>The Imperial College Fencing Club summer tour saw them invade Malta, escaping from their exams, and starting the week with a bit of night swimming at the villa they had rented in Mellieha for the competition.
The next morning saw the men’s foil entrants, still a bit bleary eyed, find a cab and get …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
