<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ywc110/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ywc110/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Programming: Easy, Peasy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-11-programming-easy-peasy/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 21:37:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-11-programming-easy-peasy/</guid>
        <description> It is now summer (for most of us at least!). If you have nothing lined up for you, and would like to learn something new or do something productive, why not consider learning how to program?
Why learn to program? Have you ever tried to rename hundreds of files, or tried to organise some data files …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Mt Gox Bitcoin Debacle
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-the-mt-gox-bitcoin-debacle/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 06:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-the-mt-gox-bitcoin-debacle/</guid>
        <description>The fledgling cryptocurrency Bitcoin suffered one of its biggest setbacks this past week when the (formerly) largest exchange Mt. Gox filed for bankruptcy protection. The beleaguered exchange has been marred by a string of management problems before it filed for bankruptcy protection. Yet, the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tired of all those Wires?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-5-tired-of-all-those-wires/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 10:22:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-5-tired-of-all-those-wires/</guid>
        <description>I hate wires. Every time I look at the back of my PC and I see the bunch of wires, my OCD kicks in. Luckily, I can usually sit at my desk and pretend the wires are not there.
Not for the mobile phone. When you need to charge it, transfer data, or listen to music, you have to pluck some bloody cables …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fancy shmancy tech from Santa
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-fancy-shmancy-tech-from-santa/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 16:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-fancy-shmancy-tech-from-santa/</guid>
        <description> Every year, as Christmas nears, I would like to think that I have some really rich and wealthy relative who is a Lord somewhere, perhaps some Lord of the Silicon. I would then write up a list of five items I would really like to have and then present it to them, knowing that I would probably get …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Encryption moving forward
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-27-encryption-moving-forward/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 16:04:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-27-encryption-moving-forward/</guid>
        <description>The recent spate of NSA tapping data and storing huge amount of internet traffic has been rather worrying. The exposé courtesy of Edward Snowden has made end-users more aware of the need for encryption, and accelerated the process of enhancing the security between end users and the service providers …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Google Releases the Nexus 5
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-6-google-releases-the-nexus-5/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 17:22:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-6-google-releases-the-nexus-5/</guid>
        <description>After many weeks of speculations, leaks, and overwhelming anticipation, Google has finally taken the wraps off their new flagship phone, the Nexus 5. The Nexus 5 is, like the Nexus 4, manufactured by LG and modelled after one of their flagship phones, and comes in black and white colours. The Nexus …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The PokéPositives of X &amp; Y
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-30-the-pokpositives-of-x-y/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 15:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-30-the-pokpositives-of-x-y/</guid>
        <description>Pokémon X &amp;amp; Y saw the first ever simultaneous release of a Nintendo title worldwide. Combined with the fact that the encryption for the 3DS has not yet been broken two years into its release, this has been one of the most exciting release of a Pokémon game in several years, and spell extremely …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Y wouldn’t you buy these amazing games? Its Pokémon, just X 2!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-y-wouldnt-you-buy-these-amazing-games-its-pokmon-just-x-2/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 01:02:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-y-wouldnt-you-buy-these-amazing-games-its-pokmon-just-x-2/</guid>
        <description>In the 17 years since the first Pokémon games were released, Game Freak have been churning out generations of iterative games, each improving upon their predecessors gradually. Now in its sixth generation of the games, Pokémon X &amp;amp; Y delivers another more-of-the-same but greatly improved game …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nexus 7 Review!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-nexus-7-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 19:30:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-nexus-7-review/</guid>
        <description>The Nexus series of devices released by Google is now a staple amongst many Android users’ arsenal of devices. Initially touted as a benchmark setting niché series of devices, the Nexus series has spawned off its own fanbase for users who are interested in always having the latest version of Android …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Back to School, Technically
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-back-to-school-technically/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 16:30:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-back-to-school-technically/</guid>
        <description> It’s the time of the year again. After a very beautiful summer, it’s time to get ready to face the cold, harsh winter and get ready for a new academic year. Winter is coming, and so are we in helping you make the best out of the new academic year, technically of course.
Productivity Software If you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Incredibly Magical iOS 7
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-21-incredibly-magical-ios-7/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2013 00:30:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-21-incredibly-magical-ios-7/</guid>
        <description>Apple fans worldwide rejoiced as detractors grieved a couple of weeks ago at the WWDC event when CEO Tim Cook unveiled yet another incredible update to the beautiful and gorgeous iOS 7, the latest iteration of Apple’s superior and world’s most advanced mobile operating system. It is chock full of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Updating Android without updating!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-6-updating-android-without-updating/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 17:47:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-6-updating-android-without-updating/</guid>
        <description>Google I/O has traditionally, for the past few years at least, been an event where Google unveils the newest and shiniest version of Android to the world. Although open source, Android is developed in-house with little known to the outside world save through the usual rumours and leaks. It’s been no …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Charging your Phone... Wirelessly
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-28-charging-your-phone-wirelessly/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 17:35:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-28-charging-your-phone-wirelessly/</guid>
        <description>Qi. This sounds like some sort of Chinese “life energy” philosophy, but that’s not what we are talking about here. Pronounced “chee”, Qi is a wireless inductive power standard that is increasingly being adopted by handset manufacturers such as Nokia and LG for inclusion into their handsets. For …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Elementary, My Dear Watson, Now Go Cure Cancer
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-elementary-my-dear-watson-now-go-cure-cancer/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 12:38:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-elementary-my-dear-watson-now-go-cure-cancer/</guid>
        <description>Watson might be becoming smarter than Holmes after all, if IBM gets its way.
Watson was first unveiled in a game show Jeopardy two years ago. Jeopardy is a game show where contestants are presented with the answers to questions they are supposed to come up with. Unsurprisingly, even though Holmes …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Love for Android Fragmentation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-love-for-android-fragmentation/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 23:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-love-for-android-fragmentation/</guid>
        <description>The big F word in the Android world: fragmentation.
This is the word that Android sceptics and users both decry and hate. It is both the bane and boon of Android. When Google made Android open source, it created a whole new set of problems and opportunities for users.
Android handset makers have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Google Nexus 4, worth it?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-google-nexus-4-worth-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 21:21:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-google-nexus-4-worth-it/</guid>
        <description>The best effort at a Nexus phone so far, albeit with some teething issues.
When Google announced the Nexus One phone in 2010, it was not too much of a success. There was a lack of consumer interest, save the enthusiasts. The phone had great hardware, at that time, but it failed to capture the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Make your 3D TV more useful
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-make-your-3d-tv-more-useful/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 02:53:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-make-your-3d-tv-more-useful/</guid>
        <description>Consumer electronics manufacturers often like to proclaim that their products boast the highest numbers in a certain arbitrary unit that often make no sense to the consumers, or are simply immaterial. Cameras like to boast that they have the highest amount of pixels while computers used to tout …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>More Jelly Bean and a new family of Nexus
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-18-more-jelly-bean-and-a-new-family-of-nexus/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2012 13:18:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-18-more-jelly-bean-and-a-new-family-of-nexus/</guid>
        <description> While Hurricane Sandy was wrecking havoc on the East Coast of America, those of us on the other side of the pond were left disappointed when Google had to cancel a press event in New York. But fear not &amp;ndash; for Google has managed to release new details on a new version of Android and a new …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reddit: Freedom of speech?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-reddit-freedom-of-speech/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 22:36:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-reddit-freedom-of-speech/</guid>
        <description>Somewhere in a dank basement, a high school white American teenager smiles to himself for discovering a cute picture of a cat, worthy of sharing with his peers. He fires up his browser and heads to a website called reddit (www.reddit.com) where he posts a link to his uploaded image in a corner of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Will W8 cause us grief?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-will-w8-cause-us-grief/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 02:25:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jason Parmar,Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-will-w8-cause-us-grief/</guid>
        <description>Some of us are not normal people (but then again, we are Imperial students). We live on the bleeding edge of technology where we thrive on using the latest and greatest of gadgets and software. We readily consume new technology and are willing to learn and adapt. In case of an interface paradigm …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
