<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/cr709/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/cr709/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Last night I dreamt of Boipeba</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-last-night-i-dreamt-of-boipeba/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christopher Richardson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-last-night-i-dreamt-of-boipeba/</guid>
        <description>I hesitate to utter the word “Bahia”. Bah-eee-yah. It’s beautiful to say it aloud. Also known by its epithet, the “land of happiness”, Bahia is a vibrant state in Northeastern Brazil that for whatever reason has managed to evade many a Latin America travel itinerary. My hesitation to utter the word …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In conversation with Professor Lord Robert Winston</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-in-conversation-with-professor-lord-robert-winston/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christopher Richardson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-in-conversation-with-professor-lord-robert-winston/</guid>
        <description>LRW, good morning. Good morning.
You are a person of many hats. How would you describe what you do? Well, they’re all crumpled hats, that’s for sure! I spend my mornings in the college and afternoons in Westminster, peppered with a lot of educational outreach throughout the week.
The common thread …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Farming in Chernobyl</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-farming-in-chernobyl/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christopher Richardson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-farming-in-chernobyl/</guid>
        <description>A leading expert on the long-term environmental consequences of nuclear disasters is to lead a study to help know when and if it is safe to go back into Chernobyl’s human exclusion zone. The results will support Ukrainian authorities in developing a timeline for when and where it will eventually be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chasing kaleidoscopic corals in Jordan’s Red Sea</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-chasing-kaleidoscopic-corals-in-jordan-s-red-sea/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christopher Richardson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-chasing-kaleidoscopic-corals-in-jordan-s-red-sea/</guid>
        <description>This summer marked the release of Chasing Coral on Netflix UK. The documentary follows a group of divers and scientists documenting disappearing coral reefs across the globe. The team used the technology behind Google’s Street View to create a set of 360-degree images, allowing anyone with internet …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>When in Rum</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-when-in-rum/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christopher Richardson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-when-in-rum/</guid>
        <description>Wadi Rum, AKA the Valley of the Moon, is Jordan’s largest valley. Not that the size matters much in itself. It’s also Hollywood’s go-to location for all movies Martian, which tells you all you need to know about the kind of landscapes on offer. I was initially dubious about spending several days of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Conquering Mount Rinjani
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-conquering-mount-rinjani/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 19:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christopher Richardson,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-conquering-mount-rinjani/</guid>
        <description> To the unacquainted, volcano climbing in the Indonesian archipelago might seem a little dumb, but in reality there’s only so much tanning and partying you can handle before you get the itch to do something a little more challenging. Having done my homework, I’d come to the conclusion that Mount …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
