<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Food on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/food/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Food on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/food/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The Do’s and Don’t of a Student Christmas Dinner: How to Keep the Festive Mood on a Student Budget</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-dos-donts-christmas-dinner-keep-festive-mood-student-budget/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,Zahra Abiola,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-dos-donts-christmas-dinner-keep-festive-mood-student-budget/</guid>
        <description>THE BIRD
A whole roast turkey is the usual fare for a Christmas dinner but unless you are ready to buy way ahead, have an inordinate amount of oven space, and you don’t mind the lengthy brining and cooking process, I would steer clear. A poorly cooked turkey is way worse than no turkey at all. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Recipe: Pasta Aglio e Olio</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-pasta-aglio-e-olio-recipe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Haider Nazerali,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-pasta-aglio-e-olio-recipe/</guid>
        <description>I first saw this amazing quick pasta dish being made in the Netflix film ‘Chef’ (100% great to watch when you’re procrastinating your next lab report or essay) and it looked delicious. Thanks to social media sites stalking my life, it didn’t take long for a recipe to appear on my YouTube suggested. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Ultimate(?) Guide to Pasta Shapes</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-ultimate-guide-pasta-shapes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-ultimate-guide-pasta-shapes/</guid>
        <description>Simultaneously a destitute student’s staple and a feature in high-end restaurants, everyone understands pasta and, more importantly, everyone loves pasta.
However, even true love can get boring. Missionary and “words of affirmation” can only keep a relationship alive for so long. Likewise, fusilli …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Take You and Your Study Buddy to Shake Shack Pronto!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-take-you-your-study-buddy-shake-shack-pronto/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Zahra Abiola,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-take-you-your-study-buddy-shake-shack-pronto/</guid>
        <description>Students of Imperial College London, we have been done a great disservice. There is a trendy, self-service, American burger place right beside South Kensington station. And it’s the one that doesn’t have a student discount. If you are tired of a specific number of men not appreciating you, you can …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Home-made Ramen: How to Class Up the Simplest and Cheapest Meal on the Student Menu</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-homemade-ramen-class-up-simplest-cheapest-meal-student-menu/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mariam Jallow,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-homemade-ramen-class-up-simplest-cheapest-meal-student-menu/</guid>
        <description>Ingredients:
 1tsp sesame oil
 1tsp olive oil
 2 garlic cloves
 2tsp grated ginger
 60g carrots
 60g mushrooms
 900ml vegetable stock
 1tbs vinegar
 3tbs soy sauce
 1tbs sriracha sauce
 80g noodles
  This week I decided to ditch the packaged staple of every student diet, instant ramen, and make it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Black Milk: The Sugar Coma you’ve been waiting for!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-Black-Milk-Sugar-Coma-Youve-Been-Waiting-For/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Zahra Abiola,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-Black-Milk-Sugar-Coma-Youve-Been-Waiting-For/</guid>
        <description>Black Milk is a café that is best known for their jaw dropping freakshakes. Now, freakshakes have been a trend that has taken the internet by storm for some time now. Originating from Australia, they can be defined as milkshakes topped with something to give it a twist. This gives a lot of leeway …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Old Dutch Monday Madness: The only way to start the week right!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-my-old-dutch-monday-madness/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Zahra Abiola,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-my-old-dutch-monday-madness/</guid>
        <description>I have a very important question to ask you all. Do you want a sweet or a savoury breakfast? Because at My Old Dutch, that is the most important decision you will be making that day. This place sports some of the largest crepe style pancakes I’ve ever seen. Their menu is just as big and is split …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pizza Union: The Cheapest Pizza You’ll Find in London!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-pizza-union-cheapest-pizza-in-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Zahra Abiola,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-pizza-union-cheapest-pizza-in-london/</guid>
        <description>I’m going to let you in on one of London’s better kept secrets. Pizza Union. They don’t even need a gimmick. This pizza place has 12” pizzas starting at £3.50. No coupon code. No Instagram exclusive. No witch making you promise your first-born child in exchange for some genuinely affordable food in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Post-Halloween Budgeting Secret: Beware the Supermarket Powers</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-post-halloween-budgeting-secret-beware-supermarket-powers/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ameena Hassan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-post-halloween-budgeting-secret-beware-supermarket-powers/</guid>
        <description>Dear Readers, I bring to you a little known secret. Writing in the dark of night while someone left the Felix closet unlocked, this London-dwelling resident can finally reveal it to you. Have you been salivating over your next piece of chocolate, only to be deterred by high prices and substandard …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>VQ: The Restaurant that Never Sleeps</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-vq-restaurant-never-sleeps/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Zahra Abiola,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-vq-restaurant-never-sleeps/</guid>
        <description>We all know how it goes. The night starts out with good intentions. You’ve handed in your coursework with just 2 minutes to spare. You want some fun. You round up your friends and dance the stress away while screaming Beyoncé lyrics at the top of your lungs, having the time of your life as a student …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Whisk Desserts: A delightfully decadent all-dessert pop-up in Angel</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-whisk-desserts-a-delightfully-decadent-all-dessert-pop-up-in-angel/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-whisk-desserts-a-delightfully-decadent-all-dessert-pop-up-in-angel/</guid>
        <description>As term ends (at last!) and summer makes its approach, we can all take a well-deserved break from the daily grind of revision and exams. Holidays abroad, lazing around in the sun, ice cream in the park - what could be better? On your list of indolent summer indulgence should definitely be Whisk …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Spice Up Your Summer in 3 Recipes</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-spice-up-your-summer-in-3-recipes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-spice-up-your-summer-in-3-recipes/</guid>
        <description>Exams are nearly over, the sun is out (thanks, global warming), and you can almost taste the sweet, sweet freedom that comes with summer; what better way to relax and refresh than by savouring some of the season’s finest produce in easy-to-follow, simple recipes?
Here are Felix’s top three recipes: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Shaken, not stirred” - Cocktails 101: A Guide for Dummies</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07--shaken-not-stirred-cocktails-101-a-guide-for-dummies/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Julia Dabrowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07--shaken-not-stirred-cocktails-101-a-guide-for-dummies/</guid>
        <description>Exams are over… at least for the majority of us, and what better way to celebrate (or grieve if you’ve still got some coming) than with some tasty ethanol-containing beverages? Thankfully, summer means a chance to venture out of your comfort zone and try something more unique than your typical Union …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Introducing Yumchop Foods</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-introducing-yumchop-foods/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abi Adefisan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-introducing-yumchop-foods/</guid>
        <description>Yumchop Foods is delighted to be partnering with Imperial College University in the heart of London to bring an authentic taste of its quintessential multi-ethnic frozen ready meals, using the innovative automatic retail kiosk (ARK), to the 24-hour Central Library.
The range includes a mixed range …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Cookie Dough: everything you never knew you needed in your life!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-my-cookie-dough-everything-you-never-knew-you-needed-in-your-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,Julia Dabrowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-my-cookie-dough-everything-you-never-knew-you-needed-in-your-life/</guid>
        <description>After reviewing Naked Dough last month, when we got the chance to try out another cookie dough place, My Cookie Dough, the excitement was real. Although both serve cookie dough, this place adds a completely different twist onto what we thought we were expecting, replacing raw cookie dough with baked …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mumbai Mix: a comprehensive review of the best Indian food on campus</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-mumbai-mix-a-comprehensive-review-of-the-best-indian-food-on-campus/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-mumbai-mix-a-comprehensive-review-of-the-best-indian-food-on-campus/</guid>
        <description>You’ve had Indian food, sure, but we guarantee you haven’t had anything that tastes close to what Mumbai Mix has to offer. If you spend a lot of time on campus, chances are you’ve probably heard of Mumbai Mix – the only authentic Indian food stall at the Farmers Market on Tuesdays. If you haven’t, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mumbai Mix: Bringing India to your doorstep</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-01-mumbai-mix-bringing-india-to-your-doorstep/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dimple Samani,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-01-mumbai-mix-bringing-india-to-your-doorstep/</guid>
        <description>We are Mumbai Mix! An Indian street food stall known for its long queues and vibrant aromas (that’s not us bragging – it’s feedback from our customers!) For anyone that hasn’t met us yet, we are part of the Farmers Market that is located on Queens Lawn every Tuesday. We write this piece following an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Did we just hear someone say brunch? </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-did-we-just-hear-someone-say-brunch/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Julia Dabrowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-did-we-just-hear-someone-say-brunch/</guid>
        <description>What comes to mind when you see the word ‘brunch’? Probably a bunch of millennials eating crunchy avocado toast, Insta-worthy smoothie açai bowls or stacks of warm waffles (drizzled with maple syrup and topped with fresh summer berries of course), and all of this costing you lots and lots of £££. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Biff’s Jack Shack: turning jackfruit into fast food is not just for the vegans</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-biff-s-jack-shack-turning-jackfruit-into-fast-food-is-not-just-for-the-vegans/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhidian Thomas,Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-biff-s-jack-shack-turning-jackfruit-into-fast-food-is-not-just-for-the-vegans/</guid>
        <description>The past 12 months have been more vegan inspired than ever; in fact, 2018 was the year of the vegan. Last year saw sales of meat-free food increase by a staggering 987%, with everyone from Beyonce to Benedict Cumberbatch getting in on the action. Like it or not, plant based (read: vegan) food is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Naked Dough: the good, the bad and the ugly</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-naked-dough-the-good-the-bad-and-the-ugly/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Julia Dabrowska,Eva Tadros,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-naked-dough-the-good-the-bad-and-the-ugly/</guid>
        <description>Remember that cute little stand that sells big tubs filled with mouthwatering cookie dough that we told you about in the “2 Girls, 1 Dessert” article earlier this year? Well, we felt like we just had to go back and satisfy our cravings, so we bring you the ultimate guide to (almost) every single …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fuwa Fuwa: an exact soufflé science</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-fuwa-fuwa-an-exact-souffl-science/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Farhat Eamon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-fuwa-fuwa-an-exact-souffl-science/</guid>
        <description>If you like delicious flavours and something different to fill your belly (and your Instagram feed) take a trip to the UK’s only soufflé pancake café!
Having first tasted these fluffy pieces of heaven in Hoshino Coffee, a chain with over 150 outlets across Japan, I was immediately hooked! London I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tapioca: your favourite bubble tea ingredient  explained!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-tapioca-your-favourite-bubble-tea-ingredient-explained/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Julia Dabrowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-tapioca-your-favourite-bubble-tea-ingredient-explained/</guid>
        <description>You’ve probably encountered, or at least heard of, tapioca at some point in your life (at least if you’ve ever come close to having boba tea or tapioca pudding). A chewy masterpiece, sometimes simply referred to as ‘pearls’, tapioca is in fact a starch extracted from the cassava root, a plant …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cheap clean eats</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-cheap-clean-eats/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-cheap-clean-eats/</guid>
        <description>Now that the new year has started, how many of those “new year, new me” posts have you seen floating around? It’s nice to think we can have a fresh start as soon as the year begins, but those first few days up until term restarts are so much of a limbo, it’s pretty much impossible to send any form …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College Food Festival: Reviewed</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-imperial-college-food-festival-reviewed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivan Parmar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-imperial-college-food-festival-reviewed/</guid>
        <description>On 24th October, the Imperial College Food Festival took place on Queen’s Lawn, featuring a diverse range of food stalls including London Smokehouse, Nick and Greek, Wafflestick and Coconut Tree. The fundraiser was part of the international Charity Week campaign held on campus, and raised a whopping …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>When life gives you lemons -12 options besides lemonade</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-when-life-gives-you-lemons-12-options-besides-lemonade/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ambika Bharadwaj,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-when-life-gives-you-lemons-12-options-besides-lemonade/</guid>
        <description>We all know that the best uses for lemons are those we can devour: lemonade, lemon pie, and of course lemon meringue&amp;hellip; yum! But have you thought of lemon as a health hack? Discover 12 more uses below.
1) Fever
Lemon juice aids in curing general sicknesses such as flus, colds and fevers. Lemons …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Can I Get Uhhh..” - Your 101 Guide to All Things Caffeine</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19--can-i-get-uhhh-your-101-guide-to-all-things-caffeine/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Julia Dabrowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19--can-i-get-uhhh-your-101-guide-to-all-things-caffeine/</guid>
        <description>Imagine this: you, craving caffeine as any typical student, walk into a coffee shop (or, depending on the time of year, stumble into the Library Café). Scanning the menu, you see many options – cappuccinos, espressos, mochas, lattes… why is choosing a coffee so hard when you don’t speak Italian and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Taste of Italy in (only)1,572km²: 5 of London’s favourite Italian spots</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-a-taste-of-italy-in-only-1-572km-5-of-london-s-favourite-italian-spots/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-a-taste-of-italy-in-only-1-572km-5-of-london-s-favourite-italian-spots/</guid>
        <description>We’ve all had our classic “Eat, Pray, Love” moment where it just seems like we desperately need to sit there and stare at a massive plate of pasta before we absolutely devour it. Unfortunately, whilst getting on the next flight to Italy might seem mouth-wateringly tempting, recreating that moment …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Five Decadent Hot Chocolates For Autumn</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-five-decadent-hot-chocolates-for-autumn/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ambika Bharadwaj,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-five-decadent-hot-chocolates-for-autumn/</guid>
        <description>This time of the year is not only perfect for flannels, plaids and woollen hats; hot chocolate is a perfect drink for transitioning into winter season. In this article, I’ve written about some of the most decadent hot chocolates I’ve had in London.
Choccywoccydoodah
Choccywoccydoodah is definitely …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Low-fat, reduced fat and fat-free foods: a healthy choice or a myth?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-low-fat-reduced-fat-and-fat-free-foods-a-healthy-choice-or-a-myth/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,Julia Dabrowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-low-fat-reduced-fat-and-fat-free-foods-a-healthy-choice-or-a-myth/</guid>
        <description>Hey, could you please grab a Greek yoghurt when you’re in Tesco? Just make sure it’s the low-fat one - thanks!”
Sound familiar? Nowadays, we’re constantly surrounded by a myriad of fat-free, low-fat and reduced fat products as the food industry’s attempt to maximise profits gains momentum – taking a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2 Girls, 1 Dessert</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-2-girls-1-dessert/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,Julia Dabrowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-2-girls-1-dessert/</guid>
        <description>Watching all those Food Insider videos on Facebook on a mundane afternoon undoubtedly leaves us all drooling, daydreaming about those Instagram-worthy desserts – just think of the food envy your friends will experience when they see a boomerang of that food! So naturally, you tag your friends …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>101 Ways to eat Pasta</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-101-ways-to-eat-pasta/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,Julia Dabrowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-101-ways-to-eat-pasta/</guid>
        <description>So you’ve got through your first week of uni madness - the wild balance of parties, events, and socials with possible introductory lectures or just straight up normal classes. Food this week has probably just been frozen pizza, toast, and of course all the sweets from Freshers’ Fair because who has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Freshers’ 10 under £10</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-20-freshers-10-under-10/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,Julia Dabrowska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-20-freshers-10-under-10/</guid>
        <description>Freshers is upon us and you know what that means – time for our bank accounts to hate us. So you keep tapping that contactless on every night out – if you don’t see the money leaving, it’s not really gone, right? If only it worked like that. It can be quite tempting to splash out during freshers and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Food taste test: instant ramen flavours</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-felix-food-taste-test-instant-ramen-flavours/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-felix-food-taste-test-instant-ramen-flavours/</guid>
        <description>There is, fairly or unfairly, perhaps no meal more closely associated with the student experience than instant ramen. Different universities may have their own iconic foodstuffs, but the ubiquity of instant noodles seems to cut across time and space. At the most basic level, instant noodles appeal …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Think you can take the heat? Read on!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-think-you-can-take-the-heat-read-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Zhihang Li,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-think-you-can-take-the-heat-read-on/</guid>
        <description>If you have ever heard about my hometown Szechuan, there is a 99.9% probability that you would relate it with spicy food. Apart from the famous Szechuan Hotpot, with loads of chilli floating on the surface, Mapo Tofu is irresistible if you fancy spicy food. It is also a perfect vegetarian or vegan …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Seven things I learnt about Italian food from my trip to Rome</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-seven-things-i-learnt-about-italian-food-from-my-trip-to-rome/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Davage,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-seven-things-i-learnt-about-italian-food-from-my-trip-to-rome/</guid>
        <description>Let’s face it, one of the main reasons why people visit Italy is for the food. Yes, there is also bucket loads of history to gaze at in awe and the sunshine is a nice change from the UK, but really, the food is the main event. When I say “Italian food,” what comes into your mind? Pizza and pasta? …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s nearly Easter – season of chocolate, chocolate, and more chocolate!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-it-s-nearly-easter-season-of-chocolate-chocolate-and-more-chocolate/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-it-s-nearly-easter-season-of-chocolate-chocolate-and-more-chocolate/</guid>
        <description>For unknown reasons, Easter is not my favourite holiday, and making food for it is not as pleasant as cooking for Christmas. So, Easter for me is more a holiday of sweets – especially Easter eggs. In my opinion, the only things that should be cooked during Easter have to have chocolate. Even if you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Worth the hype? By Chloe</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-worth-the-hype-by-chloe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bláithín Dockery,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-worth-the-hype-by-chloe/</guid>
        <description>A couple of years ago merely calling a food vegan would have made many of us shudder, picturing something dry and tasteless. However, there has clearly been a revolution as veganism has changed its image from oddball hippies to vibrant health-conscious millennials. With the number of vegans in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A couple of Asian-inspired recipes for you to fry!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-a-couple-of-asian-inspired-recipes-for-you-to-fry/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-a-couple-of-asian-inspired-recipes-for-you-to-fry/</guid>
        <description>Writing feels oddly therapeutic most of the time and I am not sure why I stayed away from it for so long – I mean, two weeks is a really long time, but I have an excuse! (I mean, I always have an excuse, don’t I?) I experimented with new ideas and tried new ingredients and culinary zones so I can …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Worth the hype: Bubble waffles</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-worth-the-hype-bubble-waffles/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bláithín Dockery,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-worth-the-hype-bubble-waffles/</guid>
        <description>Bubble waffles, also known as egg waffles, have recently risen from relative obscurity to become the next online sensation. An import from Hong Kong, egg waffles originated as a street snack in the 1950s and are made with a sweet egg-rich batter cooked on a special frying pan with small round cells. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Eat Tokyo: Budget-friendly Japanese Delights </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-eat-tokyo-budget-friendly-japanese-delights/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Davage,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-eat-tokyo-budget-friendly-japanese-delights/</guid>
        <description>I’ve been meaning to rave about this small chain that boasts authentic Japanese food for a while, but my degree has unfortunately been distracting me. Although Eat Tokyo has locations throughout London and Japan, I have only visited the Holborn restaurant so far. The Hammersmith and Notting Hill …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Temple of Seitan: The ultimate vegan fried chicken?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-temple-of-seitan-the-ultimate-vegan-fried-chicken/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chloe Foo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-temple-of-seitan-the-ultimate-vegan-fried-chicken/</guid>
        <description>If you haven’t heard of Temple of Seitan, let me give you a rundown. Vegan fried chicken.
The cries of outrage in response to the word ‘vegan’ that aligns to the reaction towards the word ‘feminism’ is to be addressed in another article. For now, it is sufficient to say that in my opinion, the myths …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Worth the Hype? Dark Sugars</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-worth-the-hype-dark-sugars/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bláithín Dockery,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-worth-the-hype-dark-sugars/</guid>
        <description>It’s January. The Christmas holidays are over, which means that winter has lost its magical charm and is now just cold and dark. But fear not, for there is a solution to your woes: chocolate. As Imperial is heavy on the science, I’m sure many of us know that chocolate is a natural mood booster, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the eighth day of Christmas, my true love gave to me… KFC IN JAPAN</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-eighth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-kfc-in-japan/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Graham Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-eighth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-kfc-in-japan/</guid>
        <description>How does a country with a very low proportion of Christians celebrate Christmas? 3 letters; K, F, C. The celebration of Christmas day has, in Japan, become inextricably linked with eating fried chicken with long queues throughout the day for some finger licking goodness. The story begins in the 70’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the eleventh day of Christmas, my true love gave to me… BRUSSELS SPROUTS</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-eleventh-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-brussels-sprouts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-eleventh-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-brussels-sprouts/</guid>
        <description>You will need&amp;hellip;
 1 kg Brussels sprouts 50 gr butter 4 tsp vegetable oil 20 gr almonds 400 ml double cream 5 tsp lemon juice 5 tbsp breadcrumbs freshly grated parmesan (the more, the better) a pinch of salt black pepper   Simmer salted water in a saucepan. Add the Brussels sprouts and boil them …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the fifth day of Christmas, my true love gave to me… MINCE PIES</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-fifth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-mince-pies/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-fifth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-mince-pies/</guid>
        <description>Every country in the world seems to have its Christmas food. Here, they are Christmas cake and mince pies – which disappointed me at first. A lot. But, hey, British food can grow on you. Eventually.
Squashed peach and almond mince pies
This was the first mince pie I’ve tried and I was a bit like …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the first day of Christmas, my true love gave to me... THE BEST ADVENT CALENDAR</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-first-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-the-best-advent-calendar/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-first-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-the-best-advent-calendar/</guid>
        <description>To be clear, this is not an advertisement for any company out there. But this year I felt very nostalgic and I decided that I should revive the childhood years when I used to get advent calendars. Should I mention that I also used to eat them in one day? Maximum two, if I really felt like I should …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the fourth day of Christmas, my true love gave to me... CUATRO ALFAJORES</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-fourth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-cuatro-alfajores/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alan Perfect Ruiz De Velasco,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-fourth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-cuatro-alfajores/</guid>
        <description>While you might have heard about the most typical Spanish Christmas foods, I want to focus on a relatively unknown Christmas sweet: the alfajor, consumed generally in the south of Spain, and definitely a high point in humanity’s culinary achievements.
An alfajor is a very special sweet, made mostly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the ninth day of Christmas, my true love gave to me… HOT CHOCOLATE ADVENTURES</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-ninth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-hot-chocolate-adventures/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Davage,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-ninth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-hot-chocolate-adventures/</guid>
        <description>Christmas announced its arrival in London several weeks ago when the department stores assembled their window display extravaganzas and numerous shopping streets had grand switch-on ceremonies for their array of twinkly lights (the annual chance for forgotten celebrities to shine).
But the recent …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the second day of Christmas, my true love gave to me... EGGNOG</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-second-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-eggnog/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-second-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-eggnog/</guid>
        <description>You will need&amp;hellip;
 700ml whole milk 250ml double cream 5 eggs 3 cinnamon sticks 1 tbsp vanilla essence/pods 1 tsp nutmeg 150g granulated sugar 200ml dark rum (I know you want more, but you need to keep it low for the consistency)   In a saucepan, combine the milk, double cream, cinnamon, vanilla …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the seventh day of Christmas, my true love gave to me… CHRISTMAS ROAST PORK WITH RIB GRAVY AND APPLE BREAD SAUCE</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-seventh-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-christmas-roast-pork-with-rib-gravy-and-apple-bread-sauce/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-seventh-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-christmas-roast-pork-with-rib-gravy-and-apple-bread-sauce/</guid>
        <description>You will need&amp;hellip;
FOR THE ROAST - 2 kg pork belly (depending on how many people you plan to feed) - 3 tbsp salt
FOR THE GRAVY - 3 tbsp olive oil - 4 pork ribs - 2 onions, chopped - 2 carrots, chopped in big chunks - 1 litre chicken stock - 8 black peppercorns - fresh bay leaves - fresh thyme
FOR …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the sixth day of Christmas, my true love gave to me… GINGERBREAD MEN</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-sixth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-gingerbread-men/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-sixth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-gingerbread-men/</guid>
        <description>You will need&amp;hellip;
 400g plain flour 1 tsp bicarbonate of soda 2 tsp ground ginger 1 tsp ground cinnamon 125g butter (unsalted) 200g honey 2 eggs   Mix all the dry ingredients and then add in the butter. This step would be really easy if you have a food processor, but I imagine that, as a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the tenth day of Christmas, my true love gave to me… BEST FOOD GIFTS</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-first-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-best-food-gifts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-first-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-best-food-gifts/</guid>
        <description>Knowing that someone likes to cook makes picking a Christmas gift a lot easier for you. Felix came here with a list of our 10 picks – hopefully, Santa will see this and will know which one you would like to see under that Christmas tree.
 Chef’s knife – This says it all. You can never have enough …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the third day of Christmas, my true love gave to me... BISCUITS</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-third-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-biscuits/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-third-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-biscuits/</guid>
        <description>Just because they are a totally different thing to gingerbread, you need two to have both – trust me. Even if your family says “We don’t need two kinds of biscuits!”, what else would you give Santa when he delivers your gifts? Everybody knows that you make biscuits for Santa! So you have no choice. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the twelfth day of Christmas, my true love gave to me… SEA BASS WITH SWEET POTATO AND GREEN BEAN CURRY</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-twelfth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-sea-bass-with-sweet-potato-and-green-bean-curry/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-twelfth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-sea-bass-with-sweet-potato-and-green-bean-curry/</guid>
        <description>You will need&amp;hellip;
 2 large sweet potatoes 3 tbsp olive oil 1 onion, finely diced 3 garlic cloves, crushed 1 tbsp grated ginger 2 lime leaves (replaceable with 1 tsp lime juice) 1 tsp curry powder ½ tsp turmeric ½ masala ¼ tsp cinnamon 160 ml coconut cream 400 ml coconut milk 100 gr green beans 4 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Asian invasion</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-asian-invasion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chun Yuan Hii,Adrian Lua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-asian-invasion/</guid>
        <description>Felix Food has been sharing simple and quick recipes for the past few issues, and that’s great! Hopefully they’ve helped you to survive the term in some ways. But don’t you occasionally imagine yourself cooking a Michelin-starred dish, unleashing your inner chef, and it no longer mattering if you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Worth the Hype? Shake Shack</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-worth-the-hype-shake-shack/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bláithín Dockery,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-worth-the-hype-shake-shack/</guid>
        <description>When you think of the United States of America what do you imagine? Towering skyscrapers? Sunny Beaches? Famous faces? How about a good ol’ American cheeseburger? The burger is an iconic American food, even recently honoured in the movie The Founder telling the story of how McDonald’s came to be. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Worth the hype? Cereal Killer Cafe</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-worth-the-hype-cereal-killer-cafe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Bláithín Dockery,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-worth-the-hype-cereal-killer-cafe/</guid>
        <description>Worth the hype? In our digital world, filled with gorgeous food pics from Instagram, drool-worthy food videos on Facebook, and constant articles on the trendiest new places to visit, how can we know where is actually worth eating, and what’s just good lighting? To solve this new-age dilemma I bring …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Finally – time to celebrate with a nice meal out! </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-finally-time-to-celebrate-with-a-nice-meal-out/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-finally-time-to-celebrate-with-a-nice-meal-out/</guid>
        <description>If you are still reading this – congratulations! You’ve made it through the first half of this first term. While it’s not a big deal, I feel like I need a pat on the back every time I manage to get more than five hours of sleep, so… surviving for so long made me think that I actually have to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Have a sweet tooth? We sure do...</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-have-a-sweet-tooth-we-sure-do/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chun Yuan Hii,Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-have-a-sweet-tooth-we-sure-do/</guid>
        <description>Admit it, we all need our sugary boost sometimes (though this might be heavily frowned upon by my friend who wrote on healthy eating last week&amp;hellip;) Maybe it’s just me, but occasionally, after a nine-to-five day full of labs and lectures, you just want to have something warm, sweet, and – most …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>From penne to puttanesca: an ode to pasta</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-from-penne-to-puttanesca-an-ode-to-pasta/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-from-penne-to-puttanesca-an-ode-to-pasta/</guid>
        <description>If there was ever an argument for the inherent goodness of humanity and the progress of mankind, it can be summed up in a single word: pasta. This humble staple of our diet is probably one of the best reasons to be alive on this earth. Whether it’s long, worm-like spaghetti drenched in a carbonara …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Healthy, mindful eating on a budget?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-healthy-mindful-eating-on-a-budget/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michelle Yeap,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-healthy-mindful-eating-on-a-budget/</guid>
        <description>One of my biggest struggles coming to university is living within a budget. I am sure many students, including myself, wonder whether it is possible to eat a healthy, balanced diet while also living on a shoestring.
For me, the supermarket is none other than the place for distraction and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grub’s up! Felix Food’s guide to campus food</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-grub-s-up-felix-food-s-guide-to-campus-food/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Davage,Chun Yuan Hii,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-grub-s-up-felix-food-s-guide-to-campus-food/</guid>
        <description>1. JCR
The canteen with blue tables has a standard deli selling fancy baguettes and a canteen with all the normal lunch grub (boxed sandwiches, crisps, etc.).
Pieminster sells gourmet pie and mash. A little pricey but sometimes they do discounts so look out for those. They offer a range of gravy, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Tis the season... again</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27--tis-the-season-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chun Yuan Hii,Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27--tis-the-season-again/</guid>
        <description>I’ll bet my lunch that you have already seen those shop-fronts decorated in orangey strips, the vampire Frappucino adverts outside Starbucks, your friends marking ‘Interested’ on Halloween-themed Facebook events, and those tacky, plasticky, not-even-scary masks lining the aisles of Tesco. Well okay, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An introduction to the art of cooking</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-an-introduction-to-the-art-of-cooking/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-an-introduction-to-the-art-of-cooking/</guid>
        <description>Writing Food is so difficult when you don’t have anyone suggesting “maybe you want to write about that?”, or when you just don’t feel inspired to write about their suggestions. So, while I struggled with finding a topic for this page, I realised that I did not say “Hi!” to you this year. So, here I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Braised partridge with carrots and peas </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-braised-partridge-with-carrots-and-peas/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-braised-partridge-with-carrots-and-peas/</guid>
        <description>When we decided to make this an autumn-food edition, I haven’t realised that I am not sure what autumn food is. And despite the world being ‘in love’ with pumpkin this season – and by this I mean Pumpkin spice latte – I feel like the only thing that deserves to be mentioned is the pumpkin pie. But …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Comfort food season begins</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-14-comfort-food-season-begins/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Davage,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-14-comfort-food-season-begins/</guid>
        <description>As Freshers’ Fortnight comes to an end, we can say an official goodbye to summer – in other words, the brief heatwave in June and the sporadic sunshine since then (for those of us who spent the summer holidays in London) – and a reluctant hello to autumn. However, as the daylight gradually vanishes …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Avoiding drunk food disasters – our guide to your post-night out snacks</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-avoiding-drunk-food-disasters-our-guide-to-your-post-night-out-snacks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Davage,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-avoiding-drunk-food-disasters-our-guide-to-your-post-night-out-snacks/</guid>
        <description>Freshers’ week. A time to make new friends and become accustomed to new surroundings, whether that be a new borough, city, or perhaps even a new country. However, for many, freshers’ week also involves a few hangovers and a number of drunk food disasters. Don’t be that person eating folded squares …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Foodie’s Guide to South Kensington</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-foodie-s-guide-to-south-kensington/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chun Yuan Hii,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-foodie-s-guide-to-south-kensington/</guid>
        <description>With Freshers’ week going on in full swing, there’s bound to be a moment when you’re a little bit too weak to go near the stove and dish out your perfectly organised, healthy and affordable meal plans. Or maybe you just need somewhere to go with your new friends without becoming financially …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Andrada’s trans-European culinary summer adventure
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-andradas-trans-european-culinary-summer-adventure/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 17:12:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-andradas-trans-european-culinary-summer-adventure/</guid>
        <description>Believe it or not, this is the last food tip of the year – and it makes me feel both sad and relieved. Because there is no dish that’s really good enough to celebrate the end of the year, the promise of summer and freedom, I decided to create the perfect trans-European food itinerary for you.
If you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>XU | the brainchild of BAO is a beautiful addition to the London food scene
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-xu-the-brainchild-of-bao-is-a-beautiful-addition-to-the-london-food-scene/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 17:10:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-xu-the-brainchild-of-bao-is-a-beautiful-addition-to-the-london-food-scene/</guid>
        <description>Two years into this half-university-student-half-food-blogger life of mine and I already have a lifetime’s worth of cringe worthy moments – mostly encountered during blogger events and restaurant invites. Imagine: turning up to the door of a launch event to know that my name had never been added to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lazy food edition | Chilled rice pudding with berry compote
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-lazy-food-edition-chilled-rice-pudding-with-berry-compote/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:39:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-lazy-food-edition-chilled-rice-pudding-with-berry-compote/</guid>
        <description> I’m back you fools and to celebrate let me share a story from my childhood.
When I was in elementary school, our teacher used to teach us different ‘life hacks’ based on science – she said. One of the most memorable things she ever said was that it’s better to drink a hot drink (hot tea) when it’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Easter egg hunting
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-easter-egg-hunting/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 16:28:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-easter-egg-hunting/</guid>
        <description> I hope you’ve enjoyed hunting for Easter chocolate eggs and that you don’t feel sorry for not letting your younger sister get more than two. Good job, by the way. But now that you are out of your sugar coma, it’s time to start wondering what you are supposed to do with all those kilos of chocolate …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Serving up Spring
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-serving-up-spring/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 16:26:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-serving-up-spring/</guid>
        <description> I was leaving college one evening after a long, dreary day huddled inside the dark warmth of ACEX (on top of some never-ending coursework), when I looked up to the sky, preparing for a deep, long sigh, as per any typical cold winter day. The sigh dissipated into thin air as the navy blue was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Spiced rack of lamb with char-grilled, smoked aubergine dip
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-spiced-rack-of-lamb-with-char-grilled-smoked-aubergine-dip/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 17:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-spiced-rack-of-lamb-with-char-grilled-smoked-aubergine-dip/</guid>
        <description> B ack home, lamb is usually cooked just as a traditional Easter dinner. Otherwise, I don’t believe we have lamb at any other point in the year. Probably, because of that I am quite reticent about cooking it – that and the fact that I hate my mom’s lamb. Mom, I love you, but you have no idea how to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kombucha Kraft
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-kombucha-kraft/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 14:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-kombucha-kraft/</guid>
        <description>I try to be healthy. Sometimes. You see, when you have to sustain a food blog full of cakes and ice creams and burgers and doughnuts, you have to find a way to balance it out. And luckily for me, the healthy food world is not limited to chomping my way through an iceberg lettuce for dinner while …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Treasures from the Levant
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-treasures-from-the-levant/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 14:02:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanjay Bhattacharya,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-treasures-from-the-levant/</guid>
        <description>To look on at the birth of a new restaurant is always exciting – I’ve been a part of it, having seen the place I worked at in Oxford rise from the ashes of a mediocre Italian cocktail bar, and realising that I really wanted to be a part of that. Teething problems ranged from gutters that drained …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Liquid Comfort
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-liquid-comfort/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 14:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-liquid-comfort/</guid>
        <description> This will start as usual, with a funny story. I wanted to write about some lamb ribs - see, I kind of have a thing with ribs, but then the subject changed to comfort food (I am stating this in case you didn’t notice already) and because East Europeans don’t do comfort foods, they do alcohol, here I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The ugly truth behind food waste
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-the-ugly-truth-behind-food-waste/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 15:57:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Kakadellis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-the-ugly-truth-behind-food-waste/</guid>
        <description> There is no way of denying it: we overproduce. Constantly. We throw. Shamelessly. We waste. Consciously. Every day, tonnes of food are thrown away simply because some food legislation has put a standardized limit ‘eat before’ date or due to surplus. Worse, because we buy more than we really need. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Life in the blogosphere #tablesituation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-life-in-the-blogosphere-tablesituation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 15:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-life-in-the-blogosphere-tablesituation/</guid>
        <description>Gosh, what a morning, I thought to myself as I landed on a lush, green, velvet chair, flushed and out of breath from an intense power walking session down Park Lane (my definition of being ‘fashionably late’). A fellow blogger sitting opposite was doing her 5th re-run on Snapchat: “…it’s too early …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ten of the best</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-ten-of-the-best/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 15:23:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-ten-of-the-best/</guid>
        <description> 1 | Dirty Bones Shoreditch Fried chicken on waffles for brunch? Definitely. Hit up Dirty Bones for their boozy brunch menu with mac ‘n’ cheese burgers, short rib crumpets and more heart attack-worthy dishes!
   Christy Lam   2 | Café Loren Looking for a homey, warming breakfast? Café Loren in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All hail the mighty Internet
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-all-hail-the-mighty-internet/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 15:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-all-hail-the-mighty-internet/</guid>
        <description>Good thing that nowadays, you are only a search away from “I want to try some Thai tonight!” or “How am I supposed to eat an artichoke?”. But sometimes the Internet does more bad than good and gives too many recommendations. I mean, how are you supposed to decide between that perfect steak and the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ballin’ on a budget #studentlyfe
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-ballin-on-a-budget-studentlyfe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 18:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shanzeh Khurshid,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-ballin-on-a-budget-studentlyfe/</guid>
        <description> Location, location, location Whilst religiously completing my daily routine of procrastination, I happened to view my friend’s, who seems to have a lot of money to spend on food, snapchat story. She always puts up gourmet looking pictures, but whenever I google the restaurants their prices are so …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hit me up, homeslice
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-hit-me-up-homeslice/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Alice Davage,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-hit-me-up-homeslice/</guid>
        <description>The hipster revolution is upon us. No food is safe. The humble burger has been embellished with a bright green avocado bun. If you haven’t tried kale or quinoa (pronounced “keen-wah”, trust me, I have been corrected multiple times), frankly, where have you been? Although the occasional twists on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bored of the classic waffle? Me too!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-bored-of-the-classic-waffle-me-too/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 16:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-bored-of-the-classic-waffle-me-too/</guid>
        <description>You should never make a comment about a restaurant before you’ve tried it.”
That was a strong lesson from a man, a total stranger, sitting at the table next to me, which ended our morning debate over the much hyped-about The Breakfast Club a few months back. For him, it was his holy grail breakfast …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Valentine’s sweets
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-valentines-sweets/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 16:21:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-valentines-sweets/</guid>
        <description> Can you smell it? Try again! I know you can, but maybe you’ve just got used to it as it’s been here for some days already: LOVE. Oh, yes, you’ve heard me right. In case you didn’t realise, Valentine’s is coming in less than a week now. And if you are alone, it’s time to worry – you cannot spend one …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Talk dirty to me | Banana Tree
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-talk-dirty-to-me-banana-tree/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 16:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Shanzeh Khurshid,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-talk-dirty-to-me-banana-tree/</guid>
        <description> Where to go On their way to the Royal Albert Hall, my friends and I caught up in Banana Tree in Bayswater. I suggested the restaurant because it’s about 30 minutes walking distance from campus, and only 20 minutes from Wilson House and Pembridge. Ever since she went on a yoga trip to Vietnam, one …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ten of the best
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-ten-of-the-best/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 17:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-ten-of-the-best/</guid>
        <description> 1 | Bleecker Burger The Bleecker Black is probably the best burger in London, with two juicy patties with a layer of black pudding in the middle.
   Christy Lam   2 | Where the Pancakes Are A cute little pancake house serving delicious, homemade pancakes at the back of a bustling food market. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All hail the sublime starch, the chieftan of cuisine, the triumphant tuber | the potato
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-all-hail-the-sublime-starch-the-chieftan-of-cuisine-the-triumphant-tuber-the-potato/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 17:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanjay Bhattacharya,Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-all-hail-the-sublime-starch-the-chieftan-of-cuisine-the-triumphant-tuber-the-potato/</guid>
        <description> The humble spud. Where to start? How many foodstuffs can compare to the tuber that brought a whole nation to its knees – and I’m not talking about the Irish potato famine, but rather the introduction of potatoes to haute cuisine. People had been searching for a starch that was affordable yet …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Want some fish in that taco?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-want-some-fish-in-that-taco/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 17:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-want-some-fish-in-that-taco/</guid>
        <description>There’s this one question I always get asked: how do I have the time to fit in lectures in the morning, project-work in the afternoon, while managing an Instagram story saturated with #bloggermail, press events and bearded baristas in tiny independent cafés in god-knows-where?
The answer is – I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Avocado for breakfast? So #2k16
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-avocado-for-breakfast-so-2k16/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 17:38:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-avocado-for-breakfast-so-2k16/</guid>
        <description>Mezze. A word meaning a selection of small appetizers. And a word that I have recently started noticing following a sharing plates trend that has finally hit the London food scene. After some hearty meals, I have adjusted my taste buds (and stomach) to this wonderful dining culture home to Turkey, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Melanzane alla Parmigiana
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-melanzane-alla-parmigiana/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-melanzane-alla-parmigiana/</guid>
        <description>I still can remember my editor’s voice, before Christmas, saying that I might want to try writing more meaty recipes: quick and easy, student friendly meat dishes. I can even see him smiling while he reads this (maybe I should say “Hello!”) but well, this is another meat-free edition. But I have an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Aubergines and their many uses
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-aubergines-and-their-many-uses/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:44:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-aubergines-and-their-many-uses/</guid>
        <description>Yes, the aubergine – delicious in dips, smokey and rich, and yet equally at home in a spicy, lip-smacking curry, the aubergine is a vehicle for flavour without compare. I think my love affair began when I would take home small scoops of baba ghanouj, a levantine dip of smoked, roasted aubergine, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An immaculate conception?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-an-immaculate-conception/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-an-immaculate-conception/</guid>
        <description>Best friend in town? You just have to take them to one of the best restaurants in town and order three times your normal portion of food – and roll out of the restaurant with a six-month food baby hoping to ‘walk’ it off with a tube journey to the next.
So when my friend came down to London all the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Basic food for basic students (you’re basic)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-basic-food-for-basic-students-youre-basic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-basic-food-for-basic-students-youre-basic/</guid>
        <description>For many of us, it’s revision week time! Yay!! Can you feel the enthusiasm? I can feel it all around campus – especially in the library late at night or when I see some girl crying in the bathroom; I’m not saying that men do not cry in the bathroom, but I for one cannot see them – the perks of using …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Breakfast, Hong Kong style
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-breakfast-hong-kong-style/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-breakfast-hong-kong-style/</guid>
        <description>Plonk.
It was the sound of a quarter-inch thick china cup hitting the glass-topped wooden table, as my milk tea lands before me just three seconds after the waiter took my order.
My mind snapped out from my fuzzy morning daydream of fluffy bunnies jumping over lush green grass back into full …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to build Hogwarts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-how-to-build-hogwarts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 16:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-how-to-build-hogwarts/</guid>
        <description> 2009 | The first gingerbread We weren’t ambitious. We built a cute little gingerbread house. It only took one batch of gingerbread and a few sweets for decoration, and it disappeared remarkably quickly. How things were to change!
2010 | The castle This took two whole batches of gingerbread. We …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>EU Xmas
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-eu-xmas/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 15:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-eu-xmas/</guid>
        <description>It’s time to get ready for the Christmas dinner – if you already had it, well, it’s never too late to have a second or third one. I mean, it’s Christmas – you can celebrate it as many times as you want. And now that you are a student, time to try something different. I’m not saying that the food …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AA Gill is away
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-aa-gill-is-away/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 15:55:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-aa-gill-is-away/</guid>
        <description>The journalist AA Gill, The Sunday Times food (and occasionally TV) critic, died last week, only three weeks after writing about his cancer diagnosis in his weekly column.
He broke the news with the kind sumptuousness of words he used in his criticisms; writing “there is barely a morsel of offal …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2016 | a #food round up
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-2016-a-food-round-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 15:49:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-2016-a-food-round-up/</guid>
        <description> Number 1. Green Tea. You know that green tea has finally taken over the land of boring English Breakfast when even Starbucks has added a green tea latte to their permanent menu. Green tea has always been a popular drink in Asia for its many health benefits. Not only is it your best coffee …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lunch box edition
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-lunch-box-edition/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 11:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-lunch-box-edition/</guid>
        <description>Lunch at somewhere outside of university is ‘the thing’ nowadays, but who has time for that with all the lab reports and homework and tutorial sheets and so on? Besides the money it saves, eating in school seems to be a pretty good idea, especially if you have to stay in pretty late: socialising …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
