<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jh308/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jh308/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>iCU Cinema All-Nighter – Tuesday 13 December
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-13-icu-cinema-all-nighter-tuesday-13-december/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2011 14:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jade Hoffman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-13-icu-cinema-all-nighter-tuesday-13-december/</guid>
        <description>It’s that time of year again, when it is so brutally cold outside that finding a good night out where it’s socially acceptable to stay wrapped up in blankets is the stuff of dreams. Fortunately, it is also the time when iCU Cinema brings us the Winter All-Nighter – the first all-nighter of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How long is too long for a sequel?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-how-long-is-too-long-for-a-sequel/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 20:10:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jade Hoffman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-how-long-is-too-long-for-a-sequel/</guid>
        <description>After the release of West is West last Friday was greeted by mostly tepid reviews, it may be disappointing – yet not all that surprising – that the sequel to 1999’s critically acclaimed East is East fell so flat. It’s been 12 years since the low-budget East is East stormed British cinema with its …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cage loses his shit... in 3D
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-cage-loses-his-shit-in-3d/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 21:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark Bruggemann,Jade Hoffman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-cage-loses-his-shit-in-3d/</guid>
        <description>When a film uses the suffix of “3D” in its title, it comes with several expectations. Not only does this generally promise an excessive, gratuitous use of 3D, but it also often means that the film will be entirely ludicrous from start to finish Enter Nicolas Cage in Drive Angry 3D. This film not …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>And the winner is... The Last Airbender!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-and-the-winner-is-the-last-airbender/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 19:09:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jade Hoffman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-and-the-winner-is-the-last-airbender/</guid>
        <description>Los Angeles this weekend was buzzing even more than usual with the awards ceremony seeing the great minds behind Sex and the City 2 and M. Night Shyamalan’s The Last Airbender scooping most of the major prizes. At the 2011 Razzies.
This annual Hollywood event is now in its 31st year and serves as a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can the BAFTAs be a good prediction for the Oscars?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-can-the-baftas-be-a-good-prediction-for-the-oscars/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 19:27:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jade Hoffman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-can-the-baftas-be-a-good-prediction-for-the-oscars/</guid>
        <description>Despite the rain on February 13th, Leicester Square was once again a buzzing night of flashbulbs and red carpet walks as it played host to the 63rd annual BAFTA awards. A semi-reliable predictor of which way the Oscars might swing, the BAFTAs has becoming an increasingly high profile event in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Classic Cinema
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-classic-cinema/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 20:50:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jade Hoffman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-classic-cinema/</guid>
        <description>With Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day approaching, I realise that it&amp;rsquo;s pretty pessimistic to be reviewing Kramer vs. Kramer – a milestone of a film that discussed the then-rare topic of divorce in frank, almost brutal honesty. Nevertheless, Kramer vs. Kramer was a hit at the Oscars in the late 70s and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why are we still accepting bad films?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-why-are-we-still-accepting-bad-films/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 19:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jade Hoffman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-why-are-we-still-accepting-bad-films/</guid>
        <description>Awards season is here, and whether you take an interest or not, it generally means the time of year when the cinemas are packed with impressive, intelligent films. Though a few of the leading films in this year’s nominees, such as The Social Network or Toy Story 3 were out a few months ago, the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Classic Cinema
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-classic-cinema/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 20:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jade Hoffman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-classic-cinema/</guid>
        <description>Considering its release in 1993, it may be a little pre-emptive to call Jurassic Park a classic film, but after almost twenty years of being referenced and spoofed countless times in hundreds of other films and television shows, I’m going to call it. From Spaced’s take on Muldoon’s “clever girl…” …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The next move for iCU Cinema
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-the-next-move-for-icu-cinema/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 20:22:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jade Hoffman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-the-next-move-for-icu-cinema/</guid>
        <description>Over this term, we have been following the relaunch of iCU Cinema and celebrating its successes – from its sold-out opening night with Inception to its recent screening of comic-book gold Scott Pilgrim vs. The World – as it brings blockbuster films back to the comfort of the Union.
But now iCU …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Casting a new light on the Western diet
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-casting-a-new-light-on-the-western-diet/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 20:46:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jade Hoffman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-casting-a-new-light-on-the-western-diet/</guid>
        <description>Directors Shelly Lee Davies and Or Shlomi are new to filmmaking. In an after-screening Q&amp;amp;A they revealed that this endeavour was one which they carried out largely alone and with what appeared to be little past experience; suffice it to say that it did show. Although the content of this film …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A return to form for iCU Cinema
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-a-return-to-form-for-icu-cinema/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 19:18:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jade Hoffman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-a-return-to-form-for-icu-cinema/</guid>
        <description>It’s easy to underestimate the scope for fun at Imperial – other universities probably had fully operational bars during Fresher’s Week and students camping out for days or even weeks in the library are not uncommon. With this in mind, when you hear about Imperial College’s Cinema, you may very well …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
