<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/dyo10/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/dyo10/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Festival Preview: Unknown Festival - Croatia
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-8-9-festival-preview-unknown-festival-croatia/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 19:48:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Daniel Oppenheimer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-8-9-festival-preview-unknown-festival-croatia/</guid>
        <description>Over the last few years Croatia’s coast on the Adriatic has become the go-to spot for electronic music festivals. This year the organisers of Field day, Warehouse Project and Hideout are bringing a fresh party to the region, Unknown.
The festival promises a line up that’s guaranteed to deliver. Live …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can you keep a secret?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-can-you-keep-a-secret/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 11:31:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Daniel Oppenheimer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-can-you-keep-a-secret/</guid>
        <description>Secret Garden Party is an unconventional festival, slicker or slacker than your average depending on preference. While the music policy is slightly questionable, it’s difficult to not be drawn in by the festival’s Wonderland-like aesthetic.
Set around a lake in the Cambridgeshire countryside, the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Beautiful Benicàssim
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-16-beautiful-benicssim/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2011 15:08:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Daniel Oppenheimer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-16-beautiful-benicssim/</guid>
        <description>Rototom Sunsplash is one of the largest and longest running Reggae, Dance Hall and Dub festivals in Europe. In fitting with the music it endorses, its appeal spans a cross-section of festival goers from the ignorant non-connoisseur to the dub-geek-stoner. The recipe is very simple: an entirely laid …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Outlook Festival returns
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-16-outlook-festival-returns/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2011 15:04:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Daniel Oppenheimer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-16-outlook-festival-returns/</guid>
        <description>Accounts of the first instalment of Outlook Festival four years back (held in a Croatian night club with relatively low attendance and a lot of rain) sound like Phoenix Nights on the Adriatic. Since then the event has come a long way.
This year saw close to 12,000 festival-goers; some of the biggest …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Continent of Hope
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-the-continent-of-hope/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 20:21:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Daniel Oppenheimer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-the-continent-of-hope/</guid>
        <description>[photo id=16]
“Yeah, these guys were proper jokers!” The Physics fresher smiles nostalgically as he leafs through a stack of photographs, taken during his travels last year. He recounts the journey that took him across Latin America, the places he visited and the people he met.
In Cuba, he shifted …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wild Balkan jungle
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-wild-balkan-jungle/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 05:41:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Daniel Oppenheimer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-wild-balkan-jungle/</guid>
        <description>The idea behind Outlook Festival is straightforward: a large number of people; an 18th century fort; a strictly UK-Jamaican bass and dub sound; beach parties; boat parties and, if you need it, a coach named “The Sunshine Bus” to get you from England to Croatia.
The festival, surely the best way of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An interview with Micah P Hinson
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-an-interview-with-micah-p-hinson/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 20:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Daniel Oppenheimer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-an-interview-with-micah-p-hinson/</guid>
        <description>Micah P Hinson’s music combines lyrical wisdom beyond his twenty-nine or so years with the kind of deep, reassuring voice your dad might use to read bedtime stories to you in. Hailing from Abilene, Texas he is often introduced as ‘the guy who dated the Vogue model and went to prison for forging …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
