<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/shivani_gangadia/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/shivani_gangadia/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>South Africa, France, Dance: An Unexpected Trio</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-south-africa-unexpected-trio/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-south-africa-unexpected-trio/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
Pioneering South African choreographer and dance, Maqoma created “Cion: Requiem of Ravel’s Boléro” a few years ago, imaginatively setting his story inspired by South African literature against the music of Ravel’s famed orchestral piece, Boléro. Maqoma founded Vuyani Dance Theatre in 1999 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Glass. Kill. Bluebeard. Imp.</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-glass-kill-bluebeard-imp/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-glass-kill-bluebeard-imp/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
As the title implies, this performance was comprised of four different plays, each increasing in length – the final play, ‘Imp’, was one hour long. ‘Glass’ tells the story of a girl made of glass, discussing important themes of abuse. However, this aspect didn’t seem to quite fit in as I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Love and Loss, Music and Mourning</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-love-loss-music-mourning/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-love-loss-music-mourning/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
This Autumn, the English National Opera is presenting an “Orpheus” series with four operas from different historical periods that retell the myth. The first of these comes from the mid-eighteenth century: ‘Orfeo ed Euridice’, by Gluck. It is of particular importance in the history of music …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Manon</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-manon/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-manon/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
Manon, based on the 1731 novel L’histoire du chevalier des Grieux et de Manon Lescaut by Abbé Prévost, was reimagined by Kenneth Macmillan in 1974 as a ballet and remains a captivating story to this day. It tells the tale of Manon who, though in love with Des Grieux, agrees to be mistress …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Class</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-class/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-class/</guid>
        <description>What begins as a simple parent-teacher meeting between recently separated Brian (Stephen Jones) and Donna (Sarah Morris), and teacher Mr McAfferty (Will O’Connell), to talk about their son Jayden’s literacy struggles in school, spirals quickly as tension bubbles about social and cultural divides …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Out of Water</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-out-of-water/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-out-of-water/</guid>
        <description>Orange Tree Theatre, once again, has a stunning new production running. This touching play, written by the remarkable Zoe Cooper, spans themes of gender identity, sexuality, new environments, and hardship. A delicately written script, along with circular staging and a trio of talented performers, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Twelfth Night</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-twelfth-night/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-twelfth-night/</guid>
        <description>Theatre company OVO whisks us through this outrageously funny play in just over 90 minutes, complete with a live jazz band and pop tunes by the likes of Rihanna, Radiohead, Britney Spears, and more. It might have seemed a little fast for Shakespeare, but I personally loved the pace, and they kept a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Funeral Flowers: part play, part poetry, all authentic</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-funeral-flowers-part-play-part-poetry-all-authentic/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-funeral-flowers-part-play-part-poetry-all-authentic/</guid>
        <description>Funeral Flowers, both written and performed by Emma Dennis Edwards, is about 17-year-old Angelique, aspiring florist trying to withstand the hardships in her life that repeatedly try to destroy her resolve time and time again. With a powerful protagonist accompanying an equally powerful script of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Vessel</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-vessel/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-vessel/</guid>
        <description>Vessel traverses a very fine line between “what the hell am I watching?” and “I can’t stop watching”. Eerie music and near humanly impossible contortions of the human body make this both the weirdest and most captivating thing I’ve ever witnessed on stage – I simply couldn’t take my eyes off it. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Medea</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-28-medea/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-28-medea/</guid>
        <description>This contemporary adaption of Euripides’ classic, performed by Internationaal Theater Amsterdam, merges the well-known tale of Medea with the modern-day case of Deborah Green, a woman still in prison to this day for poisoning her husband and murdering her children in 1979 after discovering his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jesus Hopped the ‘A’ Train</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-jesus-hopped-the-a-train/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-jesus-hopped-the-a-train/</guid>
        <description>Set in the high security wing of Rikers Island, Jesus Hopped the ‘A’ Train boldly contrasts the stories of two inmates and the circumstances that led them there. On one hand, we have new prisoner Angel Cruz, played by Ukweli Roach, who shot a religious cult leader “in the ass” for brainwashing his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tartuffe: The Imposter</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-tartuffe-the-imposter/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-tartuffe-the-imposter/</guid>
        <description>Popular and well-received by the public when it first showed in 1664, but quickly banned due to the backlash from religious groups for the portrayal of someone outwardly pious but truly a sort of lecherous con artist, Tartuffe was a masterpiece of satire on the sham of religion and its trickster …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rattled: A spotlight on postnatal mental health</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-rattled-a-spotlight-on-postnatal-mental-health/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-rattled-a-spotlight-on-postnatal-mental-health/</guid>
        <description>Rattled is Missmanaged Theatre’s debut production, both written and performed by the multitalented Rachel Harper. She bravely uses her platform to raise awareness of mental health problems in new mothers, half of whom are said to experience it in their lives. This play is an eye-opening statement on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cougar at the Orange Tree Theatre</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-cougar-at-the-orange-tree-theatre/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-cougar-at-the-orange-tree-theatre/</guid>
        <description>The title of Rose Lewenstein’s play is not vague in any way – it triggers a very obvious association with the image of an older woman, presumably in her forties, seducing a younger man into an illicit sexual relationship. Leila, (Charlotte Randle), is a superficially powerful woman leading the way …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Obscure Shakespeare receives a fun new revival</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-obscure-shakespeare-receives-a-fun-new-revival/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-obscure-shakespeare-receives-a-fun-new-revival/</guid>
        <description>The comedy centres around the lascivious Sir John Falstaff, known to many from Shakespeare’s Henry IV plays – The Merry Wives of Windsor is said to have been commissioned by Elizabeth I herself, who must have felt her beloved Falstaff deserving of his own story. This play uses this fact as a means …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Courtauld Impressionists: From Manet to Cézanne</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-courtauld-impressionists-from-manet-to-c-zanne/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-courtauld-impressionists-from-manet-to-c-zanne/</guid>
        <description>Born and brought up in London, repeatedly visiting this gallery with my father since before I could even walk, it’s safe to say I’m a hardcore National Gallery devotee. Unfortunately, this is precisely the same reason this exhibition left me feeling a sense of unfamiliar disappointment as I left the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Courtauld Impressionists: From Manet to Cézanne</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-14-courtauld-impressionists-from-manet-to-c-zanne/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-14-courtauld-impressionists-from-manet-to-c-zanne/</guid>
        <description>Born and brought up in London, repeatedly visiting this gallery with my father since before I could even walk, it’s safe to say I’m a hardcore National Gallery devotee. Unfortunately, this is precisely the same reason this exhibition left me feeling a sense of unfamiliar disappointment as I left the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jeannie: An Enchanting Revival</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-jeannie-an-enchanting-revival/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-jeannie-an-enchanting-revival/</guid>
        <description>A long-overdue journey into the repertoire of an overlooked female playwright, this is (shockingly) the first professional production of Jeannie in nearly 80 years. Within two hours we are taken on a whirlwind journey with protagonist Jeannie, who, upon receiving a generous inheritance following the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Life in the Dark: a momentary escape from the hustle and bustle of London </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-life-in-the-dark-a-momentary-escape-from-the-hustle-and-bustle-of-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-life-in-the-dark-a-momentary-escape-from-the-hustle-and-bustle-of-london/</guid>
        <description>Enter a subterranean pitch-black cave, or even the vast deep-sea of the ocean in this new Natural History Museum exhibition, which introduces us to the astonishing lives of the elusive animals that exist in these seemingly uninhabitable environments. Divided into three main parts entitled “Life at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Walk Swiftly and With Purpose: a debut to remember</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-walk-swiftly-and-with-purpose-a-debut-to-remember/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-walk-swiftly-and-with-purpose-a-debut-to-remember/</guid>
        <description>Three Sisters’ production company, brainchild of Siofra, Grainne, and Cara Dromgoole, immediately throws us into the world of a group of schoolgirls on the cusp of adulthood. Eve, Lana, Robbie, and Misha, despite the deep and powerful themes they explore together, ultimately represent the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A whole Lotto praise for this lesser-known Renaissance genius</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-a-whole-lotto-praise-for-this-lesser-known-renaissance-genius/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-a-whole-lotto-praise-for-this-lesser-known-renaissance-genius/</guid>
        <description>This exhibition takes you through Lotto’s entire career, chronologically showcasing his development and growth as an artist, from early experimentation to later existential reflection, and constant mastery of human emotion. He demonstrates a psychological depth that later found more relevance during …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All We Ever Wanted Was Everything: a fabulously fresh take on ‘gig theatre’</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-all-we-ever-wanted-was-everything-a-fabulously-fresh-take-on-gig-theatre/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shivani Gangadia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-all-we-ever-wanted-was-everything-a-fabulously-fresh-take-on-gig-theatre/</guid>
        <description>Beginning at 10-years old in the 90s against a backdrop of Harry Potter and Britpop, and finally ending amidst the more topical political chaos of 2017, All We Ever Wanted Was Everything elegantly weaves together themes of generational rifts, failing to meet our aspirations, and being doomed to …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
