<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/vaishnavignanana/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/vaishnavignanana/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Pieces Put Together</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-21-pieces-put-together/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-21-pieces-put-together/</guid>
        <description>BAC Beatbox Academy’s ‘Frankenstein: How to make a Monster’ returns to the Battersea Arts Centre for a 3-week run, following their win of an Off-West End award last year. Billed as a retelling of Mary Shelley’s classic this production is something of a misnomer: it draws on the themes of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Age really is just a number</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-03-age-really-is-just-a-number/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-03-age-really-is-just-a-number/</guid>
        <description>VAULT has returned for its 7th year under the arches at Waterloo, bringing with it a mishmash of exciting new theatre. London’s answer to Edinburgh Fringe features many shows that have come down from Edinburgh, ready to take on a new audience. Violet is one such play.
A tale of loneliness and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ambitious panto drama lack focus</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-ambitious-panto-drama-lack-focus/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-ambitious-panto-drama-lack-focus/</guid>
        <description>Aging pantomime performer Ronal Roy Humphrey returns to his dressing room, still dressed in bright dress and impressive wig. He’s as loud and as flamboyant as you would expect from a panto star. But there’s more beneath the surface for Roy. Faced with aging and the inevitable changes facing his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Curious Incident: A Triumphant Return to London</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-the-curious-incident-a-triumphant-return-to-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-the-curious-incident-a-triumphant-return-to-london/</guid>
        <description>Adapted from Mark Haddon’s book of the same name, this The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-time tells the story of Christopher Boone, a 15-year-old who is exceptionally gifted at maths yet struggles with social interactions and many every day tasks. Christopher finds his neighbour’s dog, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Caroline or Change Review</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-07-caroline-or-change-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-07-caroline-or-change-review/</guid>
        <description>Caroline Thibodeaux is only 39, but her life is already reduced to the basement of the Gellman household in which she is a maid, where the washing machine, dryer and old radio are her only companions. Well, apart from eight-year-old Noah Gellman that is. Noah idolises Caroline, taking every …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Carmen </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-14-carmen/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-14-carmen/</guid>
        <description>Don Jose, a young soldier on duty in Seville is seduced by the free-spirited Carmen as she attempts to escape being taken to prison. This marks the beginning of a tumultuous relationship between the two, driven by Carmen’s stubborn personality and Jose’s wild possessiveness. When it premiered in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dealing With Clair: psychological horror for the present</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-dealing-with-clair-psychological-horror-for-the-present/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-dealing-with-clair-psychological-horror-for-the-present/</guid>
        <description>Estate agent Clair is helping Mike and Liz, a young couple in London, sell their house. They claim they want to act “honourably” and take the first offer to meet their asking price, yet it soon becomes clear that money is too much of a temptation and they are willing to go to whatever lengths to get …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mrs Dalloway Brought to the Stage</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-mrs-dalloway-brought-to-the-stage/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-mrs-dalloway-brought-to-the-stage/</guid>
        <description>This adaptation of Virginia Woolf’s 1925 novel is clearly a labour of love, and an ambitious one at that. Mrs Dalloway is one of Woolf’s best-known works, and arguably one of her best. In 1920s London, Clarissa Dalloway prepares to host a party for her wealthy friends. On the same day, First World …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ashes to Ashes, Dust to Dust</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-ashes-to-ashes-dust-to-dust/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-ashes-to-ashes-dust-to-dust/</guid>
        <description>Her sadness has become unbearable, so Alice decides to end it. She takes her own life. But this isn’t where her story ends. We encounter Alice on the morgue slab, in her first moments of ‘death’ as she realises she is still here, a ghost, watching her body and the people she has left behind. This is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Definitive Guide to Autumn in the Capital</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-the-definitive-guide-to-autumn-in-the-capital/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Helen Money-Kyrle,Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-the-definitive-guide-to-autumn-in-the-capital/</guid>
        <description>Now until 7 October 2018
Frieze London and Frieze Masters art fairs in Regents Park.
Now until 13 October 2018
The Globe is still running open air performances; with £5 standing tickets it’s not to be missed!
Now until December 2018
Caledonian Express at the Pleasance – the best shows of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Arts guide to theatre on a student budget!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-20-felix-arts-guide-to-theatre-on-a-student-budget/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-20-felix-arts-guide-to-theatre-on-a-student-budget/</guid>
        <description>Mousetrap Theatre Projects
This charity is dedicated to making theatre accessible for disadvantaged children, including those with special needs or a sensory disability. However, they also run some amazing schemes for young people, giving access to affordable tickets to major West End plays. Their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A night of wicked cabaret takes us back in time</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-a-night-of-wicked-cabaret-takes-us-back-in-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-a-night-of-wicked-cabaret-takes-us-back-in-time/</guid>
        <description>This new collaboration between the English National Opera and Gate Theatre brings together a collection of songs from Weimar era Germany, banned by the Nazis for being ‘un-German’. The title itself is taken from a Nazi document produced for propagandist Hans Ziegler’s 1938 exhibition of these banned …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>America, vodka, and me: Tori Scott’s raucous cabaret comes to London’s Vault Festival </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-america-vodka-and-me-tori-scott-s-raucous-cabaret-comes-to-london-s-vault-festival/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-america-vodka-and-me-tori-scott-s-raucous-cabaret-comes-to-london-s-vault-festival/</guid>
        <description>Hailed by Provincetown Magazine as the “Bette Midler of the new millenium”,Texan-born singer Tori Scott is renowned for her confessional, raucous acts. Normally based at Joe’s Pub, an affiliate of New York’s Public Theatre, Scott came to London earlier this year to perform Thirsty at the Vault …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A powerful revival of the mystery of Hanging Rock</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-a-powerful-revival-of-the-mystery-of-hanging-rock/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-a-powerful-revival-of-the-mystery-of-hanging-rock/</guid>
        <description>On Valentine’s Day, 1900, three pupils and a teacher from Appleyard College, an upper-class girls’ boarding school, disappear during a class trip to Hanging Rock, a volcanic mountain in Victoria, Australia. This is the premise of Joan Lindsay’s 1967 novel and Peter Weir’s subsequent film adaptation, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Love, Life, and Cocaine on an Irish Rooftop</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-love-life-and-cocaine-on-an-irish-rooftop/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-love-life-and-cocaine-on-an-irish-rooftop/</guid>
        <description>Casey and Mikey are stuck on a rooftop, waiting for the cops to drive away – they’ve just robbed a petrol station and a house- Casey’s house to be precise. It is on this roof that they’ve found themselves cornered by the police. It’s not all bad though: their robbery has been somewhat successful – …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FemSoc tackle sexual violence</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-femsoc-tackle-sexual-violence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-femsoc-tackle-sexual-violence/</guid>
        <description>1 in 5 women aged 16 - 59 has experienced some form of sexual violence since the age of 16.
It’s finally gaining attention in the news, but what can we, as students, do to make a difference? Join IC FemSoc and share your ideas, whether it’s ways of raising awareness, changing policy, or practical …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dance and acrobatics save the plot in this immersive Underworld</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-dance-and-acrobatics-save-the-plot-in-this-immersive-underworld/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-dance-and-acrobatics-save-the-plot-in-this-immersive-underworld/</guid>
        <description>Becoming Shades is one of several shows headlining VAULT Festival 2018. Billed as London’s answer to Edinburgh Fringe this festival showcases performances from new and emerging artists and is a veritable hotbed of alternative theatre. From 24th January to 18th March it takes over the labyrinth of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pinocchio ends up a little wooden…</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-pinocchio-ends-up-a-little-wooden/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-pinocchio-ends-up-a-little-wooden/</guid>
        <description>The National Theatre’s winter production of Pinocchio is based on the 1940 Disney film, including songs from the original. Broadly following the original, it adds in some minor changes: Gepetto, the old and lonely puppet maker, longs for a child of his own even as he creates puppets for other …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Twilight Zone – between fact and fiction</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-the-twilight-zone-between-fact-and-fiction/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-the-twilight-zone-between-fact-and-fiction/</guid>
        <description>Between light and shadow, science and superstition, fear and knowledge is a dimension of imagination. An area we call the Twilight Zone.”
Amidst all the Christmas shows and pantomimes filling theatres in December, the Almeida Theatre takes on this brave adaptation of the early 1960s American sci-fi …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Antony and Cleopatra review — Antony Byrne and Josette Simon have fantastic chemistry in Royal Shakespeare Company staging</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-15-antony-and-cleopatra-review-antony-byrne-and-josette-simon-have-fantastic-chemistry-in-royal-shakespeare-company-staging/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-15-antony-and-cleopatra-review-antony-byrne-and-josette-simon-have-fantastic-chemistry-in-royal-shakespeare-company-staging/</guid>
        <description>This production of Antony and Cleopatra forms part of the Royal Shakespeare Company’s Rome MMXVII season and is one of four plays being performed at the Barbican Centre this winter. It continues the story told in Julius Caesar—also being performed at the Barbican this season —Octavius Caesar, Mark …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All the Little Lights: A Story That Needs Telling</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-all-the-little-lights-a-story-that-needs-telling/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-all-the-little-lights-a-story-that-needs-telling/</guid>
        <description>Jane Upton’s All the Little Lights looks at the world of child sexual exploitation from the perspective of the young girls who are most often its victims. It allows you to see the seemingly obvious factors at play in their lives – poverty, isolation, peer pressure – that make them vulnerable to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Angel enthrals at Arcola Theatre after Fringe success</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-angel-enthrals-at-arcola-theatre-after-fringe-success/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-angel-enthrals-at-arcola-theatre-after-fringe-success/</guid>
        <description>In London it takes something special to be a stand-out venue. The Arcola is just that: committed to diversity and accessibility, they stage performances of new and exciting plays, often fresh from festivals like Edinburgh Fringe. Its commitment to diversity and equality is reflected in its …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Anatomy of a Suicide | Alice Birch weaves a story of three women bound together by mental illness
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-15-anatomy-of-a-suicide-alice-birch-weaves-a-story-of-three-women-bound-together-by-mental-illness/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 15:32:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-15-anatomy-of-a-suicide-alice-birch-weaves-a-story-of-three-women-bound-together-by-mental-illness/</guid>
        <description>Anatomy of a Suicide follows the stories of three generations of women of the same family, linked together not only by their genetic heritage, but also by the same emotions and struggles as they battle with mental illness. Carol is a 1970s housewife, struggling to find reasons to stay in the world. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Woyzeck at the Old Vic | Strong performances can&#39;t save an overblown adaptation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-31-woyzeck-at-the-old-vic-strong-performances-cant-save-an-overblown-adaptation/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 23:31:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-31-woyzeck-at-the-old-vic-strong-performances-cant-save-an-overblown-adaptation/</guid>
        <description>Woyzeck at the Old Vic is a retelling of a play left unfinished by playwright George Büchner at the time of his death in 1837. In this version, the setting is moved to Berlin in 1981, before the fall of the Berlin Wall. The titular character, Frank Woyzeck, is a young British soldier stationed in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Levelling shows off the best of British cinema
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-4-the-levelling-shows-off-the-best-of-british-cinema/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 08:29:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-4-the-levelling-shows-off-the-best-of-british-cinema/</guid>
        <description>Director Hope Dickson Leach’s latest film The Levelling follows Clover (Ellie Kendrick), who is forced to return to her family farm in Somerset following the sudden death of her brother, Harry. However, when she arrives, she finds out her brother actually shot himself: her father Aubrey (David …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who&#39;s Gonna Love Me Now? An intimate look at an Israeli man&#39;s search for belonging
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-4-27-whos-gonna-love-me-now-an-intimate-look-at-an-israeli-mans-search-for-belonging/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 15:37:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-4-27-whos-gonna-love-me-now-an-intimate-look-at-an-israeli-mans-search-for-belonging/</guid>
        <description>Who’s Gonna Love Me Now is a touching documentary which follows the story of Saar Maoz, a 40-year-old Israeli man living in London. Maoz is a proud member of the London Gay Men’s Chorus, which has been a source of support and love through a difficult time in his life. The bulk of the documentary, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ugly Lies the Bone | VR therapy and emotional trauma
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-ugly-lies-the-bone-vr-therapy-and-emotional-trauma/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 13:43:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-ugly-lies-the-bone-vr-therapy-and-emotional-trauma/</guid>
        <description>Ugly Lies the Bone follows the story of Jess, a young woman returning home following 3 tours in Afghanistan, which have left her with severe burns after an IED. Struggling to fit back into her old life in her declining Florida home town, and struggling to cope with her disability and chronic pain, …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
