<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/maria_portela/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/maria_portela/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The Watsons: Jane Austen Spin-off Fiction Fan Club</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-18-10-watsons-jane-austen-spin-off-fiction-fan-club/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maria Portela,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-18-10-watsons-jane-austen-spin-off-fiction-fan-club/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
Laura Wade set herself up for a difficult task: to finish, as a play, a novel that Jane Austen couldn’t complete. It follows the story of Emma Watson, a young woman used to a luxurious lifestyle, who finds herself dumped back home, and financially dependent on her family. Several suitors …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Me too in Mount Olympus</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-me-too-mount-olympus/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maria Portela,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-me-too-mount-olympus/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
Jacques Offenbach composed his world-famous operetta Orphée aux enfers in late 19th century France, satirizing the society of his time, the ruling classes and their vices. Now, in the second opera of this season’s ENO’s Orpheus Series, director Emma Rice adapts this comic masterpiece to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Midsummer night’s dream</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-a-midsummer-night-s-dream/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maria Portela,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-a-midsummer-night-s-dream/</guid>
        <description>There is no line between audience and stage at The Bridge. Or rather, there are multiple lines, but they are constantly changing, with raising platforms, movable staircases and rolling beds; the actors jumping to the middle of the crowd or shouldering an unsuspecting audience member. The action …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dark, sinister, liberal America</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-27-dark-sinister-liberal-america/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maria Portela,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-27-dark-sinister-liberal-america/</guid>
        <description>Shipwreck is set in 2017, in the early times of Trump’s America. Seven New Yorkers spend their weekend in a newly restored farmhouse upstate, rendered foodless and boozeless by a snowstorm. With nothing better to do, they spend all their time in lengthy considerations about politics, obsessing about …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Crime and Punishment: Czech Edition</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-crime-and-punishment-czech-edition/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maria Portela,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-crime-and-punishment-czech-edition/</guid>
        <description>Katya Kabanova could be one of those plots we have heard a million times: a woman avoids immorality, succumbs anyway and punishes herself for her actions. Unhappy marriage, controlling mother-in-law, lover with family issues, friend who nudges her into temptation. What is unusual about this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nerone and Poppea - Falling for the Villains</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-nerone-and-poppea-falling-for-the-villains/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maria Portela,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-nerone-and-poppea-falling-for-the-villains/</guid>
        <description>FORTUNE and VIRTUE: There is no human nor divine heart that may dare to contend with Love.
LOVE: Today in a single contest both of you, overthrown by me, will admit that the world acts on my commands. (Prologue)
Opera Profile
Name L’incoronazione di Poppea
Translation Poppea’s coronation
Composer …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Counting Sheep: Join the Revolution!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-counting-sheep-join-the-revolution/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maria Portela,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-counting-sheep-join-the-revolution/</guid>
        <description>Mark and Marichka Marczyk, creators and writers of Counting Sheep, met and fell in love in the barricades in Maidan Square while fighting for life and freedom. The show is directed by Natalia Kaliada and Nicolai Khalezin, political refugees due to their illegal theatre company, the Belarus Free …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A hilarious ode to the UK we know (not so) well</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-a-hilarious-ode-to-the-uk-we-know-not-so-well/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maria Portela,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-a-hilarious-ode-to-the-uk-we-know-not-so-well/</guid>
        <description>Abdul waits during the entire show, perching in the top of a ladder and having nightmares about his wife who is trapped back in Syria. Debby stands for almost half an hour, strapped to a spider’s web with a pig-masked guard always by her side, a theatrical version of her days in the modern slavery …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Improbable fiction upon a stage</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-improbable-fiction-upon-a-stage/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maria Portela,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-improbable-fiction-upon-a-stage/</guid>
        <description>The charming ambience of Southwark Playhouse greets us with a charismatic mixture of bar, flexible theatre space and creativity hub. It is clear that this venue wants to break convention. Getting access to the performance room means exchanging a ticket for a wristband, gliding past a rainbow of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Simon Boccanegra </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-simon-boccanegra/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maria Portela,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-simon-boccanegra/</guid>
        <description>This season’s first performance of Simon Boccanegra was dedicated to the memory of Montserrat Caballé, the famous opera singer in the bel canto tradition. If the melodic, legato lines of Verdi’s arias are a meaningful tribute to this diva’s style of singing, none of the cast could quite compare to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A hell of a show</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-a-hell-of-a-show/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maria Portela,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-a-hell-of-a-show/</guid>
        <description>The room at Jermyn Street Theatre immediately transports the audience one hundred years back in time. Shelves crammed with tools and ancient military accessories, flags, photographs, a big trunk, a comfortable-looking armchair, an upright piano and the ever-present bottles of brandy give life to the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wildlife photography for all levels of expertise</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-wildlife-photography-for-all-levels-of-expertise/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maria Portela,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-wildlife-photography-for-all-levels-of-expertise/</guid>
        <description>Nature photographers from all over the world submitted their works to the Wildlife Photographer of the Year contest. From these, a jury of photojournalists, biologists and editors chose the best shots across seventeen categories, now on display. The result is a breathtaking exhibition with the power …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
