<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Theatre on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/tags/theatre/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Theatre on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/tags/theatre/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Dance and acrobatics save the plot in this immersive Underworld</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-dance-and-acrobatics-save-the-plot-in-this-immersive-underworld/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-dance-and-acrobatics-save-the-plot-in-this-immersive-underworld/</guid>
        <description>Becoming Shades is one of several shows headlining VAULT Festival 2018. Billed as London’s answer to Edinburgh Fringe this festival showcases performances from new and emerging artists and is a veritable hotbed of alternative theatre. From 24th January to 18th March it takes over the labyrinth of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ISIS, 4Chan, and WhatsApp: Theatre for the Lulz</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-isis-4chan-and-whatsapp-theatre-for-the-lulz/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adam Gellatly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-isis-4chan-and-whatsapp-theatre-for-the-lulz/</guid>
        <description>The Believers Are But Brothers opens at the Bush Theatre, after an award-winning run at the Edinburgh Fringe in 2017. It tells the stories of three young men who, through their encounters online, become exposed to and enveloped by the murky waters of extremism. Two of the stories follow young …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>If you could live a beautiful dream, why would you wake up to reality?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-if-you-could-live-a-beautiful-dream-why-would-you-wake-up-to-reality/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-if-you-could-live-a-beautiful-dream-why-would-you-wake-up-to-reality/</guid>
        <description>I have never enjoyed Chinese opera. Chinese opera to Chinese youth nowadays is a bit like what Shakespeare is to English-speaking youth – something confined to the realm of literary studies. And if they are popularly enjoyed, often it is only in some form of modern adaptation.
For just three nights …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Try a Little Tenderness: The Brothers Size at the Young Vic</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-try-a-little-tenderness-the-brothers-size-at-the-young-vic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-try-a-little-tenderness-the-brothers-size-at-the-young-vic/</guid>
        <description>Plays and movies don’t often get written about young, working class, black men; in the rare instances that they are the focus, the light in which they are shown can be less than flattering. Portrayals are often one-dimensional, heavy on aggression and toxic masculinity. In this landscape of facile …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rita, Sue and Bob Too – an exploration of power, class, and women’s voices</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-rita-sue-and-bob-too-an-exploration-of-power-class-and-women-s-voices/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-rita-sue-and-bob-too-an-exploration-of-power-class-and-women-s-voices/</guid>
        <description>It was the play that nearly didn’t happen. After the Royal Court’s founder Max Stafford-Clark was accused of sexual misconduct, a decision was made to cancel the upcoming production of Andrea Dunbar’s 1982 play Rita, Sue and Bob Too, which centres around the relationship between a married man and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Salieri versus God : Amadeus at the National Theatre</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-salieri-versus-god-amadeus-at-the-national-theatre/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-salieri-versus-god-amadeus-at-the-national-theatre/</guid>
        <description>Why do good things happen to terrible people? Who among us has not balked at the happiness and success of someone we consider to be objectively odious, absolutely awful? In the late Peter Shaffer’s classic 1979 play, the virtuoso composer Mozart’s very name – ‘Amadeus’, “beloved by God” – is an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Blood and guts (and laughter) in ancient Rome</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-blood-and-guts-and-laughter-in-ancient-rome/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sandra Engardt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-blood-and-guts-and-laughter-in-ancient-rome/</guid>
        <description>Titus Andronicus, one of Shakespeare’s Roman plays, has this fall reached the London stage at the Barbican. It is the story of the fictive Roman general Titus Andronicus, who returns to Rome after having entrapped Tamora, Queen of the Goths, and her three sons. The eldest son will soon be killed, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pinocchio ends up a little wooden…</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-pinocchio-ends-up-a-little-wooden/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-pinocchio-ends-up-a-little-wooden/</guid>
        <description>The National Theatre’s winter production of Pinocchio is based on the 1940 Disney film, including songs from the original. Broadly following the original, it adds in some minor changes: Gepetto, the old and lonely puppet maker, longs for a child of his own even as he creates puppets for other …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Twilight Zone – between fact and fiction</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-the-twilight-zone-between-fact-and-fiction/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-the-twilight-zone-between-fact-and-fiction/</guid>
        <description>Between light and shadow, science and superstition, fear and knowledge is a dimension of imagination. An area we call the Twilight Zone.”
Amidst all the Christmas shows and pantomimes filling theatres in December, the Almeida Theatre takes on this brave adaptation of the early 1960s American sci-fi …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Antony and Cleopatra review — Antony Byrne and Josette Simon have fantastic chemistry in Royal Shakespeare Company staging</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-15-antony-and-cleopatra-review-antony-byrne-and-josette-simon-have-fantastic-chemistry-in-royal-shakespeare-company-staging/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-15-antony-and-cleopatra-review-antony-byrne-and-josette-simon-have-fantastic-chemistry-in-royal-shakespeare-company-staging/</guid>
        <description>This production of Antony and Cleopatra forms part of the Royal Shakespeare Company’s Rome MMXVII season and is one of four plays being performed at the Barbican Centre this winter. It continues the story told in Julius Caesar—also being performed at the Barbican this season —Octavius Caesar, Mark …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Never the same love twice</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-never-the-same-love-twice/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-never-the-same-love-twice/</guid>
        <description>We ask a lot of short stories — they need to make the reader, or, if on the stage, the audience, feel the same peaks and troughs of emotion as a lengthier work; they need to speak to us with the same profundity, take us on the same journey with far fewer resources at their disposal. Like the best …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Politics and the value of rhetoric in early Rome</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-politics-and-the-value-of-rhetoric-in-early-rome/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adam Gellatly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-politics-and-the-value-of-rhetoric-in-early-rome/</guid>
        <description>In his second longest play, Shakespeare chronicles the election to, and subsequent removal from, the position of consul – a magistrate wielding executive power – of Caius Martius Coriolanus, played here by Sope Dirisu.
Coriolanus is elected to consul by his fellow societal-elites: a war hero and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All the Little Lights: A Story That Needs Telling</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-all-the-little-lights-a-story-that-needs-telling/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-all-the-little-lights-a-story-that-needs-telling/</guid>
        <description>Jane Upton’s All the Little Lights looks at the world of child sexual exploitation from the perspective of the young girls who are most often its victims. It allows you to see the seemingly obvious factors at play in their lives – poverty, isolation, peer pressure – that make them vulnerable to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Lady from the Sea: An adaptation worth its salt?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-the-lady-from-the-sea-an-adaptation-worth-its-salt/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jenny Lea,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-the-lady-from-the-sea-an-adaptation-worth-its-salt/</guid>
        <description>Directed by Kwame Kwei-Armah – the British actor-cum-playwright and soon to be artistic director of the Young Vic – The Lady from the Sea tells a story of marital oppression and lost love. Calypso music plays and algae grows from the walls as Kwei-Armah relocates the play from 19th Century Norway to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brexit, greed, and the making of modern Britain</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-brexit-greed-and-the-making-of-modern-britain/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Waleed A El-Geresy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-brexit-greed-and-the-making-of-modern-britain/</guid>
        <description>There is more death in that kind of life and more life in that kind of death. That is the message of Saint George in reference to a life lived under the rule of the despotic dragon. On the face of things these two characters should be at the heart of an epic tale of heroism versus evil, but Rory …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Looking for love in the lonely city</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-looking-for-love-in-the-lonely-city/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-looking-for-love-in-the-lonely-city/</guid>
        <description>Olivia Laing in her exceptional book, The Lonely City, remarks, “So much of the pain of loneliness is about concealment. But&amp;hellip;what’s so shameful about wanting?”. Loneliness, and the barriers we set up even as we try to forge new connections are at the centre of David Eldridge’s new play. In …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sondheim’s classic Follies revived in London</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-sondheim-s-classic-follies-revived-in-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-sondheim-s-classic-follies-revived-in-london/</guid>
        <description>In Follies, the shine has rubbed off from the Weisman Theatre. The musical sees a group of retired chorus girls who once performed there gather to bid farewell to their old haunt before it is demolished. It is a love letter to the New York of old, the glamour of Broadway and the pain of reaching …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mad about the boy: Jane Eyre returns to the NT</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-mad-about-the-boy-jane-eyre-returns-to-the-nt/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-mad-about-the-boy-jane-eyre-returns-to-the-nt/</guid>
        <description>Jane Eyre opens with a scream – it’s one of the moments I think most after I leave the theatre. It is at once all the things I find difficult about the performance, and what seems essential to the spirit of the original novel which is itself a howl for women’s independence and self-determination. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rhodes must fall </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-rhodes-must-fall/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lizzie E Riach,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-rhodes-must-fall/</guid>
        <description>Told through a series of compelling monologues, The Fall is a dramatisation of the real events surrounding a group of activist students studying at the University of Cape Town (UCT), several decades after apartheid. Specifically, it tells the story behind the fall of the statue of colonialist Cecil …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
