<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mk6809/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mk6809/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Seeing the light: Acting against actinic keratosis</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-seeing-the-light-acting-against-actinic-keratosis/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maya Kaushik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-seeing-the-light-acting-against-actinic-keratosis/</guid>
        <description>Easter weekend this year saw most of us out enjoying the sunshine, after digging through our cupboards to bring out our sunhats, sundresses, sunglasses and sun cream. While the first hot days of the year are always greatly appreciated, sun exposure can lead to several problems, both in the UK and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Facing the facts: Botulinum toxin in aesthetic medicine</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-facing-the-facts-botulinum-toxin-in-aesthetic-medicine/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maya Kaushik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-facing-the-facts-botulinum-toxin-in-aesthetic-medicine/</guid>
        <description>Pick up a glossy magazine to check out the latest gossip around your favourite Hollywood A-list celebrity, and you may notice that many of them have seemingly flawless faces, lacking the frown lines and crow’s feet that you might expect to see in someone of their age. Sometimes this is down to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Getting under the skin: a new hope for cancer treatment</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-getting-under-the-skin-a-new-hope-for-cancer-treatment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maya Kaushik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-getting-under-the-skin-a-new-hope-for-cancer-treatment/</guid>
        <description>Cutaneous T-cell lymphoma (CTCL) is a rare cancer of the skin, which occurs when T cells, a type of white blood cell in the lymphatic system, grow out of control within the skin. This is often initially mistaken for other skin conditions like psoriasis, dermatitis or eczema, as it presents as red, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Take a deep breath: Biologics are set to change the global treatment of severe asthma</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-take-a-deep-breath-biologics-are-set-to-change-the-global-treatment-of-severe-asthma/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maya Kaushik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-take-a-deep-breath-biologics-are-set-to-change-the-global-treatment-of-severe-asthma/</guid>
        <description>Imagine being a young woman, who is told that the drug you are prescribed by your doctor is going to cause you to gain weight, and have uncontrollable mood swings. Or perhaps, a young man who is aware that your medication may cause cataracts in your eyes, changes to the shape of your face, or your …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Galaxies far, far away: The problem of the spinning stars</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-22-galaxies-far-far-away-the-problem-of-the-spinning-stars/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maya Kaushik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-22-galaxies-far-far-away-the-problem-of-the-spinning-stars/</guid>
        <description>Princess Leia was a feminist icon of the 1980s that many of us grew up with. When Carrie Fisher passed away just over a year ago, social media and the news were filled with people mourning her death. Two days before, however, on Christmas Day in 2016, Vera Rubin quietly passed away in the USA. Rubin …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brainsnatchers: Microbes that change the way we behave
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-31-brainsnatchers-microbes-that-change-the-way-we-behave/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 10:57:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maya Kaushik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-31-brainsnatchers-microbes-that-change-the-way-we-behave/</guid>
        <description>Friday night, work finally done, I sit down in my favourite pub and order a pint. I’m tired, maybe a bit grumpy. A couple of pints in and I’m happy, my energy levels are up, I’m chatting to everyone vibrantly. A couple more pints and I’m dragging myself home somewhat stupefied.
Alcohol is just one …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Models bring sexy back
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-models-bring-sexy-back/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 02:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maya Kaushik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-models-bring-sexy-back/</guid>
        <description>This summer, cycle 8 of Britain and Ireland’s Next Top Model aired on Sky Living, featuring many exciting challenges and photo shoots, including a shoot with tarantulas, walking on CN tower, and posing with naked male models. During the series, twenty contestants were whittled down to one winner. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don&#39;t regress into despair
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-1-dont-regress-into-despair/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2012 13:30:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maya Kaushik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-1-dont-regress-into-despair/</guid>
        <description>For anyone considering a career in biological or medical research, the old catchphrase “Never work with children or animals” often comes into play. Biological data never quite does what you want it to. Sometimes a scientist’s intuition, or even looking graphs of your data, tells you that the trend …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The subtle parasite
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-the-subtle-parasite/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 20:45:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maya Kaushik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-the-subtle-parasite/</guid>
        <description>It’s the start of a cold winter’s day in London. A young man gets into his car to drive to work. Amongst the bustle of traffic, a pedestrian runs onto the road – the young man sees this, but does not react fast enough. The car swerves, bumps into the pavement, and he wakes up dazed in hospital a few …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Have sex, then select
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-have-sex-then-select/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 20:33:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maya Kaushik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-have-sex-then-select/</guid>
        <description>Last Friday night, I was sat in my favourite bar in London with my friends, when a well-dressed young man in a suit came up to me and offered to buy me a cocktail. Pretty exciting, for a single girl, right? What this guy was subconsciously signalling to me was that he had money (at least enough for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sex, the city and HIV
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-sex-the-city-and-hiv/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 20:49:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maya Kaushik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-sex-the-city-and-hiv/</guid>
        <description>Ever sat with a hanky in hand, wiping away tears as Edward climbs the fire escape with a rose in his teeth to profess his love to Vivienne, in the final scene of Pretty Woman? Or ever had a laugh at Belle and her hilarious antics in Secret Diary of a Call Girl?
Unfortunately, in reality, life for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why we allow fear to take control
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-why-we-allow-fear-to-take-control/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 19:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maya Kaushik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-why-we-allow-fear-to-take-control/</guid>
        <description>It was a dark, misty, eerie night this Halloween. I was walking alone through a deserted, narrow street in London. The sound of footsteps behind me made me start. I stopped and listened. The noise stopped. I carried on walking. The footsteps started again. All my senses were heightened. I began to …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
