<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/eb1710/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/eb1710/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Dandy Warhols silently rock Le Trianon
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-dandy-warhols-silently-rock-le-trianon/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 00:42:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edward Bals,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-dandy-warhols-silently-rock-le-trianon/</guid>
        <description>On the 29th of November I was standing in Le Trianon, a music venue in Paris, waiting for the arrival of The Dandy Warhols onto the stage. Whilst waiting I took a look around the old theatre in which I was standing, and it is truly one of the most beautiful venues that I have ever been in, with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Damn Fine Cup of Coffee
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-a-damn-fine-cup-of-coffee/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 21:53:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edward Bals,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-a-damn-fine-cup-of-coffee/</guid>
        <description>Twin Peaks manages to do the almost impossible; mixing sex, violence, mystery and even the odd dosage of the supernatural into a heady whirlwind that is sure to draw you in to its strange world. The series itself is from the early ‘90s and has been recommended to me time and time again by my family …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Big Brother... On Mars?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-big-brother-on-mars/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 22:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edward Bals,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-big-brother-on-mars/</guid>
        <description>Mars One is a not-for-profit organisation planning to use money donated from sponsors and that generated from a reality TV show ‘media storm’ to fund a project that will put a human habitat on Mars in 2023. In the first half of this year the application process will open to applications for their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>[Force Persuade] Play KOTOR
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-force-persuade-play-kotor/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 22:51:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edward Bals,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-force-persuade-play-kotor/</guid>
        <description>All right, I know my force powers don’t work through the printed word. I guess I’ll have to persuade you instead withthe actual reasons why you should play this game, and if those don’t work, well; you are strong-willed indeed.
SWKOTOR (Star Wars – Knights of The Old Republic, for those in the know) …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Smack it down to the ground, WWE style
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-smack-it-down-to-the-ground-wwe-style/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 20:08:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edward Bals,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-smack-it-down-to-the-ground-wwe-style/</guid>
        <description>THQ promised that WWE ‘12 would be the game to reinvent their tired series, and it seems that with this new entry they have succeeded, at least in part. This is a game which recreates the almost absurd dramatics and stage-play that wrestling is famous for: from The Undertaker’s chilling entrance to …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
