<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ghc07/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ghc07/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Dark tales of ice and fire
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-28-dark-tales-of-ice-and-fire/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 11:53:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guo Heng Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-28-dark-tales-of-ice-and-fire/</guid>
        <description>A Song of Ice and Fire starts out with the Seven Kingdoms under one rule – the Iron Throne at the capital, conveniently called King’s Landing. The ruling House is the Baratheons, who deposed of the Mad King Targayen. Troubles stir as rumours arise that the wealthy and ambitious House Lannister are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Master of epic fantasy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-28-master-of-epic-fantasy/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 11:42:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guo Heng Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-28-master-of-epic-fantasy/</guid>
        <description>The landscape of modern fantasy writing would have been quite different had it not been for George R. R. Martin. A Song of Ice and Fire redefined the fantasy genre from the classic Lord of the Rings-esque adventure quest cum bildungsroman story of good versus evil into a darker, more adult and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The misadventures of a Nobel physicist
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-the-misadventures-of-a-nobel-physicist/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 20:43:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guo Heng Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-the-misadventures-of-a-nobel-physicist/</guid>
        <description>Ian McEwan’s latest book, Solar, is probably the lightest piece he’s written to date. It is a departure from the serious, dark tones characteristic in most of the work that McEwan is renowned for (such as Atonement, Amsterdam and First Love, Last Rites). Solar is a satirical fiction that follows the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Whale meat, hot pools, and hiking in Iceland
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-whale-meat-hot-pools-and-hiking-in-iceland/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 20:15:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guo Heng Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-whale-meat-hot-pools-and-hiking-in-iceland/</guid>
        <description>The eruption of the glacial volcano Eyjafjallajökull last year severely disrupted European airspace but pinned Iceland on the tourist map. It’s easy to see why the island in the middle of the North Atlantic was not exactly the place most opt to go for vacation: it is not heir to a rich cultural …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The art of storytelling
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-the-art-of-storytelling/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 20:10:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guo Heng Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-the-art-of-storytelling/</guid>
        <description>Do you remember that one time when you stumbled upon a book that captivated you so much you could skip meals and read it way beyond bedtime just because you couldn’t bear to tear yourself away from the pages? Or that pang of sadness and longing as you came to the end of the novel and had to part …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bookfests galore this summer
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-27-bookfests-galore-this-summer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 14:08:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guo Heng Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-27-bookfests-galore-this-summer/</guid>
        <description>In London
London Literature Festival
30 June – 14 July
Southbank’s annual summer literary festival brings together some of the best homegrown talent, a large repertoire of worldwide literature, fresh pieces from young and emerging authors, and a dash of alternative literature; so whatever your …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A ‘biopunk’ Nineteen Eighty-four
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-a-biopunk-nineteen-eighty-four/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 05:37:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guo Heng Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-a-biopunk-nineteen-eighty-four/</guid>
        <description>Biopunk has always been considered a mere sub-genre. But recently things are beginning to change. As genomics and biotechnology are becoming more integral in our lives, there is more interest in biotech speculative fiction. All biopunk needs is a landmark book that lifts it from its ‘sub-genre’ …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Thousand Autumns of Jacob De Zoet
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-the-thousand-autumns-of-jacob-de-zoet/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 13:15:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guo Heng Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-the-thousand-autumns-of-jacob-de-zoet/</guid>
        <description>One of the joys of reading David Mitchell is the way his intricate prose immerses you into the rich, luxuriant and complex worlds he crafted; his intriguing plots and and ability to get beneath the skin of a diverse cast of characters combinres to create some of the most engrossing read in modern …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A maestro of modern literature
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-a-maestro-of-modern-literature/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 13:10:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guo Heng Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-a-maestro-of-modern-literature/</guid>
        <description>David Mitchell is a major figure in contemporary English literature. Two of his novels, number9dream and Cloud Atlas were shortlisted for the Booker Prize. His latest book, The Thousand Autumns of Jacob de Zoet, follows the adventures of a young Dutch clerk in 18th Century Edo Japan in a tale of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Swords, incest, blood and babes
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-swords-incest-blood-and-babes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 13:00:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guo Heng Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-swords-incest-blood-and-babes/</guid>
        <description>A few years ago, picking up ‘A Game of Thrones’ started a love affair that kept me up through the deep hours of midnight, and ended 5000 pages and 4 books later. I was swept away into the world of Westeros George R. R. Martin created and was entangled in the intricate plots and characters that the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Leaking Wikileaks
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-leaking-wikileaks/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 21:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guo Heng Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-leaking-wikileaks/</guid>
        <description>Since Wikileaks published their first leak in 2006, it has grown to become one of the most controversial website in the world. Wikileaks lubricated the whistle-blowing cog, resulting in a Cambrian explosion of leaks in the past couple of years via their website. Some leaks are mere objects of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>True Grit is a force to be reckoned with
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-true-grit-is-a-force-to-be-reckoned-with/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 20:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guo Heng Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-true-grit-is-a-force-to-be-reckoned-with/</guid>
        <description>True Grit was truly a surprise at the Golden Globes. Not for any record breaking achievement but rather for its surprising lack of recognition. The film was hailed as one of the racehorses set for a slew of gongs during the awards season, but gasp! The Coen brother’s latest western was not even …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>James Franco gives his right arm to 127 Hours
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-james-franco-gives-his-right-arm-to-127-hours/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 19:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guo Heng Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-james-franco-gives-his-right-arm-to-127-hours/</guid>
        <description>Based on the book Between a Rock and a Hard Place, 127 Hours is the true story of Aron Ralston, an outdoorsman in his late 20s with a passion for mountaineering. While canyoning one sunny afternoon in Utah, he misjudged a boulder and took a fall. This would not have been so bad – he is an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Happy New Year?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-happy-new-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 19:42:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jacob Lea-Wilson,Aditya Narayanan,Guo Heng Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-happy-new-year/</guid>
        <description>As another year begins again and starts us off right at the beginning of Oscar season, the Felix Film writers take a look back at the best of cinema in 2010 – in case you were in some kind of year-long coma – and discuss some of our most anticipated films of 2011.
There are three clear frontrunners …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tron Returns!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-tron-returns/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 19:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guo Heng Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-tron-returns/</guid>
        <description>Have you ever wondered what goes on inside the digital domain? What goes on inside the circuitry of your computer as packets of information are sent through it? Enter TRON. It is the sci-fi geek’s ultimate fantasy – a whole world lying out there, inside those clusters of computer networks. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Washington, we have a problem
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-washington-we-have-a-problem/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 20:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guo Heng Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-washington-we-have-a-problem/</guid>
        <description>Wikileaks strikes once again and this time it draws blood from not just the U.S. Wikileaks is releasing up to 251,287 confidential US embassy cables and the cables reveal “lying, corrupt, murderous leaderships from Bahrain to Brazil”, Wikileaks figurehead Julian Assange declared in an email. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Facebook: What’s Next?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-facebook-whats-next/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 18:56:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guo Heng Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-facebook-whats-next/</guid>
        <description>Google, the Mecca of top minds in computing, the dream workplace of fresh-grad software engineers, is shaken by a tremor of brain drain. Or rather, a brain haemorrhage. And it is Facebook who struck the blow. It started with Sheryl Sandberg, once Google’s Vice President of Global Online Sales and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix likes this...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-felix-likes-this/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 19:58:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guo Heng Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-felix-likes-this/</guid>
        <description>The Social Network may just be the movie that defines our generation. It tackles a subject that certainly defined our generation – Facebook – and after barely a month in the cinemas, critics already call it a classic. What’s the fuss about?
For one, it’s directed by David Fincher, a familiar name in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Zuckerberg: The Man
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-zuckerberg-the-man/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 19:48:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guo Heng Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-zuckerberg-the-man/</guid>
        <description>The year 2010 may just be Mark Zuckerberg’s finest. Having his net worth more than triple to $6.9 billion, he has climbed the ranks of the Forbes 400 list from #158 to #35. He even knocked Steve Jobs off the throne of Geekdom as Vanity Fair proclaimed him “our new Caesar” by placing him at #1 in its …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Facebook: Revolution
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-facebook-revolution/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 19:44:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guo Heng Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-facebook-revolution/</guid>
        <description>Facebook is taking over the world. From the dorm-run social network exclusive to Ivy-Leaguers six years ago, today it boasts over 500 million users worldwide. That’s 13.7% of the world population.
As David Kirkpartick points out in The Facebook Effect, Facebook fills a gap in the online world …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>George Clooney: A brooding Bond
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-10-george-clooney-a-brooding-bond/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 15:36:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guo Heng Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-10-george-clooney-a-brooding-bond/</guid>
        <description>The director of the much-acclaimed Ian Curtis biopic Control, is back with a bang. Anton Corbijn discards the guitar and picks up the rifle in The American, a thriller about a killer who discovers his soul. Adapted from British novelist Martin Booth’s A Very Private Gentleman (1990), the film stars …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
