<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/toc15/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/toc15/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Freshers listen up! A guide to surviving your first year at Imperial</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-freshers-listen-up-a-guide-to-surviving-your-first-year-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thomas Carroll,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-freshers-listen-up-a-guide-to-surviving-your-first-year-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Dear Freshers, Seeing as you’ve all descended upon campus to begin your arduous journey towards getting a pretty piece of paper from some people with letters in front their names, I thought I’d tell you a couple things I’ve learnt in my own time here. These are four things that I’ve learned about …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kung-Fu, Kickstarter, and how crowdfunding is changing cinema
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-kung-fu-kickstarter-and-how-crowdfunding-is-changing-cinema/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:38:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thomas Carroll,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-kung-fu-kickstarter-and-how-crowdfunding-is-changing-cinema/</guid>
        <description>Struck by lightning and bitten by a cobra, Kung Fury is a kung-fu freak of nature and the chosen one. Working as a cop on streets drenched in neon and soaked in synth pop, he defends 1980’s Miami. Enter Adolf Hitler, A.K.A. the Kung-Führer. On a temporal murder spree to prove his supremacy, Hitler …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An A* art-house experience
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-29-an-a-art-house-experience/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2015 16:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thomas Carroll,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-29-an-a-art-house-experience/</guid>
        <description>I really had no idea what to expect from my first art-house film, but if they’re all like _Güeros, _then sign me up.
Existentialist at its heart, the whole film is a joyous and somewhat satirical exploration of what it means to be young and rebellious. It follows young Tomás, his elder brother …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A mournful, brilliantly told story of warfare in Afghanistan
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-a-mournful-brilliantly-told-story-of-warfare-in-afghanistan/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 14:13:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thomas Carroll,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-a-mournful-brilliantly-told-story-of-warfare-in-afghanistan/</guid>
        <description>Tell Spring Not to Come This Year is named after a poem chosen by one of its main subjects: Commander Jalaluddin of the 3rd Brigade of the Afghan National Army (ANA). The poem is a reflection on rebirth and renewal of a country, and the impossibility of such a renewal while the land is still full of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chinese professor dumped for dissidence
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-19-chinese-professor-dumped-for-dissidence/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2015 22:28:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thomas Carroll,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-19-chinese-professor-dumped-for-dissidence/</guid>
        <description>Professor Liang Xinsheng of Lingnan Normal University has lost his managerial position in light of posts made on Weibo expressing discontent over social issues. The demotion has been widely seen as a symptom of an increasing crackdown on dissent in academia, a crackdown led by China’s premier Xi …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
