<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/anshbhatnagar/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/anshbhatnagar/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>A Decade of UK Politics</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-decade-of-uk-politics/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-decade-of-uk-politics/</guid>
        <description>As the clock ticked midnight on 1st January 2010, the nation celebrated the completion of an entire decade into the new millennium. At the time, 10 Downing Street was occupied by Gordon Brown, the Prime Minister who took the country through the global financial crash of 2008. Brown had been part of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UK Election Manifestos Review</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-uk-election-manifestos-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ansh Bhatnagar,James Thorne,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-uk-election-manifestos-review/</guid>
        <description>Labour
Brexit policy: negotiate a credible leave deal that protects jobs and living standards within three months, and put it to a referendum against remain in six months.
Titled “It’s time for real change”, the Labour manifesto certainly lives up to that promise. Labour have promised large spending …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The State we’re in…</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-the-state-were-in/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-the-state-were-in/</guid>
        <description>In the previous article it was established that the state is a necessity for capitalism, as without a state private property rights could not be enforced. A state was defined by political economist Max Weber as “a political entity that maintains a monopoly on the use of violence”. We discussed how …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is Capitalism?, Part 2: Nobody Wants to Take your Toothbrush</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-what-is-capitalism-part-2-nobody-wants-take-toothbrush/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-what-is-capitalism-part-2-nobody-wants-take-toothbrush/</guid>
        <description>Last week we looked at wage labour and the class divide, where we assessed the capitalist class to be the minority that owns the means of production, such as land, a factory, or an office, and the working class to be the majority that are made to sell their labour power in exchange for a wage and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is Capitalism?, Part 1: Boss Makes a Dollar, I Make a Dime…</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-what-is-capitalism-part-1-boss-makes-dollar-i-make-dime/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-what-is-capitalism-part-1-boss-makes-dollar-i-make-dime/</guid>
        <description>Capitalism: in its modern form, it’s the way the world works, and has worked, for the last 200 years. It shapes more than just our economic life but encroaches on our politics, our climate, our culture, our very psychology. Although it dictates our lives, it can still remain a mystery to many of us, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>No sympathy for Theresa May</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-no-sympathy-for-theresa-may/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-no-sympathy-for-theresa-may/</guid>
        <description>Let me start by stating very clearly: it is a privilege, not a right, to hold the most powerful job in the United Kingdom. This shouldn’t be a controversial statement, yet when Theresa May briefly broke down her veneer of stone-cold emotionlessness, the press immediately jumped onto it, making it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Independent Group? No thanks</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-the-independent-group-no-thanks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-the-independent-group-no-thanks/</guid>
        <description>On Monday morning, a group of 7 Labour MPs took the unprecedented step of leaving the Labour Party and forming a new centrist “party”, taking the incredibly bland name of ‘The Independent Group’. Except it was not unprecedented at all – most of these MPs, such as their ringleader Chuka Umunna, have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union Reform has only just begun – now we need you</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-union-reform-has-only-just-begun-now-we-need-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-union-reform-has-only-just-begun-now-we-need-you/</guid>
        <description>After a hefty debate about my paper, with many a discussion being had about if we need Union reform, when we need Union reform, why we need Union reform, and how we should do Union reform, the paper was passed, with an amendment limiting the scope of reform to democratic engagement; currently done …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why I’m proposing a complete restructure of the Union</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-why-i-m-proposing-a-complete-restructure-of-the-union/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-why-i-m-proposing-a-complete-restructure-of-the-union/</guid>
        <description>How much of a say do we really have in what the Union does? Whether introducing sweeping changes such as a whole new representation network (the Wellbeing Rep Network), implementing programmes like ICXP (Imperial Clubs Experience Project), tampering with election timetables (Leadership Elections …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Donkey Kong became a trans icon</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-how-donkey-kong-became-a-trans-icon/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-how-donkey-kong-became-a-trans-icon/</guid>
        <description>First, a bit of background. Trans rights are a controversial topic in the UK currently with mainstream newspapers exhibiting some of the most toxic and transphobic headlines; The Telegraph recently ran a front-page story titled “Trans row as men get access to women’s NHS wards”. Not only does this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Visit to Labour Conference: Thoughts on the Government in Waiting</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-my-visit-to-labour-conference-thoughts-on-the-government-in-waiting/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-my-visit-to-labour-conference-thoughts-on-the-government-in-waiting/</guid>
        <description>Last week, I travelled along with three other Imperial students to the annual Labour Party Conference, this year held in the great city of Liverpool. After a long, difficult summer in the party, with lots of division between the two factional wings, I didn’t know if I should be looking forward to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The state of the Union: to consult or not to consult…</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-the-state-of-the-union-to-consult-or-not-to-consult/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-the-state-of-the-union-to-consult-or-not-to-consult/</guid>
        <description>Three weeks ago, a motion to create a liberation officer to represent economically disadvantaged students was shot down at Union Council with a 50&amp;frasl;50 vote. The Deputy President (Welfare) spoke out vociferously against the idea, arguing that “it was setting up a role to fail” and “the relevant …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>RCSU Science Challenge 2018: One small step, one giant leap</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-rcsu-science-challenge-2018-one-small-step-one-giant-leap/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-rcsu-science-challenge-2018-one-small-step-one-giant-leap/</guid>
        <description>The Science Challenge is an annual science communication competition run by the RCSU. It is your chance to submit an entry communicating your passion for science, and to win up to £1000. Choose to enter in one of the four categories, answering one of the questions chosen by our panel of judges …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The failings of the Conservatives
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-failings-of-the-conservatives/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:42:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-failings-of-the-conservatives/</guid>
        <description>Theresa May went for a power grab. She wanted to wipe out Labour while her party was polling with almost 20 points ahead of them. With a fragmented opposition and Corbyn’s poor approval ratings, everyone assumed it was going to be a landslide election. So how did this all backfire and end up in a …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
