<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jia_qi_tan/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jia_qi_tan/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Best of the Decade: Editor’s Choice (Jia Qi Tan)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-best-of-the-decade-editors-choice-jia/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-best-of-the-decade-editors-choice-jia/</guid>
        <description>Choosing and ranking the best TV shows of the decade might have been the most daunting task especially in the era of “Peak TV” where every provider churns out quality pieces at an unprecedented rate. But I’ve managed to narrow the list down to ten. I’m sure I have missed many gems, and this list is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Editors’ Top Picks of the Decade</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-editors-top-picks-of-decade/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-editors-top-picks-of-decade/</guid>
        <description>When Breath Becomes Air by Paul Kalanithi
Image Above
Poetic, poignant, and profound, Paul Kalanithi’s memoir as a neurosurgeon diagnosed with Stage IV metastatic lung cancer is unbelievably powerful in Kalanithi’s quest to answer the difficult question of what makes a life worth living. It’s a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Marvelous Mrs. Maisel (Seasons 1 and 2)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-the-marvelous-mrs-maisel-seasons-1-and-2/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-the-marvelous-mrs-maisel-seasons-1-and-2/</guid>
        <description>Season 1: 5 stars
Season 2: 5 stars
Amazon Prime Video’s The Marvelous Mrs. Maisel is a period comedy-drama set in 1958 Manhattan, New York. It follows the self-discovery journey of Mrs. Miriam “Midge” Maisel, a housewife-turned-stand-up-comedian. It’s created by Amy Sherman-Palladino who is best …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Binge of the Week: Russian Doll</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-binge-of-week-russian-doll/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-binge-of-week-russian-doll/</guid>
        <description>Season 1: 5 stars
Netflix’s dramedy Russian Doll follows Nadia Vulvokov (played by Natasha Lyonne), a software developer who finds herself stuck in a time loop where she repeatedly dies and mysteriously relives her 36th birthday party. Nadia has to fix the “bug” in the code that is her life in order …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Binge of the week: Fleabag (Seasons 1 and 2)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-binge-week-fleabag-seasons-1-2/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-binge-week-fleabag-seasons-1-2/</guid>
        <description>Season 1: 5 stars
Season 2: 5 stars
BBC’s tragicomedy (yes, this genre exists) Fleabag centers around its titular role Fleabag (played by Phoebe Waller-Bridge), a young woman living in London, with the first season focusing on the feelings of guilt and grief, while the second exploring the themes of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Albert Camus’ The Myth of Sisyphus</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-albert-camus-myth-of-sisyphus/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-albert-camus-myth-of-sisyphus/</guid>
        <description>Albert Camus begins with a strong statement, “There is but one truly serious philosophical problem and that is suicide,” which immediately catches my attention. My problem with philosophy has always been its irrelevance, that is, whether you think one way or the other has little effect on how the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BBC One’s Latest Conspiracy Thriller, The Capture</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-bbc-ones-latest-conspiracy-thriller-the-capture/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-bbc-ones-latest-conspiracy-thriller-the-capture/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
BBC’s recent crime thriller The Capture presents an intriguing case of how technological advances, in this case, facial recognition and deepfakes, accelerate surveillance and threaten our privacy and integrity in the modern world. It begins with a string of seemingly unexplainable events …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Binge of the Week: Good Omens</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-binge-week-good-omens/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-binge-week-good-omens/</guid>
        <description>Terry Pratchett and Neil Gaiman’s 1990 fantasy novel Good Omens was once deemed “unfilmable” given its absurdity but now it has been brought on screen as a six-part miniseries co-produced by Amazon Studios and BBC Studios. Good Omens proves to be a faithful adaptation of Pratchett and Gaiman’s work, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Celeste Ng’s Debut Novel: Everything I Never Told You</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-celest-ngs-debut-novel-everything-i-never-told-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-celest-ngs-debut-novel-everything-i-never-told-you/</guid>
        <description>Celeste Ng once again has taken me on a bumpy ride of secrets and fears that will leave me absolutely breathless with Everything I Never Told You. Ng is the kind of writer who has keen eyes for one’s deepest and darkest desires, and you can feel every character’s flesh and blood as if you’re living …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Celeste Ng’s Little Fires Everywhere</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-celeste-ngs-little-fires-everywhere/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-celeste-ngs-little-fires-everywhere/</guid>
        <description>It’s been a while since Celeste Ng’s best-selling novels have been sitting on my shelf, but I have never figured out the right moment to read it - these are stories I knew I would love, the kind that I would want to read on a Sunday afternoon, with a cup of chamomile tea and a fine plate of vanilla …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Binge of the Week: Killing Eve (Seasons 1 and 2)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-binge-week-killing-eve-seasons-1-2/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-binge-week-killing-eve-seasons-1-2/</guid>
        <description>Season 1: 5 stars
Season 2: 4 stars
BBC America’s spring spy thriller Killing Eve takes a unique twist on a traditionally masculine genre, featuring a rather atypical tale of mutual obsession between a British intelligence investigator, Eve Polastri (Sandra Oh) and a sociopathic assassin named …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Ghost Map: dive into the 1854 London cholera outbreak</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-the-ghost-map-dive-into-the-1854-london-cholera-outbreak/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-the-ghost-map-dive-into-the-1854-london-cholera-outbreak/</guid>
        <description>The setting of this book - a cholera outbreak in Victorian England revolving around cesspools contaminations - is not particularly the most attractive thing in the world, yet it’s fascinating to see the story behind how we came to understand that cholera is water-borne, how it established the base …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>So You’ve Been Publicly Shamed: The guillotine of modern life?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-so-you-ve-been-publicly-shamed-the-guillotine-of-modern-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-so-you-ve-been-publicly-shamed-the-guillotine-of-modern-life/</guid>
        <description>As suggested by the title itself, So You’ve Been Publicly Shamed explores the world of the internet with compassion seemingly absent and every flaw amplified. In it, the author Jon Ronson details his interviews with those who were victims of ruthless attacks, perhaps for a bad joke or an immature …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Joy to your bookshelf</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-joy-to-your-bookshelf/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-joy-to-your-bookshelf/</guid>
        <description>Eleanor Oliphant is Completely Fine by Gail Honeyman
Winner of the British Book Awards, this stunning debut novel by Gail Honeyman delves deep into loneliness, connections and the power of kindness. The theme of isolation is one that is rarely explored in contemporary culture; as Honeyman puts it, …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
