<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/shaulrosten/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/shaulrosten/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The early termination of nuance: arguments around repealing the 8­th</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-the-early-termination-of-nuance-arguments-around-repealing-the-8-th/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shaul Rosten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-the-early-termination-of-nuance-arguments-around-repealing-the-8-th/</guid>
        <description>Later this month, on May 25th, the Republic of Ireland will hold an historic vote: whether or not to repeal the 8th Amendment of the Irish Constitution, which states:
“The State acknowledges the right to life of the unborn and, with due regard to the equal right to life of the mother, guarantees in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why Donald Trump is America’s best chance at true gun reform</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-why-donald-trump-is-america-s-best-chance-at-true-gun-reform/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shaul Rosten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-why-donald-trump-is-america-s-best-chance-at-true-gun-reform/</guid>
        <description>It is unnervingly common: you pick up your phone, open your news app, and scroll through the stories. As usual, there is one bemoaning what (insert name of stupid politician here) has to say. There is one, invariably, discussing Bitcoin. And there is one reporting on a shooting in a US school or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All the President’s pigs – why we can’t ignore the issue of free choice</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-all-the-president-s-pigs-why-we-can-t-ignore-the-issue-of-free-choice/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shaul Rosten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-all-the-president-s-pigs-why-we-can-t-ignore-the-issue-of-free-choice/</guid>
        <description>Picture the scene: you, a hot young 20-something in university, are invited to a dinner party by a few members of the opposite sex. They instruct you to wear something revealing and tight, and even go so far as to specify what sort of underwear you should have on. You go, and, predictably, they are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The endowment fund: to divest or not to   divest</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-the-endowment-fund-to-divest-or-not-to-divest/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shaul Rosten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-the-endowment-fund-to-divest-or-not-to-divest/</guid>
        <description>Divest Imperial is a movement urging the University to divest its endowment investments in fossil fuel-related companies, an approach similar to that taken by many large pension funds in recent years. This week the Felix team has procured data from Imperial, giving a rough breakdown of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stop  and think about it – a defence of university tuition fees</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-stop-and-think-about-it-a-defence-of-university-tuition-fees/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shaul Rosten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-stop-and-think-about-it-a-defence-of-university-tuition-fees/</guid>
        <description>Early last week, I walked past a poster in the SAF building whose message so incensed me that I felt the time had come to vent my frustration in the therapeutic pages of Felix. The poster screams:
“NATIONAL DEMO - FREE EDUCATION NOW: TAX THE RICH”
Since the General Election of 2010 we have seen …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Head-to-Head: Should antifascists use violence as a tactic?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-head-to-head-should-antifascists-use-violence-as-a-tactic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shaul Rosten,Pietro &#39;Delekof&#39; Salvi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-head-to-head-should-antifascists-use-violence-as-a-tactic/</guid>
        <description>The use of violence by antifascist groups in the US is preventing healthy democratic activism
SHAUL ROSTEN
On August 12th, a ‘Unite the Right’ march was held in the town of Charlottesville, Virginia. It was organised by a White Nationalist to protest the planned removal of a statue of American …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All shall love me in despair
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-all-shall-love-me-in-despair/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 12:51:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shaul Rosten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-all-shall-love-me-in-despair/</guid>
        <description>As we move, it seems inevitably, towards a Theresa May-led government, let&amp;rsquo;s take a moment to think about the fallout for the political landscape of the future. Leaving aside the speculations as to the potential success of Mrs. May as future PM, consider what will be left wilting on the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We should welcome Trump
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-we-should-welcome-trump/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 13:42:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shaul Rosten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-we-should-welcome-trump/</guid>
        <description>Two weeks ago, newly-elected President of the United States, Donald Trump, signed an Executive order suspending entry to the United States for residents of seven Muslim-majority countries, and for Syrian refugees. This was a key campaign pledge, and, although more crudely proposed as a total ban on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The real disgrace of executive pay
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-the-real-disgrace-of-executive-pay/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 14:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Shaul Rosten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-the-real-disgrace-of-executive-pay/</guid>
        <description>Theresa May announced this week that she intends to force companies to “justify” executive pay in response to reports that, at times, executives earn 140 times more than the average worker. High executive pay has been thrust into the headlines recently amidst the furore of the BHS collapse, and the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
