<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/klh110/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/klh110/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Is Feminism a Toxic Word? – Response
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-is-feminism-a-toxic-word-response/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 13:13:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marissa Lewis,Kirstin Hay,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-is-feminism-a-toxic-word-response/</guid>
        <description>I’ve been calling myself a feminist for about 10 years, and I started doing so for a simple reason – I believe women and men should be treated equally. I was not going to pretend not to be something because it might make others around me more comfortable.
Just to be sure, I looked up ‘feminism’ in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Robin Thicke: Trivialising Rape?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-18-robin-thicke-trivialising-rape/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 21:43:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kirstin Hay,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-18-robin-thicke-trivialising-rape/</guid>
        <description>You know you want it. You’re a good girl.
These are lines taken from Project Unbreakable, where survivors of sexual assault are photographed holding a poster with a quote from their attacker. These two lines come up again and again. They are also oft-repeated lyrics in Robin Thicke’s song, Blurred …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reclaim the Night
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-reclaim-the-night/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 22:18:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kirstin Hay,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-reclaim-the-night/</guid>
        <description>&amp;ldquo;Walking home at night should not be scary. We live in a strange society. If fear of our neighbours is considered normal, but many people are. Many women I know are afraid to walk alone in the dark, due to a perceived high danger of facing violence.
This is not a wholly surprising state of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Miliband opens debate on mental health
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-miliband-opens-debate-on-mental-health/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 12:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kirstin Hay,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-miliband-opens-debate-on-mental-health/</guid>
        <description>According to the World Health Organisation, one in four of us will have a mental illness at some point in our life, and that by 2030 depression will be the largest cause of disease around the world. That’s a scary statistic. Mental health issues, be them our own or someone else’s, affect us all, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UK GDP figures: a turn for the better?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-uk-gdp-figures-a-turn-for-the-better/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 22:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kirstin Hay,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-uk-gdp-figures-a-turn-for-the-better/</guid>
        <description>Last week, the Office for National Statistics released their first estimate for the economic growth of the UK economy in the months of July, August and September, known as the third quarter. Somewhat unexpectedly, a 1% rise in the GDP of the country was announced. Given the excuses given by the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Trade Union Members March Against Austerity
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-trade-union-members-march-against-austerity/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 02:14:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kirstin Hay,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-trade-union-members-march-against-austerity/</guid>
        <description>The sea of people ruining everyone’s travel plans around London on October 20th were the trade unionists marching against the government’s cuts to services. Teachers, nurses, fire-fighters, professors, factory workers, politicians, actors, and many more – all there to oppose what they saw as damage …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Conservative Party Conference
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-conservative-party-conference/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:24:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kirstin Hay,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-conservative-party-conference/</guid>
        <description>Party conference – the political equivalent of the office Christmas party. Careers are made or broken; too much alcohol and inappropriate sex; and all the dirty secrets get out. Thankfully much of that goes on behind the scenes, because the novelty of catching politicians with their trousers round …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Winning ways
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-winning-ways/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 23:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kirstin Hay,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-winning-ways/</guid>
        <description>Undefeated so far this season (with only one draw to compliment our string of wins), we arrived at the Staines pitch in high spirits, despite the freezing temperatures and remains of snow on the sidelines. One rapid warm-up later, and we were underway.
The standard was slightly different from the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
