<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/lwl09/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/lwl09/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Brum Photorealism
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-17-brum-photorealism/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 19:36:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-17-brum-photorealism/</guid>
        <description>What: Photorealism
Where: Birmingham Museum and Art Gallery
When: Until 30th March
Price: £6.50, £5.50 students
You’d be forgiven for thinking that London is the place to be for everything arts related. But you’d also be wrong. As vibrant as it is, the capital doesn’t have room for everything, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An epic poem of everyday Gods
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-an-epic-poem-of-everyday-gods/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 03:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-an-epic-poem-of-everyday-gods/</guid>
        <description>Kate Tempest is a 27 year old performance poet from Lewisham, London. As poetic as her name may sound, she remains unheard of to many. But all of this is changing, fast.
Tempest is the latest winner of the Ted Hughes Award for innovation in poetry, with her new piece_ Brand New Ancients,_ a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ms Mr at the Shepherd’s Bush Empire
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-ms-mr-at-the-shepherds-bush-empire/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 18:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-ms-mr-at-the-shepherds-bush-empire/</guid>
        <description>New York duo Ms Mr took to the stage of Shepherd’s Bush Empire before a crowd of excited fans before fulfilling all expectations and pleasing their audience. Their debut album Secondhand Rapture was released in May this year and despite making an unremarkable dent in the charts they nonetheless …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NHM’s wildlife photography never gets old
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-nhms-wildlife-photography-never-gets-old/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 09:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-nhms-wildlife-photography-never-gets-old/</guid>
        <description>Now in its 49th year, the Wildlife Photographer of the Year exhibition has recently returned to its original habitat the Natural History Museum. It showcases 100 photographs of the world around us that most will hardly ever get an actual glimpse of. First time visitors should prepared to be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cho Chang Goes To Work in a Chinese Factory
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-cho-chang-goes-to-work-in-a-chinese-factory/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 00:28:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-cho-chang-goes-to-work-in-a-chinese-factory/</guid>
        <description>What: The World of Extreme Happiness Where: The National Theatre Shed When: Until 26 October 2013, tickets still available Price: £12 to £20, £5 with the 16-25 Entry Pass Scheme
Could it be that there is no other play with a more sarcastic title than The World of Extreme Happiness? The play begins …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Liolà gets frisky in Irish Sicilian Gypsy Musical
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-18-liol-gets-frisky-in-irish-sicilian-gypsy-musical/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 22:05:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-18-liol-gets-frisky-in-irish-sicilian-gypsy-musical/</guid>
        <description>What: Liolà Where: The National Theatre When: Until 6 November 2013 Price: £12 to £34, £5 with the 16-25 Entry Pass Scheme
First, a disclaimer: for those with a strong aversion to musicals avoid this play at all costs. Liolà opens with a group of gypsy musicians providing music to what looks like a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Interested in enterprise?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-11-interested-in-enterprise/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 23:08:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-11-interested-in-enterprise/</guid>
        <description>Imagine you are not at Imperial. You have never heard of Felix and you are not sitting here reading this article. What a dream. No dull lectures, ridiculously difficult coursework, or seemingly un-passable exams. But imagine that it wasn’t out of choice – imagine you never obtained the opportunity …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Soar like an Eagle
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-28-soar-like-an-eagle/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2013 14:04:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-28-soar-like-an-eagle/</guid>
        <description>It is slightly perplexing for a few seconds. Laura Marling is a name seemingly sliding off everyone’s lips at the moment, yet still, seems to be unheard of to more than a fair few. Widely known but remaining anonymous, this enigma-like quality continues to run through her music, her fourth album …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>La neuro vague
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-la-neuro-vague/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 17:46:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-la-neuro-vague/</guid>
        <description>Art which tackles melange with science has been explored previously in these pages. However these clashes still remain few and far between. Science as inspiration for intriguing pieces, using art as a medium to explore the significance of science or portray its beauty has great potential and is not …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The internet presents: MS MR
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-8-the-internet-presents-ms-mr/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 20:15:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-8-the-internet-presents-ms-mr/</guid>
        <description>During a week’s worth of listening to the radio an average of 0-3 new songs make me drop everything, frown a little in an effort to identify the song / artist, then fiddle a little with the time bar on the listen-again player to figure out what exactly the wonderful noise is.
Last week this came in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Form before f(x)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-8-form-before-fx/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 13:46:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-8-form-before-fx/</guid>
        <description>After marching through the tourists packing Tower Bridge, I was worried that the Design Museum might be hidden amongst the cafés and small shops of the narrow brick walkways lining the riverside. Of course, it wasn’t. Bright, white, shining at the end of, rather than part of, a shadowy almost-alley, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Short Waves: Polish Short Film Festival
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-7-short-waves-polish-short-film-festival/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2013 19:30:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-7-short-waves-polish-short-film-festival/</guid>
        <description>Last month saw the fifth Polish Short Film Festival come to London, having made its journey around the globe. We went on down to Dalston (where else) to the cute little Rio Cinema (think Notting Hill Coronet, velveted squeaky chairs type of place) to find out what exactly Polish short films consist …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Designer genes
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-4-30-designer-genes/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 14:39:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-4-30-designer-genes/</guid>
        <description>We all fucking love science, but it has to be admitted that, frankly, it can get achingly dull. How many times have you heard the words, “after a month and a half of protocol optimisation, my experiment has failed again! Isn’t this so FUN?” That’s right, never.
Despite this, you don’t have to look …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Science Museum, Thinktank style
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-the-science-museum-thinktank-style/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 01:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-the-science-museum-thinktank-style/</guid>
        <description>”A science museum&amp;hellip; in Birmingham?! HA!” is the typical response received when I mention Thinktank Science Museum to anyone outside of the West Midlands.
As regarding jokes about stupidity which Midlanders are the butt of, Thinktank surely does not have a place among them. Its passion to place …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Taking the carapace
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-taking-the-carapace/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 23:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-taking-the-carapace/</guid>
        <description>Gregor Samsa is late for work one day. Everyone is extremely concerned, including his boss who pays him a personal visit for a personal reprimand. Instead of opening the bedroom door to find Gregor, his family and boss are surprised and subsequently disgusted by the huge beetle-like creature which …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Billie Piper and Dr. James
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-billie-piper-and-dr-james/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 23:07:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-billie-piper-and-dr-james/</guid>
        <description>Science and art rarely seem to collaborate in popular culture (and we are not talking about science fiction here). It is a shame, because science is inherently intriguing without requiring the embellishment of artistic and creative input. So, when they are combined, they are a strong force of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Polar-oids
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-polar-oids/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 00:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-polar-oids/</guid>
        <description>The Wildlife Photographer of the Year exhibition always proves an exciting, engaging, and inspiring visit if the permanent NHM displays were not already enough.
Every year, the number of categories, pictures and confusing pathways needed to navigate around each section seems to expand. This year it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oui Love
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-oui-love/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 03:36:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-oui-love/</guid>
        <description>As part of the UK tour, the promotional platform for popular French music stopped off in a tiny room of a Dalston pub for their London date.
First up was Yan Wagner, a handsome young Frenchie with a recently released debut album; slightly reminiscent of acts such as Jimmy Edgar. Being solo, it was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fear of Fiction Festival
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-fear-of-fiction-festival/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 03:35:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-fear-of-fiction-festival/</guid>
        <description>The only magazine to focus on Bristol’s music scene threw a giant street party before winter started to settle in and thwart all endeavours of extending the festival season. Of course, Felix was invited. Set along Stokes Croft - which could be deemed a mini ‘Hoxditch’ of Bristol - bars, cafés, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Moving pictures at the Barbican
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-moving-pictures-at-the-barbican/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 21:25:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-moving-pictures-at-the-barbican/</guid>
        <description>Everything is, has been, and always will be, moving. Memories of these movements shape our worlds. They metamorphose into nostalgia, sometimes even for times and places we have never physically accessed. Obsessions with an idealised past are manifested through the way in which we portray our world …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Executing Justice at the Dana Centre
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-executing-justice-at-the-dana-centre/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 12:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-executing-justice-at-the-dana-centre/</guid>
        <description>It turned out that 52% of the audience at a recent event at the Dana Centre would prefer to be executed by lethal injection than hanging, electrocution or being shot. This was before they were given information about what exactly occurs when a lethal injection is carried out. A member of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Battle star Galactia
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-battle-star-galactia/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 03:09:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-battle-star-galactia/</guid>
        <description>In 16th century Venice, female artist Galactia is commissioned by the state to paint a wall-sized canvas to commemorate the victory of the Battle of Lepanto. This initiates the events in Scenes from an Execution, a play originally written for the radio in the 1980s but now produced for the stage by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Heineken Open’er Festival 2012
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-heineken-opener-festival-2012/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:27:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-heineken-opener-festival-2012/</guid>
        <description>The first thing all Polish attendees of Open’er said when I explained that was British was how crazy I was to go to Poland when Britain has some of the best festivals in the world. They may have a point, but international festivals are definitely underrated.
As Open’er was an evening-only event, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Facing up to dementia
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-facing-up-to-dementia/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:17:47 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-facing-up-to-dementia/</guid>
        <description>In the UK, 820,000 people suffer with dementia and by 2051 this figure may rise to 1.7 million. The Foundation for Science and Technology highlighted this societal challenge by inviting four speakers to talk about the issue from unique perspectives.
The debate was started by Chief Medical Officer, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Convicts in the frame: from gaol to gallery
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-convicts-in-the-frame-from-gaol-to-gallery/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:00:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-convicts-in-the-frame-from-gaol-to-gallery/</guid>
        <description>The current exhibition at the Royal Festival Hall at the Southbank Centre consists of paintings, poetry, sculptures, textiles, and videos by offenders, secure patients, and detainees.
The fact that this is the premise for the exhibition makes it an interesting one, as it inevitably leads to a strong …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>French Radio: Pourqoui pas?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-french-radio-pourqoui-pas/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 21:29:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-french-radio-pourqoui-pas/</guid>
        <description>It seems as though the older you get, the less time there is for doing fun things, like having sex or keeping up with the best new music. (Or maybe that’s just because you have a frigid boyfriend from Imperial and you finally have better things to do with your time than read the slightly ridiculous …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Maccabees: Given to the Wild
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-27-the-maccabees-given-to-the-wild/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 12:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-27-the-maccabees-given-to-the-wild/</guid>
        <description>The third album from The Maccabees has been released after much anticipation and to critical acclaim. Sorry, “much” anticipation? Critically acclaimed by who now?
Things are expected to change for the Maccabees. Their new single has had airplay on national daytime radio and the new album has had …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Horrors still horrify, but not in a good way
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-the-horrors-still-horrify-but-not-in-a-good-way/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 21:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-the-horrors-still-horrify-but-not-in-a-good-way/</guid>
        <description>The most offensive thing The Horrors have probably ever done is release Strange House. The best thing they have ever done would have to be a toss-up between recognising this embarrassment and recording Sea within a Sea. What lies inbetween was the live show I attended.
To be honest, when you are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The return of The Maccabees
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-the-return-of-the-maccabees/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 22:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-the-return-of-the-maccabees/</guid>
        <description>Say “The Maccabees”. The response from most people, in order of frequency, would probably be a blank look, “is that something to do with the Jews?”, or one of intense gushing adoration.
In a way, they’ve had quite a bit of a struggle as five young men churning out indie-pop amongst a sea of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We all yell for Yelle!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-28-we-all-yell-for-yelle/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 10:47:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lily Le,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-28-we-all-yell-for-yelle/</guid>
        <description>Yelle Ninkasi Salle du Kao, Lyon October 22, 2011
For those of you who don’t know who Yelle is, I am not going to bother explaining; maybe because I don’t know who she is either, or maybe because if you like the sound of what she does from reading this review you are perfectly capable of finding it …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
