<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/nn1209/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/nn1209/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Anti-Austerity Protests take place in Central London
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-anti-austerity-protests-take-place-in-central-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 01:10:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,Navid Nabijou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-anti-austerity-protests-take-place-in-central-london/</guid>
        <description>Anti-austerity protests took place in London on Wednesday, with demonstrators taking to the streets alongside the Queen’s Speech in the newly elected Parliament.
Organised by the People’s Assembly, the march covered large sections of central London, moving from outside Downing Street at around …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix and Democracy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-felix-and-democracy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 00:52:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Navid Nabijou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-felix-and-democracy/</guid>
        <description>Last night I was browsing TheBig Elections website, pondering my choices of candidates. I decided to watch the Meet the Candidates video: partly because I was getting a bit lost amidst the endless succession of naïve and generic manifestos, but mostly for the comedic gold I’d been hearing about …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Feedback woes highlighted
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-feedback-woes-highlighted/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:50:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Navid Nabijou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-feedback-woes-highlighted/</guid>
        <description>TheNational Student Survey (NSS) was established in 2005 by HEFCE (the body administering government funding of UK universities), in order to independently gather feedback from students about their institutions. It is carried out every year in the spring: final-year undergraduates in almost every …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Public sector protests
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-public-sector-protests/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 21:57:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Navid Nabijou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-public-sector-protests/</guid>
        <description>This Wednesday, public sector workers up and down the country went on strike, in what was described by some as the “biggest walkout for a generation.” The action was directed against the Government’s planned reforms of public sector pensions, which comprise part of its wide-reaching deficit …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>DIY: Whiteboard Station
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-diy-whiteboard-station/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 20:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Navid Nabijou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-diy-whiteboard-station/</guid>
        <description>As a mathematician living with a group of other mathematicians, I like to think, at least some of the time, that our conversations relate to something beyond our chosen subject. But let’s face it: we’re Imperial students. Inevitably, the moment does come when normal discourse collapses into a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Exhibition Road hosts festival to coincide with Olympic Games
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-exhibition-road-hosts-festival-to-coincide-with-olympic-games/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 21:06:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Navid Nabijou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-exhibition-road-hosts-festival-to-coincide-with-olympic-games/</guid>
        <description>For those of you planning a work placement this summer, here’s something that might make you reconsider. The (Exhibition) Road Show, a nine-day street festival being held right on Imperial’s doorstep, is set to be unmissable. Part of the wider celebrations for the 2012 Olympics, the event will be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>DIY: meditation room
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-diy-meditation-room/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 22:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Navid Nabijou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-diy-meditation-room/</guid>
        <description>There isn’t a whole lot of space in my flat. Its close proximity to college is a massive plus, but one of the trade-offs is having to share rooms. This isn’t all bad by any means, but at times it can grow a bit trying. When we moved in, we realised that – thanks to the wisdom of some enlightened …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Council talk Balls and bars
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-council-talk-balls-and-bars/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 19:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,Navid Nabijou,Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-council-talk-balls-and-bars/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Union held its second Council meeting of the term on Monday 31 October, with all full members of Council attending for the first time. A variety of papers revolving around ongoing issues were brought forward with resolution reached for some.
Summer Ball Debrief
Serious issues about …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why should you go into teaching?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-why-should-you-go-into-teaching/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 19:48:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,Matthew N Colvin,Navid Nabijou,Deepka Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-why-should-you-go-into-teaching/</guid>
        <description>Can you think of any reason why an Imperial student might want to become a teacher?” “They got a third class, maybe?” This response from a second year mathematician may well sum up the opinions of some Imperial students, and indeed a section of society’s wider opinion of the profession. We’ve all …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Babar Ahmad ‘should face trial in the UK’, says sister
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-babar-ahmad-should-face-trial-in-the-uk-says-sister/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 21:14:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aemun Reza,Navid Nabijou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-babar-ahmad-should-face-trial-in-the-uk-says-sister/</guid>
        <description>With less than a month before the online petition concerning Babar Ahmad closes, his sister Amna spoke to Felix about her brother’s experience. For the past seven years, Babar Ahmad has been in prison fighting extradition to the United States. The current petition, launched two months ago, calls on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Middle East protests are secular
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-the-middle-east-protests-are-secular/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 20:09:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Navid Nabijou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-the-middle-east-protests-are-secular/</guid>
        <description>Last Thursday, the Muslim Student Council hosted an event entitled: “Middle East: Revolution, Democratisation, and the End of U.S. Hegemony.” The evening featured four invited speakers, talking about recent events in their home countries: Saeed Shehabi from Bahrain, Monjia Abidi from Tunisia, Kamal …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London is a SAD place in winter
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-london-is-a-sad-place-in-winter/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 20:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Navid Nabijou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-london-is-a-sad-place-in-winter/</guid>
        <description>Around the world, there prevails the same stereotypical image of London: dark clouds stretching to the horizon, a heavy downpour, men and women in black suits with black umbrellas wading across flooded pavements. But the reality is quite different. Compared with other global cities, rainfall here is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Our HBO-fest continues
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-our-hbo-fest-continues/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 20:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vicky Jeyaprakash,Navid Nabijou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-our-hbo-fest-continues/</guid>
        <description>The Sopranos
“A rich exploration of the paradoxes of modern life that will leave an impression on all who give it a chance.”
Perhaps no other series to date has had a greater impact on television as The Sopranos, writes Navid Nabijou. Exploding onto the airwaves in 1999, it came as a massive shock; …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>VAT rise hits prices in FiveSixEight
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-vat-rise-hits-prices-in-fivesixeight/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 21:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Navid Nabijou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-vat-rise-hits-prices-in-fivesixeight/</guid>
        <description>Spendthrift students returning from their Christmas break might have noticed a subtle shift in the cost of food and drink around campus. The recent rise in the rate of VAT has been cited as the main driver of the cost increase, although other pressures – including an increase in fuel duty, also put …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tuition fees rise to £9,000
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-tuition-fees-rise-to-9000/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 22:11:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Navid Nabijou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-tuition-fees-rise-to-9000/</guid>
        <description>And so it has come to pass. After weeks of seemingly endless student protests, vicious exchanges across the House of Commons and many uneasy grumbles from within the Liberal Democrats, the Government’s proposal to raise the tuition fee cap passed through the House of Commons late Thursday afternoon, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Debating Israel and Palestine
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-debating-israel-and-palestine/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2010 21:24:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Navid Nabijou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-debating-israel-and-palestine/</guid>
        <description>Last Tuesday IC Debating Society, Israeli Society and Palestinian Society collaborated, bringing together four prominent speakers to discuss the Israeli-Palestinian conflict under the title: “The Debate for Peace”.
In his closing remarks, Dan Judelson, former chair of Jews for Justice for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Quentin Tarantino: style over substance?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-quentin-tarantino-style-over-substance/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2010 19:56:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Navid Nabijou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-quentin-tarantino-style-over-substance/</guid>
        <description>Over the past two decades, few directors have managed to excite such acclaim – and controversy – as Quentin Tarantino. His work has sharply polarised critics, spawning a plethora of varied interpretations and deconstructions. Each new release is followed by a blaze of feverish publicity, and through …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students hit by visa changes
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-students-hit-by-visa-changes/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 19:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Navid Nabijou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-students-hit-by-visa-changes/</guid>
        <description>“Unsustainable.” That’s how Damian Green, the immigration minister, described levels of student migration to the UK. The Conservatives have been planning to curb immigration since before the election, and now more than ever it seems that universities will not be spared.
None of the changes made to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Institute of Mathematical Sciences&#39; future uncertain
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-institute-of-mathematical-sciences-future-uncertain/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 20:06:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Navid Nabijou,Matthew N Colvin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-institute-of-mathematical-sciences-future-uncertain/</guid>
        <description>The Institute for Mathematical Sciences (IMS) has been restructured, and will be moved out of its home at 53 Prince’s Gardens into a uncertain future as the Faculty of Natural Sciences &amp;ldquo;rationalises&amp;rdquo; its resources. The previous model has been deemed unsustainable and a new model is being …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Embarrassment for Union as tiles fall off FiveSixEight&#39;s bar
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-embarrassment-for-union-as-tiles-fall-off-fivesixeights-bar/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 19:55:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Navid Nabijou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-embarrassment-for-union-as-tiles-fall-off-fivesixeights-bar/</guid>
        <description>For a moment there, it looked like everything was coming together. FiveSixEight, despite problems and delays, opened to a lively first night. Everyone - even the engineers - seemed to be having a good time.
However disaster struck as a small avalanche of tiles fell off the front of the bar, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>There’s a desperate need for extra money for universities
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-theres-a-desperate-need-for-extra-money-for-universities/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 19:21:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rajat Jain,Navid Nabijou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-theres-a-desperate-need-for-extra-money-for-universities/</guid>
        <description>University funding reform has been a long time coming; the principle of free education for all, long a mainstay of British political thought, had to be abandoned in 1998 following a review by Lord Dearing. Public funding had for many years failed to keep pace with increasing student numbers: between …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
