<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mer113/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mer113/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Rhodes must fall </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-rhodes-must-fall/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lizzie E Riach,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-rhodes-must-fall/</guid>
        <description>Told through a series of compelling monologues, The Fall is a dramatisation of the real events surrounding a group of activist students studying at the University of Cape Town (UCT), several decades after apartheid. Specifically, it tells the story behind the fall of the statue of colonialist Cecil …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>&#34;Feverish Progress&#34; | Giacometti at the Tate Modern is comprehensive retrospective on a man with man
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-7-feverish-progress-giacometti-at-the-tate-modern-is-comprehensive-retrospective-on-a-man-with-man/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 08:14:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lizzie E Riach,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-7-feverish-progress-giacometti-at-the-tate-modern-is-comprehensive-retrospective-on-a-man-with-man/</guid>
        <description>Alberto Giacometti’s work has always been close to my heart. He was central to the wider body of artwork that inspired me to do art for GCSE and A level, and I&amp;rsquo;ve based countless of my own pieces on his. Despite being known more for his extremely thinly sculpted figures, it was actually his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How we’ll meet-eor our maker
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-how-well-meet-eor-our-maker/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 17:37:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lizzie E Riach,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-how-well-meet-eor-our-maker/</guid>
        <description>New computer simulations have found that if an asteroid impacted Earth, humans would be more likely to die from the blast itself, and not the subsequent effects it would have on the planet. A comforting thought. The shock waves, extreme winds and falling bits of space rock would probably deal the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sequencing all of life
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-sequencing-all-of-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 15:11:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lizzie E Riach,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-sequencing-all-of-life/</guid>
        <description>On the 23rd of February, a small group of researchers announced they wanted to sequence “all life on Earth” at a meeting organised by the Smithsonian Initiative of Biodiversity Genomics and China-based sequencing powerhouse BGI. The plan has been aptly named the Earth BioGenome Project (EBP), and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wearing your heart in your sleeve
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-wearing-your-heart-in-your-sleeve/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 16:33:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lizzie E Riach,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-wearing-your-heart-in-your-sleeve/</guid>
        <description>A so-called ‘soft robot’ has been invented to help keep the human heart beating. Developed by researchers from Harvard University and Boston Children’s Hospital, the robot fits around the heart and helps it pump blood. This could mean a significantly higher quality of life for people that have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How hot can you handle?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-how-hot-can-you-handle/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:12:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lizzie E Riach,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-how-hot-can-you-handle/</guid>
        <description>Some like it hot. But others can’t stand an inkling of chilli anywhere near their food. However, perhaps they ought to try, as researchers from the University of Vermont have found that spicy food may prolong life expectancy. In particular, consumption of red hot chilli peppers was associated with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Artificial Intelligence | fears and future
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-artificial-intelligence-fears-and-future/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lizzie E Riach,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-artificial-intelligence-fears-and-future/</guid>
        <description>Last Wednesday I attended a talk comprised of five leading experts in the fields of machine learning and artificial intelligence (AI), mediated by the calming voice of Brian Cox. It was an enlightening evening. I hadn’t really thought too much about AI, but what struck me was how much of what I did …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Barrier bleaching isn’t so Great
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-barrier-bleaching-isnt-so-great/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 14:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lizzie E Riach,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-barrier-bleaching-isnt-so-great/</guid>
        <description>Following the general vibes of this tragic excuse of a year, scientists have now confirmed that 2016 has seen the largest coral die-off ever recorded on Australia’s Great Barrier Reef. The most affected area runs along the northern part, where an average of 67% of all shallow-water coral has been …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wounds heal with (a lot of) time
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-wounds-heal-with-a-lot-of-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 13:36:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lizzie E Riach,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-wounds-heal-with-a-lot-of-time/</guid>
        <description>Since World War I, scientists have noticed how the speed of healing is much slower in older veterans compared to younger ones. But for an entire century, we had no idea why this was the case, until now.
Researchers at the Rockefeller University have started to unlock this aspect of the aging body by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Spotlight on Medicine
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-spotlight-on-medicine/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 15:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lizzie E Riach,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-spotlight-on-medicine/</guid>
        <description> 1 | HIV Testing USB Sticks Scientists here at Imperial College have created an extremely easy way of testing for HIV. A simple USB device detects the virus and sends corresponding electrical impulses that can be read on a laptop or handheld device. Not only does this allow testing to be quicker, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hair by Sam McKnight
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-hair-by-sam-mcknight/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 14:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lizzie E Riach,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-hair-by-sam-mcknight/</guid>
        <description>As I walked into Somerset House from the increasingly bitter streets surrounding the Strand, I was greeted by the world of fashion, along with a flock of fashion students. I was at the brand new exhibition, Hair by Sam McKnight, designed to mimic both the feel of a catwalk and an editorial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Will sperm ever be stopped?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-will-sperm-ever-be-stopped/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 12:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lizzie E Riach,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-will-sperm-ever-be-stopped/</guid>
        <description>Talking about Imperial Girl’s Can, isn’t it about time for a bit of equality when it comes to birth control? Men currently only have 3 options: condoms, vasectomies and withdrawal (not recommended), compared to the multiple women can choose from. Unfortunately, side effects are common alongside …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Nobel vs Ig Nobel prizes
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-7-the-nobel-vs-ig-nobel-prizes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 17:09:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lizzie E Riach,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-7-the-nobel-vs-ig-nobel-prizes/</guid>
        <description> Whereas the Nobel Prizes embody the recognition and respect all scientists strive for, the Ig Nobel Prizes are given out annually for some of the weirdest and most unlikely research materials in each category. Both are significant events in the science calendar, but for very different reasons. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The deadly orangutan cocktail
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-the-deadly-orangutan-cocktail/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 11:35:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lizzie E Riach,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-the-deadly-orangutan-cocktail/</guid>
        <description>Orangutans from a completely distinct subspecies have been accidentally introduced to another wild population, a recent genetic study has found. The population in question is situated in Camp Leakey in Tanjung Putjing National Park, within the Indonesian portion of Borneo (Central Kalimantan).
As …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Discover the Life Work of an Italian Master
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-discover-the-life-work-of-an-italian-master/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 21:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lizzie E Riach,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-discover-the-life-work-of-an-italian-master/</guid>
        <description>Are you interested in portraiture and the state of affairs in Italy during the sixteenth century? Have you ever wondered how the great masters like Caravaggio and Velasquez were inspired? The answers lie in the Royal Academy’s latest exhibition, where you are faced with works from throughout the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
