<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sex on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/sex/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sex on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/sex/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>How to dump someone (you met in Metric and subsequently fell in love with)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-how-to-dump-someone-you-met-in-metric-and-subsequently-fell-in-love-with/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 16:16:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Theresa Davey,Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-how-to-dump-someone-you-met-in-metric-and-subsequently-fell-in-love-with/</guid>
        <description> You were weak. Despite our foolproof guides on how to have a one night stand (in Metric), ‘How to have a one night stand (in Metric)’, and how not to fall in love with someone (from Metric), ‘How not to fall in love with someone (from Metric)’, you went ahead and fell in love with someone (from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The near-peg experience
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-the-near-peg-experience/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:53:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-the-near-peg-experience/</guid>
        <description>I went home last week for a few days over the bank holiday. As always when I go home, I opened up Tinder and began to swipe. I mostly use it as a way to keep track of who from school is single, but sometimes use it to shark on hot students and locals.
I swiped right on a few people before I ran out …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s not my job to please your girlfriend
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-its-not-my-job-to-please-your-girlfriend/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 16:31:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-its-not-my-job-to-please-your-girlfriend/</guid>
        <description>I don’t like being cheated on. You probably don’t either. In fact I’d go so far as to say that no one likes being cheated on. Unless you’re into cuckolding but that’s a whole other story. Last time I got cheated on it made me feel betrayed and angry not only at my partner, but also at the other …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A beginner’s guide to public sex
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-a-beginners-guide-to-public-sex/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 17:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>B. C. Maile,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-a-beginners-guide-to-public-sex/</guid>
        <description>So, since this is the last issue before the Spring break, and as people customarily tend to travel during breaks, this article is going to be about taking advantage of opportunities to have sex in unusual locations. Of course, I’m not referring to France (their love of cheese is not unusual – just …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The felix sex survey 2017 #callmedaddy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-16-the-felix-sex-survey-2017-callmedaddy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2017 19:22:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,Felix Editor,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-16-the-felix-sex-survey-2017-callmedaddy/</guid>
        <description>The 2017 felix sex survey is now LIVE! Fill it out here
</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Self love
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-self-love/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 14:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>B. C. Maile,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-self-love/</guid>
        <description> Toys for girls If you’re a girl and you’ve never tried a sex toy, that’s absolutely fine. It’s your body and you should do with it as you please. I do feel, however, that if you weren’t aware of the existence of sex toys, you should probably know about them. There are a wide range of dildos and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Enter the kink | BDSM 101
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-enter-the-kink-bdsm-101/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 16:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>B. C. Maile,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-enter-the-kink-bdsm-101/</guid>
        <description> Following the election theme, today I’m going to talk about relinquishing control of yourself to someone who you deem trustworthy enough not to cause permanent damage to your well-being. Welcome to BDSM 101.
There’s been a fair bit of press around BDSM since the release of those Fifty Shades of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Enter the kink | Looning
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-enter-the-kink-looning/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 15:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>B. C. Maile,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-enter-the-kink-looning/</guid>
        <description>Dan got into the shower, washing himself. Holly said she would clear up the mess they had made after the pump-to-pop in the sleeping bag. He still couldn&amp;rsquo;t believe what Holly did for his birthday. They had had a few sessions with balloons before but nothing like this. Last time they had a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is porn hurting your brain?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-is-porn-hurting-your-brain/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:54:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-is-porn-hurting-your-brain/</guid>
        <description>Last night I masturbated. That’s not particularly exciting in itself – a pretty standard Thursday night – but when I found myself alone in bed looking for some me-time, I automatically reached for my phone for some inspiration. Realising that I didn’t know when I got in this habit, so I decided to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fuck Valentine’s Day | Asexual and aromantic
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-fuck-valentines-day-asexual-and-aromantic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 14:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-fuck-valentines-day-asexual-and-aromantic/</guid>
        <description>The first two weeks in February are an infernal nightmare of constant bombardment with advertisements for jewellery, chocolates, and lingerie – all for that ‘special someone’. People in relationships presumably don’t mind. Single people complain incessantly about it. For aromantics however, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A gay and a lesbian walk into a bar...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-a-gay-and-a-lesbian-walk-into-a-bar/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 14:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>B. C. Maile,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-a-gay-and-a-lesbian-walk-into-a-bar/</guid>
        <description> This week, I met with B.R Coli, a female queer friend, to talk about sex. We wanted to shed some light on the general ins and outs and common misconceptions surrounding gay sex, as well as learn a bit about each other’s sex lives and see what common ground we have, and what’s different between man …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I heard you like... food?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-i-heard-you-like-food/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 18:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,B. C. Maile,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-i-heard-you-like-food/</guid>
        <description> Have you ever found yourself aroused by the thought of having a cream pie pushed into your face or cracking eggs over someone’s chest? Of course you have. Well, you’re not alone. This fringe phenomenon is called ‘Wet and Messy Fetishism’, often abbreviated to WAM or simply called sploshing. Fans of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How not to fall in love with someone (from Metric)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-how-not-to-fall-in-love-with-someone-from-metric/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Theresa Davey,Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-how-not-to-fall-in-love-with-someone-from-metric/</guid>
        <description> This is a follow up to our piece ‘How to have a one night stand (in Metric)’. For those of you who somehow missed it, we provided a tried-and-tested plan of action designed to get you laid after a night in Metric. This plan was meant to get you in and out without leaving any trace. But expectedly, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tossing fruit salad
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-tossing-fruit-salad/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 16:21:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-tossing-fruit-salad/</guid>
        <description> I know that times are tough when you go back home for the holidays. You’ve got used to having your freedom and privacy during term time, and maybe even got used to having a bae that keeps the sexual frustration at bay. Maybe you’ve got used to being able to use that corn-on-the-cob shaped vibrator …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to have a one night stand (in Metric)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-how-to-have-a-one-night-stand-in-metric/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 16:14:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-how-to-have-a-one-night-stand-in-metric/</guid>
        <description> 1 | Preparation If you’re planning on pulling, you need to prepare yourself and your environment. This means making sure that your personal grooming is on point and your fridge is stocked. Sex is 90% preparation, 10% copulation. Good things to have - A clean bathroom - Spare towels (clean spare …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Disabled people are not sexless
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-disabled-people-are-not-sexless/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 15:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-disabled-people-are-not-sexless/</guid>
        <description>Life is hard, and finding our way through the labyrinth of dating, relationships, and sex is one of the hardest and most formidable tasks we face as millennials. One thing that’s usually a given is that we all like sex (unless you’re asexual, which is totally okay, or you make the choice not to have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Masturbation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-masturbation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 14:46:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-masturbation/</guid>
        <description>  Yes, masturbation. We all do it, and those who say they don’t are probably lying. Right? Well, actually, maybe not. The felix Sex Survey reveals that year on year, about 10% of us never indulge in a little self-pleasure, with that number skewed by around a quarter of the women who never polish the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Masc4Masc
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-masc4masc/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 15:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-masc4masc/</guid>
        <description>Masculinity. Is it good? Is it bad? Will it get you laid, or do you just think it will? In short: who knows? But we did some research (and asked a lot of people) to try and at least vaguely answer some of these questions.
It was really interesting talking to straight men about masculinity and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The politics of pubes
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-the-politics-of-pubes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 15:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-the-politics-of-pubes/</guid>
        <description> Have you ever felt like someone was judging your pubes? Most of us have felt under some pressure to neaten up, groom, or man-scape our bits, but is this a social expectation that we place on ourselves, or do other people actually care about how well maintained we are down there?
When it comes to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We asked for your sex stories. This is what we got.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-we-asked-for-your-sex-stories-this-is-what-we-got/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 15:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-we-asked-for-your-sex-stories-this-is-what-we-got/</guid>
        <description> Call me James It’s the day after the 2015 General Election. I, a Labour voter, am heartbroken, and have just spent four hours on a coach to visit my tory-voting then-boyfriend. I’m pleasantly surprised by the lack of gloating and the sex has temporarily taken my mind off of my woes – that is until …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Drunk consent is not consent. My rape story
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-drunk-consent-is-not-consent-my-rape-story/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 22:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-drunk-consent-is-not-consent-my-rape-story/</guid>
        <description>This week the coat I lost on the night I was raped found its way back to me.
Having languished, dirty and unloved, at the back of a cupboard in a house I occasionally visited for parties, it was unearthed in a start-of-year clean and returned to me. I had been there a year and a half ago for a club …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are you a Tinder racist?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-21-are-you-a-tinder-racist/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 12:49:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-21-are-you-a-tinder-racist/</guid>
        <description>Racial discrimination. It’s everywhere. Blatant or covert. If you deny that it’s an integral part of our society, you’re either an alien or white. Workplace, education, media. It seeps through every aspect of society. So it obviously comes as no surprise that it would influence the way we select our …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ten things I hate about you
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-7-ten-things-i-hate-about-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 17:32:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Theresa Davey,Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-7-ten-things-i-hate-about-you/</guid>
        <description> We’ve come to the end of Freshers’ Week, and maybe you’ve had a bit too much fun. We’ve all been there, made mistakes, and done things that we live to regret with the bad-boy (or girl) hall senior who seems so mature and experienced. Regardless of how, when, or why, many people all over Imperial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sex in London | A short introduction
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-sex-in-london-a-short-introduction/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 20:32:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-sex-in-london-a-short-introduction/</guid>
        <description> You moved to London! Wooh! Soon you’ll realise that this city is split into various different areas, each with it’s own set of tribes, social hot spots and cultural practices. Speaking of cultural practices, there are certainly sex things that are more likely to occur in some places rather than …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
