<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ck806/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ck806/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Cillian Murphy Mesmeric in NT’s Misterman
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-cillian-murphy-mesmeric-in-nts-misterman/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 17:38:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Knight,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-cillian-murphy-mesmeric-in-nts-misterman/</guid>
        <description>God, redemption, religion, the forces of good and evil. It is hard to tackle these none too light topics in a manner which doesn’t become cumbersome. Peter Cadwell did it in The Fighter’s Ballad, but confronts the bull head-on – the film is no laughing matter. Enda Walsh’s Misterman deals with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Take your seat
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-take-your-seat/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 22:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Knight,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-take-your-seat/</guid>
        <description>What starts off as the kind of play you think will predominantly explore the extremes to which political correctness is taken – sometimes creating just the awkwardness and indignity it hopes to avoid – changes course and ends up shining a very cynical light on the soulless and business-only …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science fiction, but not as you know it
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-27-science-fiction-but-not-as-you-know-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 14:14:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Knight,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-27-science-fiction-but-not-as-you-know-it/</guid>
        <description>The small, dusty and cramped environs of the Imperial College Science Fiction Library may serve as a true reflection of how the genre is valued and viewed by many&amp;hellip; and this is the science fiction library of the country’s leading science university. The tiny library houses over 7000 books and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Globe: just as you like it
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-the-globe-just-as-you-like-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 23:48:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Knight,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-the-globe-just-as-you-like-it/</guid>
        <description>The British summer has officially begun. Shakespeare’s Globe theatre has set its band of players onto the road for three months of comedy – As You Like It. And what a riotous three months it promises to be. James Dacre directs a cast of eight who take on double that number of parts in this Victorian …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Swinging from the chandeliers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-7-swinging-from-the-chandeliers/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2011 09:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Knight,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-7-swinging-from-the-chandeliers/</guid>
        <description>It all started in the early Sixties, in New York, of course. The clear delineations between artists and dancers were broken down and the Judson Dance Theatre came into being. A dance troupe operating in the spirit of its time, rebelling against the conventions of modern dance and ballet – a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Breakfast at Tiffany&#39;s
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-17-breakfast-at-tiffanys/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 11:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Knight,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-17-breakfast-at-tiffanys/</guid>
        <description>5am, October 2nd 1960 and director Blake Edwards is granted an extremely rare and fortuitous moment of calmness, undisturbed by traffic, on New York’s Fifth Avenue. It is the first hour of the first day of filming what will become one of the most iconic romantic comedies of all time. A young woman …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Art of the Album
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-17-the-art-of-the-album/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 11:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Knight,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-17-the-art-of-the-album/</guid>
        <description>The South Bank’s OXO Tower is known for its vertiginous height, but resting at its base at river level is a small gem of a gallery, currently home to ‘The Art of the Album’ exhibition. The Hyper Gallery specialises in “rock n roll image making” – it is not often that one is welcomed to a gallery by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FELA! Leave your shy outside
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-12-fela-leave-your-shy-outside/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2010 17:10:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Knight,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-12-fela-leave-your-shy-outside/</guid>
        <description>Musician. Freedom fighter. Sax, trumpet and keyboard player. Polygamist. Fela Ransome Kuti, the Father of Afrobeat, was something of a phenomenon. His infectious and politically charged music was quick to sweep the African continent and then the world throughout the 70s and beyond. He created a wild …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Descent into Dotage
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-2-the-descent-into-dotage/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2010 12:22:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Knight,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-2-the-descent-into-dotage/</guid>
        <description>One actor, no more than a few minutes of monologue and the rest tape recordings. Combined with little action and the ponderous nature of Samuel Beckett’s plays, Krapp’s Last Tape doesn’t necessarily promise the most easy going of theatre experiences. Michael Gambon (no introductions necessary) plays …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The ENO&#39;s new season kicks off with a new version of Gounod&#39;s Faust
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-9-23-the-enos-new-season-kicks-off-with-a-new-version-of-gounods-faust/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2010 10:31:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Knight,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-9-23-the-enos-new-season-kicks-off-with-a-new-version-of-gounods-faust/</guid>
        <description>One expects one&amp;rsquo;s first trip to the opera to dazzle. Or one expects to be overwhelmed by its cultural gravitas and highbrow nature. Naively thinking that opera would be free from the gimmicks and glitz of musical theatre, this reviewer&amp;rsquo;s first foray into opera left a lot to be desired. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Liberté, égalité, fraternité
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-9-21-libert-galit-fraternit/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 14:12:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Knight,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-9-21-libert-galit-fraternit/</guid>
        <description>The rhetorical bombast of revolutionary Paris, 1794, puts the modern era of bland soundbites, media management and political PR to shame. Obsessive revolutionaries, following and manipulating the public will according to their own bloodthirsty instinct for self-preservation, fill this new production …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You&#39;ve gotta ask yourself one question: Do I feel lucky? Well, do ya, Punk?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-9-15-youve-gotta-ask-yourself-one-question-do-i-feel-lucky-well-do-ya-punk/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 17:12:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Knight,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-9-15-youve-gotta-ask-yourself-one-question-do-i-feel-lucky-well-do-ya-punk/</guid>
        <description>Exactly one year after making its debut on stage at the Lyric Theatre, Simon Stephens’ Punk Rock crashes back to Hammersmith with an updated cast of bright young things.
While one may question the cultural relevance of punk rock to a play that was written in 2009 and which doesn’t (strictly …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
