<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/stv07/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/stv07/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>In Search of Inspiration
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-in-search-of-inspiration/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 20:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-in-search-of-inspiration/</guid>
        <description>Complacency is a cruel mistress. She lures you in with a sense of comfort: that failing an exam, or not getting the degree you wanted, or that mediocrity itself might just be… fine. That you’ll survive, and see tomorrow, and the next day – and nothing will really change. And if nothing changes, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New term, new season and a new colour palette to match
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-new-term-new-season-and-a-new-colour-palette-to-match/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:21:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,Alice Yang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-new-term-new-season-and-a-new-colour-palette-to-match/</guid>
        <description>Red
Red has always held a special place in the hearts of women as a symbol of power, confidence and sensuality – an eye-catching scarlet lipstick for seduction, chic red nails for timeless elegance and, of course, scarlet-soled Louboutins for a woman truly in control.
Red is a colour for turning …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A guide to blagging fashion month
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-a-guide-to-blagging-fashion-month/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 20:54:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-a-guide-to-blagging-fashion-month/</guid>
        <description>For those unfamiliar, fashion month is a bi-annual occasion made up of fashion weeks in the four fashion capitals, where the fashion community (editors, buyers, bloggers and celebrities alike) collects to view the major designers’ collections for the following season. This September saw the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fashion week highlights for autumn/winter 2012
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-fashion-week-highlights-for-autumnwinter-2012/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 20:55:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,Alice Yang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-fashion-week-highlights-for-autumnwinter-2012/</guid>
        <description>Alexander McQueen
Once again, the organic references at McQueen were seared with a modern intricacy, the shoes heel-less and the models’ eyes hidden behind mirrored visors. It was curious to watch the clothes move, each shaggy twist of Mongolian lamb fur, ostrich feather and goat fur undulating and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Suit Up: an idiot’s guide to the who, what, where, and how of formalwear
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-suit-up-an-idiots-guide-to-the-who-what-where-and-how-of-formalwear/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 20:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Yang,Saskia Verhagen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-suit-up-an-idiots-guide-to-the-who-what-where-and-how-of-formalwear/</guid>
        <description> Double-Breasted Suit The Man
The double-breasted suit was once thought to be reserved for a particular type of imperious middle-aged bore, chortling at something distinctly unfunny at a gentleman’s club or boating event of some description. Thankfully, this stereotype no longer applies. A favourite …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Give your gifts in style
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-give-your-gifts-in-style/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 21:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,Alice Yang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-give-your-gifts-in-style/</guid>
        <description>UNDER £20 Girls: Body-chain (£12-15)
 A completely unique gift inspired by Leonardo himself, and beautifully crafted by one of our own (Annabel St John-Lyle, Year 4 MechEng), these cross-body necklaces lend a downtown-chic touch to the plainest of outfits. Worn over a white tee, or a black dress, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Interview Dressing: Womenswear
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-interview-dressing-womenswear/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 20:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-interview-dressing-womenswear/</guid>
        <description>Informal Interviews
Here we’re talking about a company dinner with a few executives, or perhaps a casual interview for a cool media post somewhere you’ll find yourself fetching everyone’s tea order for your first six months of employment. This type of interview means deciphering the impossible …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2012 Spring/Summer highlights hot from the catwalks
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-12-2012-springsummer-highlights-hot-from-the-catwalks/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2011 17:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,Alice Yang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-12-2012-springsummer-highlights-hot-from-the-catwalks/</guid>
        <description>Alexander McQueen
Surely those most critical of critics in the fashion industry must get tired of singing the praises of a woman who has slipped so perfectly into the 8-inch sculpted platforms of a designer whose shoes they claimed could ne’er be filled. Alas, no dice. Sarah Burton’s latest aquatic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Having a fashion fling online
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-having-a-fashion-fling-online/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 22:09:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laura Johnston,Saskia Verhagen,Alice Yang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-having-a-fashion-fling-online/</guid>
        <description>Style Bubble
Susanna Lau (aka Susie Bubble) is undoubtedly Britain’s most followed fashion blogger. The London-based 28-year-old, who once wrote about sneaking into fashion week shows, claiming, “If you’re ballsy enough to act like you’re somebody, SOMEONE’s gonna fall for it eventually,” now graces …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fashion through the decades, the good and the bad
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-fashion-through-the-decades-the-good-and-the-bad/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 21:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Yang,Saskia Verhagen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-fashion-through-the-decades-the-good-and-the-bad/</guid>
        <description>1940s
Iconic: Dior&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;New Look&amp;rsquo;
“In 1947, my first collection was successful beyond my wildest dreams,” remarked Christian Dior after he showcased a catwalk so revolutionary that it not only defined the 40s by majorly changing the way women dressed, but is still constantly referred …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Designer Horcrux
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-a-designer-horcrux/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 10:22:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,Federica Amato,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-a-designer-horcrux/</guid>
        <description>Which girl, provided she has already satisfied all primary concerns (food, water, shelter etc.) doesn’t dream of a clothing collection on the scale of, say, Blair Waldorf or Carrie Bradshaw? And within those ladies’ swoon-inducing wardrobes, which does not contain their essential Louis Vuitton …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tisci to replace disgraced Galliano?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-tisci-to-replace-disgraced-galliano/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 20:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-tisci-to-replace-disgraced-galliano/</guid>
        <description>After allegations of anti-semitic and racial slurs against a couple in a Parisian café, and the release of a damning video evidencing yet more abusive behaviour, John Galliano was dismissed from his role as designer for Christian Dior last Thursday. Although the fashion world has been rocked by the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Boutique du jour: One, Two, Three...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-boutique-du-jour-one-two-three/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 19:33:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-boutique-du-jour-one-two-three/</guid>
        <description>Tucked away in Shoreditch, lives one of London’s most exciting concept stores. 123. Offering beautifully crafted, locally sourced British clothing and accessories, as well as homeware and other trinkets, the main ethos of 123 is anti-mass production: British and vintage sourcing and recycling. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Menswear in Milan: Trendwatch
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-menswear-in-milan-trendwatch/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 19:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-menswear-in-milan-trendwatch/</guid>
        <description>Crayola Bright Colour
Unusually for the Autumn/Winter menswear collections, the runways were rather jolly - credited to the flashes of colour seen especially at Burberry Prorsum, Jil Sander and Bottega Veneta. There was none of the jewel-hued colour blocking we saw over at womenswear, but just pops …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The rise and rise of the Fashion Blog
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-the-rise-and-rise-of-the-fashion-blog/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 20:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-the-rise-and-rise-of-the-fashion-blog/</guid>
        <description>The fashion industry has always been deemed inaccessible, elitist and perhaps slightly indimidating by general consensus. It seems only natural, then, for people to start taking fashion into their own hands, and out of the perfectly manicured talons of the fashion editrixes at Vogue and the like. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An iconic life in pictures: Audrey Hepburn by Bob Willoughby
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-an-iconic-life-in-pictures-audrey-hepburn-by-bob-willoughby/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 20:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-an-iconic-life-in-pictures-audrey-hepburn-by-bob-willoughby/</guid>
        <description>Yet another photographic tome on the ubiquitous Ms Audrey Hepburn – there are so many out there now that if you didn’t know better, this one, by the late renowned Hollywood photographer Bob Willoughby is just another one on the shelf.
I would beg to differ. Bob Willoughby’s favourite subject, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Santi: A South Kensington sanctuary
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-santi-a-south-kensington-sanctuary/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 20:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-santi-a-south-kensington-sanctuary/</guid>
        <description>There is a place, inconspicuous and elusive to the untrained eye, where the weathered creatures of West London emerge calm, bright and restored. A spa, in South Kensington, which offers the most advanced techniques to enhance and perfect the skin. Only what they don’t tell you, is that it all goes a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to London
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-welcome-to-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 19:09:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-welcome-to-london/</guid>
        <description>London is a quintessential fashion capital. Though we don’t have the edgy cool of New York, the elegant chic of Paris or the classic luxury of Milan, we have quirkiness and an extraordinary propensity to seek originality, using every sartorial tool in the box to illustrate exactly who we are, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Renaissance of the Chino
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-10-renaissance-of-the-chino/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 15:41:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saskia Verhagen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-10-renaissance-of-the-chino/</guid>
        <description>Good news medic boys! Your favourite sports night style staple and go-to firms-wear has found itself on the hottest catwalks of London, Paris, Milan and New York: yes, chinos are actually in vogue.
Admittedly, the modest chino is somewhat underrated; it is the male equivalent of the trusty black …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
