<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ozbil_ege_dumenci/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ozbil_ege_dumenci/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Amelie: A Warm Hug in this Cruel World</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-amelie-warm-hug-in-cruel-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-amelie-warm-hug-in-cruel-world/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
Adapted from the five-time Oscar nominated French language movie of the same name, Amelie tells the story of a girl with a wild imagination who takes pleasure in performing “small, but extraordinary acts of kindness” with the goal of bringing joy to those around her. What must she do to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best of the Decade: Editor’s Choice (Ozbil Ege Dumenci)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-best-of-decade-editors-choice-ozbil/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-best-of-decade-editors-choice-ozbil/</guid>
        <description>Let me start this by saying this is by no means an exhaustive list. I’m sure there’s shows that I haven’t got around to seeing yet that are just as great or even better than the stuff on this list. So, before you get all angry at me for not including Breaking Bad or Westworld on the list, it’s only …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Binge of the Week: The Crown (Season 3)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-binge-of-week-the-crown-season-3/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-binge-of-week-the-crown-season-3/</guid>
        <description>Season 3: 4.5 stars
Upon the initial release of the first season back in 2016, it was made very clear that the audience should not get too attached to the cast, as they would only be playing the Royal Family for the first two seasons. However, Claire Foy, Matt Smith and Vanessa Kirby, who played …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tepid Reviews for Dear Evan Hansen?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-tepid-reviews-dear-evan-hansen/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-tepid-reviews-dear-evan-hansen/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
It was rather surprising to me that the majority of the professional reviews for Dear Evan Hansen, the Broadway juggernaut that just made its way to the West End stage, have been rather tepid. Unlike its Broadway counterpart, which was showered with endless praise and a plethora of five …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Illusion of Accessible Theatre: How Far Have we Come and How Far do we Have Left to Go?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-illusion-accessible-theatre/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-illusion-accessible-theatre/</guid>
        <description>Ever since my stint as a Felix arts editor began, I’ve been preaching the importance of making theatre more accessible. For the most part, the baby-boomer leaning demographics at the theatre astonish me. I strongly believe this medium of arts can be a formative part of a young person’s development. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>War Horse: A Year Later</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-war-horse-a-year-later/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-war-horse-a-year-later/</guid>
        <description>Last year, I was lucky enough to watch War Horse at the National Theatre, its return to the original National Theatre venue a celebration of the centenary of Armistice Day.I loved it so much the first time that I grabbed a different friend the next evening and ended up queueing for return tickets to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My life with Michael: 10 Years of Thriller Live, Written by Gary Lloyd</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-my-life-with-michael-10-years-of-thriller-live-written-gary-lloyd/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-my-life-with-michael-10-years-of-thriller-live-written-gary-lloyd/</guid>
        <description>2.5 stars
It seems quite ironic to me that the author, despite the title, has never actually met Michael Jackson. In fact, this admission comes as the very first sentence of the book. With this out of the way, the book focuses on the long-running (10 years, to be exact) West End show, Thriller …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Death of a Salesman</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-death-salesman/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-death-salesman/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
Written by the iconic Arthur Miller, Death of a Salesman is often hailed as one of the best plays of the 20th century. Adding to its fame, the play recently made the news when the roof of the theatre ‘collapsed’ on the audience twenty minutes into the show, a mere 48 hours after my own …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Arts: Interview with Anita-Joy Uwajeh</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-interview-with-anita-joy-uwajeh/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-interview-with-anita-joy-uwajeh/</guid>
        <description>Cyrano de Bergerac is a French verse-play written in 1897, telling the fictionalised story of the eponymous nobleman., whose large nose prevents him from winning his love, Roxane. Despite its somewhat peculiar plot, the play has proven surprisingly timeless through the ages. There are at least five …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Binge of the Week: Barry (Seasons 1 and 2)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-binge-week-barry-seasons-1-2/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-binge-week-barry-seasons-1-2/</guid>
        <description>Season 1: 4 stars
Season 2: 5 stars
Despite taking the States by storm, Barry has been a pretty low-key show on this side of the pond. With 30 Emmy nominations, the HBO show tells the story of Barry (Bill Hader), a hitman who follows his target to an acting class in Los Angeles, and, by some miracle …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lungs: Royalty Takes Over the Old Vic</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-lungs-royalty-takes-old-vic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-lungs-royalty-takes-old-vic/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
Running for a mere three weeks at The Old Vic, Lungs promised to recapture the magic that Claire Foy and Matt Smith brought to the first two seasons of The Crown on Netflix to the stage. I’m not one to blindly buy tickets for the sake of the play’s star power (I made that mistake once with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Meet the Editors: Ozbil - The Fanatical One</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-meet-editors-ozbil-fanatical-one/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-meet-editors-ozbil-fanatical-one/</guid>
        <description>Having joined Felix Arts as a writer last year, I often think about how different life would have been had I joined sooner. I first heard about Felix Arts from my housemate, and quickly realised that this would be one of the best ways to enjoy the London theatre scene on a student budget – and enjoy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Noises Off</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-noises-off/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-noises-off/</guid>
        <description>2 stars
Hailed as ‘iconic’ and as ‘the funniest farce ever written’, I thought I was in for a treat when I went to see Noises Off at the Garrick Theatre. Having been revived on Broadway various times, I was sure that the play would be nothing short of magnificent. Oh, boy, was I wrong.
Noises Off is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Schitt’s Creek is the Best Show On-air Right Now and you Should Really Get on Board</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-schitts-creek-best-show-on-air-right-now-get-on-board/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-schitts-creek-best-show-on-air-right-now-get-on-board/</guid>
        <description>In my close friendship circles, I have always had a bit of a reputation for getting a little too passionate about, well, pretty much everything. So, when I started to relentlessly insist that everyone should really, really, REALLY should be getting on board the Schitt’s Creek train and binge this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Beginner&#39;s Guide to the West End: how to score cheap (or even free) tickets</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-a-beginners-guide-to-the-west-end-how-to-score-cheap-tickets/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-a-beginners-guide-to-the-west-end-how-to-score-cheap-tickets/</guid>
        <description> Studying at such a science-based university, it is often easy to forget that London is one of the world’s art capitals, with an endless number of plays, musicals, and exhibitions at our doorstep. Unfortunately, the theatre has a bit of a reputation for being expensive, and therefore inaccessible …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fiddler on The Roof</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-fiddler-on-the-roof/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-fiddler-on-the-roof/</guid>
        <description>I’ve always had a relative fondness towards Fiddler on The Roof, with a vague memory of watching the movie, at least the ‘If I Were A Rich Man’ segment from the movie, at my aunt’s house when I was much, much smaller. Therefore, I was delighted to hear that not only the show was being revived on the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This is Going to Hurt</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-this-is-going-to-hurt/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-this-is-going-to-hurt/</guid>
        <description>Adam Kay is a former junior doctor specializing in obstetrics and gynaecology, and he just happens to be an Imperial College School of Medicine (ICSM) graduate. During his gruelling training, he kept a diary, scribbling away the often-funny details of his time working for the NHS. Upon quitting his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Downstate</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-27-downstate/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-27-downstate/</guid>
        <description>Now playing at the National Theatre, Downstate is a National Theatre-Steppenwolf Theatre Company co-production written by the Pulitzer-winning Bruce Norris. It deals with the lives of four men convicted of sex crimes against minors forced to live together in a group home due to circumstances beyond …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Switzerland: Patricia Highsmith is deeply unlikable… but is there more to the iconic author?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-switzerland-patricia-highsmith-is-deeply-unlikable-but-is-there-more-to-the-iconic-author/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-switzerland-patricia-highsmith-is-deeply-unlikable-but-is-there-more-to-the-iconic-author/</guid>
        <description>Patricia Highsmith (portrayed by Phyllis Logan), the American author of some of the most beloved murder novels such as Strangers on a Train and The Talented Mr. Ripley , is visited by Edward Ridgeway (Calum Finlay) in her retreat bunker in Switzerland. Ridgeway, a young publisher, has been sent …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>War Horse: Theatre At Its Finest, Moving From First Moment to Curtain Call.</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-war-horse-theatre-at-its-finest-moving-from-first-moment-to-curtain-call/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-war-horse-theatre-at-its-finest-moving-from-first-moment-to-curtain-call/</guid>
        <description>My friends always make fun of me for seeing certain plays multiple times. There are some shows, like Hamilton or Harry Potter and the Cursed Child (I know, controversial), that as I leave the theatre, I know that I need to witness again to truly appreciate. Well, let me just say that, not only did I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Courage Everywhere: And Others – Emotion-Packed to The Core</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-courage-everywhere-and-others-emotion-packed-to-the-core/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-courage-everywhere-and-others-emotion-packed-to-the-core/</guid>
        <description>Over the last week, the National Theatre has marked the 100th anniversary of (some) women in the UK getting the right to vote through a series of talks, rehearsed readings and screenings that reflect on suffrage and the fight for equality. And Others, aptly named to represent the women whose voices …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Company</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-company/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ozbil Ege Dumenci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-company/</guid>
        <description>As I walked to my seat in Gielgud Theatre, the main worry I had was whether swapping the genders in this classic musical would be anything more than an audience-grabbing gimmick.
Well, it did work. I was there, praying that it would add more than advertising value to the show.
The play explores …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
