<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Travel on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/travel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Travel on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/travel/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>7 Must-See Destinations for Under £70</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-seven-must-see-destinations-under-70/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-seven-must-see-destinations-under-70/</guid>
        <description>Above: Copenhagen, Denmark
Student life is hard enough as it is, but travelling on a tight budget is a whole other struggle. Finding the perfect getaway only for your bank balance to shatter all your dreams is top two most heart-breaking feelings, and hint – it’s not number two. That’s why for our …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Exploitation of Animals in Wildlife Tourism </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-exploitation-animals-wildlife-tourism/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maya Prashad,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-exploitation-animals-wildlife-tourism/</guid>
        <description>Ecotourism has gained traction in recent years, focusing on socially responsible travel to destinations where flora, fauna, and cultural heritage are the main attractions. Wildlife-encounter tourism is not a new phenomenon, but thanks to social media it has steadily gained popularity. Who amongst us …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How is Brexit Going to Affect My Next Holiday?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-how-brexit-affect-holiday/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-how-brexit-affect-holiday/</guid>
        <description>I know what you’re thinking - another day, another Brexit article. But if you’re anything like us and have the travel bug, then you’re going to want to read this one. With Brexit being delayed once again to January at the soonest, there’s no better time to grab a bargain and finally book flights to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Small Place, Big Adventures</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-small-place-big-adventures/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-small-place-big-adventures/</guid>
        <description>As one of the world’s smallest countries, Singapore has gained popularity as Asia’s corporate capital, but there’s so much more than business on offer when visiting this South East Asian country. Singapore is also one of the safest places you could possibly visit - so whether you’re embarking on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hamburg’s Miniature Delight</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-hamburgs-miniature-delight/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aina Naim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-hamburgs-miniature-delight/</guid>
        <description>While Hamburg is the second largest city in Germany after Berlin, it still lags behind the capital and Munich when in comes to the number of foreign visitors, particularly those who are seeking cultural and historical values that the aforementioned cities offer abundantly.
However, these numbers …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Top 6 Cities You Should Visit in the UK</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-top-6-cities-you-should-visit-in-UK/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Tadros,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-top-6-cities-you-should-visit-in-UK/</guid>
        <description>You might’ve just moved to London and are already missing home and looking for something to do to help distract you – be it camping in the countryside, or lunch on the seaside, England has so much to offer, and London is only the tip of the iceberg, Make the most of your time here and make it a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The cats are finally out of the bag in the Wakayama Prefecture in Japan</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-the-cats-are-finally-out-of-the-bag-in-the-wakayama-prefecture-in-japan/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aina Naim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-the-cats-are-finally-out-of-the-bag-in-the-wakayama-prefecture-in-japan/</guid>
        <description>When a small district at the fringe of a bigger town becomes more and more obscure, how do we revive it? These are the things that are occurring more and more commonly in the rural areas of Japan. Various methods were undertaken with varying degrees of success, but one remote village located just …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Last night I dreamt of Boipeba</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-last-night-i-dreamt-of-boipeba/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christopher Richardson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-last-night-i-dreamt-of-boipeba/</guid>
        <description>I hesitate to utter the word “Bahia”. Bah-eee-yah. It’s beautiful to say it aloud. Also known by its epithet, the “land of happiness”, Bahia is a vibrant state in Northeastern Brazil that for whatever reason has managed to evade many a Latin America travel itinerary. My hesitation to utter the word …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Snæfellsnes Peninsula - Iceland’s hidden gem</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-sn-fellsnes-peninsula-iceland-s-hidden-gem/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aina Naim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-sn-fellsnes-peninsula-iceland-s-hidden-gem/</guid>
        <description>The recent explosive rise in tourism in Iceland is nothing short of amazing. In fact, the Icelandic government is struggling to control the burgeoning tourism industry as more and more curious tourists make their way to the lone nation island to find out what the hype is all about. While Iceland has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Kabylie wedding: stories of volunteering abroad!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-a-kabylie-wedding-stories-of-volunteering-abroad/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marco Rodrigues,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-a-kabylie-wedding-stories-of-volunteering-abroad/</guid>
        <description>I found myself in the in the middle of an AIESEC reunion, right in the heart of Alger, when this tall Algerian man approaches me in Portuguese. I was not expecting that at all, as the spoken language at this meeting was either English, French or Arabic. A week had passed since I left Portugal to do …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Weekend getaways: Poland </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-weekend-getaways-poland/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joana Correia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-weekend-getaways-poland/</guid>
        <description>Poland is probably the most under-rated country of the Baltic states. It sounds distant, cold, under-developed, stuck in the past. None of which is true. Speaking from personal experience, I too was apprehensive about visiting Poland. In simpler words, I was not excited at all. But on a student …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LISBON - is the hype real?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-lisbon-is-the-hype-real/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joana Correia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-lisbon-is-the-hype-real/</guid>
        <description>The plane prepares for landing by circling the beaches, vast kilometres of deep blue waters and white sand dotted by sun-lovers, it makes its descent by overlooking the city and its hills. If this isn’t a scenic landing, I don’t know what is.
Lisbon truly offers it all. And I’m not just talking …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flutes, Flights and Fire-Breathing Dragons</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-flutes-flights-and-fire-breathing-dragons/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lorenzo Silvestri,Rachel Wilson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-flutes-flights-and-fire-breathing-dragons/</guid>
        <description>Dragons, lakes, and music. These three words defined the event of the summer that everyone in IC Wind Band had been looking forward to. This year, Wind Band went further than we’ve ever ventured before, touring in the (mostly) sunny land of Slovenia.
Slovenia’s capital city, Ljubljana, was a welcome …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flying First Class: is it worth the hype?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-flying-first-class-is-it-worth-the-hype/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Noppasit Pongsak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-flying-first-class-is-it-worth-the-hype/</guid>
        <description>Back in 2016, when the rest of my family were on holiday in Hong Kong (where I refused to go as I needed to revise for my January exams), my mother said I needed to take some rest by taking some time off as I was working too hard. So I decided to book a last minute flight with Thai Airways to join …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Scusi, we’re going to Italy: a trip to Verona &amp; Venice</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-scusi-we-re-going-to-italy-a-trip-to-verona-venice/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edita Pileckyte,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-scusi-we-re-going-to-italy-a-trip-to-verona-venice/</guid>
        <description>Italy is a perfect choice for your summer vacation since it has everything – from big famous cities to quiet lesser-known villages and beach towns. You can pop in for a quick weekend getaway or spend a few weeks touring all around the country, whatever floats your boat. It’s also easy to score …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What you need to do before you leave Imperial</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-what-you-need-to-do-before-you-leave-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Alice Davage,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-what-you-need-to-do-before-you-leave-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Watch a premiere
Ever noticed those bright spotlights encircling the night sky over campus? No, they are not signalling an alien invasion. The police are not scouring campus for a wanted criminal either. Although, both of these things would certainly liven up exam season. They are in fact a sign …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Exploring San Francisco: the Golden City by the bay</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-exploring-san-francisco-the-golden-city-by-the-bay/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edita Pileckyte,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-exploring-san-francisco-the-golden-city-by-the-bay/</guid>
        <description>Getting around
Compared to many famous cities in the States, San Francisco is relatively small, so you can easily get around by foot. However, to get a more authentic experience you might want to opt for cycling, which has become increasingly popular in the past few decades – there’s even a Bike to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Top tips for visiting the Greek Islands on a budget</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-top-tips-for-visiting-the-greek-islands-on-a-budget/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elina Michaelidou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-top-tips-for-visiting-the-greek-islands-on-a-budget/</guid>
        <description>Dreaming of visiting the Greek Islands but don’t have all you need to enjoy an Instagram-perfect trip (i.e. money)? Don’t worry, you can still take your memorable shots and experience Greece to its maximum while travelling on a budget if you follow the following tips.
Travel off-peak
Or at least …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Beach better have my money: affordable seaside destinations</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-beach-better-have-my-money-affordable-seaside-destinations/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edita Pileckyte,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-beach-better-have-my-money-affordable-seaside-destinations/</guid>
        <description>With the upcoming summer break, many of us will want to get away from busy and polluted London and relax on the beach. I can’t count the times I was tempted to buy a plane ticket to Spain or Greece for a weekend just to treat myself to some sun and sea. However, flight costs can skyrocket to over …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dartmoor training weekend: rehearsal for hiking in Crete</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-dartmoor-training-weekend-rehearsal-for-hiking-in-crete/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Niamh French,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-dartmoor-training-weekend-rehearsal-for-hiking-in-crete/</guid>
        <description>Our team leader Georgios had asserted himself early on by arriving to our training weekend in a blindingly stylish grey-and-buttercup-yellow outfit. We will be hiking across the Greek island of Crete for three weeks this September with the financial support of Imperial’s Exploration Board, and we …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Los Angeles, I’m yours: five days in Pacific paradise </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-los-angeles-i-m-yours-five-days-in-pacific-paradise/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edita Pileckyte,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-los-angeles-i-m-yours-five-days-in-pacific-paradise/</guid>
        <description>On the first day, we visited the beaches, starting from Santa Monica. It’s a separate city with lively streets, full of shops and diners to choose from. The beach is enormously wide and separated from the streets by tall cliffs. The Santa Monica pier offers a breath-taking view of the Pacific Ocean …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Paris mon amour: three days in the City of Lights</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-paris-mon-amour-three-days-in-the-city-of-lights/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edita Pileckyte,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-paris-mon-amour-three-days-in-the-city-of-lights/</guid>
        <description>Paris holds a special place in my heart because it was my first travel destination since I moved to London, and it made me fall in love with travelling. It was during the revision period for my January exams in 2nd year, when I got the idea, which seemed so crazy at the time, to just pack my bags …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London from above: Felix’s guide to the best views</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-london-from-above-felix-s-guide-to-the-best-views/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elina Michaelidou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-london-from-above-felix-s-guide-to-the-best-views/</guid>
        <description> The London Eye
 The London Eye is one of the most famous attractions in London, where you can see views of Big Ben, the Houses of Parliament, and other Westminster buildings unfold along the River Thames. It has 32 capsules that run non-stop when the attraction is open, and each of them can carry …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The French Riviera – a dreamy Mediterranean seaside paradise!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-the-french-riviera-a-dreamy-mediterranean-seaside-paradise/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edita Pileckyte,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-the-french-riviera-a-dreamy-mediterranean-seaside-paradise/</guid>
        <description>As one of the most popular Mediterranean resorts, Nice does really live up to its expectations! Its main highlight is the azure sea, so blue it almost looks artificial and does justice to the region’s name. The only imperfection of the beach is that it’s made of sharp stones – quite uncomfortable to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grand Canyon and Death Valley: the pride of South-West USA</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-grand-canyon-and-death-valley-the-pride-of-south-west-usa/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edita Pileckyte,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-grand-canyon-and-death-valley-the-pride-of-south-west-usa/</guid>
        <description>During my three day stay in Las Vegas, I decided to visit two of the most famous North American national parks – Grand Canyon in Arizona and Death Valley in California. They were a huge contrast from the busy and posh Vegas, and were an integral part of my US experience. While one day is more than …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Out of season in North America’s national parks</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-out-of-season-in-north-america-s-national-parks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Konstantin Holzner,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-out-of-season-in-north-america-s-national-parks/</guid>
        <description>There are many valid reasons why you should visit North America’s national parks in high season. It’s when the weather is reliably good, when the flowers are in bloom, or when certain wildlife encounters are the most likely. However, high season comes at a price, and not just literally. Many of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>From Imperial to the Amazon jungle</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-from-imperial-to-the-amazon-jungle/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charlotte Pickering,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-from-imperial-to-the-amazon-jungle/</guid>
        <description>Oh God, where am I? All these trees look the same. The way up was easy (it was just, well, up). But now every direction is down, I can’t hear the stream anymore and I can’t see anything through these trees.” Sometimes in life, you find yourself someplace odd and you struggle to understand how you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix’s Guide to backpacking in South East Asia</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-felix-s-guide-to-backpacking-in-south-east-asia/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yan Kee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-felix-s-guide-to-backpacking-in-south-east-asia/</guid>
        <description>I’m sure many people either are thinking about or have had the idea before of a backpacking trip around South East Asia (SEA). It’s a region filled with its own unique culture, traditional cuisine that you can’t find anywhere else in the world, and – most importantly – its beautifully untouched yet …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mallorca – more than just a party island!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-mallorca-more-than-just-a-party-island/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Whiting,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-mallorca-more-than-just-a-party-island/</guid>
        <description>Despite its reputation as a European party destination, there is much more to Mallorca than drinking the night away in its numerous party resorts, such as Magaluf. With a peak higher than Ben Nevis in Scotland (the highest mountain in the British Isles) and many spots for hiking and climbing, this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>When sky is not the limit: nature’s light show among the stars</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-when-sky-is-not-the-limit-nature-s-light-show-among-the-stars/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Exploring Hobbit,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-when-sky-is-not-the-limit-nature-s-light-show-among-the-stars/</guid>
        <description>The enchanting Aurora Borealis, or northern lights, frolic in the sky when charged particles from the sun become trapped in the Earth’s magnetic field, emitting colourful lights of green, scarlet, crimson, and more. The lights unravel themselves usually on dark clear nights. It is proposed that the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The miners make it to the end of the trail</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-05-the-miners-make-it-to-the-end-of-the-trail/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Georgios Chatzitheoklitos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-05-the-miners-make-it-to-the-end-of-the-trail/</guid>
        <description>Day 11 – Stage 11A
Having set our minds on doing the alternative high route in pursuit of more stunning views, we agreed to leave at 7am. The girls were punctual as always, and at 7am they went to the boys tent to find them still sleeping! But the boys overslept after having a nightmare with the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The trip must go on: moving on up in Corsica</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-the-trip-must-go-on-moving-on-up-in-corsica/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Georgios Chatzitheoklitos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-the-trip-must-go-on-moving-on-up-in-corsica/</guid>
        <description> Day Six: Stage Five
 A day behind our schedule due to the storm on day four, we began hiking at 6:30am just as the sun was rising. The first two hours were relentless climbing in 70mph winds that kept blowing us over. At the top, the wind was so strong that we could lean our whole body weight into …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Further adventures on the toughest trail in Europe</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-further-adventures-on-the-toughest-trail-in-europe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Georgios Chatzitheoklitos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-further-adventures-on-the-toughest-trail-in-europe/</guid>
        <description> Day One: Stage 1A
 On the first day we began early, waking up at 5:15am. Kindly driven to our starting point in a small town named Calenzana by our host from the night before, we were nervous but eager to set off. We were all very silent during that drive, contemplating what lay ahead of us. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kicking off the year with the toughest trail in Europe</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-kicking-off-the-year-with-the-toughest-trail-in-europe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Georgios Chatzitheoklitos,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-kicking-off-the-year-with-the-toughest-trail-in-europe/</guid>
        <description> How it all started…
 Being an overly excited prospective student, I was reading all the emails sent by the college. There I stumbled upon the Imperial College Exploration Board and learned about all the student expeditions to various exotic places that the Board had previously supported. Any …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Travelling the Americas in an old fire engine</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-travelling-the-americas-in-an-old-fire-engine/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Konstantin Holzner,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-travelling-the-americas-in-an-old-fire-engine/</guid>
        <description>About three days into our trip, I found myself sitting on a beach in St. Vincent’s Bay, Newfoundland. It’s pretty stunning in general, but for about six weeks every summer it becomes a particularly breath-taking place to be. Humpback whales are abundant in these waters during that time, and this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Exploring Copenhagen (the happiest place on Earth!?)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-exploring-copenhagen-the-happiest-place-on-earth/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elina Michaelidou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-exploring-copenhagen-the-happiest-place-on-earth/</guid>
        <description>This time two years ago, I was on my way to a spontaneous trip to Copenhagen. The spring term had just started, and on Friday of week one, we hopped on an Uber to go to the airport as quickly as possible. I finished my last lecture of the day at 6pm, and the flight was to depart at 8.45pm. I had to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lights will guide you home: catching the northern lights in the UK</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-lights-will-guide-you-home-catching-the-northern-lights-in-the-uk/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elina Michaelidou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-lights-will-guide-you-home-catching-the-northern-lights-in-the-uk/</guid>
        <description>The UK has quite a few spots where the northern lights, or Aurora Borealis, are visible. As you may have guessed already, you have higher chances to see them somewhere up north, particularly in Scotland. However, you’ll be surprised to learn that Aurora Borealis has been noticed as south as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sick of London? Three of England’s gems for a quick weekend getaway</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-sick-of-london-three-of-england-s-gems-for-a-quick-weekend-getaway/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-sick-of-london-three-of-england-s-gems-for-a-quick-weekend-getaway/</guid>
        <description>Who doesn’t like to travel? It’s exciting, adventurous, and a great way to discover new cultures. But sometimes, due to time or price constraints, that’s not an option. In that case, why not take a holiday in our own motherland, the United Kingdom? It has many fantastic travel options that we tend …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chasing birds in Wales: a wildlife experience</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-chasing-birds-in-wales-a-wildlife-experience/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mingke Pan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-chasing-birds-in-wales-a-wildlife-experience/</guid>
        <description>While jogging in the park, have you ever spotted people holding binoculars and looking up in the sky? Or those flipping through a pocket-sized booklet that says ‘Collins Bird Guide’ on the cover? They are birdwatchers, with the love for birds and curiosity to explore nature. As one of them, I go out …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Calling all cyclists: take your bike on holiday for an unforgettable cycling adventure </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-calling-all-cyclists-take-your-bike-on-holiday-for-an-unforgettable-cycling-adventure/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charlotte Pickering,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-calling-all-cyclists-take-your-bike-on-holiday-for-an-unforgettable-cycling-adventure/</guid>
        <description>Most people think of Thailand as a party destination to go to with “the lads”, packed with cheap nights out, but my trip was a bit different. I’m a lone female traveller who doesn’t understand clubs and booze, but I do love cycling, and Thailand has some great mountains with well-maintained roads. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A new craze is taking over Los Angeles, and it just might be your Happy Place</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-a-new-craze-is-taking-over-los-angeles-and-it-just-might-be-your-happy-place/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edita Pileckyte,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-a-new-craze-is-taking-over-los-angeles-and-it-just-might-be-your-happy-place/</guid>
        <description>Currently, the people of Los Angeles are losing their minds over a new pop-up gallery called the Happy Place. Situated in the Arts District in Downtown LA, the place offers a perfect opportunity to forget about your everyday problems and promises to put a smile on your face. The project also prides …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Snowdonia through the eyes of a Fellwanderer</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-snowdonia-through-the-eyes-of-a-fellwanderer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ming Toh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-snowdonia-through-the-eyes-of-a-fellwanderer/</guid>
        <description>There is a rumour that there are more sheep than humans in Wales. And all the road signs are in Welsh and English. Plus you can see the Milky Way when the weather is nice. Intrigued? Come and find out for yourself!
Wales has several national parks with quite different features. Snowdonia National …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The hidden side of Cyprus</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-the-hidden-side-of-cyprus/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elina Michaelidou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-the-hidden-side-of-cyprus/</guid>
        <description>Last month, I found myself at Troodos square in the mountainous part of Cyprus. It wasn’t my first time there (I usually go twice a year) but this time was different. Whilst walking in a small park there, I noticed a sign to the Atalanti Nature Trail, which reminded me that I wanted to visit the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>When in Rome: a weekend-getaway in the Eternal City</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-when-in-rome-a-weekend-getaway-in-the-eternal-city/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edita Pileckyte,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-when-in-rome-a-weekend-getaway-in-the-eternal-city/</guid>
        <description>Among all the deadlines and stress, we deserve some time off, so we can recharge and stay happy, healthy, and productive. And travelling is one of the best ways to do that, am I right? I assume you agree since you’re reading the Travel section. Well, lucky for us travellers, it’s possible to visit …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Time to get your hops up: Felix’s guide to Hop-on Hop-off bus tours</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-time-to-get-your-hops-up-felix-s-guide-to-hop-on-hop-off-bus-tours/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elina Michaelidou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-time-to-get-your-hops-up-felix-s-guide-to-hop-on-hop-off-bus-tours/</guid>
        <description>A Hop-on Hop-off bus tour is a city sightseeing tour, usually on a double-decker bus with the upper level left open. The tour involves a free audio guide in different languages, with the number and variety of the languages depending on the city that the tour bus operates in. In large cities, the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>California on a budget</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-california-on-a-budget/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edita Pileckyte,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-california-on-a-budget/</guid>
        <description> After a draining year at Imperial, and quite possibly an internship-packed summer, most of us crave a vacation, preferably outside London. While coming back home is often enjoyable, going somewhere completely new can be even more appealing. One of the most popular travel destinations is the United …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>When in Rum</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-when-in-rum/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christopher Richardson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-when-in-rum/</guid>
        <description>Wadi Rum, AKA the Valley of the Moon, is Jordan’s largest valley. Not that the size matters much in itself. It’s also Hollywood’s go-to location for all movies Martian, which tells you all you need to know about the kind of landscapes on offer. I was initially dubious about spending several days of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London Calling! Felix’s guide to the capital’s best spots</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-london-calling-felix-s-guide-to-the-capital-s-best-spots/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edita Pileckyte,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-london-calling-felix-s-guide-to-the-capital-s-best-spots/</guid>
        <description>Starting at university, especially one as highly demanding as Imperial, can be both exciting and overwhelming. Most students often find themselves swamped with work from the second week of term, but it’s always worth remembering that by studying here you also live in one of the greatest and most …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bukhara: Dreams of Another Land
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-20-bukhara-dreams-of-another-land/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2015 17:30:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-20-bukhara-dreams-of-another-land/</guid>
        <description>“But there is no such thing as a Silk Road!”
I didn’t quite know how to react. What did she mean? Had my grand plans of an adventure along the ancient Silk Road this summer all been in vain, chasing an imaginary past in the vast and stifling wastelands of Turkestan?
I was giddy in anticipation of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London calling - summer in the captial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-9-london-calling-summer-in-the-captial/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2015 15:52:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-9-london-calling-summer-in-the-captial/</guid>
        <description>Not all of us have the time to jet off to a different location and spend the summer holidays hopping from one destination to another, but that doesn’t mean that you can’t have fun in good old London either. In fact, London is one of the most visited cities of all times and there’s probably a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Travel made easy - the world of apps
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-9-travel-made-easy-the-world-of-apps/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2015 15:10:47 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-9-travel-made-easy-the-world-of-apps/</guid>
        <description>It’s no secret that the internet has revolutionized the world: there are a whole host of information and applications available now that wasn’t there a few decades ago. People can now do everything on their phone that no one could even dream of before – in fact, I still remember putting my phone …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Packing tips for budget airline
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-9-packing-tips-for-budget-airline/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2015 15:03:47 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-9-packing-tips-for-budget-airline/</guid>
        <description>Travelling on budget airline isn’t easy – you got the luggage restriction, liquid restriction and only airline magazines for entertainment. However, with their unbeatable prices you can only grit your teeth and adhere to the increasingly intricate rules of hand luggage restriction to save the extra …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cruising through Colchagua (Valley)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-1-cruising-through-colchagua-valley/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 17:38:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-1-cruising-through-colchagua-valley/</guid>
        <description>A couple of months ago I was just like you: I’d crafted what I thought at the time was the perfect route through South America, cruising merrily along the gringo trail, diverting occasionally for the miscellaneous hidden gems I’d heard about through the grapevine. But as it turned out there were …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Losing yourself in Venice: to boat, or not to boat
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-25-losing-yourself-in-venice-to-boat-or-not-to-boat/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2015 12:59:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-25-losing-yourself-in-venice-to-boat-or-not-to-boat/</guid>
        <description>Perhaps one of the most frequently asked question for travelers in Venice is whether they should take the water buses or not.
And the answer to these questions, as always, is that it depends. On what exactly, you might ask? Here’s a list of factors for you to consider:
1) Are you able to walk for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Volunteer Experience: Working away in Chile’s Colchagua Valley</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-4-volunteer-experience-working-away-in-chiles-colchagua-valley/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 16:35:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-4-volunteer-experience-working-away-in-chiles-colchagua-valley/</guid>
        <description>I’m sure you’re all depressingly familiar with the concept of unpaid internships by now: roll in with a smile, do a little grunt work, leave with a frown, only to be replaced by the next person on the unending list of the exploited. WorkAway.info is a little different. In exchange for a mere 25 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Around the World in 19 Festivals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-17-around-the-world-in-19-festivals/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2015 18:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-17-around-the-world-in-19-festivals/</guid>
        <description>Travel is the only thing you can buy that would make you richer – there’s no denying that visiting a place in person brings history to live in a way that words never can.
What better way to get to know a place and its culture than to take part in a festival? With over 6,500 spoken languages, 194 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Working Holiday - the substainable and immersive way to travel
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-17-working-holiday-the-substainable-and-immersive-way-to-travel/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2015 14:45:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-17-working-holiday-the-substainable-and-immersive-way-to-travel/</guid>
        <description>I had been fascinated by the concept of working holiday for a while now and even more so when an old friend of mine embarked on her own journey to Australia with her boyfriend, updating us on her 6-months adventure through social media. It seems to be a popular alternative for many young people …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Unforgettable, amazing Oaxaca...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-17-the-unforgettable-amazing-oaxaca/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2015 14:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aditya Narayanan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-17-the-unforgettable-amazing-oaxaca/</guid>
        <description>Holidays in Mexico are stereotypically presented as being all about that beach. From Cancun to Tijuana (and Acapulco), the golden sands and azure seas are well trodden by the average foreign tourist. With glorious sunshine all year and relatively calm and clear water, it is the perfect place to laze …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Discover new places through your friends
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-17-discover-new-places-through-your-friends/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2015 14:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-17-discover-new-places-through-your-friends/</guid>
        <description>Or have you ever found an amazing place tucked away in a city that you think you know everything about and wanted to share it to the world?
Whether the answers to both questions are correct, then Kites is the app for you. It allow users to view and write short recommendations anywhere in the world. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kickstarting my life in Mexico City
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-17-kickstarting-my-life-in-mexico-city/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2015 19:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aditya Narayanan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-17-kickstarting-my-life-in-mexico-city/</guid>
        <description>Mexico City glitters at night. Dots of yellow flow across the ground. Like a train of ants, they follow a path as if preordained, in a robotic line with no destination. I can feel the energy from my plane window.
Drugs. Violence. Human trafficking. The typical Western news cycle on most developing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Could College pay for your next holiday?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-17-could-college-pay-for-your-next-holiday/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2015 19:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kamil McClelland,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-17-could-college-pay-for-your-next-holiday/</guid>
        <description>How many people knew there was such a thing as the Imperial Exploration Board? Apparently not that many, as I found out when telling people that I had received their endorsement for a cycling expedition myself and a few friends are planning this summer across Central Asia. And so, I decided to talk …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is buying travel deals on Groupon safe?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-is-buying-travel-deals-on-groupon-safe/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 14:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-is-buying-travel-deals-on-groupon-safe/</guid>
        <description>With Groupon becoming more and more universally well known, one can purchase virtually anything, from clothes to household appliances to restaurant deals, at a discounted price. However, a lot of people hesitate in the face of travel deals.
For those of you less familiar with the concept, Groupon is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Top 5 places to visit when in Brussels
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-top-5-places-to-visit-when-in-brussels/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 14:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-top-5-places-to-visit-when-in-brussels/</guid>
        <description>Only a two hour train ride away is the dazzling city of Brussels, full of gastronomical and architectural treasures. The capital of Belgium is known to be small, but the three days I spent there wasn’t enough to visit everywhere I wanted to – though if you go all out on the transport, you might be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Conquering Mount Rinjani
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-conquering-mount-rinjani/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 19:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christopher Richardson,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-conquering-mount-rinjani/</guid>
        <description> To the unacquainted, volcano climbing in the Indonesian archipelago might seem a little dumb, but in reality there’s only so much tanning and partying you can handle before you get the itch to do something a little more challenging. Having done my homework, I’d come to the conclusion that Mount …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Up in Ubud: Dabbling the delights in Bali’s undisputed cultural capital</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-up-in-ubud-dabbling-the-delights-in-balis-undisputed-cultural-capital/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 19:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-up-in-ubud-dabbling-the-delights-in-balis-undisputed-cultural-capital/</guid>
        <description> Bali: the four letters roll eloquently off the tongue, and immediately conjure up images of beautiful beaches, bronze bods, and bottled Bintang. But a stone’s throw – literally one hour by shuttle bus – into the island’s core teleports you to a different kind of paradise: the kind that featured …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oh Christmas lights, so Christmas-y
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-oh-christmas-lights-so-christmas-y/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 19:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-oh-christmas-lights-so-christmas-y/</guid>
        <description>It is getting to everyone’s favourite time of the year again, and the capital has already decked out for the season.
From white fairy lights to giant reindeer, there’s no end to what London can dream up with.
Here’s some of my favourite.
Oxford Street
There’s nothing like the glittering Christmas …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s the most, wonderful time, of the year...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-its-the-most-wonderful-time-of-the-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 19:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-its-the-most-wonderful-time-of-the-year/</guid>
        <description>Every Christmas holiday, people are often tempted to go abroad, whether to visit famous Christmas markets or enjoy the festive vibes of the country.
However, there is just as much to do on this island, especially in the capital where we are. I have scoured through the internet for the most …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grecian Myth – Santorini
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-grecian-myth-santorini/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 20:42:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emmilyn Yeoh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-grecian-myth-santorini/</guid>
        <description>A single mention of Greece would bring squeals from the general public considering the fact that it is typically described as a true heaven by most tourists. I don’t know about you, but it definitely makes me wonder sometimes, does it actually live up to its reputation? I therefore decided to pay a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The highlights of Berlin
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-the-highlights-of-berlin/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 20:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nam N Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-the-highlights-of-berlin/</guid>
        <description>It has been almost thirty years since the fall of the Berlin Wall when the capital of Germany finally became whole again. Left with gaping wounds on their landscape, the city has been reborn in an extraordinary way in the last three decades whilst embracing its cultural heritage.
On one hand you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Travel! ...And other narcotics
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-travel-and-other-narcotics/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 16:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Travel,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-travel-and-other-narcotics/</guid>
        <description>Travel is, in so many ways, a powerful drug. This resemblance is one that I’ve always considered, and the analogy seems to hold true with respect to most of travel’s traits, except perhaps for the fact that you can’t physically sniff travel through a crisp fifty after crushing it with a credit card. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On safari: East African delights
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-on-safari-east-african-delights/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 16:41:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Priyank Shah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-on-safari-east-african-delights/</guid>
        <description>I’ve had the privilege of growing up in East Africa, complete with the staple diet of safaris, beaches, poor roads and corruption. So having been to most national parks and game reserves in Kenya, we finally decided to venture next door to the fellow Swahili-speaking nation that is Tanzania, home of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Experience: volunteering in scenic Gorna
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-experience-volunteering-in-scenic-gorna/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 09:47:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mandeep K Dhingra,Mimi Li,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-experience-volunteering-in-scenic-gorna/</guid>
        <description>This summer we spent two weeks volunteering in Gorna, as part of a trip with Imperial College Aid to the Balkans (ICAB). Gorna is a small, picturesque town in northern Bulgaria with just over 30,000 inhabitants. ICAB is a student-run charity that typically sends its volunteers to Bulgarian …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Some guys just can’t handle La Paz</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-some-guys-just-cant-handle-la-paz/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 23:53:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-some-guys-just-cant-handle-la-paz/</guid>
        <description> Bolivia isn’t exactly a fresh addition to the Latin American gringo trail – it features heavily in countless itineraries (indeed, I even ran into an old Felix editor whilst there) – yet it’s managed to retain an essence of individuality whilst neighbouring countries have started to subside. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hangzhou: a forgotten pearl from heaven
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-hangzhou-a-forgotten-pearl-from-heaven/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 19:45:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Zhuoqi Shi,Shukai Wang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-hangzhou-a-forgotten-pearl-from-heaven/</guid>
        <description> Hangzhou Hangzhou is the capital city of and largest city in the Zhejiang Province, Eastern China, with 3.56 million people living in its six urban core districts. Lying on the Hangzhou Bay, just southwest of Shanghai, Hangzhou has great economic power. It has been one of the most renowned and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>To the far West and beyond
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-to-the-far-west-and-beyond/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 22:28:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kleoniki Petrou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-to-the-far-west-and-beyond/</guid>
        <description>When listening to those words in the title immediately we all think of deserted cities with one main road, as these places were presented in the Western movies. This might be true for some places, though this article will present some nature’s most famous creations, namely the Canyons and the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Making a splash in Mexico
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-7-making-a-splash-in-mexico/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2013 19:37:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephanie Walton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-7-making-a-splash-in-mexico/</guid>
        <description>Mexico receives such bad press these days that it is hard to believe it has a safe and beautiful peninsula kicking out into the Caribbean Sea. There are white beaches, fascinating Mayan ruins and magnificent colonial cities. It seems that the only two drawbacks to this balmy “Yucatán” Peninsula are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dream a little Greek dream
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-7-dream-a-little-greek-dream/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2013 19:32:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kleoniki Petrou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-7-dream-a-little-greek-dream/</guid>
        <description>With summer vacations just a stone’s throw away, it seemed ideal for me to think about possible summer destinations. The first thing that crosses all our minds when thinking about summer is, of course, sun, and consequently we think about Mediterranean countries. This article will be dedicated to my …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Viva Las – oooops, scratch that – Los Angeles!!!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-viva-las-oooops-scratch-that-los-angeles/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 00:06:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Travel,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-viva-las-oooops-scratch-that-los-angeles/</guid>
        <description>I know most of you have connected the above phrase with Las Vegas, but I decided it’s high time that we turned our attention also to Los Angeles and its hidden gems. From the moment you land there, you really feel you are in a truly cosmopolitan city, which at the same time features lots of green …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wallowing in the Wadden
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-wallowing-in-the-wadden/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 12:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephanie Walton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-wallowing-in-the-wadden/</guid>
        <description>I doubt many visitors to The Netherlands stray far beyond the amazing museums, canals and liberal attractions of Amsterdam. So it was perhaps unsurprising that I was met with quizzical looks when I announced that I was off to The Netherlands to go Wadlopen. Wadlopen, the art of walking on mudflats …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cruising up the backwaters</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-25-cruising-up-the-backwaters/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 18:15:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-25-cruising-up-the-backwaters/</guid>
        <description>As the saying goes: even a poor-quality photo taken on a beaten digital camera can tell a thousand brilliant words. Or something like that. If the accompanying photograph doesn’t appeal to you then hopefully the remainder of this article will inspire you to take a trip.
The destination in question …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Accidents, emergencies, and Ajmer
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-accidents-emergencies-and-ajmer/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 19:09:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephanie Walton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-accidents-emergencies-and-ajmer/</guid>
        <description>How far is it to Ajmer?”, I asked, concerned.
Ajmer, although famous for its holy Muslim shrine to the great Sufi saint Moinuddin Chishti, was not originally on our itinerary. So how did we find ourselves seeking its Accident and Emergency department at 11pm on Easter Saturday?
Puskhar, a sacred …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Summer festival ambitions</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-summer-festival-ambitions/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 18:50:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-summer-festival-ambitions/</guid>
        <description>I’m sure we all agree that much of the British festival scene is in tatters. Sure, if you’re willing to deviate from the likes of Reading you might catch some acts that are a little (read: endlessly) more interesting than Kasabian, but ultimately you’ll probably still be forking out far too much …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Post-exam Paris to Dakar
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-post-exam-paris-to-dakar/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 21:04:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Daniel Hyde,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-post-exam-paris-to-dakar/</guid>
        <description>This summer I will be part of a group of five Imperial students cycling from Paris to Dakar. Dakar is the capital of Senegal, the most westerly point of continental Africa and over 5,500km from Paris. We will leave from Paris after exams, nipping through the traffic and cutting into the calmer …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Heart of Hyderabad
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-the-heart-of-hyderabad/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 20:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vaidehi Konteti,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-the-heart-of-hyderabad/</guid>
        <description>Hyderabad city, India. Capital of the state of Andhra Pradesh, the second largest city in South India, and my hometown for the first few years of my life. Having lived in Hyderabad for almost a decade, and visited the place virtually every year since, you can understand why the city is extremely …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to the jungle</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-welcome-to-the-jungle/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 21:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-welcome-to-the-jungle/</guid>
        <description>By the time I hit Kerala I was more than ready for it: with Rajasthan’s dusty forts a distant memory I was ready to hit up something a little more tropical. That’s the incredible thing about Kerala: after a short and breezy (read: forty hour and mosquito-infested) coastal train down from the north, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Things to do in Saariselkä
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-things-to-do-in-saariselk/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 22:47:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Veli Akiner,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-things-to-do-in-saariselk/</guid>
        <description>Saariselkä is a small tourist village in mountainous northern Finland which offers a beautiful landscape, various snow-based activities to get involved in and, of course, an opportunity to see the Northern Lights.
 Freeze to death  This is the Arctic Circle, which means temperatures that will …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Making a difference in Malawi
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-making-a-difference-in-malawi/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 23:19:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Travel,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-making-a-difference-in-malawi/</guid>
        <description>September 2011: From the air, it looked like a leopard’s coat: hills of dry grass were dotted with random dark spots of green mango trees and large boulders. I landed in the capital of Malawi, Lilongwe, at the peak of the dry season in south eastern Africa.
Independent since 1964, and democratic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Positive social change for Honduras
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-positive-social-change-for-honduras/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 22:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rubeena Ramjan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-positive-social-change-for-honduras/</guid>
        <description>September 1, 2011 was the day that I became a Global Brigader, and 11 am was the time that I looked out onto the beautiful landscape of an undiscovered country and fell in love. I must admit that I joined Global Brigades because I thought it would be a fun summer trip and, undeniably, it was a fun …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Picture-perfect Prague
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-picture-perfect-prague/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 20:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dushiyanthi Arumuganesan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-picture-perfect-prague/</guid>
        <description>In Prague, New Year’s Eve (or Silvestr as the Czech would say) is a major celebratory holiday. With three days to experience Prague and see in 2012, my main concern was that I’d become one of the many that are inevitably frustrated by, or caught in, the tourist trap that Prague is famed for being. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Friends in high places: a Cannabis Cup special
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-friends-in-high-places-a-cannabis-cup-special/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 22:14:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Travel,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-friends-in-high-places-a-cannabis-cup-special/</guid>
        <description>As a kid, Usain Bolt probably dreamt of the Olympics while he was outstripping all his mates on the running track. Neil Armstrong probably gazed at the Moon and wondered “what if?” Charlie, Mandy and Bobby Brown almost certainly sat monged in the wee hours of the morning and all agreed they really …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Christmas in the capital
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-christmas-in-the-capital/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 22:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dushiyanthi Arumuganesan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-christmas-in-the-capital/</guid>
        <description>With just over two weeks left to go, the capital has been transformed into a beautifully illuminated, life-sized snow globe (minus the snow) in the countdown to Christmas day. So here’s your guide to enjoying the best of London’s Christmas highlights this year.
As far as traditional Christmas fairs …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jaipur: up, up and away</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-jaipur-up-up-and-away/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 20:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-jaipur-up-up-and-away/</guid>
        <description>Having been on the road for a while at this point in time, I’d lost all sense of a sleeping pattern: probably for the best when facing a 4:30 start. After overcoming that bitter morning sensation we peered from our hostel window to see what appeared to be a hot-rod straight out of Kill Bill: we …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Terrific Tarnovan tales
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-terrific-tarnovan-tales/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 20:13:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dushiyanthi Arumuganesan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-terrific-tarnovan-tales/</guid>
        <description>Veliko Tarnovo is one of the oldest settlements in Bulgaria, dating back at least five million years. Nicknamed ‘the Old Capital’, this timeworn city sits in a mountainous region of northern Bulgaria, surrounded by forestry and wildlife unlikely to be seen almost anywhere else in Europe.
Bulgaria …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gallivanting the golden sands of gorgeous Goa</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-gallivanting-the-golden-sands-of-gorgeous-goa/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 20:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-gallivanting-the-golden-sands-of-gorgeous-goa/</guid>
        <description>Let’s be honest about it, the existing beach scene has very much gone to the dogs: Ibiza is past its expiry date, Koh Phangan is being sucked into that same black hole (thanks, The Hangover Part II), and Malia-napa-luf is far too saturated with sleaze for me to waste my time with a rant. My point is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Volunteering on top of the world
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-volunteering-on-top-of-the-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 23:16:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-volunteering-on-top-of-the-world/</guid>
        <description>Nepal provided me with one of the most surreal experiences of my life; from the touchy landing on the pothole-ridden runway, to the ‘seductive’ dancing policeman in one of the local bars. Looking for an experience of a lifetime, I wasn’t disappointed.
After stepping out into the oppressive humidity, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bustling in vibrant Berlin
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-bustling-in-vibrant-berlin/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 23:34:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dushiyanthi Arumuganesan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-bustling-in-vibrant-berlin/</guid>
        <description>Having been bitten by the travel bug severely this summer, and with just enough time and money (for once!), I wanted to book a holiday somewhere remote and unexplored. I wanted to discover the sights, sounds and smells of a foreign land for myself without feeling obligated to visit all the suggested …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Acclimatising to incredible India</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-acclimatising-to-incredible-india/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 13:10:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-acclimatising-to-incredible-india/</guid>
        <description>When I first touched down in New Delhi I have to say I was a tad deceived. Having skimmed my trusty Lonely Planet, I was expecting the Paharganj area to be a bustling Th Khao San à la Bangkok, but was greeted with something else entirely. I suppose I have my own ignorance to thank; I’d been told …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Priya&#39;s Epic South American Adventure
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-7-18-priyas-epic-south-american-adventure/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2011 12:45:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Priya Garg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-7-18-priyas-epic-south-american-adventure/</guid>
        <description>[photo id=17]Click the linked text to read more about Priya&amp;rsquo;s trip
For eight weeks starting in September 2010 we decided to embark on an epic, whistlestop tour of South America, following the well-renowned gringo trail. Beginning in Rio de Janeiro, we soaked in the Latin vibrancy and passion …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why drive?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-why-drive/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 21:08:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel Furse,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-why-drive/</guid>
        <description>I have yet to take helicopter gunships seriously. Whenever I hear about them—which has been regularly since the business in Libya kicked off—I immediately think they are referring to something out of science fiction, or at least Bucky O’Hare.
As you might imagine, this is a far cry from commuting on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Return of the Mummy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-return-of-the-mummy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 21:03:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Priya Garg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-return-of-the-mummy/</guid>
        <description>Arequipa, informally termed “la ciudad blanca” due to its luxurious white buildings, almost Arabic in stone and construction, lies in the Andes mountains overlooked by the looming snow-peaked volcano of El Misti, which rises majestically some 5822 feet above the city. Bordering El Misti lay the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
