<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/gb610/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/gb610/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Cyclists Explore the Peak District
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-23-cyclists-explore-the-peak-district/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2012 00:12:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>George Barnett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-23-cyclists-explore-the-peak-district/</guid>
        <description>It’s 5pm on a Friday as I join 16other somewhat intrepid cyclists by the Queen’s Tower, prepared for a weekend of cycling on some of the Peak District’s finest roads. The plan was pretty simple; load up the buses, drive in a vaguely northerly direction, find the Youth Hostel in Edale, spend the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Student protest march held in London on Wednesday
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-student-protest-march-held-in-london-on-wednesday/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 22:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>George Barnett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-student-protest-march-held-in-london-on-wednesday/</guid>
        <description>Last Wednesday, 21 November 2012, saw thousands of students marching through the streets of London to protest the rising cost of education. Dubbed “Demo 2012”, the demonstration, arranged by the National Union of Students (NUS)expected to have 10,000 attendees. The demonstration by the NUS passed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Today your diary entry will read: “took a prozzie hostage and was shot by three armed bastards!”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-today-your-diary-entry-will-read-took-a-prozzie-hostage-and-was-shot-by-three-armed-bastards/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 21:32:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix TV,George Barnett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-today-your-diary-entry-will-read-took-a-prozzie-hostage-and-was-shot-by-three-armed-bastards/</guid>
        <description>Alex Drake (the smoking hot Keeley Hawes) is a trained police psychologist and negotiator who has recently been researching the case of Sam Tyler, an officer who claimed to have been sent back to 1973 after being hit by a car in 2006.
In the first two of the five series (Life On Mars), Tyler was in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A return to form for Top Gear?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-a-return-to-form-for-top-gear/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 20:56:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>George Barnett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-a-return-to-form-for-top-gear/</guid>
        <description>Ever since its rebirth in 2002, Top Gear has provided me with Sunday night entertainment and it’s always been brilliant. Well actually that isn’t entirely true. You see, _Top Gear_’s entertainment value has decreased hugely in recent years – the ‘humour’ has become entirely predictable and largely …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Balderdash and other lies
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-balderdash-and-other-lies/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 21:18:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>George Barnett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-balderdash-and-other-lies/</guid>
        <description>I discovered a game called Balderdash at a dinner party last week (I can feel the mid-life beckoning me already – damn). For those of you unaware of the game, it essentially involves making things up to trick people. A player reads something off a card; an acronym, a name, a law, or something else …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Feeling under the weather? This’ll make you right as rain
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-feeling-under-the-weather-thisll-make-you-right-as-rain/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 21:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>George Barnett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-feeling-under-the-weather-thisll-make-you-right-as-rain/</guid>
        <description>Watching this week’s BBC Weather, the viewer is immediately gifted with the presence of the pride of the meteorological arena: Alex Deakin. A physics graduate (thanked, apparently, in S. F. Helsdon and T. J. Ponman’s paper “The intragroup medium in loose groups of galaxies”) turned Met Office …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A response to all of the critics
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-a-response-to-all-of-the-critics/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 21:39:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>George Barnett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-a-response-to-all-of-the-critics/</guid>
        <description>I must say; I was rather taken aback by the hullabaloo caused by my (somewhat overemphasised) opinions when I reviewed the Jeremy Kyle show a few weeks ago, and for that, I extend my apologies to anyone who was offended by it. I have never professed to be any good at this writing malarkey – …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wilfred - bizarre humour has a new leash of life
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-wilfred-bizarre-humour-has-a-new-leash-of-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 20:24:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>George Barnett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-wilfred-bizarre-humour-has-a-new-leash-of-life/</guid>
        <description>A hapless ex-lawyer (Elijah Wood) wakes up after trying to commit suicide the night before. Clearly a fruitless attempt – damn you sugar pills! Ryan is confronted by his neighbour, Jenna, asking him to look after her dog, the eponymous Wilfred (played superbly by Jason Gann, and no, I hadn’t heard …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dexter is my ‘favourite’ psychotic serial killer
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-dexter-is-my-favourite-psychotic-serial-killer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 10:42:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>George Barnett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-dexter-is-my-favourite-psychotic-serial-killer/</guid>
        <description>Jeff Lindsay’s book ‘Darkly Dreaming Dexter’ (which I’m told is very good) is the basis for Showtime’s multi award winning program Dexter. The protagonist, who gives the show its name, is cunning, brutal and funny. By day he’s a blood spatter analyst for Miami Metro Police Department. By night, a …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
