<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/kv07/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/kv07/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>How Risky Is It Really?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-how-risky-is-it-really/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 20:03:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katya-yani Vyas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-how-risky-is-it-really/</guid>
        <description>David Ropeik tackles a subject that both fascinates and bewilders us, taking apart the human psyche to try and explain why it is that we fear the things we do, however irrational those fears are. He separates the risks associated with common fears such as snakes from long-term risks which in the end …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Teach Quantum Physics to Your Dog
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-how-to-teach-quantum-physics-to-your-dog/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 18:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katya-yani Vyas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-how-to-teach-quantum-physics-to-your-dog/</guid>
        <description>I received this book as a Christmas present, probably as a humorous allusion to my ineptitude at physics. The premise is very simple: Emmy the dog is adopted by Orzel, a physics Professor, and subsequently becomes enraptured with his work and how it applies to everyday dog issues. Orzel is happy to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The New World of Mr Tompkins
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-the-new-world-of-mr-tompkins/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 19:38:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katya-yani Vyas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-the-new-world-of-mr-tompkins/</guid>
        <description>I&amp;rsquo;m going to be a little self-indulgent this week, with a book that triggered my interest in physics. The new world of Mr Tompkins is a revised version of Gamowís classic, bringing the witty and engaging story of Mr Tompkins up to date with current physics. Taking the reader on a whirlwind …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Book Review: A Life in Science by John Gribbin and Michael White
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-book-review-a-life-in-science-by-john-gribbin-and-michael-white/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 20:18:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katya-yani Vyas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-book-review-a-life-in-science-by-john-gribbin-and-michael-white/</guid>
        <description>John Gribbin made his name with ‘In Search of Schrodinger’s Cat’, an essential read for any aspiring Physics student. Before this, however, he collaborated with Michael White to produce this early biography of Stephen Hawking. The book covers his formative years and the reputation he built as a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Finding moonshine
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-finding-moonshine/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 20:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katya-yani Vyas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-finding-moonshine/</guid>
        <description>In this whirlwind of mathematics, du Sautoy provides us with an irresistible combination of anecdotes, mathematical mysteries and history. Articulately conveying his own love for the subject whilst also providing us with a plethora of mathematics, he weaves an intricate and emotive tale of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Strung along by Brian Greene
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-strung-along-by-brian-greene/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 18:41:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katya-yani Vyas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-strung-along-by-brian-greene/</guid>
        <description>String theory is not a subject that would enthral most people, it is hard physics, mathematical, untested and impossible to visualise. On Thursday the 28th of October at the Wellcome Institute, I attended a discussion with Brian Greene on the subject of String theory and the controversy and debate …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Essential things that all scientists should know
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-1-essential-things-that-all-scientists-should-know/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 21:38:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katya-yani Vyas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-1-essential-things-that-all-scientists-should-know/</guid>
        <description>Five Awesome Science Chat-up Lines
You’ve all heard about the famous Imperial ratio, so yes, we are a male-dominated university. However, if you are male, you are quite likely to run into a female that catches your attention at some point. In this event the following chat-up lines are to be in no …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
