<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sustainability on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/sustainability/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sustainability on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/sustainability/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Tragedy of the Commons: A Drama That Our Planet Is Not Enjoying</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-tragedy-commons-drama-planet-not-enjoying/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xiuchen Xu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-tragedy-commons-drama-planet-not-enjoying/</guid>
        <description>You may have heard of the term tragedy of the commons before, or you may have even studied about it. It is an important economic concept and is extremely relevant to many of the prevailing environmental issues. The problem stems from deep within human nature and is at the heart of corruption and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>General Election 2019: What are the environmental policies and promises of the parties?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-general-election-2019-what-are-environmental-policies-promises-of-parties/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xiuchen Xu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-general-election-2019-what-are-environmental-policies-promises-of-parties/</guid>
        <description>There is a short &amp;lsquo;glossary&amp;rsquo; near the end of the article to explain certain bits of jargon!
The public concern towards environmental issues are at a peak, and this is reflected in the manifestos of political parties, which have a heavier focus on environmental policies than those of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Researchers Show Noise Pollution is Threatening the Survival of a Number of Species</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-researchers-show-noise-pollution-threatening-survival-species/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xiuchen Xu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-researchers-show-noise-pollution-threatening-survival-species/</guid>
        <description>New research from Queen’s University Belfast has indicated that noise pollution is threatening to over 100 different species.
The researchers found that noise affects the behaviour of a wide range of species including amphibians, birds, fish, mammals and reptilians. Noise pollution can affect …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Greenwashing – Are you Falling Victim?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-greenwashing-falling-victim/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dunin Borkowska,Aleksandra A,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-greenwashing-falling-victim/</guid>
        <description>Efforts to decrease the environmental impact of our consumer culture are being prevented by confusion over terminology and outrageous greenwashing. In a world where ‘sustainability’ is all the rage, you might be drawn to the chocolate bar with a small green leaf on it, making promises of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>California Fires Put Pressure on the US to Improve Environmental Policies</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-california-fires-put-pressure-on-US-improve-environmental-policies/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Leah Denoun,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-california-fires-put-pressure-on-US-improve-environmental-policies/</guid>
        <description>For the past week, statewide wildfires in California have been blazing, having turned to ashes more than 80 000 acres, most in the counties of Sonoma and LA. The biggest fire is the Kincade Fire in the North of California. As of now, the fire is only 15% contained and has burned at least 74 000 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Have a Halloween that isn’t Spooky for the Environment</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-have-halloween-not-spooky-for-environment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xiuchen Xu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-have-halloween-not-spooky-for-environment/</guid>
        <description>It’s the time of the year for trick or treating! However, being festive does not mean we should pollute and bring damage to our beloved planet.. Halloween activities can be incredibly wasteful, so here is a look at three ways we can make Halloween more sustainable.
Costumes
Halloween is the peak …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial’s Surcharge on Plant-based Milks</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-imperial-surcharge-plant-based-milks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tamara Fernandez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-imperial-surcharge-plant-based-milks/</guid>
        <description>While many green enthusiasts celebrated the rise in Imperial’s coffee cup levy from 15p to 25p this September, there has been a new surcharge that has gone relatively unannounced.
Behold the new, sneaky little 30p surcharge on plant-based milks which has been introduced across Imperial food outlets. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Aftermath of the Extinction Rebellion Ban in London by the Police</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-aftermath-extinction-rebellion-ban-london-by-police/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xiuchen Xu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-aftermath-extinction-rebellion-ban-london-by-police/</guid>
        <description>As of Monday 14th October, the Scotland Yard has announced that all Extinction Rebellion (XR) protests must cease. The Met’s has banned all protests linked to the XR ‘Autumn Uprising’ under Section 14 of the Public Order Act. Since then, the police have cleared infrastructure from protest sites such …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Need for a Green Rebellion</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-need-for-green-rebellion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Filip Aniés,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-need-for-green-rebellion/</guid>
        <description>We are running out of time
In wartime, no one questions the urgency of the situation. Everyday politics is often put aside, as survival becomes the only priority at hand. Cooperation becomes the focus on all levels of society; leaders unite, industries work towards the most urgent needs, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>No Silent Spring with Extinction Rebellion</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-no-silent-spring-with-extinction-rebellion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-no-silent-spring-with-extinction-rebellion/</guid>
        <description>The past nine months have seen the birth of Extinction Rebellion in the UK, the global school strike for climate movement and, of course, the weekly Sustainability column in Felix. Before the newspaper goes on hiatus until October, it seems only fitting to report on the events which, to a large …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Palm Oil: Friend or Foe?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-palm-oil-friend-or-foe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Petra Bachanová,Samuel  G Jones,Eshita Joshi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-palm-oil-friend-or-foe/</guid>
        <description>Palm oil is a widely used vegetable oil derived from the fruits of the African oil palm. This article aims to summarize the implications of growing production and export of palm oil, primarily from South-East Asia and the controversial question of its sustainability and certification.
Palm oil has a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Today China has consumed more natural resources than it can replenish</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-today-china-has-consumed-more-natural-resources-than-it-can-replenish/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-today-china-has-consumed-more-natural-resources-than-it-can-replenish/</guid>
        <description>For each year since 1970, the first year that humanity began to consume more resources than the Earth can replenish in a year, the Global Footprint Network (a non-profit think tank) has calculated the date when humanity exhausts its budget of natural resources for the year. The calculation of this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flying regularly not crucial for success in academia</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-flying-regularly-not-crucial-for-success-in-academia/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-flying-regularly-not-crucial-for-success-in-academia/</guid>
        <description>Science is quite rightly celebrated for being an international enterprise, and academics often feel required or obliged to fly frequently and over long-distances in order to conduct their work or maintain professional relationships. But how important is long-distance travel to a scientific career, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ground-Breaking Hackathon to make meat without animals</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-ground-breaking-hackathon-to-make-meat-without-animals/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Clarisse Beurrier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-ground-breaking-hackathon-to-make-meat-without-animals/</guid>
        <description>Calling on all scientists, engineers, business students and hackers! Do you want to harness the power of technology and join the revolution? You are invited to use your skills and passion at the world’s first “Cellular Agriculture Hackathon at Imperial”.
Cellular agriculture is the process of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In response to Big Daddy Oil</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-in-response-to-big-daddy-oil/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-in-response-to-big-daddy-oil/</guid>
        <description>A recent article in Felix, “Big Daddy Oil outearns Apple and Google, wants more”, reported on records seen by the Financial Times which assert that the state-owned oil company Saudi Aramco has a greater net income than any other company worldwide. Since many of the graduates of this university, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Witnessing Life on the Frontline of Climate Change</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-witnessing-life-on-the-frontline-of-climate-change/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Monami Miyamoto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-witnessing-life-on-the-frontline-of-climate-change/</guid>
        <description>On April 18th, BBC One broadcasted the highly anticipated documentary “Climate Change: The facts”. Needless to say, it was one of the most devastating hours of my entire easter holiday (really putting revision into perspective). Hosted by the trusted veteran, sir David Attenborough, this documentary …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is it the end of the road for livestock farming?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-01-is-it-the-end-of-the-road-for-livestock-farming/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elliot Dryer-Beers,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-01-is-it-the-end-of-the-road-for-livestock-farming/</guid>
        <description>Conversations surrounding human contributions to global warming are naturally fraught with confusion due to the sheer enormity and complexity of the issue, but can also be twisted by those whose proximal goals conflict with the changes necessary to address it.
One such point of confusion frequently …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don’t call your country “developed” </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-don-t-call-your-country-developed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-don-t-call-your-country-developed/</guid>
        <description>Is the UK developed or developing? What about Vietnam - developed or developing?
The World Bank no longer uses the terms “developed” or “developing” and I couldn’t agree more. The distinction of “developed” and “developing” countries date to the period just after the Second World War, when …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Greening Imperial Week 2019</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-greening-imperial-week-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charlotte Griaud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-greening-imperial-week-2019/</guid>
        <description>Last year, Imperial was placed 141st out of 154 universities in the “People and Planet University League”. This league table ranks universities based on environmental and ethical performance. It is saddening that we have such poor reputation on environmental and ethical stances.
Greening Imperial is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Land of Hope and Glory</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-land-of-hope-and-glory/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Monami Miyamoto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-land-of-hope-and-glory/</guid>
        <description>On Tuesday, VegSocs from Imperial, LSE, Kings and Middlesex University collaborated to host a film screening of “Land of Hope and Glory”, followed by a talk by the producer, Ed Winters. Ed Winters, also known as “Earthling Ed” is one of the most well-known faces of UK vegan activism, and has been …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Not yet (bothered to be) recycled</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-not-yet-bothered-to-be-recycled/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-not-yet-bothered-to-be-recycled/</guid>
        <description>From crisps to coke, and pears to pizzas, almost everything we buy today is wrapped, boxed or bottled in plastic. Disposable packaging is, by definition, used just once yet, according to the government recycling agency WRAP, they make up 40% of all plastic used in the UK. A key part to changing this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tap Here to Stop Food Waste</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-tap-here-to-stop-food-waste/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Monami Miyamoto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-tap-here-to-stop-food-waste/</guid>
        <description>On 11th February the Social Innovation Academy at LSE (London School of Economics) hosted a talk titled ‘The War on Food Waste’, with 3 entrepreneurs from start-ups tackle food waste. These companies included ODDBOX, DayOld and OLIO, each represented by their founders or board members.
Food waste is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Creative Green</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-a-creative-green/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-a-creative-green/</guid>
        <description>Hi there,
*
I am a bin
Your humble biographer
Wherever I may be
Beside the kitchen sink yawning in the morning to catch your cereal packet or an unwashed peanut butter jar
*
Standing on the landing at University you pass me everyday occasionally greet me with a screwed up tissue.
*
At lunchtime I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lettuce Eat Better</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-lettuce-eat-better/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Elliot Dryer-Beers,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-lettuce-eat-better/</guid>
        <description>Now that Veganuary 2019 has come to an end, it’s the perfect time to reflect on the cultural shift veganism and the plant-based message experienced in recent decades. Veganism, it’s fair to say, has recently experienced a leap from the fringe into the spotlight, with many reasons underlying its …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Book Review: Green Giants</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-book-review-green-giants/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Monami Miyamoto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-book-review-green-giants/</guid>
        <description>Although ‘sustainability’ is a constant buzzword in our society and people seem to understand that its somewhat important, I feel that many of us don’t know what it really means to be sustainable. Should we stop using plastic all together? Should we abandon eating all meat and dairy? Should we never …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FRIENDs for life</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-friends-for-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xiuchen Xu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-friends-for-life/</guid>
        <description>UUpon arrival to FRIEND animal sanctuary, we were greeted by the loud clucks of chickens and the turning heads of cows. We made our way through the muddy terrain to an open field, where we were welcomed by Dave, who was a full-time volunteer at the sanctuary. Behind him followed Ging whose puppy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2018: A big year for the vegan movement</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-2018-a-big-year-for-the-vegan-movement/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Monami Miyamoto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-2018-a-big-year-for-the-vegan-movement/</guid>
        <description>Last Tuesday (15th of January), Environmental Society, VegSoc and APES collaborated to host a movie screening event for the film VEGAN 2018. Out of curiosity I attended. I came out of it feeling a mixture of emotions - partly overwhelmed by the density of the information, partly empowered to know …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Real men care about the environment</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-real-men-care-about-the-environment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jessica-Lee Cole,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-real-men-care-about-the-environment/</guid>
        <description>Toxic masculinity is currently a hot topic, wearing many guises – this was most recently highlighted in the new Gillette ad campaign on the subject. This advert has caused great controversy. resulting in many people admonishing Proctor and Gamble, for standing up to toxic masculinity. Many people …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oddly inspiring</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-oddly-inspiring/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Monami Miyamoto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-oddly-inspiring/</guid>
        <description>I’d like to believe that every one of us, at least in part, can do something better for the environment. But I also know that for some, this can seem dauting, difficult, or just too time consuming - which is why, I thought I’d share my experience with ODDBOX, a UK based company committed to tackling …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Season of change</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-season-of-change/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xiuchen Xu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-season-of-change/</guid>
        <description>The Plant-Based Imperial campaign combines initiatives from Greening Imperial, Environmental Society (ESoc), VegSoc and Animal Protection &amp;amp; Education Society (APES). The main aim of the campaign is to reduce the carbon footprint of the college and work towards a more sustainable college. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The meat of the problem	</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-the-meat-of-the-problem/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Han Cai,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-the-meat-of-the-problem/</guid>
        <description>It’s January 2019. Following another festive holiday, many people may be seeking new year’s resolutions to adhere to, ideally in support of good causes. Going vegan or “zero waste” might be an option worth considering when it comes to environmental sustainability. But will cutting down meat …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Extinction Rebellion campaign continues</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-extinction-rebellion-campaign-continues/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Celina Chien,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-extinction-rebellion-campaign-continues/</guid>
        <description>Over 1,000 protesters from the environmental campaign group Extinction Rebellion came together in Central London on the Saturday 28th November to demand environmental justice and demand legislative action to confront climate breakdown and the global biodiversity crisis.
The Extinction Rebellion …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I started a Summer social project!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-i-started-a-summer-social-project/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yan Kai Kee,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-i-started-a-summer-social-project/</guid>
        <description>Hey, what are you going to do for the summer man? Intern? Which company have you applied for?” As we creep towards the end of second term, that’s the question to ask whenever you meet another fellow high-achieving acquaintance of yours at Imperial, isn’t it? For my first and second year at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I’m dreaming of a green Christmas</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-i-m-dreaming-of-a-green-christmas/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matilda Burridge,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-i-m-dreaming-of-a-green-christmas/</guid>
        <description>Tables heaving with plates of food, stacks of presents spilling out from under a tree smothered in tinsel and baubles, and rolls of lights beaming into outer space… This may seem like the epitome of the festive season, but is Christmas really not about more than what we consume? Christmas has become …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The cost of wasting meat</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-the-cost-of-wasting-meat/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Roberta Franchi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-the-cost-of-wasting-meat/</guid>
        <description>Consuming meat is bad for the environment. Meat production produces huge amounts of greenhouse gases, consumes millions of liters of water and takes up monstrous quantities of land. Yep, we’ve heard it over and over again. However, have you ever considered the impact of actually throwing away the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An app a day keeps the greenhouse effect at bay</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-an-app-a-day-keeps-the-greenhouse-effect-at-bay/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theana Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-an-app-a-day-keeps-the-greenhouse-effect-at-bay/</guid>
        <description>To start, a few facts: 12 million tons of plastic end up in our oceans each year. One third of all food produced globally goes to waste. The greenhouse gas emissions involved in the production of food which go to waste mean that if food waste were a country it would be the third largest emitter of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Going on in the world this week</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-going-on-in-the-world-this-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-going-on-in-the-world-this-week/</guid>
        <description>Brazil – This week Brazil’s government announced that it will no longer be hosting the UN global summit on climate change next year citing costs. The conference could cost Brazil up to $100 million. Brazil spent $4.6 billion on the 2015 Olympic games and it is expected that $33 trillion worth of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can a tiger change its stripes?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-can-a-tiger-change-its-stripes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Celina Chien,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-can-a-tiger-change-its-stripes/</guid>
        <description>China has postponed previous plans to lift the 25-year-old ban on the sale and use of rhinoceros horn and tiger bone for Traditional Chinese Medicine (TCM), following an international furore. This announcement comes two weeks after the State Council’s decision in October to reverse the 1993 ban on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Going on in the world </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-going-on-in-the-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-going-on-in-the-world/</guid>
        <description>Monday sees the beginning of the COP 24 conference in Katowice, Poland. Previous conferences include 2015’s COP 21, in which 190 nations committed to limiting the rise in global temperatures to 1.5°C above pre-industrial levels.
In other news, Felix sees the beginning of a new column on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grinding to a halt – China bans imports of waste</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-grinding-to-a-halt-china-bans-imports-of-waste/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sam Owens,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-grinding-to-a-halt-china-bans-imports-of-waste/</guid>
        <description>The UK has declared war on single-use plastic. Reusable coffee cups are everywhere, with Imperial’s cafes charging those without one an extra 15p, and plastic bags and straws are looked upon with horror. The government is riding this wave of public opinion, having imposed a 5p levy on the former in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How trashy is your period?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-how-trashy-is-your-period/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Petchara Newson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-28-how-trashy-is-your-period/</guid>
        <description>Since the 5p carrier bag charge, the thought of throwing away a perfectly good plastic bag is enough to make most of us cringe. Now imagine unknowingly throwing away 80 plastic bags every month. That’s how much plastic the average woman uses over her period if she throws away 20 disposables a month! …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
