<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/an406/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/an406/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The Unforgettable, amazing Oaxaca...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-17-the-unforgettable-amazing-oaxaca/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2015 14:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aditya Narayanan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-17-the-unforgettable-amazing-oaxaca/</guid>
        <description>Holidays in Mexico are stereotypically presented as being all about that beach. From Cancun to Tijuana (and Acapulco), the golden sands and azure seas are well trodden by the average foreign tourist. With glorious sunshine all year and relatively calm and clear water, it is the perfect place to laze …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kickstarting my life in Mexico City
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-17-kickstarting-my-life-in-mexico-city/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2015 19:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aditya Narayanan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-17-kickstarting-my-life-in-mexico-city/</guid>
        <description>Mexico City glitters at night. Dots of yellow flow across the ground. Like a train of ants, they follow a path as if preordained, in a robotic line with no destination. I can feel the energy from my plane window.
Drugs. Violence. Human trafficking. The typical Western news cycle on most developing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fairtrade Fortnight comes to an end
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-fairtrade-fortnight-comes-to-an-end/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 21:33:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aditya Narayanan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-fairtrade-fortnight-comes-to-an-end/</guid>
        <description>It began with an old favourite. A cold Thursday in late February with the promise of ice cream; Ben &amp;amp; Jerry’s ice cream to be exact. The academic year had been welcomed with a raucous first session in October seeing Activity Space 1 crammed with attendees of a two hour frozen dessert buffet. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fairtrade: the lowdown before Fairtrade fortnight
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-fairtrade-the-lowdown-before-fairtrade-fortnight/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 02:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aditya Narayanan,Nicholas Greenwood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-fairtrade-the-lowdown-before-fairtrade-fortnight/</guid>
        <description> What is Fairtrade? How many of you drink coffee or tea to get you started in the morning? Or sneak a banana/bar of chocolate to get through afternoon lectures? How many of you wear clothes to uni? Throughout our daily life we reap the benefits of consuming all manner of products made using cash …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Dandy Warhols
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-the-dandy-warhols/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 17:52:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aditya Narayanan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-the-dandy-warhols/</guid>
        <description>The band is The Dandy Warhols. The location is the Kentish Town Forum. The mission? To start a mosh pit. My friend, a die-hard punk fan who is also coming to see the gig remains sceptical. A band known for producing radio-friendly power pop hits to supplement their back catalogue of psychedelic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Obscure Japanese Kamikaze Girls gets belated praise
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-obscure-japanese-kamikaze-girls-gets-belated-praise/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 20:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aditya Narayanan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-obscure-japanese-kamikaze-girls-gets-belated-praise/</guid>
        <description>Mention that you’ve watched a film called Kamikaze Girls the first thing people tend to ask is whether you have a fetish for Japanese adult videos. Appearances can be deceptive however, and this adaptation of Novala Takemoto’s novel tells the story of the quirky friendship that develops between two …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Happy New Year?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-happy-new-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 19:42:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jacob Lea-Wilson,Aditya Narayanan,Guo Heng Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-happy-new-year/</guid>
        <description>As another year begins again and starts us off right at the beginning of Oscar season, the Felix Film writers take a look back at the best of cinema in 2010 – in case you were in some kind of year-long coma – and discuss some of our most anticipated films of 2011.
There are three clear frontrunners …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How comic book geeks get girls: Exhibit A
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-10-how-comic-book-geeks-get-girls-exhibit-a/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 15:38:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aditya Narayanan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-10-how-comic-book-geeks-get-girls-exhibit-a/</guid>
        <description>Grosse Pointe Blank. Back to the Future. The Dark Knight. Three films that I could watch on repeat – again and again. I left Scott Pilgrim vs the World wanting to go straight back in for another round. The titular character, played by Michael Cera, is a 23-year-old with no job, who splits his time …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
