<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/me1409/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/me1409/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Boiler Room Make Session 008
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-boiler-room-make-session-008/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 15:22:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark England,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-boiler-room-make-session-008/</guid>
        <description>The Boiler Room sessions are always a treat. When Make Session 008 descended on Hoxton I was sure to get in the queue to get a space. Red Stripe had teamed up with long term friends T-Shirt Party. You have to love a brand whose vision is “REAL G’s WEAR WHITE T’s”. Inside an art gallery next to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Iceage thaw out Elektrowerkz
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-1-iceage-thaw-out-elektrowerkz/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 14:25:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark England,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-1-iceage-thaw-out-elektrowerkz/</guid>
        <description>Iceage’s second album You’re Nothing is getting critics frothing at the mouth, and for good reason. It keeps the raw, visceral vitality of their debut album, New Brigade, and marries it to a more intricate post-punk undercurrent. In fact, whisper it, new track ‘Morals’ seems to be an attempt at a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>So epic it Hurts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-so-epic-it-hurts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 02:54:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark England,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-so-epic-it-hurts/</guid>
        <description>Hurts are a duo from Manchester who I was undecided about; were they some bizarrely intelligent synth pop saviours (their debut sold over a million copies worldwide), or were they, in fact, an industry joke: two blokes with very good connections, who possibly have shares in Moss Bros, and a good eye …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Veronica Falls at St Leonard’s
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-veronica-falls-at-st-leonards/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 12:57:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark England,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-veronica-falls-at-st-leonards/</guid>
        <description>I have recently discovered the real reason the Pope is giving up on wearing his natty white gown and driving about in his suped-up Pope-mobile to devote more of his time to chillaxing. He must have been present at St Leonard’s Church last Friday where Veronica Falls blew away the congregation with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sharon Van Etten: This lady is no Tramp
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-sharon-van-etten-this-lady-is-no-tramp/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 00:48:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark England,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-sharon-van-etten-this-lady-is-no-tramp/</guid>
        <description>If the highlights of 2012’s musical offering involved bitching about Lana Del Ray’s face, swagging with Odd Future, or simply dancing like a drunk antelope to a Korean pop mega-hit, then I fear the album of the last year has passed you by like a proverbial leaf in a stream. Sharon Van Etten’s third …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Vaccines at the Ally Pally
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-the-vaccines-at-the-ally-pally/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 22:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark England,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-the-vaccines-at-the-ally-pally/</guid>
        <description>Wandering around the large and looming Alexandra Palace, simultaneuosly trying to avoid drunky, lairy forty year old men who wanted to “ave it large” while attempting not to trip over the large number of excited teenage girls scurrying about, it became blindingly obvious how much of a big deal The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rolo Tomassi give XOYO a fright
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-23-rolo-tomassi-give-xoyo-a-fright/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2012 00:20:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark England,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-23-rolo-tomassi-give-xoyo-a-fright/</guid>
        <description>On a chilly Halloween night, it was a great idea to warm our bodies with a pumped up punk show at XOYO courtesy of Rolo Tomassi. Dressed as the Addams family, with the spritely lead singer, Eva Spence, appearing as Morticia, the band kicks off the night with ‘Howl’.
From the get-go the crowd were a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An interview with Japandroids
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-an-interview-with-japandroids/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 21:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark England,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-an-interview-with-japandroids/</guid>
        <description>Brian King, lead singer and guitarist of Japandroids, talked to me about London. his favourite record and where their awesome name originates from.
Where does the name Japandroids come from?
There was no inspiration for the name Japandroids specifically. As a matter of fact, it was more of a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Japandroids: live
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-japandroids-live/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 21:32:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark England,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-japandroids-live/</guid>
        <description>How much noise can two people make? I thought the decibel limit was set by Kat and Alfie from Eastenders or possibly Gordon Brown on a bad day, but it seems that Brian King and David Prowse can beat them all with the intense garage rock made by Japandroids. I used to really love this band three …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Everything is good
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-everything-is-good/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 14:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark England,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-everything-is-good/</guid>
        <description>Everything Everything at the Village Underground in Shoreditch was certainly a hot ticket; the show had sold out well in advance and obscene amounts of money were being exchanged online to gain entry. As people crammed intothe relatively small venue the anticipation for hearing Everything …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Cribs are back on top
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-the-cribs-are-back-on-top/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 23:10:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark England,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-the-cribs-are-back-on-top/</guid>
        <description>The Cribs are a band of many contradictions. They are a band who pack their shows with huge choruses that bring the roof down whilst also getting long poetic spoken word pieces into one of their songs; they are a band who manage to satisfy those fans who want the more visceral punk rock side of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Yawning at Field Music
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-yawning-at-field-music/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 03:15:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark England,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-yawning-at-field-music/</guid>
        <description>It is an affliction of the internet age that, nowadays, a band must be tragically cool to get noticed. They must have the right haircuts, a certain amount of buzz about them and normally a postcode from Dalston, Shoreditch or at the moment South London. Field Music, however, are the antithesis of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Zulu Winter: worth the hype?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-25-zulu-winter-worth-the-hype/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 19:09:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark England,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-25-zulu-winter-worth-the-hype/</guid>
        <description>Zulu Winter are a curious band. They seem to be a band beloved by hipsters at the minute, yet their soaring ambitions surely cannot be contained to playing to only the trendy crowds of London. The band’s recent singles are highly reminiscent of the stadium bothering doom-pop of White Lies and the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Returning heroes triumphant at the Ally Pally
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-returning-heroes-triumphant-at-the-ally-pally/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 20:06:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark England,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-returning-heroes-triumphant-at-the-ally-pally/</guid>
        <description>This was my first time at the epic venue which is Alexandra Palace and I was not disappointed. With support from Rae Morris and Lianne la Havves, the evening had a solid start but it was the first few songs of Bombay Bicycle Club’s set that really kicked the show into gear.
The set was largely …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bombay fever hits London
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-bombay-fever-hits-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 19:59:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark England,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-bombay-fever-hits-london/</guid>
        <description>_I interviewed Jack Steadman from Bombay Bicycle Club before they played the biggest ever UK headline show of thier career at London’s Alexandra Palace. With the North London band returning home to celebrate their extra-ordinary third album, A Different Kind of Fix, it was to prove a memorable …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Soko at the Union Chapel
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-soko-at-the-union-chapel/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 21:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark England,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-soko-at-the-union-chapel/</guid>
        <description>If any of you have seen the recent contentious article from The New York Times talking about how depraved and culturally rigid London has become. Thankfully, Soko, whose origins lie in France, but spends most of her time in California, doesn’t hold such views about our fair capital. You can see from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kurt Vile, we like your style
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-kurt-vile-we-like-your-style/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 23:22:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mohammad Mirza,Mark England,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-kurt-vile-we-like-your-style/</guid>
        <description>We are going to start this review with a bold statement: Kurt Vile’s _Smoke Rings for my Halo _was the hottest album of 2011. No matter how poignant PJ Harvey’s Let England Shake was or how acclaimed the Horror’s Skying was, no-one can convince us otherwise. It was with this in mind that we headed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Shins are back, but should I care?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-the-shins-are-back-but-should-i-care/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 21:06:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark England,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-the-shins-are-back-but-should-i-care/</guid>
        <description>I would like to be honest and say that I had little hope for The Shins in 2012. Their Grammy nominated delight, Wincing the Night Away, shoved lead singer/songwriter into the limelight but nearly five years have passed and the musical landscape has changed significantly. When I heard the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Fresh Prince of Kentucky
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-the-fresh-prince-of-kentucky/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 21:55:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark England,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-the-fresh-prince-of-kentucky/</guid>
        <description>Bonnie ‘Prince’ Billy, aka Will Oldham, is a name who should be on everyone’s lips. Instead, in the current landscape of indie-folk/Americana he has been overlooked for the watered-down beige-athon that is Mumford and Sons. Many commendable elements of the current scene can be seen in Bonnie …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Forgive me Father, for I have scened
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-forgive-me-father-for-i-have-scened/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 11:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark England,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-forgive-me-father-for-i-have-scened/</guid>
        <description>Times New Viking’s third album Rip It Off, their first to be released on Matador Records, became the darling of the so called ‘shitgaze’ scene. Whichever Pitchfork employee exhausted the synonym function on his computer to come up with such labels as witch house, chillwave and nu-gaze certainly …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
