<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/alicedavage/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/alicedavage/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>What you need to do before you leave Imperial</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-what-you-need-to-do-before-you-leave-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Alice Davage,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-what-you-need-to-do-before-you-leave-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Watch a premiere
Ever noticed those bright spotlights encircling the night sky over campus? No, they are not signalling an alien invasion. The police are not scouring campus for a wanted criminal either. Although, both of these things would certainly liven up exam season. They are in fact a sign …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Seven things I learnt about Italian food from my trip to Rome</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-seven-things-i-learnt-about-italian-food-from-my-trip-to-rome/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Davage,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-seven-things-i-learnt-about-italian-food-from-my-trip-to-rome/</guid>
        <description>Let’s face it, one of the main reasons why people visit Italy is for the food. Yes, there is also bucket loads of history to gaze at in awe and the sunshine is a nice change from the UK, but really, the food is the main event. When I say “Italian food,” what comes into your mind? Pizza and pasta? …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Eat Tokyo: Budget-friendly Japanese Delights </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-eat-tokyo-budget-friendly-japanese-delights/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Davage,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-eat-tokyo-budget-friendly-japanese-delights/</guid>
        <description>I’ve been meaning to rave about this small chain that boasts authentic Japanese food for a while, but my degree has unfortunately been distracting me. Although Eat Tokyo has locations throughout London and Japan, I have only visited the Holborn restaurant so far. The Hammersmith and Notting Hill …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the ninth day of Christmas, my true love gave to me… HOT CHOCOLATE ADVENTURES</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-ninth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-hot-chocolate-adventures/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Davage,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-ninth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-hot-chocolate-adventures/</guid>
        <description>Christmas announced its arrival in London several weeks ago when the department stores assembled their window display extravaganzas and numerous shopping streets had grand switch-on ceremonies for their array of twinkly lights (the annual chance for forgotten celebrities to shine).
But the recent …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grub’s up! Felix Food’s guide to campus food</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-grub-s-up-felix-food-s-guide-to-campus-food/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Davage,Chun Yuan Hii,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-grub-s-up-felix-food-s-guide-to-campus-food/</guid>
        <description>1. JCR
The canteen with blue tables has a standard deli selling fancy baguettes and a canteen with all the normal lunch grub (boxed sandwiches, crisps, etc.).
Pieminster sells gourmet pie and mash. A little pricey but sometimes they do discounts so look out for those. They offer a range of gravy, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Comfort food season begins</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-14-comfort-food-season-begins/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Davage,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-14-comfort-food-season-begins/</guid>
        <description>As Freshers’ Fortnight comes to an end, we can say an official goodbye to summer – in other words, the brief heatwave in June and the sporadic sunshine since then (for those of us who spent the summer holidays in London) – and a reluctant hello to autumn. However, as the daylight gradually vanishes …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Avoiding drunk food disasters – our guide to your post-night out snacks</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-avoiding-drunk-food-disasters-our-guide-to-your-post-night-out-snacks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alice Davage,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-avoiding-drunk-food-disasters-our-guide-to-your-post-night-out-snacks/</guid>
        <description>Freshers’ week. A time to make new friends and become accustomed to new surroundings, whether that be a new borough, city, or perhaps even a new country. However, for many, freshers’ week also involves a few hangovers and a number of drunk food disasters. Don’t be that person eating folded squares …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hit me up, homeslice
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-hit-me-up-homeslice/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Alice Davage,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-hit-me-up-homeslice/</guid>
        <description>The hipster revolution is upon us. No food is safe. The humble burger has been embellished with a bright green avocado bun. If you haven’t tried kale or quinoa (pronounced “keen-wah”, trust me, I have been corrected multiple times), frankly, where have you been? Although the occasional twists on …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
