<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/olly_dove/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/olly_dove/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>From Jaws to jaws: the impact of shark-fin soup</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-from-jaws-to-jaws-the-impact-of-shark-fin-soup/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Olly Dove,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-from-jaws-to-jaws-the-impact-of-shark-fin-soup/</guid>
        <description>Over forty years ago, a film was released into cinemas that would forever haunt those swimming in the open sea. But the main star of Jaws, the infamous great white shark, sadly has more to fear from humans than we do from them. While we may think of sharks preying upon us, in this case it is humans …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Iolanthe: an odd choice for the current climate</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-iolanthe-an-odd-choice-for-the-current-climate/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Olly Dove,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-iolanthe-an-odd-choice-for-the-current-climate/</guid>
        <description>Baffling, bright, and bonkers would be an accurate way to sum up the English National Opera’s take on Iolanthe. Having originally been performed back in 1882, the satirical comedy about the House of Lords versus a band of fairies has been somewhat rejuvenated, including a Boris Johnson look-a-like …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pluto: a manga come to life</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-pluto-a-manga-come-to-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Olly Dove,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-pluto-a-manga-come-to-life/</guid>
        <description>Pluto, in summary, is the most visually impressive play you’ve likely never heard of. Before seeing the show, all I knew was that it involved Astro Boy, a character I vaguely recalled from my childhood. What I now know is that my interest in the ethical questions underpinning artificial intelligence …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dominica’s hurricane disaster</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-dominica-s-hurricane-disaster/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Olly Dove,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-dominica-s-hurricane-disaster/</guid>
        <description>&amp;ldquo;I don’t know if I’m so tired or have grown used to the wind that it now has become the norm to hear utter destruction in the background but I feel like I’m in a dream. I feel like I woke up today in a dimension that was far removed from the island I know and I will be more certain of that …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
