<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/cif110/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/cif110/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Fritz the cat
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-fritz-the-cat/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 23:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christian Franke,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-fritz-the-cat/</guid>
        <description>It was towards the end of a long, drawn-out evening at a festival during the summer, and totally by chance some good chums and I came across a cinema showing Fritz the Cat. I coincidentally had only read about it a couple of days earlier so I suggested to the cohort that we catch the closing 15 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Music, through the ages
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-music-through-the-ages/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 12:32:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christian Franke,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-music-through-the-ages/</guid>
        <description>Is there a more appealing time warp than an old record player? Not only does the standard matte black metal and peeling wood-look veneer sum up a bygone era, but the sound quality still surpasses anything that digitised files can muster. I’m sure that most of us have, at some point in our …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>When the Dinner’s Over
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-when-the-dinners-over/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 19:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christian Franke,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-when-the-dinners-over/</guid>
        <description>After having a long, drawn out and indulgent dinner, what does one have whilst engaging in sophisticated conversation and to cleanse the palate after the cheese board? To continue drinking wine simply lacks imagination, besides it wouldn’t be best suited to aid digestion. Fortunately a whole genre …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Down in one? I think not...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-down-in-one-i-think-not/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 18:47:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christian Franke,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-down-in-one-i-think-not/</guid>
        <description>Not everybody may agree with me, but is there a more satisfying tipple than a whisky? The aromas, the warmth, the flavour, come to think of it, there are few drinks I would rate more than a good scotch. Whilst its taste is acquired and occasionally referred to as a kin to petrol by philistines, this …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
