<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/anthony_onwuli/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/anthony_onwuli/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Highlights from the Electronic Entertainment Expo</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-highlights-from-the-electronic-entertainment-expo/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anthony Onwuli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-highlights-from-the-electronic-entertainment-expo/</guid>
        <description>E3 is drawing to a close but the big reveals have already happened. There are many games releasing this year and next year which we get to look forward to, but let’s dig into the highlights from some of the conferences.
EA
After multiple controversies with the Star Wars Battlefront series from DICE, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Road to E3 2019: Everything we know so far and what we expect to see revealed</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-the-road-to-e3-2019-everything-we-know-so-far-and-what-we-expect-to-see-revealed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anthony Onwuli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-the-road-to-e3-2019-everything-we-know-so-far-and-what-we-expect-to-see-revealed/</guid>
        <description>Officially, the expo runs for three days. However, the E3 phenomena is more than just the LA convention. It encompasses all the announcements for new computer and video game releases, as well as the teasing of new video game hardware. From publishers announcing the next set of DLC as a means of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Okay Google. What’s a replacement to consoles? </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-okay-google-what-s-a-replacement-to-consoles/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anthony Onwuli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-okay-google-what-s-a-replacement-to-consoles/</guid>
        <description>Console generations have been marked with gamers dropping over £300-£400 on a new console, £50 on new titles, and more recently £60 a year to play their games online. But what if the future of the next generation required no consoles, no fancy rigs nor any need to pay to access the boradband your …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The convoluted road to Kingdom Hearts 3: A Kingdom Hearts Retrospective and Story Summary</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-the-convoluted-road-to-kingdom-hearts-3-a-kingdom-hearts-retrospective-and-story-summary/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anthony Onwuli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-the-convoluted-road-to-kingdom-hearts-3-a-kingdom-hearts-retrospective-and-story-summary/</guid>
        <description>Back in 2002, Square Enix (developers for the Final Fantasy and Dragon Quest franchises) and Disney collaborated on a video game project which resulted in the first Kingdom Hearts game on the PlayStation 2. Since then the franchise has gone on to grow in many different directions as the story has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Destiny Divorce - Activision and Bungie Split Up</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-the-destiny-divorce-activision-and-bungie-split-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anthony Onwuli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-the-destiny-divorce-activision-and-bungie-split-up/</guid>
        <description>Bungie and Activision Blizzard started their partnership in 2010 after Bungie gained their independence from Microsoft. Activision had in place a 10-year contract with the aim of helping Bungie launch their first project after Halo – Destiny. However, this 10-year contract has now been cut short …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Super Smash Bros. Ultimate</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-super-smash-bros-ultimate/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anthony Onwuli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-super-smash-bros-ultimate/</guid>
        <description>Super Smash Bros. Ultimate is the latest entry into the Super Smash Bros. video game series. This franchise made its debut in 1998 on the Nintendo 64 and has appeared on every Nintendo home console since: with Melee on the Gamecube, Brawl on the Wii and SSB4 on the Wii U and N3DS.
For those who do …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Microtransactions: the covert gambling ring of the gaming community</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-microtransactions-the-covert-gambling-ring-of-the-gaming-community/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anthony Onwuli,Sam Welton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-microtransactions-the-covert-gambling-ring-of-the-gaming-community/</guid>
        <description>The gambling accusation refers to loot boxes, effectively Pokémon booster packs for in-game cosmetics and perks. Much like card packs, most of the contents are common trash, but there is always potential of finding something rare and flashy that you can show off. Fundamentally, both card packs and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kingdom Hearts 3: A Hands On Review</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-kingdom-hearts-3-a-hands-on-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anthony Onwuli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-kingdom-hearts-3-a-hands-on-review/</guid>
        <description>This 16-year-old franchise has a special place in many gamers’ hearts for a variety of reasons. Some, for how convoluted the story has become from the original Kingdom Hearts, but many have come to love the franchise due to the crossover between the Final Fantasy and Disney characters, and how they …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Buck up for the Bronco: Red Dead Redemption 2</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-buck-up-for-the-bronco-red-dead-redemption-2/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,Anthony Onwuli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-buck-up-for-the-bronco-red-dead-redemption-2/</guid>
        <description>With the rising storm of hype brewing around Red Dead Redemption 2, we thought we’d shed a light on some of the features being added and what you can expect from the game. The majority of the information we’ve got here is straight from the horse’s mouth, in particular the developers themselves, with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix’s Gaming Section wants you! </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-felix-s-gaming-section-wants-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,Anthony Onwuli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-felix-s-gaming-section-wants-you/</guid>
        <description>Hello from the Games editors,
The Games editors not writing about games? Preposterous! This isn’t the content I expect in my Felix Newspaper! Alright, ease the frothing at the mouth and hear us out, I know it’s a strange concept but we’ve decided that rather than hog the gaming section we should …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>October Gaming Highlights</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-october-gaming-highlights/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,Anthony Onwuli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-october-gaming-highlights/</guid>
        <description>Forza Horizon 4 - Xbox One, PC - October 2nd:
Another fantastic addition to the series, Forza Horizon 4 steers clear from its traditional setting, with the game being set in an open world version of the United Kingdom as opposed to America. With a dynamic weather system, beautiful environment and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gamer’s guide to London: A comprehensive guide of all things tabletop, video games and more! </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-20-gamer-s-guide-to-london-a-comprehensive-guide-of-all-things-tabletop-video-games-and-more/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,Anthony Onwuli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-20-gamer-s-guide-to-london-a-comprehensive-guide-of-all-things-tabletop-video-games-and-more/</guid>
        <description>Leicester Square Station – Orbital Comics
For the vintage comic hunter Orbital Comics brings an expansive catalogue of comics new and old that can truly satiate the atypical comic book enthusiast. Within their collection they also boast a large amount of graphic novels as well as comic artworks. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I Herts Lacrosse 3.0: Fresher’s Tournament</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-i-herts-lacrosse-3-0-fresher-s-tournament/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anthony Onwuli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-i-herts-lacrosse-3-0-fresher-s-tournament/</guid>
        <description>The University of Hertfordshire Lacrosse club hosted a tournament to get freshers playing lacrosse, giving them a lot more game time and allowing them to develop their sticks skills. How else would you spend your Sunday? Playing lacrosse of course!
The Men’s 2s gathered at around midday, ready to …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
