<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/lh1009/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/lh1009/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Should we legalise marijuana?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-should-we-legalise-marijuana/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 12:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christopher Dillon,Lingxi Huang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-should-we-legalise-marijuana/</guid>
        <description>Yes – Chris Dillon
“The government has a contradictory policy”
Why can’t I smoke cannabis? Why should the government stop me doing what I want, taking what risks that I choose, with my body? Yes, the government does other things in the name of public health, e.g. making us wear a seatbelt. However, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Municipal bonds: The latest bubble?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-municipal-bonds-the-latest-bubble/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 20:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lingxi Huang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-municipal-bonds-the-latest-bubble/</guid>
        <description>As the sovereign default crisis in Europe continues to send tremors through the global financial system, the next perfect storm in the market may already be brewing on the other side of the Atlantic. Meredith Whitney, whose fame is attributed to her accurate predictions of the 2008 subprime mortgage …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Immigration cap will hit international students the hardest
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-12-immigration-cap-will-hit-international-students-the-hardest/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2010 14:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lingxi Huang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-12-immigration-cap-will-hit-international-students-the-hardest/</guid>
        <description>Speaking to the House of Commons on 23rd of November, the Home Secretary Theresa May announced plans to cut the number of non-EU immigrants by a fifth from next year. Student visas are amongst one the proposed targets for the cut. In light of the impending visa restrictions, the future of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rifts reappear less than a fortnight after G-20 pact
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-rifts-reappear-less-than-a-fortnight-after-g-20-pact/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2010 20:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lingxi Huang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-rifts-reappear-less-than-a-fortnight-after-g-20-pact/</guid>
        <description>After meeting in Seoul two weeks ago, governments from the G-20 group of the world’s 19 largest economies plus the EU agreed to halt competitive currency devaluation in hopes of allaying fears of an all-out currency war. The G-20 finance ministers vowed to address tensions in the currency markets. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>G-20 meets amid growing talk of a currency war
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-g-20-meets-amid-growing-talk-of-a-currency-war/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 19:30:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lingxi Huang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-g-20-meets-amid-growing-talk-of-a-currency-war/</guid>
        <description>After their meeting in Seoul, G-20 finance ministers expressed optimisim that a much-hyped global currency war may yet be avoided. Thoughts have now turned to the longer-term motivations for countries to manipulate their currencies to help exporters, and measures that can be taken against this.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
