<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rw507/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rw507/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The consolation prize? Nah, you can keep it.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-29-the-consolation-prize-nah-you-can-keep-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 16:23:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Webster,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-29-the-consolation-prize-nah-you-can-keep-it/</guid>
        <description>If you’ve been living under a rock these last two weeks, there was a lot of hype, building up to the reveal of Microsoft’s latest console – the last real contender in the latest saga of the console wars. As with anything that has ever had that much anticipation built up for it, you could hear the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Heads... or tails...?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-1-heads-or-tails/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 14:07:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Webster,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-1-heads-or-tails/</guid>
        <description>The long wait is finally over. After being teased for way over a year, the third game of the Bioshock franchise is out. I dedicated a good chunk of my life to the game already, so I think I’m in a good enough place to review it.
I’m going to skip my usual spiel about the history of the series, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The humble end of term bundle
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-the-humble-end-of-term-bundle/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 01:43:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Webster,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-the-humble-end-of-term-bundle/</guid>
        <description>Call me old fashioned, but I always thought that phones were for talking to people, rather than browsing the internet, watching moviesand playing games. Nowadays, it seems that phones are primarily used to avoid having to talk to people.
So, in my old fashioned-ness, I never really got into playing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Playing cops and robbers – a Police Force review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-playing-cops-and-robbers-a-police-force-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 22:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Webster,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-playing-cops-and-robbers-a-police-force-review/</guid>
        <description>From the pile of simulator games in the Felix office, this week’s random selection is Police Force. From the maker of the hit title Emergency, Police Force sees you patrolling the streets of Germany, towing illegally parked cars, setting up speed traps and arresting vandals. Plus, there’s a gun on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>La Playstation formidable?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-28-la-playstation-formidable/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 17:48:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Webster,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-28-la-playstation-formidable/</guid>
        <description>And here, in the wilderness of the internet, we can see grainy footage of the species, that many of us expect will beckon in a new age of couch-based gaming.
This beast has been in hibernation for a long time. Few have stumbled upon this elusive animal, and we had sketchy reports of its …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to the insane asylum
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-welcome-to-the-insane-asylum/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 14:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Webster,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-welcome-to-the-insane-asylum/</guid>
        <description>It has been a long time since my brain has hurt this much. I’ve just worked out how to reach the bottom of an endless staircase, and now I’m faced with alaser puzzle that needs 30 pieces, when I’ve only got 12, and I can’t even move them around. Welcome to Antichamber.
Imagine a game like Portal, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Aim for the heart... and try not to miss
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-aim-for-the-heart-and-try-not-to-miss/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 23:37:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Webster,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-aim-for-the-heart-and-try-not-to-miss/</guid>
        <description>Unsurprisingly, the sequel to the 2005 tactical shooter Sniper Elite, Sniper Elite V2 sees you ripping your way through Berlin, and anyone who looks at you slightly odd. The campaign co-op plays as you would expect – both players are identical in gameplay terms. You’ll look different, and you can …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Valentine’s Day: The Heist
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-valentines-day-the-heist/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 23:35:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Webster,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-valentines-day-the-heist/</guid>
        <description>Nothing says “I love you” more than robbing a bank together. Even if it’s four guys with a fetish for masks and gold.
In Payday: The Heist your fine self, and up to three other humans/A.I.s aim to steal as much money as you can, whilst under the imminent threat of being tazed in the groin. You’re …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Keep rollin’ rollin’ rollin’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-keep-rollin-rollin-rollin/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 23:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Webster,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-keep-rollin-rollin-rollin/</guid>
        <description>I feared this would happen. It was foretold by an ancient Mayan calendar, and Nostradamus mentioned it somewhere. It’s a simulator game that I like, and won’t take the mickey out of. Much.
From the studio that brought us Euro Truck Simulator (numbers 1 and 2), Trucks &amp;amp; Trailers has you in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A bit that will really drive you a long way
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-a-bit-that-will-really-drive-you-a-long-way/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 21:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Webster,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-a-bit-that-will-really-drive-you-a-long-way/</guid>
        <description>Hah – you thought that you would escape my zombie fanaticissm this week, but you haven’t! This week’s selection is Zombie Driver, the spiritual sequel to Zombie Chauffeur, the game adaptation of the BAFTA winning Driving Miss Zombie.
Disappointingly, your exploits are not narrated by Morgan Freeman …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Take us to your editor
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-take-us-to-your-editor/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 21:07:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Webster,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-take-us-to-your-editor/</guid>
        <description>Assuming that it’s not just your mothers that read Felix, you’ll probably be aware of the simulator surplus that has hit the Felix office. Well, Excalibur Publishing (those lovely folk who send us these games) also publish real games. Sorry if I sound condescending to you hardcore sim-junkies (you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bridging the gap
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-bridging-the-gap/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 00:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Webster,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-bridging-the-gap/</guid>
        <description>I wonder if any of you actually get any revision done – by an almost unanimous vote, this week’s review selection is The Bridge Project. A quick introduction to the game’s genre would be as follows: you have a bridge you need to build, and you’ve limited resources. Your bridge will have to stand up …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ControverZ
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-controverz/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 23:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Webster,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-controverz/</guid>
        <description>It’s not exactly a secret that I’m a fan of zombie games. From fully-fledged team-based games such as Left 4 Dead, to mods such as No More Room in Hell and DayZ. If you’ve been around this genre before, you’ll notice that it nearly always takes place in the ruins of cities and towns. It makes sense, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Year’s 2048x1152
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-new-years-2048x1152/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 23:22:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Webster,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-new-years-2048x1152/</guid>
        <description>With the Steam sales now over, it’s officially the start of the 2013 gaming calendar. Even before I got to mark ten days on my pin-up calendar of Alyx ‘Miss January’ Vance, there’s news that blows away the cobwebs of 2012. As it’s exam time, I’m gonna be light on your mind and not hide any secret …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial vs. UCL Round 2
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-imperial-vs-ucl-round-2/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 22:54:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Webster,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-imperial-vs-ucl-round-2/</guid>
        <description>This Tuesday, it was Imperial’s turn to host the Imperial vs. UCL gaming tournament. The room was packed, so I was expecting fierce fighting from both sides. Instead, I was met with familiar faces at every turn. In fact, about 80% of the room were Imperial students, from what I’ve heard.
My spies, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Abandonment Issues
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-abandonment-issues/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 23:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Webster,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-abandonment-issues/</guid>
        <description>It happened again this week. I was running around the ruins of a mining operation, in a cave, now made accessible by the departure of a floating city, which acted like a cork upon this bottle of badly-aged acid, when I looked up and I got the urge. This isn’t the kind of urge that involves running …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First impressions: Halo 4
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-first-impressions-halo-4/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 16:03:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Webster,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-first-impressions-halo-4/</guid>
        <description>Let me point this out before I start – I love the Halo universe and the progression and impact the game series has made within the industry. I remember picking up Halo: CE many years ago and not having a PC that could play it, faster than I could draw the frames with a novelty pencil the size of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Haunted Holland Halloween
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-a-haunted-holland-halloween/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 22:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Webster,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-a-haunted-holland-halloween/</guid>
        <description>It was a Wednesday afternoon like any other. Laptops, consoles and “You n00b!” screaming across the room, marking the start of the training session for this week’s UCL vs Imperial gaming tournaments. This was just the beginning.
In the dark depths of the Sherfield building (beneath Holland Club, to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A rock and a hard place
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-a-rock-and-a-hard-place/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 22:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Webster,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-a-rock-and-a-hard-place/</guid>
        <description>This week, I played a game that saved my life.
It was a dark night. The stars were smothered by the sodium-lit clouds and the rain had flushed the vermin from the street. It was a quiet night. I kept on walking, a silhouette against the bright shop fronts, welcoming the shadows of the houses. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I left my will to live in San Francisco
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-i-left-my-will-to-live-in-san-francisco/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 02:43:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Webster,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-i-left-my-will-to-live-in-san-francisco/</guid>
        <description>So, for those of you who actually read these colour-anemic boxes, last week I put up a vote for which simulator game I should play and review. I had a deluge of emails telling me to try the ‘social life’ simulator and that I should get out of the Felix office, but the joke’s on them – I’m dead …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A DayZ by any other name...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-12-a-dayz-by-any-other-name/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2012 10:57:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Webster,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-12-a-dayz-by-any-other-name/</guid>
        <description>Zombie games have taken all shapes and sizes over the years, from Wii-based Evil Dead-style games within the Resident Evil universe (Umbrella Chronicles) to frantic rooftop gunfights in the Left 4 Dead series. They all bring in the element of isolation into the mix, surrounded by crumbling cities …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You’re-a-Gamer Expo
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-youre-a-gamer-expo/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 11:34:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Webster,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-youre-a-gamer-expo/</guid>
        <description>Last weekend saw the start of the London Games Festival, heralded in by the fifth Eurogamer Expo. Not exactly as groundbreaking as an Apple Keynote, the Eurogamer (EG) Expo is a place for developers and publishers to offer up their latest works to the willing public, letting us play games months …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A visit from St Nicholas
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-a-visit-from-st-nicholas/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 21:28:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Webster,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-a-visit-from-st-nicholas/</guid>
        <description>‘Twas the night before Christmas, when all through the lab, Not a test subject was stirring, not even the crab. The turrets were placed by the windows with care, In hopes that St Nicholas soon would be there.
The cubes were nestled all snug in their beds, While visions of loved ones danced in their …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
