<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/charlestitmuss/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/charlestitmuss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Midsummer in Midwinter</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-midsummer-in-winter/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-29-midsummer-in-winter/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
For those unfamiliar with the plot, A Midsummer Night’s Dream is a classic Shakespearean comedy. In this adaptation by the National Youth Theatre (NYT), several changes to the plot and setting have been made. The most obvious setting change was that instead of the traditional Athens of, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Fourth Response on “Companies in China”</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-fourth-response-companies-in-china/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-fourth-response-companies-in-china/</guid>
        <description>This article forms part of a series of articles and responses, originating with Charles Titmuss&amp;rsquo; (2019 Comment Editor) article &amp;ldquo;Companies in China&amp;rdquo;.
It would appear that I have drawn the ire of two commentators due to articles that I wrote a couple of weeks ago. This is the last …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Response to “A Response to Companies in China”</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-08-11-a-response-to-a-response-to-companies-in-china/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-08-11-a-response-to-a-response-to-companies-in-china/</guid>
        <description>A couple of weeks ago, I wrote an article concerning Blizzard’s censorship of pro-Hong Kong protests entitled “Companies in China.” We have republished the article in question to provide context to this issue. Felix received a response which I recommend you look over before reading this, on the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Companies in China</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-08-11-companies-in-china/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-08-11-companies-in-china/</guid>
        <description>For those of you that live on Instagram and have never met a cheeto-eating basement dweller, Blizzard are a gaming company that have developed some of the most popular titles over the last 20 years including Starcraft, Hearthstone and, of course, World of Warcraft. These games are popular all over …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Frankenstein: Resurrected for the Modern Day</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-frankenstein-resurrected-for-modern-day/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-frankenstein-resurrected-for-modern-day/</guid>
        <description>It’s been a long time since Frankenstein was first published. Written in 1818 by Mary Shelley, the gothic novel swiftly became a cultural icon. Widely regarded as one of the first science fiction novels ever written, Frankenstein follows the tragic tale of Dr Victor Frankenstein and his destructive …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gaslight- A Play About Mental Delusion</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-gaslight-play-mental-delusion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-gaslight-play-mental-delusion/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
I had always assumed that ‘gaslighting’, a form of psychological manipulation which systematically breaks down another person’s grip on reality, was a very modern phenomenon. Imagine my surprise when I found out that its etymology derives from a play first written in 1938. Gaslight tells the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Great Expectations</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-great-expectations/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-great-expectations/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
My week began this Monday with Great Expectations. I was richly rewarded by a play that was wonderfully acted and brought to life the world of Pip, Miss Havisham and Magwitch.
For those of you unfamiliar with the plot, it follows the life of Pip, an adopted blacksmith’s son. Pip, whilst …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Moving to Mars</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-moving-mars/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-moving-mars/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
Space travel and design go hand in immaculately engineered glove. Rockets and rovers, space stations and satellites, the unique environmental challenges that extra-terrestrial exploration must solve are fascinating. The exhibition, “Moving to Mars,” is the engrossing result of the human …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Turkish Invasion of Syria</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-turkish-invasion-syria/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-turkish-invasion-syria/</guid>
        <description>Turkey has always occupied a strategically significant place in history. As the bastion for the Byzantine Empire, as the base for Ottoman dominance of the Middle East and as the gateway to the Crimea, Turkey has always been a valuable prize. More recently, Turkey’s membership of NATO was a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Companies in China</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-companies-in-china/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-companies-in-china/</guid>
        <description>This article resulted in a series of follow-up articles and responses from the author and student respondents, which can be found in the Comment section.
For those of you that live on Instagram and have never met a cheeto-eating basement dweller, Blizzard are a gaming company that have developed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Interview with the Makers of Now is the Time to Say Nothing</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-interview-makers-now-time-say-nothing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-interview-makers-now-time-say-nothing/</guid>
        <description>Would you mind briefly summarising your stories?
Caroline Williams: This is the story of Syrian artist Reem Karssli’s life during the Syrian conflict. It follows the story of what happens when a group of teenagers from London tries to contact her. It is about how we can stay connected to the people …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Now is the Time to Say Nothing</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-now-time-say-nothing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-now-time-say-nothing/</guid>
        <description>3 stars
This article was followed by an interview with the makers, available in the Arts section.
What to say for Now is the Time to Say Nothing? Now is the Time&amp;hellip;, is primarily a piece of artwork about relationships. Although there is a focus on the relationship between one group of Western …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We need an election</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-we-need-an-election/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-we-need-an-election/</guid>
        <description>There have been moments in world politics in the past four years where I have been surprised and perturbed by the result. Post-election hangovers are nearly always the best way to dull the immediate pain of being slapped in the face by certain events. At precisely 13:21 on Thursday 13th June, I read …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pointless, homophobic protests</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-pointless-homophobic-protests/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-pointless-homophobic-protests/</guid>
        <description>The introduction of the No Outsiders programme to schools in Birmingham has resulted in significant nationwide protests. The goal of the programme was to teach children about the protected characteristics in the Equalities Act 2010, including LGBT+ groups. Following its introduction, some parents …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dinomania</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-21-dinomania/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-21-dinomania/</guid>
        <description>Last Tuesday I had the pleasure of attending a production of the play Dinomania, produced by the Kandinsky theatre company at the New Diorama Theatre, courtesy of Felix Arts.
Dinomania is a production focused on the life of Gideon Mantell, a figure at the centre of the scientific movement that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who should vote on what?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-who-should-vote-on-what/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-who-should-vote-on-what/</guid>
        <description>The Brexit vote has been in the zeitgeist for the past month as everything comes to a head. I humbly ask the reader to cast their minds back to that rosy day on the 23rd of June when the nation voted inconclusively for something to do with Europe. Although much attention has been paid to the way the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Death Register: a review</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-death-register-a-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-death-register-a-review/</guid>
        <description>Death Register is a novel outside my literary comfort zone. It follows the formative years of Chauncey Knuckle and his group of friends, growing up in the city of Montego Bay. It explores their relationships with their peers, their families and their teachers against the intensely homophobic and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Legitimate violence?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-legitimate-violence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-legitimate-violence/</guid>
        <description>Violence, or the threat of violence has been one of the governing factors of human interaction for as long as humans have been in existence, from the earliest social groups right through to the foundation of the modern state. In the modern day, violence and the threat of violence are the fundamental …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We Must Fight Inequality Using the State</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-we-must-fight-inequality-using-the-state/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-we-must-fight-inequality-using-the-state/</guid>
        <description>Governments and the state itself exist due to their ability to marshal large forces of people to achieve a common goal. The modern state was inexorable in its ability to extend its influence around the globe, to the point that where there are humans, there are now states to govern them. The nation …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why faith schools are just grammar schools by another name</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-why-faith-schools-are-just-grammar-schools-by-another-name/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-why-faith-schools-are-just-grammar-schools-by-another-name/</guid>
        <description>Faith schools are about to become a major topic of conversation in UK politics. The new education secretary, Damian Hinds, has committed to remove the 50% cap on the number of students belonging to a certain religious denomination at a school. It is thought that this would benefit primarily Catholic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dystopian sci-fi is absolutely necessary</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-dystopian-sci-fi-is-absolutely-necessary/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-dystopian-sci-fi-is-absolutely-necessary/</guid>
        <description>In an article published last week, the current TV Editor proposed that the dystopian futures shown in contemporary sci-fi are no longer necessary, for a wide range of reasons. I disagree: the purpose of this article is to highlight instead the value of these forms of entertainment, especially in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tête á Tête: Fred’s dead baby, Fred’s dead</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-t-te-t-te-fred-s-dead-baby-fred-s-dead/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alan Perfect Ruiz De Velasco,Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-t-te-t-te-fred-s-dead-baby-fred-s-dead/</guid>
        <description>The revolution has finally arrived at the Felix Comment section!
Charles Titmuss
People rejoice! The brutal dictator General Fyles is no more! His evil reign has finally come to an end, after a prolonged internal struggle, led by the brave Colonel Alan Perfect and ably supported by Major Charles …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kim Jong-un is perfectly sane</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-kim-jong-un-is-perfectly-sane/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-kim-jong-un-is-perfectly-sane/</guid>
        <description>North Korea, as a state, adheres to the Juche philosophy. Created by Kim Il-sung, the founding ruler of North Korea, it expounds a policy of self-reliance. Under the guiding hand of successive members of the Kim dynasty, North Korea has moved into the 21st century as a deeply repressive and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Defeating ISIS is impossible. Dealing with them is not
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-defeating-isis-is-impossible-dealing-with-them-is-not/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 14:53:24 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-defeating-isis-is-impossible-dealing-with-them-is-not/</guid>
        <description>The UK has been subjected to a number of terrorist acts. At this point in time it is appropriate to mourn and honour the dead and remember that nothing can justify these acts. At the same time, it is important to look at this topic with nuance if we as a nation wish to solve this problem. Two …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The West&#39;s little nuclear problem
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-the-wests-little-nuclear-problem/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 15:48:24 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-the-wests-little-nuclear-problem/</guid>
        <description>In the last month, relations between North Korea and the rest of the world have soured, due to a series of missile launches. North Korea is one of the world’s most secretive and oppressive states, and has harboured nuclear ambitions for a long time. Its complex relationship with the rest of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Labour has a one way ticket to Switzerland
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-labour-has-a-one-way-ticket-to-switzerland/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 14:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-labour-has-a-one-way-ticket-to-switzerland/</guid>
        <description>T he by-elections in both Stoke and Copeland were both called recently, due to their respective MPs resigning. As I’m sure you are aware, Labour lost the Copeland seat and held on to the Stoke seat, but suffered a reduction in the proportion of votes compared to 2015. This is viewed by many, myself …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Putin has a huge power hard on
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-putin-has-a-huge-power-hard-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 14:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-putin-has-a-huge-power-hard-on/</guid>
        <description>From his images in National Media (and yes, those do require capital letters), it’s clear that Vladimir Vladimirovich Putin has a hard on for one man: himself. Whether he’s shirtless fishing, riding a horse, or killing a bear with his bare hands, Putin’s got a thing for being the manliest manly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Leave Trident alone
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-leave-trident-alone/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 15:54:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-leave-trident-alone/</guid>
        <description>Trident was announced as the UK’s new deterrent back in 1980, and patrols with the missile began in 1994. The renewal of trident was debated in July 2016, to replace the current submarines with the newer Dreadnought Class by 2028. The estimated cost of the upgraded weapons system is around £31 …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
