<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ps3411/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ps3411/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Students are taking to the campaign trail too
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-1-students-are-taking-to-the-campaign-trail-too/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:26:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Plabon Saha,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-1-students-are-taking-to-the-campaign-trail-too/</guid>
        <description>As a member of the Liberal Youth, I was invited to go canvassing in various target seats in the country. It’s a great scheme where they give you some money towards travel, free accommodation and food and there’s a social to cap things off at the weekend.
I went to the marginal seat of Oxford West …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Alumni in Politics: Tom Brake
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-4-10-imperial-alumni-in-politics-tom-brake/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2015 19:56:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Plabon Saha,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-4-10-imperial-alumni-in-politics-tom-brake/</guid>
        <description>Tom Brake has been a MP for Carshalton and Wallington since 1997. In this parliament he has served as the Deputy Leader of the House of Commons and assistant whip for the Liberal Democrats. Tom graduated from Imperial in 1983 and recently returned to campus in an event hosted by the Imperial Liberal …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Alumni in Politics: Layla Moran
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-4-1-imperial-alumni-in-politics-layla-moran/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 17:01:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Plabon Saha,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-4-1-imperial-alumni-in-politics-layla-moran/</guid>
        <description>Layla Moran, a physics graduate from Imperial College London is currently running for Parliament in the ultra-marginal seat of Oxford West and Abingdon. Last weekend the Imperial Liberal Democrats popped down to help Layla with her campaign. We caught up with Layla over lunch.
Plabon: Tell us a bit …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Open letter from the Royal College of Science Union
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-open-letter-from-the-royal-college-of-science-union/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 12:15:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Plabon Saha,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-open-letter-from-the-royal-college-of-science-union/</guid>
        <description>Dear all, The start of the new term is here and it gives me great pleasure to see everyone back on campus. And of course I must not forget to welcome the freshers who will be joining this brilliant institution and especially the scientists who are lucky enough to be part of the best constituent …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>RCSU Freshers Fortnight: Legit review from the RCSU Office
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-rcsu-freshers-fortnight-legit-review-from-the-rcsu-office/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 12:12:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Plabon Saha,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-rcsu-freshers-fortnight-legit-review-from-the-rcsu-office/</guid>
        <description>Someone told me today that you shouldn’t write reviews of your own events. I obviously didn’t listen to their advice; after all, who can know better what went down at the RCSU events than people within the RCSU?! My sincerest apologies to the other constituent unions who are obviously lagging …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The real cost of our cheap clothing
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-1-the-real-cost-of-our-cheap-clothing/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 14:50:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imogen Smith,Plabon Saha,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-1-the-real-cost-of-our-cheap-clothing/</guid>
        <description>As a new term dawns we know we won’t be the only ones indulging in a little online shopping procrastination. We are often reminded to think about where the various elements of our life come from, our food, our energy, but what about our clothes? At a time when your moral and ethical values are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Halestorm brings down the house in Camden
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-halestorm-brings-down-the-house-in-camden/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 02:50:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Plabon Saha,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-halestorm-brings-down-the-house-in-camden/</guid>
        <description>I like to think my taste in music has greatly varied over the years. I have gone through the teenage phase of listening to Green Day, Sex Pistols, Fall out Boy, Panic! At the Disco etc. You get the gist of it all. There was also a time when I used to listen to hard rock in the form of System of a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Johnny Marr scores above par
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-28-johnny-marr-scores-above-par/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 23:29:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Plabon Saha,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-28-johnny-marr-scores-above-par/</guid>
        <description>At 49 years of age, it seems slightly odd that it took Johnny Marr this long to put out a solo album. Renowned for being the guitarist of the influential indie pop band The Smiths in the 80’s, Marr has been busy since then playing in many bands such as Modest Mouse, accompanied by The Healers and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>RCSU on top
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-rcsu-on-top/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 20:49:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Plabon Saha,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-rcsu-on-top/</guid>
        <description>Fresher’s Fair 2012 saw an unprecedented rise in mascotry and the RCSU-CGCU rivalry was re-ignited with a burning vengeance. After the capture of the ICSMU’s Phoenix head last year the RCSU went a step further as it is currently holding onto City and Guild Union’s Bolt and Spanner and the ICSMU’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I am an Anti-Christ, I am an Anarchist
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-i-am-an-anti-christ-i-am-an-anarchist/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 20:22:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Plabon Saha,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-i-am-an-anti-christ-i-am-an-anarchist/</guid>
        <description>For anyone who knows about the history of punk music, they will instantly recognise the title as part of one of the most famous songs that went on to define the genre. In the 70’s the Sex Pistols, fronted by Johnny Rotten a.k.a John Lydon, started a revolution in the music scene with just one album. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A power play with the most powerful family in Britain
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-a-power-play-with-the-most-powerful-family-in-britain/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 22:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Plabon Saha,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-a-power-play-with-the-most-powerful-family-in-britain/</guid>
        <description>After a successful first season, Sherlock is back on our screens. Giving the detective stories a 21st century make-up, the second season does not disappoint. In fact it picks up exactly where it left off, full of suspense, comedy and twists. The way things are turning out, Sherlock should be added …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
