<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/kr1512/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/kr1512/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Russia and the situation in Ukraine
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-14-russia-and-the-situation-in-ukraine/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 03:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kartikeya Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-14-russia-and-the-situation-in-ukraine/</guid>
        <description>Ukraine has been currently going through a very tumultuous period with protests and rioting in various parts of the country. The interest of the Russian government in Ukraine may have a grave impact on the Sochi Winter Olympics and lead to further scrutiny of the Putin government by western powers …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nuclear agreement signed with Iran
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-nuclear-agreement-signed-with-iran/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 21:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kartikeya Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-nuclear-agreement-signed-with-iran/</guid>
        <description>After months of escalating tensions between Iran and the United States, a nuclear deal has finally been signed. After intense negotiations between the P5+1 nations- the Permanent members of the UN Security Council and Germany- and Iran was signed in Geneva. The agreement is one, which manages to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The situation in Iraq after the war with US
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-the-situation-in-iraq-after-the-war-with-us/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 09:43:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kartikeya Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-the-situation-in-iraq-after-the-war-with-us/</guid>
        <description>Ever since the US troops were withdrawn from Iraq in 2011, there has been little international coverage about the situation in Iraq. Iraq is in a state of dysfunctional governance and civil strife. This has caused the present Prime Minister, Nuri Al-Maliki, to ask for military assistance from the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tensions Escalate Between US and Germany
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-tensions-escalate-between-us-and-germany/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 09:29:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kartikeya Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-tensions-escalate-between-us-and-germany/</guid>
        <description>NSA whistleblower, Edward Snowden, has recently leaked documents stating that the US has been monitoring phone calls of Angela Merkel and other European leaders. According to a German newspaper, Der Spiegel, the US has been monitoring Angela Merkel’s phone since 2002. Such operations are said to be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This Week in Politics: October 12 2013
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-11-this-week-in-politics-october-12-2013/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 23:32:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kartikeya Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-11-this-week-in-politics-october-12-2013/</guid>
        <description>UK e-borders scheme deemed ineffective:
Reports have suggested that the £500m ‘e-borders’ programme propelled by the Home Office has not been very effective in dealing with migrants who are said to be potentially dangerous. This scheme, which took 10 years to develop, was made to ensure that ‘high …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who Are Al Shabbab?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-who-are-al-shabbab/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 00:43:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kartikeya Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-who-are-al-shabbab/</guid>
        <description>A devastating attack in a shopping mall in Nairobi took place on the 23rd of September. Gunmen killed 67 people, according to government sources , in the Westgate Mall. These militants were said to belong to the extremist group originating from Somalia called Al Shabbab. But who are these peddlers …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>US Government Shutdown
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-us-government-shutdown/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 00:39:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kartikeya Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-us-government-shutdown/</guid>
        <description>The non-essential services provided by the US government have grinded to a halt as there is disagreement in Congress about the current budget. This not only weakens the country financially but also shows the inefficiency US congress has to deliberate and compromise in situations where ideologies …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The summer in politics
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-the-summer-in-politics/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 14:13:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kartikeya Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-the-summer-in-politics/</guid>
        <description> Well hello there all you freshers (and everybody else)! Here comes yet another year of Imperial. A small amount of us do tend to have an interest in politics surprisingly enough. So if you are one of those people who likes to learn about world affairs or likes to have a drunk rant, like I do, about …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Democracy and the Lack of Representation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-11-democracy-and-the-lack-of-representation/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2013 00:47:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kartikeya Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-11-democracy-and-the-lack-of-representation/</guid>
        <description>In this day and age, democracy does not necessary mean equal representation as we are made to believe. In this editorial, I will look at certain issues from around the world that seem to elucidate upon this problem.
Discrimination by a democratic government due to a certain persons belief and/or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Discontent in Colombia
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-3-discontent-in-colombia/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2013 09:45:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kartikeya Rana,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-3-discontent-in-colombia/</guid>
        <description>Angry protestors took to the streets of the capital on Thursday to let their discontent be known. A large number of protesters, banging pots and pans, marched through the streets of Bogotá, while avoiding riot police.
There is outrage in Columbia due to the free trade agreement that President Juan …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
