<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mjj15/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mjj15/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Manifesto breakdowns
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-manifesto-breakdowns/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:59:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,Cale E Tilford,Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-manifesto-breakdowns/</guid>
        <description> This piece aims to break down the main party manifestos and summarise a few key policies. This is by no means a full and in-depth analysis of each party. Mainly because the manifestos are long and complex, and it’s exam season. [Insert tinfoil hat theory that the timing of the election coincides …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An idiot’s guide to the UK general election
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-an-idiots-guide-to-the-uk-general-election/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:57:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-an-idiots-guide-to-the-uk-general-election/</guid>
        <description>Ding ding ding, it’s election time again. No, you haven’t woken up from that nap in 2020, they’ve called an early election. Do you have no idea who you’re voting for? Well, you’re in luck my friend, because we’ve got a whole pull-out complete with manifesto breakdowns, and personal views on who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Palestinian Ambassador gives talk
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-palestinian-ambassador-gives-talk/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 16:54:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-palestinian-ambassador-gives-talk/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College was host last week to Manuel Hassassian, the Palestinian Authority’s diplomatic representative to the UK, following reactions to a talk with the Israeli ambassador Mark Regev back in January (Dr. Hassassian does not have the rank of ambassador as the UK does not presently recognize …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>SPA awards shortlist announced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-spa-awards-shortlist-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 16:28:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-spa-awards-shortlist-announced/</guid>
        <description>UPDATE: We didn&amp;rsquo;t win anything, there is no god, and everything sucks
April saw felix getting shortlisted for four Student Publication Association Awards last month, with Editor Lef Apostolakis and Comment Editor/Millennials Queen/felix Vice Chair/Office Legend Tessa Davey each garnering two …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Business School appoints new Dean
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-business-school-appoints-new-dean/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 13:07:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-business-school-appoints-new-dean/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Business School appointed a new Dean this week, Professor Francisco Veloso. Veloso takes on the position in August after a year of temporary leadership from Professor Nelson Phillips, who held the role of Acting Dean after the previous Dean (Professor G. ‘Anand’ Anandalingam) …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>No mascotry resolution in sight
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-no-mascotry-resolution-in-sight/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 14:21:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-no-mascotry-resolution-in-sight/</guid>
        <description>The age-old Imperial tradition of mascot stealing (also known as mascotry) was once again brought up at Union Council on Monday, in an attempt to create a new, contemporary set of rules to regulate the competitive ‘sport’.
Mascotry involves the theft of the various antique items that each of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Israeli ambassador’s visit | Wraith speaks up
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-israeli-ambassadors-visit-wraith-speaks-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 13:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-israeli-ambassadors-visit-wraith-speaks-up/</guid>
        <description>Two weeks ago the Israeli ambassador to the UK, Mark Regev, visited Imperial to give a talk to students in an event that was shrouded in secrecy. An article detailing what went on at the event and the build-up to the day itself was published in felix last week but since then the chair of the talk, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Israeli ambassador’s secret visit to Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-israeli-ambassadors-secret-visit-to-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 14:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-israeli-ambassadors-secret-visit-to-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Last week the Israeli Ambassador to Britain, Mark Regev visited Imperial College, giving a talk in the Clore Lecture Theatre in Huxley Building. The talk, for which publicity was incredibly limited, was attended by around 200 students and was shrouded in secrecy right up until the very last moment. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BEEP BEEP BEEP | Brexit update
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-beep-beep-beep-brexit-update/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 14:19:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-beep-beep-beep-brexit-update/</guid>
        <description>The sun keeps on rising, the world keeps on spinning and the Brexit debate rages on. Last week Theresa May made a speech at Lancaster House which outlined her twelve point plan for the UK’s negotiation plan as she looks to trigger Article 50 and leave the European Union for good.
The main headline …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An idiot’s guide to 2016
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-an-idiots-guide-to-2016/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 14:28:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-an-idiots-guide-to-2016/</guid>
        <description> It’s been a rollercoaster ride. Except a rollercoaster ride where you threw up on yourself at the start. But, let’s take a trip down memory lane; there are a few nuggets of joy to be found amongst the pile of crap that was 2016. Promise.
January So it didn’t really get off to the best of starts did …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union’s three year strategy proposal
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-unions-three-year-strategy-proposal/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 13:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-unions-three-year-strategy-proposal/</guid>
        <description>The Union this week released its plan so far for 2017-2020 and opened it up to feedback from the student body. This is the final round of drafting, feedback, and re-drafting of the proposals, in a process that’s been ongoing since the start of this calendar year.
The previous round of consultation …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union puts forward NSS recommendations
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-union-puts-forward-nss-recommendations/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 14:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-union-puts-forward-nss-recommendations/</guid>
        <description> The National Student Survey (NSS) came out earlier this year and the long and the short of it is that students are getting less and less satisfied with both College and the Union. The Union has now published its list of recommendations it wanted College to enact to try and reverse the slump, all of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial team wins iGEM competition
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-imperial-team-wins-igem-competition/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 11:50:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-imperial-team-wins-igem-competition/</guid>
        <description>Imperial triumphed at the International Genetically Engineered Machine (iGEM) competition in Boston last week, with their project ‘Ecolibrium’ beating almost 300 other undergraduate teams from around the globe.
The project centres around a process known as ‘Co-culturing’ where different types of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The US Presidential Election fallout
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-the-us-presidential-election-fallout/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 11:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-the-us-presidential-election-fallout/</guid>
        <description> They only went and bloody voted for him, didn’t they? By now if you haven’t seen the news that Donald Trump, the Washington outsider, is the 45th President of The United States then I’m not sure if you’ve actually been conscious since Wednesday. For those of you that read the headline and started …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An idiot’s guide to the US Election
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-3-an-idiots-guide-to-the-us-election/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 23:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-3-an-idiots-guide-to-the-us-election/</guid>
        <description> Remember 2012? The London Olympics, (almost) the end of the world and the last US presidential election? Well fast forward four years and we’ve had another set of Olympics, another election cycle is coming to a climax and, if you believe everything people are saying on Twitter, the world is coming …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Professor Hawking visits Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-21-professor-hawking-visits-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 09:39:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Selin Olenik,Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-21-professor-hawking-visits-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Esteemed theoretical physics boffin, Professor Stephen Hawking, gave a lecture on Monday evening, speaking on black holes, Hawking Radiation, and AI.
Taking place in a packed Great Hall, Professor Hawking was introduced via a video from The Big Bang Theory’s Sheldon Cooper before launching into his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Alice Gast’s autumn letter
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-21-alice-gasts-autumn-letter/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 09:18:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Selin Olenik,Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-21-alice-gasts-autumn-letter/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College President, Alice Gast, released her autumn letter this week and set out College’s vision for the future, a post Brexit future.
The letter touched on the fact that (spoiler alert) Brexit is happening and what the College plans to do to keep the status quo as much as possible. Gast …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hunt reveals his NHS plans
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-14-hunt-reveals-his-nhs-plans/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 09:48:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Selin Olenik,Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-14-hunt-reveals-his-nhs-plans/</guid>
        <description>Jeremy Hunt revealed his new plan for the future of the NHS last week, a mix of creating more British doctors and attempting to keep the ones that are trained here for longer.
Currently there’s a cap of 6,000 students attending medical schools country-wide and Hunt plans to raise this by 25%, giving …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Government asks for listing of foreign workers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-14-government-asks-for-listing-of-foreign-workers/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 09:22:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-14-government-asks-for-listing-of-foreign-workers/</guid>
        <description>Plans released at the Conservative Party Conference last week outlined a proposal for a register of foreign workers in UK companies. Amber Rudd, the new Home Secretary, announced that companies may be forced to submit a list of workers to the government in order to “nudge them into better …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Another club bites the dust
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-another-club-bites-the-dust/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 17:04:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-another-club-bites-the-dust/</guid>
        <description>The iconic Islington Club, Fabric, shut it’s doors for possibly the last time over summer after it had its licence revoked by the local council.
Two deaths earlier in the year prompted a review of the club which concluded that its security and searches were “inadequate and in breach of the licence”. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Night tube dream, finally a reality
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-night-tube-dream-finally-a-reality/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 17:02:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-night-tube-dream-finally-a-reality/</guid>
        <description>Remember last summer when London was oh-so close to having a 24 hour tube service on the weekend? Well it’s here, it’s finally bloody here.
After delays due to striking unions and arguments over pay and working conditions, the whole of the Victoria line and a good chunk of the Central line (Ealing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An idiot’s guide to... Summer 2016
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-an-idiots-guide-to-summer-2016/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 16:53:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-an-idiots-guide-to-summer-2016/</guid>
        <description> Ah, summer. That brief and fleeting moment of respite between the end of one exam period and the start of the next? Well here’s a recap for those of you who either forgot what went down or were on one of those holidays where you’re in a cave for a month because it cleanses your soul.
Brexit So, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College contemplating smoking ban
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-college-contemplating-smoking-ban/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 11:08:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-college-contemplating-smoking-ban/</guid>
        <description>If you follow the IC Union pages on Twitter or Facebook you may have seen the recent poll they ran on the question of “Should smoking be allowed on campus?”.
The snap poll was taken by the Union not as their own initiative but in order to get a broader view of the student body’s opinion.
A College …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Idiot’s Guide To A Post Brexit World
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-7-4-an-idiots-guide-to-a-post-brexit-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 09:55:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-7-4-an-idiots-guide-to-a-post-brexit-world/</guid>
        <description>So, we’re out. What now, eh? What came to pass last Thursday and early Friday morning was, whichever way you cut it, historic. No full country, this deep in the EU, has left it before and now we’ve got to deal with the fallout for better or for worse.
Chaos was the undoubtedly the adjective of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial is one of Europe’s most innovative universities
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-imperial-is-one-of-europes-most-innovative-universities/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 08:52:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-imperial-is-one-of-europes-most-innovative-universities/</guid>
        <description>Thomson Reuters this week released a report listing the most innovative universities in Europe, with Imperial coming in 2nd on the list just behind KU Leuven in Belgium.
Innovation was defined by using ten different parameters, notably the volume of academic papers it published (indicating the basic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Top investor buys shares in Imperial Innovations
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-top-investor-buys-shares-in-imperial-innovations/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 08:51:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-top-investor-buys-shares-in-imperial-innovations/</guid>
        <description>One of the UK’s top investors, Neil Woodford has invested a further £11.6 million into Imperial Innovations, the intermediary between Imperial research and the wider world, taking his stake over 20%.
Imperial Innovations had posted a pre tax loss of £5.9 million in the six months before the end of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>EU debate takes place at Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-eu-debate-takes-place-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 08:14:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-eu-debate-takes-place-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Last Thursday, The Big EU Debate took over Skempton building with members of both the leave and remain campaign battling it out over the key battlegrounds of the economy, immigration and democracy as a whole.
Speaking for the remain campaign were Mary Honeyball (Labour MEP for London) and Amelia …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial sells off last shares of life sciences start-up
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-imperial-sells-off-last-shares-of-life-sciences-start-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 08:35:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-imperial-sells-off-last-shares-of-life-sciences-start-up/</guid>
        <description>Imperial Innovations Group, the company which oversees the spin-off companies from technology developed at Imperial, has sold its remaining shares in Alkion Biopharma to chemical giant, Evonik Industries.
Alkion Biopharm specialises in technologies relating to biochemistry, chiefly in producing and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tuition fees will rise with inflation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-tuition-fees-will-rise-with-inflation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 08:48:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-tuition-fees-will-rise-with-inflation/</guid>
        <description>The government has released a white paper this week outlining its future plans for higher education, most notably allowing universities to charge more than £9000 per year in tuition fees.
These plans come just four years after the trebling of tuition fees by the coalition government (and the ensuing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An idiot’s guide to the EU referendum
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-an-idiots-guide-to-the-eu-referendum/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 08:57:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-an-idiots-guide-to-the-eu-referendum/</guid>
        <description>Over the course of the last UK election period and for the bulk of 2016 so far, the media and news in general has been focussed on the UK’s membership within the European Union, but what’s actually going on?
Where did the EU come from?
In essence the European Union (EU) is a group of 28 countries …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Student hopeful for Kensington by-election success
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-student-hopeful-for-kensington-by-election-success/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:00:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-student-hopeful-for-kensington-by-election-success/</guid>
        <description>Next week, local elections are happening up and down the country, most notably the London Mayoral elections, but slightly closer to home is the Kensington and Chelsea Councillor by-election in which Imperial College physics student Ben Fernando is standing.
University Challenge star, Fernando, is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Business Schools speak of visa trouble
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-business-schools-speak-of-visa-trouble/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 11:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-business-schools-speak-of-visa-trouble/</guid>
        <description>A group of business school deans and those responsible for international recruitment at 15 UK universities, including Imperial, were interviewed as part of a report which concluded that current visa rules are making study in the UK “difficult and unattractive”.
With almost 35% of the student body …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Leadership Election results announced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-12-leadership-election-results-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 13:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-12-leadership-election-results-announced/</guid>
        <description>The Leadership Election results are in, the votes have been counted, and your new sabbatical officers and constituent union presidents are as follows:
President: Nas Andriopoulos
Deputy President of Welfare: Emily-Jane Cramphorn
Deputy President of Clubs and Societies: James Cox
Deputy President of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UCL rent strike steps up a gear
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-ucl-rent-strike-steps-up-a-gear/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 11:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-ucl-rent-strike-steps-up-a-gear/</guid>
        <description>The rent strikes that UCL students have been undertaking since late January are gaining more and more traction, now boasting a cohort of over 500 disgruntled tenants.
The unpaid rent now exceeds £1,000,000 and as the strike action continues more and more people are joining, adding to this total on a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Night Tube resurrected
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-night-tube-resurrected/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 11:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-night-tube-resurrected/</guid>
        <description>One of the four main unions representing London Underground drivers, RMT, voted in favour of a renegotiated contract on Monday, paving the way toward the Night Tube service that was due to be implemented in September last year.
84% of the union’s 10,000 members voted in favour of a contract which …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Violent Gloucester Road mugging video released
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-violent-gloucester-road-mugging-video-released/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 11:23:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-violent-gloucester-road-mugging-video-released/</guid>
        <description>CCTV of a violent mugging that took place last month near Gloucester Road has been released by the Metropolitan Police, in the hopes that the perpetrators will be found.
The attack, which took place on Cornwall Gardens, under ten minutes walk away from campus, involved a pair of muggers attacking a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It has to be Hinds
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-it-has-to-be-hinds/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 11:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-it-has-to-be-hinds/</guid>
        <description>Ana Perrote, Carlotta Cosials, Ade Martin and Amber Grimbergen. Together they are Hinds, a Spanish band on the cutting edge of the garage rock scene in Madrid with a debut album poised to break them out further still. Formed in the summer of 2011 by Ana and Carlotta (the vocalists and guitarists of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Junior Doctors strike again
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-junior-doctors-strike-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 11:20:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-junior-doctors-strike-again/</guid>
        <description>England&amp;rsquo;s Junior Doctors are set to strike again with three 48-hour walkouts planned for the coming two months, meaning that planned operations and procedures may well be affected, but emergency care will be maintained.
These strikes, to be held on 9th of March, and the 6th and 26th of April, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Nuff(ield) said
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-nuffield-said/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 11:47:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-nuffield-said/</guid>
        <description>Monday evening saw the first outing of the new term for the seemingly unstoppable University Challenge team that is Ben Fernando, Ashwin Braude, Onur Teymur and their captain James Bezer. The team were riding high on the back of their 305-75 demolition of Sidney Sussex, Cambridge, but as we all …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An idiot’s guide to the US Election
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-an-idiots-guide-to-the-us-election/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 09:07:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-an-idiots-guide-to-the-us-election/</guid>
        <description>The United States Presidential election. The $6 billion race for the White House. The battle between Democrats and Republicans, Donkeys versus Elephants. Like an Olympics for politicians, it happens every four years and has the potential to shape world economics and policy until the next one.
But …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tube drivers to strike in two weeks
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-15-tube-drivers-to-strike-in-two-weeks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2016 11:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-15-tube-drivers-to-strike-in-two-weeks/</guid>
        <description>All tube services will be suspended on January 26th, February 15th and February 17th from 9:14pm for a full 24 hours, it emerged this week. The industrial action comes after months of negotiations over the 24-hour tube service that Mayor Boris Johnson aimed to introduce back in September, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Junior doctors vote to strike in December
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-19-junior-doctors-vote-to-strike-in-december/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2015 22:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-19-junior-doctors-vote-to-strike-in-december/</guid>
        <description>On Thursday it was announced that junior doctors had voted overwhelmingly to take action against proposed contract changes, with 98% voting to take strike action and 99.4% in favour of industrial action short of striking.
The first proposed strike is scheduled for Tuesday 1st December and would see …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
