<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/fcomment/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/fcomment/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Eating Disorder Awareness Week 2014 – It’s Time to Speak Out
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-eating-disorder-awareness-week-2014-its-time-to-speak-out/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 03:29:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-eating-disorder-awareness-week-2014-its-time-to-speak-out/</guid>
        <description>Numbers. To the average Imperial student, they are part of everyday academia, to others they are enthralling and engaging, but for some of us they represent a punitive regime by which we live. Numbers are our self-worth, our being, our everything. Kilos, calories, clothes size. Small numbers are our …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Social Innovation: Saving the World
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-social-innovation-saving-the-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 21:29:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-social-innovation-saving-the-world/</guid>
        <description>Bet you didn’t know your one idea can save the world! You will be surprised to find that in a typical week, the average UK household is throwing away what would have been six complete meals. Not shocking enough? Well, how about picturing five Wembley Stadiums full of food waste? That is the amount …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hear Hidden Voices of Africa at ICBS
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-hear-hidden-voices-of-africa-at-icbs/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 13:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-hear-hidden-voices-of-africa-at-icbs/</guid>
        <description>Hope comes before sunrise, a dream in hand and the promise of a better future. For the children of Tanzania, this is not always true. Less than 20% of Tanzanian children have access to secondary school education. This is due to the lack of funds and secondary schools that do not work closely …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don’t be Agnostic About Interfaith
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-dont-be-agnostic-about-interfaith/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 02:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-dont-be-agnostic-about-interfaith/</guid>
        <description>Next week is National Interfaith Week, established four years ago to bring people of different faiths and beliefs together and build bridges and mutual appreciation between social groups that may not mix on a regular basis. While it hasn’t been ‘celebrated’ or ‘observed’ at Imperial College …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tibet: a brighter future than the rest of China
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-tibet-a-brighter-future-than-the-rest-of-china/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 02:21:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-tibet-a-brighter-future-than-the-rest-of-china/</guid>
        <description>N.B. Articles in the comment section are the opinion of the author and do not necessarily reflect the opinion of the newspaper or Imperial College. -Ed.
Lately an article in Felix, “What does the future hold for Tibet” has received great attention, calling for peace and independence for Tibet. While …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An 80km jaunt in Wales
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-an-80km-jaunt-in-wales/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 10:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-an-80km-jaunt-in-wales/</guid>
        <description>As most regular runners will testify, there comes a point when having followed a routine for a long time, you feel compelled to mix things up and try something new. It’s the runner’s mid-life crisis. This seems reasonable analogy for it involves committing to something rash, a bad idea. For me this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Confessions of a GTA: Part 3
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-confessions-of-a-gta-part-3/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 00:06:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-confessions-of-a-gta-part-3/</guid>
        <description>I was really looking forward to my teaching class with the final years. At last these were people that did not care if you did not know the answer of the top of your head as long as you tell them what the heck is going on or at least what should be. I think this is something to do with the Fear. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Joy of Dichotomy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-the-joy-of-dichotomy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 00:05:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-the-joy-of-dichotomy/</guid>
        <description>Dichotomy is the act of separating anything into two separate components, A and B. A great asset of this is to keep things simple, easy to manage, and reduce variables to a minimum. An example of this is “you’re either with me, or you’re against me”.
This dichotomy seems fairly straightforward (if a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Confessions of a GTA: Part Two
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-18-confessions-of-a-gta-part-two/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 21:37:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-18-confessions-of-a-gta-part-two/</guid>
        <description>Sadly, this is true. In fact it is an acronym for ‘graduate teaching assistant’. You know, the ones standing at the front chatting to the professors instead of helping you out. Yep, I’m one of those and as far as I’m aware we do not steal cars, only solutions to questions when the lecturers truly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Confessions of a Graduate Teaching Assistant (GTA): Part One
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-11-confessions-of-a-graduate-teaching-assistant-gta-part-one/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 23:47:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-11-confessions-of-a-graduate-teaching-assistant-gta-part-one/</guid>
        <description>I’ve always wanted to be a GTA. It wasn’t because they were doing amazing PhDs on their own desks, in which they cured cancer or published ground-breaking articles which they presented at world conferences. This was all pretty cool but actually, it had a lot to do with them being rubbish at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College put students last at Harlington
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-28-college-put-students-last-at-harlington/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2013 14:52:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-28-college-put-students-last-at-harlington/</guid>
        <description>I have to say that it is my view that this communication should be going to the Rector of the College and in my day as a student we would have had the right to take a letter straight to his door. However of course in my day I could have raised this matter to the rector either in my weekly meetings …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Farewell to HOST
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-farewell-to-host/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 22:17:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-farewell-to-host/</guid>
        <description>I still cherish the memory of the first meeting of the IC Heads of Departments I attended – it was both educational and amusing.. Having received the invitation, my predecessor immediately tried to dissuade me from accepting it; nobody expected the Librarian to discuss College business, shamefully I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to decide what to do with “the rest of your life”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-how-to-decide-what-to-do-with-the-rest-of-your-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 18:49:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-how-to-decide-what-to-do-with-the-rest-of-your-life/</guid>
        <description>Deciding what to do with ‘the rest of your life’ after graduation can be a daunting prospect. If you feel you have become pigeon-holed with too few opportunities available to you, or that you are capable of doing anything but don’t know how to choose which road to take, then this article is for you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How far would you go to save your life
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-how-far-would-you-go-to-save-your-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 18:46:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-how-far-would-you-go-to-save-your-life/</guid>
        <description>The world was stunned this week to learn that actress and director Angelina Jolie had a preventive mastectomy to avoid 87% odds of breast cancer due to the BRCA1 genetic mutation. Seattle performer and composer Eva Moon faced the same impossible choice.
Now the touring artist has written a solo …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sex: a direct approach
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-1-sex-a-direct-approach/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 17:59:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-1-sex-a-direct-approach/</guid>
        <description>&amp;ldquo;Can I come on your tits?” – I thought this was a somewhat forward request for our first night together but personally I’m quite sexually liberated and as a result didn’t think much to it. Well not until later when he asked to come on my face. Don’t get me wrong It’s not that I have anything …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My favourite things about exams
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-1-my-favourite-things-about-exams/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 17:54:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-1-my-favourite-things-about-exams/</guid>
        <description>It’s that time of year again: with the joy of the excessive chocolate consumption that is Easter comes The Fear. Exams are just round the corner and you suddenly realise you haven’t been to an entire week of lectures since October.
However, I was once told that every cloud has a silver lining. And …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let’s Find Out Then!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-lets-find-out-then/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 20:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-lets-find-out-then/</guid>
        <description>Now, I have a huge confession to make. Well, it’s something that I can’t really help, aside from the non-stop verbal diarrhea. When it began is as misty as a fading memory skipping on old stones in a running brook, but it must have been somewhere in my childhood.
It became my friend, almost always …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Love Europe, Hate the EU
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-love-europe-hate-the-eu/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 00:55:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-love-europe-hate-the-eu/</guid>
        <description>f you really love Europe then you ought to be a Eurosceptic by now.
It’s been striking to see the amount of pro-EU articles in these pages over recent weeks. First Pietro Aronica wrote about the need for a ‘United States of Europe’, and now Leonardo Ialongo has written two pieces on ‘A European …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Paragon Nightmare
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-my-paragon-nightmare/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 01:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-my-paragon-nightmare/</guid>
        <description>I was fully prepared for the difficulty of the first year. I was prepared for the step up in terms of work and difficulty of the course. I was prepared for the task of finding new friends all over again. I was even prepared to live alone and take care of myself. I was not however, prepared to find …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Populist Legislation Sure to Destroy London’s Economy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-populist-legislation-sure-to-destroy-londons-economy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 01:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-populist-legislation-sure-to-destroy-londons-economy/</guid>
        <description>Well, this is turning into a delightful little serial isn’t it? Today, I would like to discuss the most controversial of all issues concerning investment banking: remuneration. This has been a hot topic since the (thoroughly understandable) moral outrage at bankers still raking in massive bonuses …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dr. Strangelove: or why I just really love finance, not salary
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-dr-strangelove-or-why-i-just-really-love-finance-not-salary/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 18:55:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-dr-strangelove-or-why-i-just-really-love-finance-not-salary/</guid>
        <description>Followinglast week’s article in Felix, and what I perceive to be a generally anti-finance attitude amongst Imperial undergraduates – you may think said attitude doesn’t exist, but I can assure you I have had to defend my career choices many times – I decided to take it upon myself to fight the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Life of a Total (W)Banker
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-the-life-of-a-total-wbanker/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 23:11:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-the-life-of-a-total-wbanker/</guid>
        <description>You’ve finished your degree. You worked hard and you got the grades. The world is your metaphorical oyster. With your hard earned piece of paper you can do whatever your heart desires. So why do nearly a third of us end up working in the financial services?
With banks as public enemy number one, the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>*Friends* With Benefits?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-friends-with-benefits/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 23:10:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-friends-with-benefits/</guid>
        <description>Casual sex, no fuss no muss: the holy grail for most guys. In this modern society, the taboo has largely been lifted on satisfying one’s own sexual needs. You only need to browse truelad.com for five mins to realise that most guys are probably whacking one out in the five minute break between …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Isolated Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-isolated-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 23:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-isolated-imperial/</guid>
        <description>So, imagine you’re at a party with all the UK’s universities. Standing in a corner are the Russell Group, stroking their rugby team ties and snubbing the rest of the unis, who are actually having fun. Out in the hallway are a bunch of businessmen in a circle, all jacking off onto Imperial, who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Over-analysing - an Imperial tradition
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-over-analysing-an-imperial-tradition/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 23:37:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-over-analysing-an-imperial-tradition/</guid>
        <description>Perhaps, everybody has Murphy in their life. Perhaps, many just do not notice it. Being a sensitive over thinker, I am always a little bit too aware ofMurphy and his quirky laws. Basically, the theory goes that anything that can go wrong will go wrong.
Murphy always seemed to be in the picture, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Failed your exams, huh?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-failed-your-exams-huh/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 00:35:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-failed-your-exams-huh/</guid>
        <description>Last year, a friend of mine failed his PhD. He turned to me for advice.
I reviewed the case, and discovered that he had not been offered a second viva, contrary to the university’s regulations. Without a second viva, he had no opportunity to defend his thesis orally. The examiners had little …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pick-up artistry &amp; arseholery
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-pick-up-artistry-arseholery/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 23:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-pick-up-artistry-arseholery/</guid>
        <description>Single? Virgin? Afraid to admit this because Felix told you you should quit whining about it, so now you just keep it all bottled up inside and wank while you cry yourself to sleep at night? Don’t worry, you’re not alone! Er, sorry, you are alone, but this is Imperial, and there’s a lot of other …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gategate and the press
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-gategate-and-the-press/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 02:35:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-gategate-and-the-press/</guid>
        <description>On Friday Andrew Mitchell - the Government’s chief whip - resigned after a confrontation with a policeman that happened over a month ago, involving a gate, a bike and (possibly) the word ‘pleb’. It was all a bit awkward; especially since the policeman and Mr Mitchell gave differing accounts. Someone …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mandatory castrations for all!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-mandatory-castrations-for-all/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 21:25:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-mandatory-castrations-for-all/</guid>
        <description>Because that’s what feminism’s all about, right? Right? Wrong, but from the incredulous looks, comments and questions we got at Freshers’ Fair, it seems like a lot of you really believe that the goals of feminism are to overthrow and subjugate men and introduce a gynocratic fempire. Consider your …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are extradition treaties justified?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-are-extradition-treaties-justified/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 21:16:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-are-extradition-treaties-justified/</guid>
        <description>Extraditing criminals is both damaging to overall world justice and an example of snide and sneaky backdoor politics.
When someone commits a crime, there are always victims and there will always be consequences. Whether it is assault, where the victim has been physically harmed, or theft, where the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Repel evil with what is best
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-repel-evil-with-what-is-best/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 12:57:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-repel-evil-with-what-is-best/</guid>
        <description>Make no mistake: “The Innocence of Muslims” is a vile film, and an insult to the Founder of Islam and Muslims the world over. Yet the response to it across the Muslim world has done far more to tarnish the name of Islam than any short film ever could.
It is, for the unacquainted, the amateur film …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In Imperial College we trust?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-in-imperial-college-we-trust/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 22:55:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-in-imperial-college-we-trust/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Union’s Clubs &amp;amp; Societies Board (CSB) voted to cut its contribution towards the “tours pot” from £9,000 to £0 at its annual budgeting round on Monday. The move, at the recommendation of Deputy President (Clubs &amp;amp; Societies) Monya Zard, was due to a £7,500 increase in funding …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who did that? – A letter to the Editor
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-9-who-did-that-a-letter-to-the-editor/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2011 15:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-9-who-did-that-a-letter-to-the-editor/</guid>
        <description>Dear Sir,
Since the beginning of this term Mech Eng students and staff, who are in early enough have boarded the lifts in the morning only to be assailed through the nostril by what appears to be last night’s curry chemically processed through the duodenum to a noxious mixture subsequently evacuated …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I hate Christmas
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-i-hate-christmas/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 22:05:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-i-hate-christmas/</guid>
        <description>It’s about that time of year again. Bloody Christmas time. You’re probably reading this right now with the most appalled look on your face. I suggest you remove it before someone notices. ‘But why? Why do you hate Christmas?’ You must be asking. Well let me tell you. Because its frickin’ irritating. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ashura: A lesson from Islam&#39;s history
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-ashura-a-lesson-from-islams-history/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 21:52:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-ashura-a-lesson-from-islams-history/</guid>
        <description>Instinctively, we all admire the ‘good’ things in humankind – compassion, honesty and justice. Our free will to actively pursue such attributes through our actions is arguably what gives us our worth as human beings. But have you ever considered the lengths you go to in order to stand by what you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The journey through nature
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-the-journey-through-nature/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 20:43:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-the-journey-through-nature/</guid>
        <description>How many moments have you actually lived? Or reflected upon, or marvelled… or just, been? Now, this is not some kind of hippy wisdom, this is an understanding of the world around us. Have you ever ran through rain puddles on a sunny day and seen a rainbow at your side? It might seem comical, but try …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My life after graduation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-my-life-after-graduation/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 23:20:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-my-life-after-graduation/</guid>
        <description>This is an irrelevant time of the year for this article. As usual, my timing is wrong (must set a reminder to be in sync with the rest of the herd). Thoughts and hopes of graduation begin to emanate at about early May to late June, sparkly spring seems to set in motion a chain of celebration. Then, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your meat offends me, deal with it
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-your-meat-offends-me-deal-with-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 22:49:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-your-meat-offends-me-deal-with-it/</guid>
        <description>I was eating my lunch in the JCR (two-bean goulash YUM! :D) and this random guy just comes and sits down next to me and starts devouring a greasy stinky burger. I asked him if he minded moving because I find the stench of cooked meat to be nauseating. As you may have guessed, I’m a vegan. When I see …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Frankenscience versus the world
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-14-frankenscience-versus-the-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 00:34:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-14-frankenscience-versus-the-world/</guid>
        <description>Science fiction often paints a scary picture of the future where science and technology have run amok with devastating consequences. Titles such as Brave New World, The Day After Tomorrow and Frankenstein conjure up fearful images in our minds. Many scientists feel that such works have hindered …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I&#39;m a girl with opinions, just deal with it!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-14-im-a-girl-with-opinions-just-deal-with-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 00:32:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Comment,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-14-im-a-girl-with-opinions-just-deal-with-it/</guid>
        <description>So I was told that my pseudonym was not particularly inventive, but that’s simply what I am: a girl with opinions. Got a problem with that!? Then go away and read something else. I’m here to get nitty and gritty and talk about the things that others are too afraid to even think about. In such a …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
