<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/pt1114/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/pt1114/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Goodbye old friends
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-goodbye-old-friends/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 12:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Panukorn Taleongpong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-goodbye-old-friends/</guid>
        <description>Last Sunday saw our last game of the season against the Bath Killer Bees, the Immortals were determined not to end the season with a loss; however, after a long game, the score was 49-8 to the Killer Bees.
We started out the game with a kick off. After a fantastic kick, the defensive team were on. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Relegation for the Immortals after Kingston loss
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-relegation-for-the-immortals-after-kingston-loss/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 12:09:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Panukorn Taleongpong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-relegation-for-the-immortals-after-kingston-loss/</guid>
        <description>In our last home game of the regular season, the Immortals faced the Kingston Cougars. After an amazing performance against the Lions last Sunday, the team was confident coming into the game. However, after a long and hard-fought game, the final score was 12-20 to the Cougars.
Early on in the game, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lions trump Immortals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-lions-trump-immortals/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 12:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Panukorn Taleongpong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-lions-trump-immortals/</guid>
        <description>Last Sunday the Immortals faced the top team of the Southern Premiership league, the Birmingham Lions. The Immortals knew that with such a strong team like the Lions, they had to come out firing. The Immortals did just that and despite putting up a phenomenal fight the Lions had the edge towards the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Immortal no more: Lions take the glory
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-immortal-no-more-lions-take-the-glory/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 14:24:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Panukorn Taleongpong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-immortal-no-more-lions-take-the-glory/</guid>
        <description>After a successful scrimmage last Saturday, the Immortals travelled up to Birmingham for their season opener against the University of Birmingham Lions.
After the disappointing loss from last year against the 5-time national champions, we were unable to turn the tables around and were beaten by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Immortals put through their paces
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-30-immortals-put-through-their-paces/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 15:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Panukorn Taleongpong,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-30-immortals-put-through-their-paces/</guid>
        <description>Last Saturday saw the Immortals’ three-way scrimmage against Solent and Brunel. The Immortals were hungry for some contact after many intense training sessions. The day started off with each university’s offensive team going up against each defensive team for ten plays before switching around. This …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
