<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ial08/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ial08/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Promotion and port for IC Hockey Ladies 1s after Brunel tussle
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-2-promotion-and-port-for-ic-hockey-ladies-1s-after-brunel-tussle/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 17:42:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-2-promotion-and-port-for-ic-hockey-ladies-1s-after-brunel-tussle/</guid>
        <description>  Cruella de Vil had better watch out – they’re armed and dangerous (with sticks)  Cruella de Vil had better watch out – they’re armed and dangerous (with sticks)   We arrived at Harlington knowing that a win would secure promotion, so we were ready to f*** s*** up, despite our chunderous captain …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Synchronised swimming: 5 years old
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-2-synchronised-swimming-5-years-old/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 17:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-2-synchronised-swimming-5-years-old/</guid>
        <description>  Incredibly Cool. Obviously that’s what IC really stands for  Incredibly Cool. Obviously that’s what IC really stands for   Credit: IC Synchronised Swimming
Everything started five years ago with a Felix article to recruit members. The founding member Danai Balfoussia now admits “Come to think of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pulling their weight
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-2-pulling-their-weight/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 17:24:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-2-pulling-their-weight/</guid>
        <description>  Working hard to bring home the medals  Working hard to bring home the medals   Credit: Tim Richards
The BUCS 4s and 8s Head on the River Nene in Peterborough never fails to be a challenging race for all involved and 2012 was no exception. In a weekend of two halves, the gales of Saturday played …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On target
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-on-target/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 21:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-on-target/</guid>
        <description>Wednesday afternoon saw the latest chapter in Imperial College Fencing Club’s stellar season unfold. The men’s first team kicked off proceedings in Ethos at 2pm, facing a Durham side who turned up with minutes to spare before the scheduled 2pm start. Confidence was high amongst the guys, having been …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Touché: Fencers win Premiership(s)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-touch-fencers-win-premierships/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 23:10:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-touch-fencers-win-premierships/</guid>
        <description>The mantle of success is never an easy thing to bear, especially so in sport. Success breeds expectation, which translates into pressure – exactly the sort of thing you don’t want when you’re trying to reproduce past exploits.
On the weekend of the 20th of January, the Imperial men’s and women’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Captains&#39; Interviews: Handball
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-captains-interviews-handball/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 22:59:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-captains-interviews-handball/</guid>
        <description>Ladies and Gentlemen, I hope you’re having a good Friday afternoon (I won’t, I have lectures till 6). Sport editor gripes aside, I am pleased to present this week’s interviewees: the lovely Annabelle Mayers, handball women’s captain, and the dashing Stefan Bauer – goalkeeper extraordinaire and a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Captains&#39; Interviews: Netball
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-20-captains-interviews-netball/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 17:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-20-captains-interviews-netball/</guid>
        <description>After a nice, long (but not long enough) Christmas break, your Felix Sport captains’ interviews are back! This week, two lovely ladies from Netball: Lucie Hazell, Club Captain, and Feroza Kassam, Club Treasurer.
Felix Sport: Netball is one of those clubs which always has a pretty strong turnout, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Men’s and women’s 1sts prepare for premiership clashes
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-20-mens-and-womens-1sts-prepare-for-premiership-clashes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 12:09:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-20-mens-and-womens-1sts-prepare-for-premiership-clashes/</guid>
        <description>The Imperial fencing men’s and women’s teams stand to win their respective leagues this weekend, the men’s and women’s Southern Premiership, if they can fight off the likes of Oxford, Cambridge, and London rivals such as Queen Mary or ULU.
The women’s team currently stand top of the southern …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Eagles held by Great Danes
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-imperial-eagles-held-by-great-danes/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 20:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-imperial-eagles-held-by-great-danes/</guid>
        <description>Have you ever felt that tension, that awareness that to achieve your goal you will have to fight and exceed your own limits? On the day of the most important match of the season the Imperial Eagles felt exactly that way.
The Eagles were about to play the second team of the English first division …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>discDoctors grab BUCS points
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-discdoctors-grab-bucs-points/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 20:36:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-discdoctors-grab-bucs-points/</guid>
        <description>On Friday 25 November, 11 of Imperial College discDoctors’ finest men embarked on a campaign to compete against the other 15 best university indoor teams in the country. It was the weekend of Open Indoor Nationals and it carried the potential for discDoctors (dD) to earn some BUCS points for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rugby League play first ever game
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-rugby-league-play-first-ever-game/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 20:10:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-rugby-league-play-first-ever-game/</guid>
        <description>Imperial played their first competitive fixture of the season against Woking College in what was a development fixture for both sides. Woking won 54-22 but it proved a fantastic experience for the new Imperial team.
The first half was very competitive with Imperial’s Padhraic Comerford, later named …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Men&#39;s and Women&#39;s fencers make progress in BUCS knockouts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-mens-and-womens-fencers-make-progress-in-bucs-knockouts/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 21:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-mens-and-womens-fencers-make-progress-in-bucs-knockouts/</guid>
        <description>Imperial’s fencing teams produced a solid set of results last week in the BUCS knockout championships to ensure their progress to the quarter-finals. Only the Men’s Seconds suffered an unfortunate loss at the hands of Aberystwyth, having made the somewhat epic journey all the way to the West coast …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Captains’ Interviews: Dodgeball Club Captain
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-captains-interviews-dodgeball-club-captain/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 21:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-captains-interviews-dodgeball-club-captain/</guid>
        <description>As we roll into December, the Captains’ interviews just keep on coming! This week, we have one of the quirkier Imperial sports on display: Dodgeball. Alan Soltani, a 3rd year physicist and Dodgeball club captain, is the man of the hour. We meet up in Beit quad to talk about balls, wrenches and more. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Captains&#39; Interviews: Synchronised Swimming
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-captains-interviews-synchronised-swimming/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 23:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-captains-interviews-synchronised-swimming/</guid>
        <description>Another week, another interview for your intrepid Felix Sport Editor. Today: Synchronised Swimming! Yep, I know you’re excited about this one. I meet up with Carla, the treasurer, Delphine, the club secretary and Zara, the club president in 568 to talk swimming pools, holding your breath underwater, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bittersweet results for IC Fencing Men&#39;s 1st
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-bittersweet-results-for-ic-fencing-mens-1st/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 23:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-bittersweet-results-for-ic-fencing-mens-1st/</guid>
        <description>Fencing
Men’s 1st 135 ULU 1st 74 Men’s 1st 114 Cambridge 1st 107 Men’s 1st 101 Bristol 1st 100 Men’s 1st 98 Oxford 1st 98* (*Oxford win the match on weapons)
Last weekend saw the Imperial College Fencing Club Men’s 1st team travel to Oxford for their first Southern Premiership weekend tournament. An …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Captains’ Interviews: Rowing Club Captain
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-captains-interviews-rowing-club-captain/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 22:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-captains-interviews-rowing-club-captain/</guid>
        <description>I hope that the avid Sport readers (you know who you are) have been enjoying the Captains’ Interviews series – because we’ve decided to go weekly on you. After having the Rugby first XV captain last week, we turn to an equally popular (and equally gruelling) sport. Live from the Boathouse in Putney, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Club Captain Interview: Rugby
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-club-captain-interview-rugby/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 22:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-club-captain-interview-rugby/</guid>
        <description>After the mad rush that was Issue 1500, the Club Captains are back for a third interview! This week we feature the Captain of the Imperial College Rugby Union Football Club (to give him his full title), Charlie Esberger.
We manage to meet up briefly on Wednesday, just before the 1sts match against …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>1500 weeks of Sport
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-1500-weeks-of-sport/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 22:12:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-1500-weeks-of-sport/</guid>
        <description>This is it, then. The big one. The one you’ve all been waiting for. I don’t know about the rest of the Felix team, but I hope you have as much fun reading this one as us editors down here have had doing it.
I also hope you enjoyed the back cover, which was the fruit of quite a bit of trawling …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC Hurlers off to strong start
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-ic-hurlers-off-to-strong-start/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 22:10:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-ic-hurlers-off-to-strong-start/</guid>
        <description>For Imperial’s ﬁrst match there couldn’t have been much of a better way to start the Hurling season. With blue skies and a light breeze in Greenford the boys in blue new they were in for something good.
Despite Oxford not getting a team, there was a good showing from St Mary’s, Cambridge and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Records broken at annual bike auction
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-records-broken-at-annual-bike-auction/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 19:29:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-records-broken-at-annual-bike-auction/</guid>
        <description>This Monday saw the Union conduct a bike auction in Beit Quad, raising over £7000 for RAG; a new record. 106 bikes and one scooter were up for sale, having been left chained to railings and bike racks around campus, presumably abandoned by their owners.
This year, Sport Imperial had a hand in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Saturday afternoon in the park
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-a-saturday-afternoon-in-the-park/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 10:28:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-a-saturday-afternoon-in-the-park/</guid>
        <description>Picture the scene: Regent’s Park on a sunny Saturday afternoon. Families are out, the squirrels are being pretty inquisitive and the pedal boats on the lake are politely bumping into each other. In the middle of it all, a sprawling white structure with a pretty weird wooden entrance, out of which …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Postmodernism... wait, don’t run away!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-postmodernism-wait-dont-run-away/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 22:27:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-postmodernism-wait-dont-run-away/</guid>
        <description>I don’t know if you’ve heard, but there’s an exhibition on at the V&amp;amp;A at the moment. You know, that nice building on the other side of Exhibition Road – the one that has “art” and “design” in it. If you’re a fresher, and you haven’t paid it a visit yet, that’s fair enough. I do suggest you go at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial captains gear up for new season
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-imperial-captains-gear-up-for-new-season/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 00:57:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-imperial-captains-gear-up-for-new-season/</guid>
        <description>Head of Sport Imperial Neil Mosley sounded the start of the new sports season on Monday at the Club Captains’ meeting held in Ethos. Introducing himself and the rest of the Sport Imperial team to the hundred or so team captains and sports club committee members, he was full of praise for the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Need sleep... OK, just one more website
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-need-sleep-ok-just-one-more-website/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 06:09:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-need-sleep-ok-just-one-more-website/</guid>
        <description>DISCLAIMER : I am in no way to be held responsible for any loss of productivity, social life, or ability to graduate caused by this article.
I can&amp;rsquo;t sleep at night. Shadows dance around my room, lit by an eerie, diffuse glow. Sometimes I catch sight of my pale, haggard reflection looking back …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Here’s to Imperial’s sportsmen and women
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-heres-to-imperials-sportsmen-and-women/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 20:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-heres-to-imperials-sportsmen-and-women/</guid>
        <description>People&amp;rsquo;s habits when they pick up a Felix every week can be quite telling. What kind of reader are you?
Are you more of the half-arsed-skim-through type, trying to escape a boring lecture? Do you flick straight to the centrefold to see if there are any girls in it this week? Maybe you&amp;rsquo;re …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Give viewers a sporting chance
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-give-viewers-a-sporting-chance/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 19:58:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-give-viewers-a-sporting-chance/</guid>
        <description>Picture the scene: the Olympic Stadium, East London, less than a year and a half from now, on a balmy August evening. There is little wind; the heat is slowly rising from the track. The atmosphere is heavy, but that has little to do with the weather. The entire world’s gaze is fixed upon the ten men …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Long distance relationships
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-13-long-distance-relationships/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2011 13:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-13-long-distance-relationships/</guid>
        <description>I’m banging out my comment piece quite quickly this week, as I haven’t had time to think about it much. I’ve been quite busy. Appropriately enough for the Valentine’s day issue, the thing that’s been taking up all of my time is my girlfriend. She’s visiting me for a week, for the second time in four …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dude, where’s my country?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-dude-wheres-my-country/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 20:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-dude-wheres-my-country/</guid>
        <description>Where do you live? A simple enough question, in appearance. I’ve been asked it a lot this year. Meeting an endless stream of new people from various countries makes for a large number of introductions. After you’ve said hello to the fifteenth German girl at the party, whose name you’ve already …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wish I was there...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-wish-i-was-there/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 19:42:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-wish-i-was-there/</guid>
        <description>January is generally not the best month in anyone’s year. What passed for enjoyable, seasonal weather in December has become dreary, cold and depressing in the new year. For all Imperialites, the first month of the year is stressful, sleep-scarce and just generally bollocks.
While reading this on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Murray &amp; co. Down Under
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-22-murray-co-down-under/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 13:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indy Leclercq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-22-murray-co-down-under/</guid>
        <description>Ah, the familiar pleasures of January. Slate-grey skies and precipitation that can’t make up its mind as to whether it wants to be snow, or rain, or something in between. Without forgetting to mention the pervasive and inescapable COLD. Not so for everyone, though. If you happen to be a professional …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
