<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/krithika_balaji/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/krithika_balaji/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Should we subsidise pre-schools?’ - a debate between man and AI</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04--should-we-subsidise-pre-schools-a-debate-between-man-and-ai/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Krithika Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04--should-we-subsidise-pre-schools-a-debate-between-man-and-ai/</guid>
        <description>Earlier this month, IBM Research and Intelligence Squared U.S. sponsored an event where Project Debater, IBM’s AI debating machine, and Harish Natarajan, a debating expert, discussed whether pre-schools should be subsidized. Both sides had fifteen minutes to prepare on the topic given on the spot. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are we nearing the last stages of the Apple wave?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-are-we-nearing-the-last-stages-of-the-apple-wave/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Krithika Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-are-we-nearing-the-last-stages-of-the-apple-wave/</guid>
        <description>Apple - the one phone brand everybody knows. Even if you haven’t owned an Apple product in the past decade, you have probably seen somebody in Hyde Park taking a selfie with their new iPhone XR or the person sitting next to you in the library on their MacBook Air. Ever since 2007, Apple has enjoyed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Medical Devices under the Spotlight</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-medical-devices-under-the-spotlight/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aline Buat,Krithika Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-medical-devices-under-the-spotlight/</guid>
        <description>Technology has dramatically changed every aspect of life as we know it, with medicine being one of the most important aspects. Medicine has been revolutionized through medical imaging, drugs, implants and more. What happens, however, when the medical device industry fails? The International …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is Elon Musk Making the Biggest Crypto-Giveaway in the World?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-is-elon-musk-making-the-biggest-crypto-giveaway-in-the-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Krithika Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-is-elon-musk-making-the-biggest-crypto-giveaway-in-the-world/</guid>
        <description>This Monday, more than a dozen verified accounts were hacked into by scammers impersonating Elon Musk. The scammers claimed that they were giving away 10,000 Bitcoin(BTC) after resigning from the job of being the director of Tesla.
“I’m giving 10 000 bitcoin (BTC) to all community! I left the post …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcoming the most powerful iPad Pro yet</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-welcoming-the-most-powerful-ipad-pro-yet/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Krithika Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-welcoming-the-most-powerful-ipad-pro-yet/</guid>
        <description>Another iPad was introduced this week - the iPad Pro. It isn’t, however, just another iPad as this is said to have the biggest changes ever and will push the functionality of these devices farther than ever before.
This model has a 11-inch and 12.9-inch Liquid Retina displays to the edges of iPad …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your hours are numbered – Emit style!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-your-hours-are-numbered-emit-style/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Krithika Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-your-hours-are-numbered-emit-style/</guid>
        <description>Be honest with me - how many times did you pull an all-nighter last year? How many times did you start an assignment at the last minute, this questionable decision justified by saying that “diamonds are made under pressure”? We are three weeks into college and some of us have already found that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Volkswagen – you are one SaaSy car!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-your-filename/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Krithika Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-your-filename/</guid>
        <description>Volkswagen (VW) has recently signed a deal with Microsoft to use their Azure cloud-based system. This gives them the portal to the highly sought after world of Software as a Service (SaaS).
“The Volkswagen Automotive cloud will be built from the ground up on top of Microsoft’s Azure cloud and IoT …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix reports: Wearable Technology Show 2018</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-felix-reports-wearable-technology-show-2018/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Krithika Balaji,Robert Jin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-felix-reports-wearable-technology-show-2018/</guid>
        <description> Virtual Reality – the shift from gaming to healthcare
 Current therapy for psychological phenomena like anxiety, depression, and addiction involves going to a therapist on a regular basis (maybe once a week) and talking with them about your progress. They would suggest treatment goals and tips that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Amazon’s latest purchase – a ‘smart’ doorbell</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-amazon-s-latest-purchase-a-smart-doorbell/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Krithika Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-amazon-s-latest-purchase-a-smart-doorbell/</guid>
        <description>Recently, Amazon, an American electronic commerce and cloud-computing company, bought US firm Ring for more than $1 billion. The firm produces high-tech doorbells that records live videos of the customer’s doorstep and sends it to their smartphone. Ring hopes that working with Amazon will allow it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sweat analysis – a new direction for wearables</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-sweat-analysis-a-new-direction-for-wearables/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Krithika Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-sweat-analysis-a-new-direction-for-wearables/</guid>
        <description>Northwestern University professor John A. Rogers last Friday published, along with other scientists, his research on a wearable microfluidics sweat analytics device in the journal Science Advances. He is now collaborating with many partners such as Gatorade, the Seattle Mariners, and the U.S. Air …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The future of medicine – edible QR codes?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-12-the-future-of-medicine-edible-qr-codes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Krithika Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-12-the-future-of-medicine-edible-qr-codes/</guid>
        <description>If you are ill, chances are you would book an appointment with your doctor. They would listen to your heartbeat, do some tests and then prescribe some medicines based on your symptoms. A trip to your local pharmacy would result in a bag full of medications, some of which being the ones that your …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Organs-on-Chips – A catalyst for drug testing?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-organs-on-chips-a-catalyst-for-drug-testing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Krithika Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-organs-on-chips-a-catalyst-for-drug-testing/</guid>
        <description>According to the World Health Organization (WHO), antibiotic resistance in bacteria is one of the biggest threats to global health today. Bacteria gaining resistance is a natural process, but this has been accelerated by the misuse of medicines. The consequence of this is that bacteria remain …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
