<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/adrian_lamoury/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/adrian_lamoury/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Big Riffs, Small Ideas: Foals are Far too Comfortable to Leave the Stadium Rock Arena</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-big-riffs-small-ideas-foals-too-comfortable-leave-stadium-rock-arena/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-big-riffs-small-ideas-foals-too-comfortable-leave-stadium-rock-arena/</guid>
        <description>3.5 stars
Early this year, following four years of relentless touring, Oxford-based indie quartet, Foals, teased that they had a new album ready. This was not to be any ordinary album, however, as they had recorded simply too much material for one record, meaning it would have to be released in two …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Music’s astronomical anthems</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-felix-music-s-astronomical-anthems/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-felix-music-s-astronomical-anthems/</guid>
        <description>Next month will mark 50 years since the Apollo 11 Moon landing/Stanley Kubrick pulled off the world’s most elaborate lampoon (delete as appropriate). To celebrate, here’s a select few celestial bangers to blast you out of this world.
‘Space Oddity’, David Bowie
Honestly, this whole list could very …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reasserting indie rock dominance - Part 1</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-reasserting-indie-rock-dominance-part-1/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-reasserting-indie-rock-dominance-part-1/</guid>
        <description>Too young to fully engage with the monumental breakthrough of Arctic Monkeys, but too old to care the slightest bit about the 1975, Foals were MY band. Despite only receiving my backing in earnest following their third album (2013’s Holy Fire ), they soundtracked such a pivotal part of my …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The man with the Midas touch, ante-ambient</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-the-man-with-the-midas-touch-ante-ambient/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-the-man-with-the-midas-touch-ante-ambient/</guid>
        <description>Apart from creating the Windows 95 start-up sound, Brian Eno is perhaps best known for pioneering the genre of ‘ambient music’, where extended instrumental compositions slowly loop and bubble, creating soundscapes that are intricate yet discreet. His work in this area went on to directly inspire …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The real star of the show</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-the-real-star-of-the-show/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-the-real-star-of-the-show/</guid>
        <description>Following the launch of the long-awaited Parker Solar Probe by NASA in August, the focus for many in the scientific world has shifted heavenwards, towards the most undeniably omnipotent giver of life we know – our Sun. The Science Museum celebrates our local star with a highly interactive and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to the pleasuredome</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-welcome-to-the-pleasuredome/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,Henry Eshbaugh,Asad Raja,Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-welcome-to-the-pleasuredome/</guid>
        <description>My friend Kunal from Singapore calls me the grime guy. I like the way that sounds so I don’t correct him. In truth, as far as grime or UK rap goes, I consider myself a semi-casual listener (you won’t catch me listening to anyone less niche than, like, Ghetts). Though I stay open to most genres, US …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>While you were away...</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-while-you-were-away/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,Henry Eshbaugh,Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-while-you-were-away/</guid>
        <description>Family of Aliens
The third full-length effort by this indie pop quartet packs all the wholesome family-friendly goodness that fans have come to expect, but not without a wicked sense of humour and a quirky, sci-fi inflected glaze. A new crisply produced electronic vibe replaces their traditionally …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The times, they are a-changin’: a precarious balance of alienation and progression</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-the-times-they-are-a-changin-a-precarious-balance-of-alienation-and-progression/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-the-times-they-are-a-changin-a-precarious-balance-of-alienation-and-progression/</guid>
        <description>The recent release of Arctic Monkeys’ Tranquillity Base Hotel &amp;amp; Casino divided fans. A far cry from the angst-laden and frenetic rock of the noughties, TBH&amp;amp;C brought with it a toned-down, lounge vibe, filled with nuances and subtleties rather foreign to their previously brash and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>David Byrne is far too happy for my liking</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-david-byrne-is-far-too-happy-for-my-liking/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-david-byrne-is-far-too-happy-for-my-liking/</guid>
        <description>As frontman and founder of New York art-rock band Talking Heads, David Byrne is no stranger to experimentation. Since their final album, Naked, in 1988, he’s released a string of semi-successful solo albums and collaborative projects with the likes of Brian Eno and St. Vincent. Something of a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An album for cold weather</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-an-album-for-cold-weather/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-an-album-for-cold-weather/</guid>
        <description>It’s been a while since I wrote a proper review.
This isn’t a proper review.
Though really, they seldom are.
I’ve listened to this album twice.
Once yesterday while I was working, and once more this morning as I walked through the snow into the Felix office. I think it’s pretty great.
I have neither …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Roxy Music’s For Your Pleasure</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-roxy-music-s-for-your-pleasure/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-roxy-music-s-for-your-pleasure/</guid>
        <description>In a time when Elton John dominated radio play and sales, crowds flocked to catch a glimpse of David Bowie’s on-stage theatrics, and the bulk of underground intelligentsia attributed artistic merit to Pink Floyd, it was pretty hard to break into the British music scene. No surprise then, that Roxy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Django Django venture into new territories</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-django-django-venture-into-new-territories/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-django-django-venture-into-new-territories/</guid>
        <description>It would’ve been a good name for a marbled paper collage I made about four years ago – or at least a better one than whatever hedonistic tripe I presumably came up with. Marble Skies, British art-rock quartet Django Django’s third album, actually bears something of a resemblance to my teenage …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New year, new music</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-12-new-year-new-music/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-12-new-year-new-music/</guid>
        <description>2017 was a year of highs and lows for the music world. In a beige scene dominated by Taylor Swift and Ed Sheeran, we were treated to rare glimpses of colour from the likes of LCD Soundsystem, Kendrick Lamar, and Arcade Fire. Some lived up to expectations, some exceeded them, and some sadly did …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Top albums of 2017, Adrian’s picks</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-top-albums-of-2017-adrian-s-picks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-top-albums-of-2017-adrian-s-picks/</guid>
        <description>10 Oczy Mlody **The Flaming Lips **
Tucked away at the beginning of the year was the 14th album by psychedelic veterans The Flaming Lips. Blending rock and electronica, this colourful LP is a neatly produced experimental piece that, despite the many references to unicorns and a bizarre feature by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The most disappointing albums of 2017</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-the-most-disappointing-albums-of-2017/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-the-most-disappointing-albums-of-2017/</guid>
        <description>Everything Now Arcade Fire
Four years of relative silence followed the transcendental double LP Reflektor. Produced by LCD Soundsystem’s James Murphy, the album represented a departure from their rockier roots, instead ushering in drum machines and glitter-pop. July’s Everything Now was one of this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bowie, Berlin, and battling sobriety </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-bowie-berlin-and-battling-sobriety/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-bowie-berlin-and-battling-sobriety/</guid>
        <description>Unofficially dubbed ‘the Berlin Trilogy’, the three studio albums that David Bowie produced between 1977 and 1979 were arguably him at his creative peak. With the help of Brian Eno, Low, “_Heroes_”, and Lodger brought all kinds of sonic experimentation, far from the Ziggy-era flamboyance and Thin …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chameleon Queen out in the open</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-chameleon-queen-out-in-the-open/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-chameleon-queen-out-in-the-open/</guid>
        <description>Writing a follow up to 2014’s gargantuan, Grammy-winning, self-titled album was never going to be an easy task for Annie Clark, so perhaps that’s why it took so long to do. Mind you, when you’re being hailed as the modern day Ziggy Stardust, you want to make sure you get things right. St. Vincent’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chasing intercontinental friendships</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-chasing-intercontinental-friendships/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-chasing-intercontinental-friendships/</guid>
        <description>Historically, collaborative albums have generally been reserved for ageing legends. Lou Reed &amp;amp; Metallica. Jay Z &amp;amp; Kanye. Eno &amp;amp; Byrne. Eno &amp;amp; Fripp. Eno &amp;amp; Cale. But if you haven’t got a string of successful glam albums and the invention of ambient music under your belt, these can …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Alternative Music Society Recommends An Album</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-alternative-music-society-recommends-an-album/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-alternative-music-society-recommends-an-album/</guid>
        <description>Tom Petty sadly passed away this week, aged 66. He was prolific, both as a solo artist and within groups. One notable side project of his was the Travelling Wilburys, a late eighties supergroup with a stellar line up of Petty, Jeff Lynne, Bob Dylan, George Harrison and Roy Orbison. Some years …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>No edges lost, but still trouble waking up</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-no-edges-lost-but-still-trouble-waking-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-no-edges-lost-but-still-trouble-waking-up/</guid>
        <description>“I’m losing my edge” claimed LCD’s James Murphy as far back as 2002; fashionably late to the party with a debut single aged 32, he had something to prove to the youngsters - and prove it, he did. 15 years, 3 albums and a 4 year hiatus later, the band is back in possibly their finest form to date. …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
