<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/je615/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/je615/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Avocados and drugs? Yes, they are related – and in a very toxic way</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-12-avocados-and-drugs-yes-they-are-related-and-in-a-very-toxic-way/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jennifer Eden,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-12-avocados-and-drugs-yes-they-are-related-and-in-a-very-toxic-way/</guid>
        <description>This week I was supposed to talk about the Imperial College Endowment Fund. But given the post mortem has been carried out and Imperial students have got back to thinking about the science stuff, I thought I’d write about drugs and avocadoes.
Let’s start with the latter. They’re green, they’re clean …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let’s not politicise the modern pandemic of mental health</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-let-s-not-politicise-the-modern-pandemic-of-mental-health/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jennifer Eden,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-let-s-not-politicise-the-modern-pandemic-of-mental-health/</guid>
        <description>During the Labour Party conference last month, sixteen year old Lauren Stocks delivered a speech on the state of mental health in pupils studying for their GCSE’s. She was bold and passionate; she stirred the audience, received a standing ovation, and later the video of her speech went viral. She …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cuba Libre: What’s more to achieve than revolution?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-cuba-libre-what-s-more-to-achieve-than-revolution/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jennifer Eden,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-cuba-libre-what-s-more-to-achieve-than-revolution/</guid>
        <description>On returning from my holiday to Cuba this year, I immediately got to work making a shiny new photo album for all those Facebook friends out there who’d probably rather I didn’t. Revolutionary Square is in there, lots of palm trees, and even that most cliché of images: a hollowed-out pineapple with a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2017 | the year of the (big) cat
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-2017-the-year-of-the-big-cat/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jennifer Eden,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-2017-the-year-of-the-big-cat/</guid>
        <description>Big news for big cats and other exotic pets. The United Arab Emirates has banned the private ownership and dealing of wild animals. Status pets are on the way out and, hopefully, back into the wild.
Animal rights activists are understandably thrilled, for this is a triumph. The UAE was a hotspot for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cocaine’s bloody trail into the UK
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-cocaines-bloody-trail-into-the-uk/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 13:32:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jennifer Eden,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-cocaines-bloody-trail-into-the-uk/</guid>
        <description>If you haven’t already got hooked on a Netflix series then I would recommend Narco’s – a fast-paced, no frills, straight to the point story of Pablo Escobar and his cocaine empire. From the get-go the audience is thrust into the life of the world’s most famous drug trafficker and immersed in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stop trying to domesticate the wild
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-stop-trying-to-domesticate-the-wild/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 14:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jennifer Eden,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-stop-trying-to-domesticate-the-wild/</guid>
        <description>Having watched enough music videos and viewed the odd ‘Rich Kids of Instagram’ profile, it’s not unusual to spot an exotic animal being used as a power status symbol or display of wealth for social media. A tiger padding over a marble floor, a marmoset monkey hanging from a chandelier, or a snake …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The West needs to learn from its mistakes or be doomed to repeat them (again)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-7-the-west-needs-to-learn-from-its-mistakes-or-be-doomed-to-repeat-them-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 18:02:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Jennifer Eden,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-7-the-west-needs-to-learn-from-its-mistakes-or-be-doomed-to-repeat-them-again/</guid>
        <description>It’s the 2nd of August 1990. Saddam Hussain has just invaded Kuwait in order to absorb the country as the ‘19th province’ of Iraq. The next year a counter invasion to expel the Iraqis from Kuwait (known as Operation Desert Storm) is launched by the US and other western countries on the orders of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Remaining to keep Africa impoverished
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-remaining-to-keep-africa-impoverished/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 18:54:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Jennifer Eden,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-remaining-to-keep-africa-impoverished/</guid>
        <description>Upon joining the European Union in 1973, Britain joined an exclusive trade bloc based on its geographical location. A western country joining a western organisation designed to help already wealthy countries protect their own market interests. Yet, amidst the panic that followed the Brexit vote, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The royals should pay for themselves
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-25-the-royals-should-pay-for-themselves/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 14:28:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jennifer Eden,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-25-the-royals-should-pay-for-themselves/</guid>
        <description>For a long time, the UK has been wading through an era of cuts, cuts and more cuts. The NHS is expected to shave off £20bn in costs by 2021, schools are preparing for 16% cuts over the next three years, and controversial plans to reduce working tax credits have been in the public eye recently. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The mighty hedgehog will roar
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-27-the-mighty-hedgehog-will-roar/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 14:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jennifer Eden,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-27-the-mighty-hedgehog-will-roar/</guid>
        <description>The lion has long been hailed a most majestic and fearsome creature. Respected by the other animals within its habitat, the lion has a purpose, pride and courage. And as far back as the time of Richard I, the lion has been used as England’s national animal for all the aforementioned reasons. As a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The North South divide is part of being a Brit
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-the-north-south-divide-is-part-of-being-a-brit/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 14:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jennifer Eden,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-the-north-south-divide-is-part-of-being-a-brit/</guid>
        <description>Where I come from, in rainy old Manchester, I’m considered relatively posh. Hop across the imaginary divide though, and I might as well have just come up from the mines with a pie in one hand and a ferret in the other.
Visits to see the family in Sussex are always a reminder of this, as many a time …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The modern-day hypocrite
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-the-modern-day-hypocrite/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 11:51:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jennifer Eden,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-the-modern-day-hypocrite/</guid>
        <description>The inner hypocrite has been lurking within you for some time. Occasionally it appears in its most obvious form, whereby said hypocrite exclaims, “I don’t watch trash TV,” and then binge watches 20 episodes of Keeping up with the Kardashians. Of course, “I only watched it to see what all the fuss …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
