<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/snb11/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/snb11/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Lots Road redevelopment to go ahead
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-4-lots-road-redevelopment-to-go-ahead/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2015 23:19:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Ball,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-4-lots-road-redevelopment-to-go-ahead/</guid>
        <description>Lots Road power station, on the Chelsea waterfront, is to join the likes of Battersea and Bankside as it undergoes redevelopment. The project will add 706 homes and two tower blocks to the site close to the Thames.
The project had recently been put on hold due to the General Election and fears of a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Scientists create model of extinct lung parasite
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-imperial-scientists-create-model-of-extinct-lung-parasite/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 01:16:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Ball,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-imperial-scientists-create-model-of-extinct-lung-parasite/</guid>
        <description>A 3D model of a 425 million year old fossil of a sea creature has allowed researchers to obtain the first examples of Invavita piratica (invading pirate) an ancient ancestor of a lung parasite called Tung Worm, sometimes found in humans.
The research team from the University of Leicester including …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jihadi John identified as Westminster graduate
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-27-jihadi-john-identified-as-westminster-graduate/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2015 00:29:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Ball,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-27-jihadi-john-identified-as-westminster-graduate/</guid>
        <description>Sources at the US Government have confirmed the identity of ‘Jihadi John’ to be Mohammed
Emwazi, a computing graduate of the University of Westminster. ‘Jihadi John’ is featured in videos and pictures showing the beheading of a number of Western hostages.
Following the announcement by the press of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lord Fellowes comes to Campus
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-lord-fellowes-comes-to-campus/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 20:44:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Ball,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-12-lord-fellowes-comes-to-campus/</guid>
        <description>Julian Fellowes, creator of Downton Abbey, visited Imperial College on Friday 6th February for a tour of the research labs and also met with the College President, Professor Alice Gast. Their tour finished with a trip out on Jezebel, the RCSU’s fire engine mascot, who appeared in Downton Abbey last …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union Clock in Beit Quad is once again keeping time
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-5-union-clock-in-beit-quad-is-once-again-keeping-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2015 23:47:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Ball,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-5-union-clock-in-beit-quad-is-once-again-keeping-time/</guid>
        <description>The Clock on the Union Building is once again keeping time after a group of past and current students repaired the drive mechanism and constructed a new power system. The Clock had been non-operational for over three years after the original control system on Campus was removed and a replacement …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Venture Catalyst Challenge begins shortly
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-venture-catalyst-challenge-begins-shortly/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 01:35:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Ball,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-venture-catalyst-challenge-begins-shortly/</guid>
        <description>Do you have an idea that could change the world, or that could even become a career itself? Imperial’s Create Lab is once again hosting its Venture Catalyst Challenge – a competition that gives it participants the chance of winning £10,000, one-to-one mentoring from industry experts, evening …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Acton halls with panoramic views
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-21-acton-halls-with-panoramic-views/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2014 13:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Ball,Benjamin Fernando,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-21-acton-halls-with-panoramic-views/</guid>
        <description>Felix paid a visit to the construction site of the new Halls, One Victoria Road, to investigate how things were progressing and to talk to Campus Services about the latest news and updates ον τηε προϕεχτ.
Currently, no decision has yet been taken on the future of Evelyn Gardens. All that is known …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Council Divided? A House which can have fun
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-a-council-divided-a-house-which-can-have-fun/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 18:09:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Ball,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-a-council-divided-a-house-which-can-have-fun/</guid>
        <description>For most people the thought of attending Union Council is not good – to be honest, most people don’t even know what Council is – but for those who do it is often thought of as a chore and is an evening that they would rather spend elsewhere. Personally I rather enjoy the process of locking people in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Powerful Man moves from the Union to the Blue Cube
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-24-a-powerful-man-moves-from-the-union-to-the-blue-cube/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2014 12:37:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ellen Mathieson,Stephen Ball,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-24-a-powerful-man-moves-from-the-union-to-the-blue-cube/</guid>
        <description>Dr Philip Power is finally leaving the Union after 16 years of involvement at Imperial College London, first as an undergraduate, then a postgraduate and finally as a member of staff for Imperial College Union.
During his time as a student at Imperial, first in the Department of Mathematics and then …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union Exec Meets for the Second time in 9 months
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-2-union-exec-meets-for-the-second-time-in-9-months/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 12:40:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Ball,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-2-union-exec-meets-for-the-second-time-in-9-months/</guid>
        <description>Following a large number of meetings being cancelled, the Union Executive Committee has met for only the second time this academic year. Charged with overseeing the general running of the Union and enacting policies of Union Council, Exec is scheduled to meet once a month. However this year a lack …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Election Scandal for Another Union Club
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-23-election-scandal-for-another-union-club/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 17:15:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Ball,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-23-election-scandal-for-another-union-club/</guid>
        <description>The Chinese Students and Scholars Association (CSSA) has joined the Christian Union in having a major election dispute this year after a number of its members wrote a joint letter of complaint to the Imperial College Union reporting that ballot papers were destroyed and that the current committee …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
