<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ashley_luckyram/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ashley_luckyram/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Can we break the glass chair, and bring more women directors into the film industry?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-can-we-break-the-glass-chair-and-bring-more-women-directors-into-the-film-industry/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-can-we-break-the-glass-chair-and-bring-more-women-directors-into-the-film-industry/</guid>
        <description>Hollywood is narcissistic. A community that reflects the vanity and self-obsession of its constituents, when Tinseltown reflects back on 2017 they will not remember it for the Fall of Mosul, the Rohingya Crisis, or the ousting of Robert Mugabe, but for the wave of allegations of sexual misconduct …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Film’s guide to the Oscars – who will win, who should win, and who’ve been left out in the cold</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-felix-film-s-guide-to-the-oscars-who-will-win-who-should-win-and-who-ve-been-left-out-in-the-cold/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Ashley Luckyram,Mark Aduol,Mikhail Demtchenko,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-felix-film-s-guide-to-the-oscars-who-will-win-who-should-win-and-who-ve-been-left-out-in-the-cold/</guid>
        <description>Oscars season is upon as! And, as is traditional, Felix are here to give you a rundown of what will win on the night, as well as what should win, and who didn&amp;rsquo;t even get a nomination:
 Best Picture
 It’s been a complicated awards season. Call Me by Your Name started out in the lead when it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Phantom Thread: A haunting masterpiece</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-phantom-thread-a-haunting-masterpiece/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-phantom-thread-a-haunting-masterpiece/</guid>
        <description>Though he excelled as a young actor in the National Youth Theatre, in 1975 Daniel Day-Lewis made a decision that almost deprived us of some of the very greatest performances ever seen on screen. Then an unruly 18 year old, Day-Lewis elected not to pursue the arts, instead applying for a five year …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On Directing Film</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-on-directing-film/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-on-directing-film/</guid>
        <description>The announcement of the Academy Award nominations last week saw the usual surprises and snubs roll in. One particular category has continued to be the source of much debate throughout awards season, with commentators and voters alike unable to come to agreement. Across the Golden Globes, BAFTAs, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Shape of Oscars</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-the-shape-of-oscars/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-the-shape-of-oscars/</guid>
        <description>While not as glamorous as an affair as the big ceremony at the Dolby Theatre in the Spring, the announcement of the Academy Award nominees is nonetheless an anticipated event. Streamed live from the Samuel Goldwyn Theatre in Beverley Hills, announcers Tiffany Haddish and Andy Serkis had some …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sundance Film Festival: Start as you mean to go on</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-18-sundance-film-festival-start-as-you-mean-to-go-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-18-sundance-film-festival-start-as-you-mean-to-go-on/</guid>
        <description>In 1978 the very first Sundance Film Festival took place, with the goal of showcasing the potential of American independent cinema. On offer were films from the likes of Martin Scorsese and Elia Kazan. It is fair to say that since then Sundance has been an integral part of the independent film …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Awards season contenders: our top picks</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-21-awards-season-contenders-our-top-picks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-21-awards-season-contenders-our-top-picks/</guid>
        <description>Were this article a film, I’d like to think that it would be in contention for recognition from the Academy. It had a clear and bold start, compelling second act, and now, hopefully, a memorable ending. But seriously, let’s talk about who will end up winning the big prizes next spring. There are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>For your consideration: the first annual Felix Film Awards for 2017</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-21-for-your-consideration-the-first-annual-felix-film-awards-for-2017/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-21-for-your-consideration-the-first-annual-felix-film-awards-for-2017/</guid>
        <description>As the year winds to a close, in lieu of compiling a list of the best films, directorial work and acting performances, we have decided to hand out prizes to those who merit them for their outstanding creative efforts. We imagine that the finest talents in world cinema are sat at the edge of their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Our guide to the 2018 awards season contenders II: the Film Editors strike back: Judgement Day: Reloaded</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-our-guide-to-the-2018-awards-season-contenders-ii-the-film-editors-strike-back-judgement-day-reloaded/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-our-guide-to-the-2018-awards-season-contenders-ii-the-film-editors-strike-back-judgement-day-reloaded/</guid>
        <description>As the year winds down I always find myself reflecting back on the best films to emerge over the past twelve months, and this inevitably leads to speculation on which ones might end up with Academy Award nominations and wins. These two categories do not always align, and last week I ran through some …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Our guide to the 2018 awards season contenders (Part 1)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-our-guide-to-the-2018-awards-season-contenders-part-1/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-our-guide-to-the-2018-awards-season-contenders-part-1/</guid>
        <description>Fall festival season is over, trailers for the final films of the year have dropped, and prestige pictures are beginning to roll out their wide releases left, right, and centre. You guessed it: it’s awards season. While there are strong arguments to made that artworks shouldn’t really be compared in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wonder Women: who rules the silver screen? Part Deux</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-wonder-women-who-rules-the-silver-screen-part-deux/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-wonder-women-who-rules-the-silver-screen-part-deux/</guid>
        <description>5 Marion Cotillard
Best Performances: La Vie en Rose, Two Days One Night, The Immigrant, Rust and Bone
Hailing from Paris, Marion Cotillard has always mixed English and French roles, particularly from 2003 onwards. She announced herself on the global stage in 2007 by winning the Oscar for best …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wonder Women: who rules the silver screen?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-wonder-women-who-rules-the-silver-screen/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-wonder-women-who-rules-the-silver-screen/</guid>
        <description>Following the release of the trailer for Sir Daniel Day-Lewis’ final film, Phantom Thread, last week, I looked at who may attempt to fill his enormous boots as the finest actor in the world. There were a number of excellent candidates, and in the end Day-Lewis’ fellow Paul Thomas Anderson …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Moving on from Daniel: where do we go now?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-moving-on-from-daniel-where-do-we-go-now/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-moving-on-from-daniel-where-do-we-go-now/</guid>
        <description>As he named The Master the best film of 2012, Peter Bradshaw of The Guardian labelled the anticipation around the release of a Paul Thomas Anderson film as “event cinema”, only comparable to the legend surrounding the great Stanley Kubrick. America’s newest master’s latest, esoterically titled …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An operatic nightmare of psychological trauma</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-an-operatic-nightmare-of-psychological-trauma/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-an-operatic-nightmare-of-psychological-trauma/</guid>
        <description>You Were Never Really Here
Dir: Lynne Ramsay. Script: Lynne Ramsay. Starring: Joaquin Phoenix, Ekaterina Samsonov, Judith Roberts, John Doman. 85 minutes
4.5 Stars
An unprecedented level of discussion was prompted when the line-up was announced for the Cannes Film Festival in the spring. The new …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Death of Stalin: Armando Iannucci returns</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-the-death-of-stalin-armando-iannucci-returns/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-the-death-of-stalin-armando-iannucci-returns/</guid>
        <description>Scotsman Armando Iannucci is the finest political satirist of the 21st century. Through his television shows The Thick of It and it’s American adaptation Veep, he has shown a propensity for mocking politicians who ostensibly claim to have the interests of the people at heart, while actually only …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
