<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/connor_winzar/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/connor_winzar/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Digimon Story: Cyber Sleuth</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-digimon-story-cyber-sleuth/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-digimon-story-cyber-sleuth/</guid>
        <description>Now I don’t know about you, but Digimon was the bread and butter of my childhood, with its classic animation style and collection of surprisingly dark moments. I’m still traumatised by their equivalent of Sean Bean, Leomon, who seemingly could not go an episode without falling.
So you can imagine …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>POV: The Haunted Island A Frog Detective Game</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-POV-haunted-island-frog-detective-game/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-POV-haunted-island-frog-detective-game/</guid>
        <description>Browsing one of my favourite gaming news websites, Destructoid, I came across a recommendation for this game (currently sold for $1 on Humble Bundle and £3.99 on Steam). The game in question is “Grace Bruxner presents: The Haunted Island a Frog Detective Game”, and despite its long title, the game …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>POV: The Ingenuity of the Emulation Community</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-POV-ingenuity-emulation-community/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-POV-ingenuity-emulation-community/</guid>
        <description>This POV is dedicated to the breathtaking (cue Keanu Reeves) community of coders that make emulation possible. For those unfamiliar with the term, video game emulation is the practice of running or simulating games on machines that they’re not meant to be running on – for example running Nintendo …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>EGX: Games Galore For Every Type of Gamer! Tabletop, Retro, Triple-A and more!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-egx-games-galore-every-type-gamer-tabletop-retro-triple-a-more/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-egx-games-galore-every-type-gamer-tabletop-retro-triple-a-more/</guid>
        <description>This weekend I had the opportunity to go to the gaming convention EGX to scope the latest and hottest games - courtesy of press tickets #GamesEditorPrivilege #ApplyNow. The event was phenomenal, although its position at the distant ExCeL (Royal Victoria Dock) was less so. While the journey to the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>POV: Super Mario Bros. Film Because That Exists!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-POV-super-mario-bros-film-that-exists/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-POV-super-mario-bros-film-that-exists/</guid>
        <description>This week I sacrificed my Sunday evening to watch (again) the horrific video game movie that is “Super Mario Bros.”. Directed by Rocky Morton and Annabel Jankel, the film was both atrocious in its directing and actual content, with so much miscommunication between previous directors and Nintendo …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>POV: Ratchet and Clank 2016 ... just ... just why?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-POV-ratchet-clank-2016-just-why/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-POV-ratchet-clank-2016-just-why/</guid>
        <description>Having just finished Ratchet and Clank 2016 in its entirety I have to say: considering the great reviews, I’m not actually convinced reviewers were playing the same game. Before I start the inevitable ensuing rant, I would like to say that the series holds a special place in my heart. I got into it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>POV: Yakuza 0, the perfect blend of everything</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-POV-yakuza-0-perfect-blend-everything/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-POV-yakuza-0-perfect-blend-everything/</guid>
        <description>With what little time I have left outside of RSM drinking events, and dreading the upcoming workload of this term; I like to chill out, sit down and do what normal people do organise my in-game property portfolio whilst slamming Thug’s faces so hard into the ground that it sprays out money confetti- …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>E3 - You’ve heard of the good releases that came from E3, now get ready to read about the downright awful!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-e3-you-ve-heard-of-the-good-releases-that-came-from-e3-now-get-ready-to-read-about-the-downright-awful/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-e3-you-ve-heard-of-the-good-releases-that-came-from-e3-now-get-ready-to-read-about-the-downright-awful/</guid>
        <description>E3 has always been Christmas for gamers, with plenty of good releases that fill you with surprise and wonder, as well as a fair handful of bad releases, the ones that make you question how the marketing directors keep their jobs. Now, I can imagine most people have heard about some of the better …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Resident Evil 2 Remake- Mr. X Gon Give It To Ya</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-resident-evil-2-remake-mr-x-gon-give-it-to-ya/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-resident-evil-2-remake-mr-x-gon-give-it-to-ya/</guid>
        <description>A love letter written to fans in gory detail, Resident Evil 2 remake makes the otherwise grim situation a brilliant beauty to behold. Taking the original game which was released in 1998 on the PS1, RE2 remake polishes it up for the modern era, with all new content, better camera angles and graphics …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Games’ new addition: Smash Corner </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-felix-games-new-addition-smash-corner/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-felix-games-new-addition-smash-corner/</guid>
        <description>It’s clear that the Nintendo titan that is Reggie heard the cries of the dissatisfied Smash player, for he has finally achieved perfection with the magnificent game that is Super Smash Bros. Ultimate. On a serious note, Smash Ultimate is a spectacular game; despite not quite capturing the nostalgia …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Good times ahead for gaming with the upcoming release of Kingdom Hearts 3 and more!  </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-good-times-ahead-for-gaming-with-the-upcoming-release-of-kingdom-hearts-3-and-more/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-good-times-ahead-for-gaming-with-the-upcoming-release-of-kingdom-hearts-3-and-more/</guid>
        <description>January
Friday 11th:
 Mario &amp;amp; Luigi: Bowser’s Inside Story + Bowser Jr.’s Journey - 3DS New Super Mario Bros U Deluxe - Switch Tales of Vesperia: Definitive Edition - PS4, Xbox One, PC, Switch  Tuesday 15th: - Onimusha: Warlords - PS4, Xbox One, PC, Switch - The Walking Dead: The Final Season …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jonny Woo’s All-Star Brexit Cabaret</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-jonny-woo-s-all-star-brexit-cabaret/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-jonny-woo-s-all-star-brexit-cabaret/</guid>
        <description>For one glorious night, the creative mind of Jonny was unleashed yet again in theatrical form, but this time at the prestigious London Coliseum. With phenomenal costumes that glistened so much that they would make disco balls blush, a spectacularly funny recollection of the history of Brexit and and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Reviews: Deltarune Chapter 1</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-felix-reviews-deltarune-chapter-1/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-felix-reviews-deltarune-chapter-1/</guid>
        <description>It has been three long years since the release of the RPG wonder that was Undertale. With its interesting gameplay mechanics, outstanding OST and plethora of brilliant characters, it’s hard to believe that its creator, Toby Fox, could possibly top it. I can just about say that Deltarune has the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fallout 76- I want to love you</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-fallout-76-i-want-to-love-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,Sam Welton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-fallout-76-i-want-to-love-you/</guid>
        <description>Let me lay down my biases up front. I do love fallout; I’ve clocked an irresponsible number of hours in 4 and New Vegas over the last few years. I gel with the art direction, I like the setting and I love a good open world. I, however, also ardently defended Fallout 76 when it was announced. I saw …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rough times ahead for E3? Sony announces that they won’t be attending the 2019 convention</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-rough-times-ahead-for-e3-sony-announces-that-they-won-t-be-attending-the-2019-convention/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,Kai Lawrence,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-rough-times-ahead-for-e3-sony-announces-that-they-won-t-be-attending-the-2019-convention/</guid>
        <description>The Electronic Entertainment Expo (E3) is a massive gaming convention aimed at showcasing upcoming content from major developers and publishers. With its initial start-up being in 1995, it has continued since with thriving attendance and popularity. Just the mention of E3 within the gaming community …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Games reviews: Hitman 2 </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-felix-games-reviews-hitman-2/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-felix-games-reviews-hitman-2/</guid>
        <description>It’s the return of your favourite barcode brandishing assassin in the latest instalment to the Hitman series; with an all-new set of weapons and costumes, Agent 47 is better than ever. I can definitely tell you it’s better than ever, having played through several psychotic rampages as a soda can …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Is this an out of season April fools joke?” </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16--is-this-an-out-of-season-april-fools-joke/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16--is-this-an-out-of-season-april-fools-joke/</guid>
        <description>Now, my dear reader, you may be confused by the title, but please, indulge me as I detail you the PR disaster that was the Blizzcon 2018 Diablo announcement, in what seemed like a case of trying to put out a fire by pouring oil on it. Let me preface this article by stating that I am not a diehard …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Halloween Horror Game Recommendations </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-halloween-horror-game-recommendations/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,Kai Lawrence,Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-halloween-horror-game-recommendations/</guid>
        <description>With Halloween right around the corner, there’s always plenty of scares including: coursework deadlines, peer pressure and our very own Horror game recommendations! We thought we’d give you a fright this Felix issues with our personal selection of horror games old and new, that you can enjoy this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Buck up for the Bronco: Red Dead Redemption 2</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-buck-up-for-the-bronco-red-dead-redemption-2/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,Anthony Onwuli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-buck-up-for-the-bronco-red-dead-redemption-2/</guid>
        <description>With the rising storm of hype brewing around Red Dead Redemption 2, we thought we’d shed a light on some of the features being added and what you can expect from the game. The majority of the information we’ve got here is straight from the horse’s mouth, in particular the developers themselves, with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix’s Gaming Section wants you! </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-felix-s-gaming-section-wants-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,Anthony Onwuli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-felix-s-gaming-section-wants-you/</guid>
        <description>Hello from the Games editors,
The Games editors not writing about games? Preposterous! This isn’t the content I expect in my Felix Newspaper! Alright, ease the frothing at the mouth and hear us out, I know it’s a strange concept but we’ve decided that rather than hog the gaming section we should …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>October Gaming Highlights</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-october-gaming-highlights/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,Anthony Onwuli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-october-gaming-highlights/</guid>
        <description>Forza Horizon 4 - Xbox One, PC - October 2nd:
Another fantastic addition to the series, Forza Horizon 4 steers clear from its traditional setting, with the game being set in an open world version of the United Kingdom as opposed to America. With a dynamic weather system, beautiful environment and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gamer’s guide to London: A comprehensive guide of all things tabletop, video games and more! </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-20-gamer-s-guide-to-london-a-comprehensive-guide-of-all-things-tabletop-video-games-and-more/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,Anthony Onwuli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-20-gamer-s-guide-to-london-a-comprehensive-guide-of-all-things-tabletop-video-games-and-more/</guid>
        <description>Leicester Square Station – Orbital Comics
For the vintage comic hunter Orbital Comics brings an expansive catalogue of comics new and old that can truly satiate the atypical comic book enthusiast. Within their collection they also boast a large amount of graphic novels as well as comic artworks. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I’m just saiyan: Dragon Ball FighterZ</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-i-m-just-saiyan-dragon-ball-fighterz/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-i-m-just-saiyan-dragon-ball-fighterz/</guid>
        <description>Playing this game as a long-time fan of Dragon Ball Z and the fighter genre, I can say, without a doubt, that DBZ Fighterz feels like a love letter written to its fans. The game has surpassed both limits and expectations of the fighting game genre, going even further beyond with spectacular original …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICSF do Picocon!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-icsf-do-picosoc/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Connor Winzar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-icsf-do-picosoc/</guid>
        <description>After an exciting year of festive socials, leaky libraries, and trips to see some of the biggest film releases in decades, Imperial College Science Fiction and Fantasy Society (ICSF) is finally approaching their biggest event of the year. Bringing together over 100 fans of science fiction and …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
