<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/bsc14/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/bsc14/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Documentary Corner | Citizenfour
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-documentary-corner-citizenfour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 15:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-documentary-corner-citizenfour/</guid>
        <description>Sometimes a perfect opportunity can just present itself to a director. Citizenfour is a film whose mere existence is incredible. Based on the drama of Edward Snowden’s whistleblowing on the mass surveillance being performed by the NSA in America, Citizenfour is the final film in director Laura …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Documentary Corner | James Marsh Special
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-documentary-corner-james-marsh-special/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 14:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-documentary-corner-james-marsh-special/</guid>
        <description>I often hear people sing the praises of director James Marsh and his two supposed classics Project Nim and Man on Wire. Having recently seen both films, I thought it would be interesting to present my reviews this week in tandem. The reason for this is that I noticed a lot of similarities in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Documentary Corner: Life Itself
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-documentary-corner-life-itself/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 15:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-documentary-corner-life-itself/</guid>
        <description>A year after publishing his 2011 memoir Life Itself, Roger Ebert contacted Steve James, the accomplished director of Stevie and Hoop Dreams, to make an accompanying documentary of the same name. It must have been a daunting proposition. Assembling the definitive life story of the world’s most famous …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Do old bonobos need to go to specsavers?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-do-old-bonobos-need-to-go-to-specsavers/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 14:51:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-do-old-bonobos-need-to-go-to-specsavers/</guid>
        <description>Age related far-sightedness in humans can easily be demonstrated by simply observing one of your older relatives as they tip their glasses and extend their arm out to read the morning paper. This phenomenon, known as presbyopia, is brought about by the hardening of the lens and weakening of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Documentary corner: King of Kong
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-documentary-corner-king-of-kong/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 09:09:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-documentary-corner-king-of-kong/</guid>
        <description>As this will be my last Documentary Corner feature of the year, I thought it fitting to end on a high note, with my favourite documentary of all time – King of Kong: A Fistful of Quarters. It works in every way a documentary should, and then some. Director Seth Gordon was able to create a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The top three Japanese Films that aren’t animated
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-the-top-three-japanese-films-that-arent-animated/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 09:06:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-the-top-three-japanese-films-that-arent-animated/</guid>
        <description>Two weeks ago I slagged off the French film-making philosophy. In an effort to be more positive this week, I’m going to heap praise on my favourite film-producing country – Japan. Looking past the endlessly churned out anime crap, animated Japanese cinema may very well be the best in the world. – …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Documentary corner: Going Clear
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-documentary-corner-going-clear/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 10:14:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-documentary-corner-going-clear/</guid>
        <description>Scientology is not exactly the rarest documentary topic. Countless attempts have been made in the past to expose various aspects of this ‘Church’ in the past – discussing its history or telling the stories of those who have left its ranks. Perhaps the most famous documentary prior to the release of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The top three Superhero Films that aren’t Marvel
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-the-top-three-superhero-films-that-arent-marvel/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 10:12:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-the-top-three-superhero-films-that-arent-marvel/</guid>
        <description>Okay guys, seriously now, Disney is starting to scare me. Now that they own ESPN, ABC, Lucas films, Pixar AND Marvel the ludicrous amount of money they make could, theoretically (and I’m not saying this is a definite), fund a pretty decent world domination effort. I’m just saying. The only way to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where are all the women in hip-hop?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-where-are-all-the-women-in-hip-hop/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 09:59:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-where-are-all-the-women-in-hip-hop/</guid>
        <description>With hip hop, as a genre and a culture, passing its 40th anniversary in recent years, a female presence is as absent as ever. This is, of course, not for a lack of talent. Ignoring some examples like Iggy Azalea and Kreayshawn, there is a lot of female talent to be found in the realm of hip hop …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Documentary corner: Blackfish
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-documentary-corner-blackfish/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:39:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-documentary-corner-blackfish/</guid>
        <description>Back in November of last year I wrote one of my first ‘Documentary Corner’ features on the film The Cove – a powerful environmentalist piece which showcased the grim reality of dolphin and whale hunting in Japan. As I mentioned in that review, The Cove remains one of a relatively small list of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The top three European Films that aren’t French
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-the-top-three-european-films-that-arent-french/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:37:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-the-top-three-european-films-that-arent-french/</guid>
        <description>As much as I love the more abstract/pretentious cinema offerings at any one time, I can’t bloody stand French films. I’m not saying that all French films are bad – that would be ridiculous. My argument, which I would hope is at least somewhat informed, is that the French ‘style’ of filmmaking is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Documentary corner: Senna
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-documentary-corner-senna/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 11:59:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-documentary-corner-senna/</guid>
        <description>My fool-proof method for determining whether a biopic is good or not is as follows: if I go in with no knowledge/interest in its subject matter, and 1) understand what’s going on the whole time, and; 2) become genuinely invested in its subject matter, then it passes. Senna was the first majorly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The top three Murder Mysteries that aren’t Rear Window
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-the-top-three-murder-mysteries-that-arent-rear-window/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 11:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-the-top-three-murder-mysteries-that-arent-rear-window/</guid>
        <description>Ok, so the original plan for this week was to put together an election-themed section. Maybe ‘best films featuring presidents’ or ‘best political dramas’? The truth of it is that I’m a bit election’d out right now… Either that or I couldn’t find anything on Google other than Lincoln. You know what’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The top three Oscar winners who aren’t Leo DiCaprio
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-the-top-three-oscar-winners-who-arent-leo-dicaprio/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 11:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-the-top-three-oscar-winners-who-arent-leo-dicaprio/</guid>
        <description>Well damn, he did it. The meme is dead. 22 years after his first nomination, good old Leo has finally nabbed his long-awaited Oscar for his leading role in Alejandro Iñárritu’s epic The Revenant. Whilst this is good news, let’s not get carried away in our celebrations. Why not have a look at some of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Documentary corner: 20 Feet From Stardom
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-documentary-corner-20-feet-from-stardom/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 11:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-documentary-corner-20-feet-from-stardom/</guid>
        <description>Darlene Love, Merry Clayton, Lisa Fischer… you probably don’t know these names but I guarantee you know the voices. 20 Feet from Stardom is a talking-heads documentary that tells of the relatively unknown world of such backup vocalists. Prior to making this film, its director, Morgan Neville, spent …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Documentary corner: Dear Zachary
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-documentary-corner-dear-zachary/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 11:51:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-documentary-corner-dear-zachary/</guid>
        <description>Before I begin this review, I’m going to really strongly recommend that if you haven’t already seen the film you should avoid reviews or summaries online. Should you watch this documentary – as I did – with no foreknowledge then I guarantee that watching Dear Zachary: A Letter to a Son about his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The top three car chases that aren’t in Fast &amp; Furious
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-the-top-three-car-chases-that-arent-in-fast-furious/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 11:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-the-top-three-car-chases-that-arent-in-fast-furious/</guid>
        <description>They’re great guilty pleasures, the Fast and Furious films, aren’t they? How can anyone not enjoy having some drinks and a pizza while watching several ripped guys illegally street race and pull off stupid heists? Fast and Furious is simply a very fun, enjoyable set of action films, and – of course …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The top three actor-musicians who aren’t Madonna
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-the-top-three-actor-musicians-who-arent-madonna/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 11:37:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-the-top-three-actor-musicians-who-arent-madonna/</guid>
        <description>Considering my age it’s hard for me imagine that, at one time, Madonna was the biggest star in the world. Unfortunately though, often with a great music career comes a terrible film career. Anyone who’s seen Swept Away or The Next Best Thing should know that she’s never set the bar high for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Life of Pablo
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-the-life-of-pablo/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 12:19:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-the-life-of-pablo/</guid>
        <description>For those of us who have been following the run-up to The Life of Pablo album, it’s been a ride. The release cycle was so messy at times many people began to expect disappointment. Four album names and endless delays later however, Kanye West’s seventh studio album has finally dropped. And, despite …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Documentary corner: Exit Through the Gift Shop
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-documentary-corner-exit-through-the-gift-shop/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 12:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-documentary-corner-exit-through-the-gift-shop/</guid>
        <description>Last week we had The Imposter – a gripping documentary following a bizarre case of identity fraud and murder. The film was heavy with recreation scenes and utilised them to such an extent that it blurred the lines between documentary and feature drama. The documentary of choice this week continues …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The top three gangster films that aren’t The Godfather
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-the-top-three-gangster-films-that-arent-the-godfather/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 12:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-the-top-three-gangster-films-that-arent-the-godfather/</guid>
        <description>Francis Ford Coppola’s Godfather films (excluding The Godfather III – no one likes the third one, let’s be real) are often considered to be two of the greatest films ever made. In fact, they sit nicely below _The Shawshank Redemption_’s top spot on IMDb’s Top 100 Films list. However, The Godfather …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The top three strong women leads who aren’t Elle Woods
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-the-top-three-strong-women-leads-who-arent-elle-woods/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 11:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-the-top-three-strong-women-leads-who-arent-elle-woods/</guid>
        <description>Legally Blonde is a decent enough film, and I appreciate the effort of the filmmakers to create a stereotype-defying and intelligent female lead. However, the fact remains that Woods only gets into law school because the admissions officer fancies her, and her big show of intelligence at the end of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Documentary corner: The Imposter
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-documentary-corner-the-imposter/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 11:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-documentary-corner-the-imposter/</guid>
        <description>On the 13th of June, 1994, thirteen-year-old Nicolas Barcley went to play a game of basketball with his friends in San Antonio, Texas. This was the last time he was seen. Missing for three years and presumed dead, he was suddenly discovered in Linares, Spain. Or was he? Well, his family said it was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Documentary corner: Chimpanzee
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-documentary-corner-chimpanzee/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 12:34:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-documentary-corner-chimpanzee/</guid>
        <description>Oh a genuine big-budget nature documentary,&amp;rdquo; I thought excitedly. As a biologist and lover of all things primate I was instantly excited to watch this film upon seeing its name online. Unfortunately, my excitement quickly flip-flop’d when I saw the second part of the title: ‘Disney nature’. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The top three Korean films that aren’t Oldboy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-the-top-three-korean-films-that-arent-oldboy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 12:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-the-top-three-korean-films-that-arent-oldboy/</guid>
        <description>A rather weird exchange of words comes about every time I recommend maverick Korean Director Chan-wook Park’s 2003 masterpiece Oldboy: ‘Trust me this film is so amazing and messed up, it will scar you for life!’ It’s something that has to be seen to be understood. What is for sure is that Oldboy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Documentary corner: American Movie
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-documentary-corner-american-movie/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 09:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-documentary-corner-american-movie/</guid>
        <description>It’s not often you see a documentary split opinion in such a love-it-or-hate-it fashion. I suppose that is something that comes with ‘cult film’ territory, and personally, when I think of the label of ‘cult classic’, American Movie is the first film that comes to mind. The star here is Mark …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The top three Oscar snubs not involving DiCaprio
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-the-top-three-oscar-snubs-not-involving-dicaprio/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 09:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-the-top-three-oscar-snubs-not-involving-dicaprio/</guid>
        <description>Well it looks like the drought is finally over. After putting out several arguably ‘Oscar-worthy’ performances Leonardo DiCaprio may finally be awarded his long awaited and joked-about Oscar. We have Alejandro G. Iñárritu and The Revenant to thank for this. However, whilst DiCaprio is the most …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Documentary Corner: Jesus Camp
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-6-documentary-corner-jesus-camp/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2015 14:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-6-documentary-corner-jesus-camp/</guid>
        <description>“Is there anyone in here who believes that God can do anything?” the energized Pentecostal preacher Becky Fischer questions her baying crowd as the camera cuts to a mother raising her two uninterested children’s hands excitedly. The opening scene of Jesus Camp places the viewer right in the middle …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Top Western films that aren’t The Good, the Bad, and the Ugly
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-6-the-top-western-films-that-arent-the-good-the-bad-and-the-ugly/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2015 14:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-6-the-top-western-films-that-arent-the-good-the-bad-and-the-ugly/</guid>
        <description>The Top Western films that aren’t The Good, the Bad, and the Ugly
When we think of Westerns we think of Clint Eastwood. This association, as you will see later, is one I cannot easily escape from either. The final instalment in Sergio Leone’s ‘Dollars’ trilogy, The Good, the Bad, and the Ugly is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>3 action films that aren&#39;t Die Hard
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-29-3-action-films-that-arent-die-hard/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2015 16:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-29-3-action-films-that-arent-die-hard/</guid>
        <description> I love Die Hard. In fact, I’m one of those people who call it one of the best Christmas films of all time. The issue is that I am banned – as we all should be – from watching the film until at least the start of December. Until then, it looks like we need some other action films to fill the void: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Documentary Corner: Indie Game: The Movie
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-29-documentary-corner-indie-game-the-movie/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2015 16:24:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-29-documentary-corner-indie-game-the-movie/</guid>
        <description>In the last decade or so, the video game industry has seen a meteoric rise in success. Previously seen as a pastime for nerds alone, the medium is now as mainstream and popular as any other. A relatively new phenomenon is the concept of the ‘indie developer’; while game production was previously …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Top three Sports Films that aren&#39;t Rocky
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-top-three-sports-films-that-arent-rocky/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 14:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-top-three-sports-films-that-arent-rocky/</guid>
        <description>People always say the original Rocky is a classic, but I’ve never really seen this. I challenge its fans to watch it again today, and tell me it’s aged well. Yes, there are some iconic scenes, but this is not because they’re good – rather it’s because the film was popular. What we have here is a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Documentary Corner
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-documentary-corner/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 09:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-documentary-corner/</guid>
        <description>Much like Bowling for Columbine, our featured film of last week, The Cove stands as a masterful example of a documentary with a message. A renowned critical darling, the film boasts countless awards, including the Academy Award for ‘Best Documentary Feature’. Despite being heavily one-sided, it is a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The top three sports films that aren’t Rocky
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-the-top-three-sports-films-that-arent-rocky/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 09:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-the-top-three-sports-films-that-arent-rocky/</guid>
        <description> People always say the original Rocky is a classic, but I’ve never really seen this. I challenge its fans to watch it again today, and tell me it’s aged well. Yes, there are some iconic scenes, but this is not because they’re good – rather it’s because the film was popular. What we have here is a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Warriors&#39; ambitious subject matter fails to pack a punch
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-15-warriors-ambitious-subject-matter-fails-to-pack-a-punch/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2015 10:51:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-15-warriors-ambitious-subject-matter-fails-to-pack-a-punch/</guid>
        <description>Warriors is an important and, at times, genuinely moving documentary. It tells the story of the Maasai warriors of Nairobi, how their culture promotes FGM, and its ties into the AIDS epidemic. In a society where the elders are believed to have a link to God, it’s hard for the youth to be heard. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Documentary Corner
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-documentary-corner/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 14:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-documentary-corner/</guid>
        <description>Found in a subway station of downtown Tokyo and seating only a mere ten people, it’s fair to say Sukiyabashi Jiro is one of the more inconspicuous three-Michelin-starred restaurants in the world. Since expanding their gaze to the Far East, the Michelin guide has become enchanted by the food of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The top three animated films that aren’t made by Pixar
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-the-top-three-animated-films-that-arent-made-by-pixar/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 14:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-the-top-three-animated-films-that-arent-made-by-pixar/</guid>
        <description> I love Pixar. Chances are you love Pixar. too. In all honesty, I’d hazard a guess that the vast majority of sane people on earth love them. Their films are iconic and have set the precedent for animated films that both children, adolescents and their parents can enjoy. But instead of watching …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
