<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/gm1509/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/gm1509/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Ski Food
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-ski-food/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 19:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>George McIntyre,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-ski-food/</guid>
        <description>I don’t know a lot about you and to be honest I don’t really care (only kidding…no really, I don’t care). but I was fortunate enough to spend Christmas in Les Alpes. Personally, and unsurprisingly (being a wannabe food critic) my favorite part was the food. So again I have another gem of a recipe to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>100 ways to eat eggs! Actually just three…
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-100-ways-to-eat-eggs-actually-just-three/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 20:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>George McIntyre,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-100-ways-to-eat-eggs-actually-just-three/</guid>
        <description>Apparently eggs are the ultimate fast food. Some of you may already know this. In fact I know one guy who eats scrambled eggs nearly everyday. Good effort, Steve!
Anyway, the fact is they are high in protein, low in fat and carbohydrates and therefore very good for you! Here are three simple recipes …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are you coming out for a Ruby Murray tonight?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-are-you-coming-out-for-a-ruby-murray-tonight/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 21:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>George McIntyre,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-are-you-coming-out-for-a-ruby-murray-tonight/</guid>
        <description>National Curry Week is happening next week (22-26 November) so find yourself some drunken mates who can take the heat of a Vindaloo, bring some beer, and give these places a go..
Sheba, Brick Lane
by Vivien Wong
Sunday makes me think of Brick Lane, the buzz and atmosphere there is perfect for a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union food worthy of a Michelin star?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-union-food-worthy-of-a-michelin-star/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 19:44:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>George McIntyre,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-union-food-worthy-of-a-michelin-star/</guid>
        <description>So, I was recently asked about the best perk of working behind the new bar at the Union. Now, before you say, it’s not the verbal abuse from the pretty much universally hated miners and no, it’s not the funky shirts. It’s without a doubt, the free food.
Mid-shift there is absolutely nothing you want …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
