<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/wm207/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/wm207/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Double win for Ice Hockey B team against Cambridge
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-double-win-for-ice-hockey-b-team-against-cambridge/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 21:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Mason,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-double-win-for-ice-hockey-b-team-against-cambridge/</guid>
        <description>The Devils were confident going up against the bottom-of-the-league Cambridge, but remained cautious after their previous close call with Oxford Women’s.
The game saw the Devils with the first 3-line roster this term, and some changes to the individual lines. This clearly paid off as the Devils’ …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>League leaders too much for Devil B’s
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-league-leaders-too-much-for-devil-bs/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 21:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Mason,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-league-leaders-too-much-for-devil-bs/</guid>
        <description>A relatively up-beat third ranked team arrived at Streatham to see away a home match with the division leaders. In the second game without coach Coolegem the B-Team were confident in themselves although this may have manifested into arrogance. A solid pre-game tactics session by bench coaches Dolan …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oxford no match for the Devils
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-oxford-no-match-for-the-devils/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 21:33:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Mason,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-oxford-no-match-for-the-devils/</guid>
        <description>Devils B were psychologically strong going into last Wednesday&amp;rsquo;s game against Oxford Women&amp;rsquo;s. Despite an overall mixed season and a previous game close loss to Bristol (4-3), the Devils had reaped the benefits of match experience and knew Oxford was a team they could and should beat. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oxford falls to the power of the Devils
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-oxford-falls-to-the-power-of-the-devils/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 20:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>William Mason,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-oxford-falls-to-the-power-of-the-devils/</guid>
        <description>Imperial Devils A were confident on the back of their recent win against Kent Knights and were prepared to dish out some punishment to Oxford who had beaten them in the first game of the season. The roster was uncertain as many players had other commitments, including exams the following day. …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
