<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jr1911/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jr1911/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Egypt’s New Constitution
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-egypts-new-constitution/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 17:56:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jash Rughani,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-egypts-new-constitution/</guid>
        <description>In January 2011, when Egypt’s political landscape was marred by widespread distrust in President Hosni Mubarak’s regime the citizens of Egypt took to the streets with zeal for new hope and better governance. Protests were bolstered by the involvement of youth and there was a unanimous demand for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Geneva 2- Peace Talks for the Syrian Crisis
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-geneva-2-peace-talks-for-the-syrian-crisis/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 21:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jash Rughani,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-geneva-2-peace-talks-for-the-syrian-crisis/</guid>
        <description>After a political turmoil that took a toll on the lives of thousands of hapless innocent Syrians, peace talks between opposing factions has emerged as the only recourse for the multitude. The situation on ground has deteriorated beyond recognition- derelict streets, blast ravaged homes, unemployed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Piracy and the need to tackle it
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-piracy-and-the-need-to-tackle-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 09:42:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jash Rughani,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-piracy-and-the-need-to-tackle-it/</guid>
        <description>Piracy grips the public imagination. Witness the success of “Captain Phillips”, a film in which a vessel captained by the actor Tom Hanks is hijacked by Somalis. Somali pirate operations have been a major threat to ships in the Gulf of Aden and those bypassing the Indian Ocean. Yet the pirate modus …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Talks held between India and China over a border dispute
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-talks-held-between-india-and-china-over-a-border-dispute/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 09:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jash Rughani,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-talks-held-between-india-and-china-over-a-border-dispute/</guid>
        <description>China’s presence on the global economic platform has been colossal since the turn of the millennium. It has followed the tenets of inclusive growth and has managed to eradicate rural poverty while the GDP is pegged at about 9 trillion dollars annually. However, the dragon country’s real problems and …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
