<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/zahra_abiola/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/zahra_abiola/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The Do’s and Don’t of a Student Christmas Dinner: How to Keep the Festive Mood on a Student Budget</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-dos-donts-christmas-dinner-keep-festive-mood-student-budget/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Syon Lee,Zahra Abiola,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-dos-donts-christmas-dinner-keep-festive-mood-student-budget/</guid>
        <description>THE BIRD
A whole roast turkey is the usual fare for a Christmas dinner but unless you are ready to buy way ahead, have an inordinate amount of oven space, and you don’t mind the lengthy brining and cooking process, I would steer clear. A poorly cooked turkey is way worse than no turkey at all. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Take You and Your Study Buddy to Shake Shack Pronto!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-take-you-your-study-buddy-shake-shack-pronto/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Zahra Abiola,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-take-you-your-study-buddy-shake-shack-pronto/</guid>
        <description>Students of Imperial College London, we have been done a great disservice. There is a trendy, self-service, American burger place right beside South Kensington station. And it’s the one that doesn’t have a student discount. If you are tired of a specific number of men not appreciating you, you can …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Black Milk: The Sugar Coma you’ve been waiting for!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-Black-Milk-Sugar-Coma-Youve-Been-Waiting-For/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Zahra Abiola,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-Black-Milk-Sugar-Coma-Youve-Been-Waiting-For/</guid>
        <description>Black Milk is a café that is best known for their jaw dropping freakshakes. Now, freakshakes have been a trend that has taken the internet by storm for some time now. Originating from Australia, they can be defined as milkshakes topped with something to give it a twist. This gives a lot of leeway …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Old Dutch Monday Madness: The only way to start the week right!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-my-old-dutch-monday-madness/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Zahra Abiola,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-my-old-dutch-monday-madness/</guid>
        <description>I have a very important question to ask you all. Do you want a sweet or a savoury breakfast? Because at My Old Dutch, that is the most important decision you will be making that day. This place sports some of the largest crepe style pancakes I’ve ever seen. Their menu is just as big and is split …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pizza Union: The Cheapest Pizza You’ll Find in London!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-pizza-union-cheapest-pizza-in-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Zahra Abiola,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-pizza-union-cheapest-pizza-in-london/</guid>
        <description>I’m going to let you in on one of London’s better kept secrets. Pizza Union. They don’t even need a gimmick. This pizza place has 12” pizzas starting at £3.50. No coupon code. No Instagram exclusive. No witch making you promise your first-born child in exchange for some genuinely affordable food in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>VQ: The Restaurant that Never Sleeps</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-vq-restaurant-never-sleeps/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Zahra Abiola,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-vq-restaurant-never-sleeps/</guid>
        <description>We all know how it goes. The night starts out with good intentions. You’ve handed in your coursework with just 2 minutes to spare. You want some fun. You round up your friends and dance the stress away while screaming Beyoncé lyrics at the top of your lungs, having the time of your life as a student …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
