<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ir112/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ir112/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Gemcraft: Labyrinth
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-29-gemcraft-labyrinth/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 16:37:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imran Rashid,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-29-gemcraft-labyrinth/</guid>
        <description>Gemcraft Labyrinth is the 3rd Chapter of the epic tower defense series of Gemcraft from Game In a Bottle. Gemcraft Labyrinth offers a deep gameplay with its combination of strategy and RPG elements making it easily one of the best tower defense games of 2013.
The basic gameplay of Labyrinth remains …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Star in Command
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-the-star-in-command/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 16:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imran Rashid,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-the-star-in-command/</guid>
        <description>Delays, delays and more delays, at the end of which only 30% of the game had been realised. Truly… the cake was a lie. I’m talking, of course, about the Kickstarter campaign of Star Command, a game that was pitched as a strategic space simulator, where aspiring Captain Kirks would explore planets …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Clicking your way to cookies
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-clicking-your-way-to-cookies/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 16:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imran Rashid,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-clicking-your-way-to-cookies/</guid>
        <description>Cookie Clicker is the highly addictive game with the goal of producing an infinite number of cookies! Yup – it’s a game that never ends as much as it never lets you go.
To make a cookie is simple. Just click the giant cookie on the screen.
Cookies are the currency of the game. With enough cookies …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kingdom Rushing to the Frontier
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-kingdom-rushing-to-the-frontier/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 16:09:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imran Rashid,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-kingdom-rushing-to-the-frontier/</guid>
        <description>For those who loved the original Kingdom Rush are really in for a treat with the new Kingdom Rush Frontiers available on android, apple, and now Armorgames. This game employs the same incredibly polished Tower Defence gameplay, artstyle, and presentation as its prequel with new elements that enhance …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Amore - not part of Armor Mayham
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-30-amore-not-part-of-armor-mayham/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 15:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imran Rashid,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-30-amore-not-part-of-armor-mayham/</guid>
        <description>Armor Mayhem is a Halo and Unreal Tournament inspired game set in the future when our planet Earth has run out of energy. Major corporations send teams to scavenge the universe in search for more energy. Eventually, energy is detected on planet 55001 and to their astonishment they find infinite …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Far Cry 3: Pirate Infested Tropical Dystopia
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-16-far-cry-3-pirate-infested-tropical-dystopia/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 14:13:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imran Rashid,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-16-far-cry-3-pirate-infested-tropical-dystopia/</guid>
        <description>Partying. Hostages. Drinks. Machetes. Skydiving. Friends. Pirates. The game starts off with a montage of you (as Jason Brody), your brothers and your friends having the time of their life on a large island in the south pacific. The nightmare quickly begins when Jason wakes up to find himself …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lara Croft dies. Tomb Raider is born.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-lara-croft-dies-tomb-raider-is-born/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 19:29:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imran Rashid,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-lara-croft-dies-tomb-raider-is-born/</guid>
        <description>The Lara Croft we see in this game is very different to how we might usually perceive her: confident, strong, comfortable with diving into dark caves or putting bullets into enemies. Instead, our main character starts off as anxious, afraid and averse to violence. This game takes us back to the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
