<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/cac111/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/cac111/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Union award winners announced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-11-union-award-winners-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 22:18:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-11-union-award-winners-announced/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Union Council ratified the list of individual Union Award winners at its meeting on Tuesday 8 June, which sees 156 students out of the 310 who were nominated receiving various accolades. The awards recognise those working across the Union, from clubs and societies to representation, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Student Academic Choice Award winners announced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-14-student-academic-choice-award-winners-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 22:32:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-14-student-academic-choice-award-winners-announced/</guid>
        <description>The Imperial College Union Student Academic Choice Awards (SACAs) award ceremony took place on Monday evening at the Union Concert Hall. Eight awards were featured that evening, with six shortlisted members of staff per award.
The SACAs, now in their third year, were set up to recognise staff for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Car flipped over on Exhibition Road, two injured
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-14-car-flipped-over-on-exhibition-road-two-injured/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 22:17:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-14-car-flipped-over-on-exhibition-road-two-injured/</guid>
        <description>Two women were treated for minor injuries after their car was flipped onto its roof due to a collison with a lorry on Exhibition Road. The incident occurred on Tuesday afternoon outside the Natural History Museum, which also saw a Rolls-Royce take damage.
Speaking to the London Evening Standard, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What you may have missed over Easter
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-4-30-what-you-may-have-missed-over-easter/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2015 22:58:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-4-30-what-you-may-have-missed-over-easter/</guid>
        <description>420: Thousands gather in Hyde Park, more than 50 arrested
As pro-cannabis protesters openly smoked the drug in Hyde Park on April 20 (an annual global celebration of cannabis, where calls for drug law reform take place), police ended up arresting 53 people. 16 were taken into custody, whereas 21 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>THE World Reputation Rankings place Imperial 14th
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-19-the-world-reputation-rankings-place-imperial-14th/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 23:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-19-the-world-reputation-rankings-place-imperial-14th/</guid>
        <description>In the latest release of the Times Higher Education (THE) World Reputation Rankings, Imperial College London dropped one place from 13th in 2014 to 14th in 2015. The THE World Reputation Rankings are a spin-off supplement from the internationally acclaimed THE World University Rankings, where …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First annual animal research practise report released by College
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-13-first-annual-animal-research-practise-report-released-by-college/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 01:22:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-13-first-annual-animal-research-practise-report-released-by-college/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London has released its first annual report on animal research practices within College. The 30-page document was launched at a specially held event as part of the Imperial Fringe series, which was open to the public and drew a crowd of around 200.
Attendees had the opportunity to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What’s going on with student visas?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-27-whats-going-on-with-student-visas/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2015 00:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-27-whats-going-on-with-student-visas/</guid>
        <description> An influential group of MPs has criticised the Government’s student visa policy this week. In a report published by the All-Party Parliamentary Group on Migration, the MPs argued for re-opening of the “post-study work route” following graduation.
Up until 2012, international students could remain …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Police ask for more information on Kensington stabbing
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-29-police-ask-for-more-information-on-kensington-stabbing/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2015 23:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-29-police-ask-for-more-information-on-kensington-stabbing/</guid>
        <description>Two men in their mid-20s were taken to hospital after a stabbing near Notting Hill Gate station in the early hours of Monday morning. They are both said to be in stable condition, but the first was described as serious and the second as critical.
Officers received a call from the London Ambulance …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial appoint its first Vice President for Advancement
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-29-imperial-appoint-its-first-vice-president-for-advancement/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2015 23:38:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-29-imperial-appoint-its-first-vice-president-for-advancement/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London announced Sarah Porter Waterbury as its very first Vice President (Advancement) on 27th January. The new role, which she will take up in April this year, sees Mrs Waterbury in charge of all things encompassing alumni relations, events and development.
As New York University’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Old friends, new ventures
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-old-friends-new-ventures/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 18:37:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-old-friends-new-ventures/</guid>
        <description>In the last fortnight I’ve had the pleasure of meeting up with my former colleagues from Earl’s Court on two separate occasions. The weekend before term, a work junior of mine invited me for a catch-up cocktail to gossip about changes at my old workplace.
Over my lovely Tiramisu martini, made by my …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to quickly use your noodle(s)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-how-to-quickly-use-your-noodles/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 18:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-how-to-quickly-use-your-noodles/</guid>
        <description>Happy 2015, everyone! Between deadlines in early January, prepping for new module lectures this term and catching up with the stuff I missed last term when the Vile Bug of Winter ‘14 hit Imperialites (and their dogs&amp;hellip;) finding time to cook decent meals has been rather difficult: So difficult …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix investigates: the admin that didn’t remain anonymous
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-felix-investigates-the-admin-that-didnt-remain-anonymous/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 01:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Philippa M Skett,Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-felix-investigates-the-admin-that-didnt-remain-anonymous/</guid>
        <description>Felix has reason to believe that a single student may be behind many of the popular Imperial Facebook pages.
We suspect the individual has now graduated, after completing an undergraduate degree in Aeronautics. Felix has managed to procure email correspondence and personal anecdotes from a number of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Shutterbug-gered: legal action may be sought against Imperial students
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-16-shutterbug-gered-legal-action-may-be-sought-against-imperial-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 12:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-16-shutterbug-gered-legal-action-may-be-sought-against-imperial-students/</guid>
        <description>A photo booth hire service is considering further legal action after incurring damages to its equipment during the joint RCSU-CGCU Winter Ball in early December last year.
Felix was told that the RCSU, who made the hire arrangement on behalf of the joint organizing committee, had paid the cost of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Death of Professor Grimm: the world reacts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-12-death-of-professor-grimm-the-world-reacts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 12:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-12-death-of-professor-grimm-the-world-reacts/</guid>
        <description>After the initial uproar amongst academics caused by the publication of Stefan Grimm’s damning posthumous email, discussion has spread amongst academics outside the English-speaking scientific community.
The biggest response by far has been seen amongst Chinese-speaking scientific academics. A …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What a meaty issue! (not)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-what-a-meaty-issue-not/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 20:38:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-what-a-meaty-issue-not/</guid>
        <description>When Kamil (you’ll recognise him as one of our Arts Editors) pitched this piece, I was really stoked. I’m not deeply for or against vegetarianism myself; after all, I live happily with a vegetarian housemate (who taught me how to make one of my favourite cream pasta dishes), and I willingly go …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Marking boycott comes to an end
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-21-marking-boycott-comes-to-an-end/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2014 13:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-21-marking-boycott-comes-to-an-end/</guid>
        <description>After a fortnight of industrial action, the University and College Union (UCU) and Universities UK (UUK) have reached an agreement on Wednesday to a series of negotiation meetings.
Through this, UCU and UUK have jointly agreed to suspend industrial action (a marking boycott that had taken place at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Bitcoin competition prize fund
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-21-new-bitcoin-competition-prize-fund/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2014 13:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-21-new-bitcoin-competition-prize-fund/</guid>
        <description>The Imperial College Business School (ICBS) has teamed up with Entrepreneur First (EF), a pre-seed investment programme, to launch a new competition prize fund for students. Up to £3000 could be won from the Imperial/EF Bitcoin Prize Fund for projects that utilise Blockchain technology, which allows …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First ever ‘Royal Mixer’ is held at Imperial College Union
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-21-first-ever-royal-mixer-is-held-at-imperial-college-union/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2014 13:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-21-first-ever-royal-mixer-is-held-at-imperial-college-union/</guid>
        <description>The first ever Royal Mixer, which took place last Thursday 13th Nov 2014 at Metric, saw students from a host of other “Royal” institutions in London attend an Imperial-based social for the first time.
The event was jointly organized by the unions at Imperial, the Royal College of Music (RCM), the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Anger over Odeon Cinema demolition
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-anger-over-odeon-cinema-demolition/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 20:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-anger-over-odeon-cinema-demolition/</guid>
        <description>Kensington residents have been up in arms over a recent planning application submitted by Minerva Ltd to the Royal Borough of Kensington and Chelsea (RBKC), which entails demolishing a number of iconic Kensington High Street buildings, including the Odeon Kensington cinema.
The specific sites which …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Self-righting wheelchair technology developed by students
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-self-righting-wheelchair-technology-developed-by-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 20:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-14-self-righting-wheelchair-technology-developed-by-students/</guid>
        <description>A team of students from the Department of Bioengineering have augmented a sports wheelchair in order to enable disabled athletes to re-right themselves back on their wheels after a crash. Jacqueline Beddoe-Rosendo, Bianca de Blasi and Simone Castagno developed the prototype during a UROP this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New ideas aplenty...starring YOU!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-new-ideas-aplentystarring-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 22:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-new-ideas-aplentystarring-you/</guid>
        <description>Eh-up, Imperialites – welcome back to another instalment of Felix Food! The weather’s turned turtle and it seems all of us in my flat have fallen victim to some form of Freshers’ Flu (despite not being freshers, pah.) That said, however, it’s perfect weather for all the comfort foods we associate …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Red in my ledger
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-red-in-my-ledger/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 21:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-red-in-my-ledger/</guid>
        <description>I managed to get a trip down memory lane this week – well, this was when I was making a batch of red velvet cupcakes for our ed-in-chief’s birthday on Tuesday (happy birthday again Philippa!) Many moons ago, when I was a not-so-jaded fresher, I was actually known amongst some peers as the queen of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Sun offers money for “Jihadi John” photos
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-the-sun-offers-money-for-jihadi-john-photos/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 18:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-the-sun-offers-money-for-jihadi-john-photos/</guid>
        <description>The Sun has now come under fire from various student unions, after it emerged that their reporters have offered money in exchange for images of controversial Halloween costumes.
Editors at a number of university newspapers have since spoken out, claiming that “thousands of pounds” and “a potential …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A few of our favourite things... - Caz&#39;s Take
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-2-a-few-of-our-favourite-things-cazs-take/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 13:19:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-2-a-few-of-our-favourite-things-cazs-take/</guid>
        <description> Okay, it’s not winter - but summer term is still a high-stress term here in Imperial, we’ll grant you that. Everyone’s got their own comfort foods/snacks (season be damned), favourite eateries, kitchen gadgets they’re biased towards. Even us as Food editors - we’re not going to pretend we don’t …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Introducing: Stir fry pasta
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-16-introducing-stir-fry-pasta/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 02:13:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-16-introducing-stir-fry-pasta/</guid>
        <description>Sharing the Cheah family recipe:
Quick, tasty and different!
Boil the pasta until al dente. Try buying good quality pasta, otherwise it is more likely to stick and become a mush when you stir fry it. Drain and reserve the starchy water.
Fry minced garlic in a drop of oil until fragrant - be careful …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bored of your meals?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-bored-of-your-meals/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 14:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Y K Chung,Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-bored-of-your-meals/</guid>
        <description> As students, our food budgets might be limited, but this does not mean our diets are boring! Eating out or ordering takeaway is neither cheap nor healthy most of the time, but not only can you control the cost and what goes into your food when you cook yourself, we guarantee you will find it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Check(mate) your Privilege
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-10-checkmate-your-privilege/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 10:06:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-10-checkmate-your-privilege/</guid>
        <description>It&amp;rsquo;s one thing to write a review for an Imperial College student production. It&amp;rsquo;s another thing to write a review for such a show you&amp;rsquo;ve personally been involved in for two years (both in acting and production) - and therefore already know the good/bad/ugly that comes with it. You …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mandarin Orange Creme Brulee
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-mandarin-orange-creme-brulee/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 04:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-mandarin-orange-creme-brulee/</guid>
        <description>Before we begin, a disclaimer: Satsumas, clementines, tangerines - basically any easy-peel citrus orange with easy to separate segments you can think of falls under the category of mandarin oranges. Think of it this way - all clementines are mandarin oranges, but not all mandarin oranges are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Some Like It Hot...well, not all
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-some-like-it-hotwell-not-all/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 11:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-some-like-it-hotwell-not-all/</guid>
        <description>It seems to have been quite a tumultuous year in foodie arena, with many food items under threat. Just this Halloween, fans of the global cult favourite Sriracha hot sauce (affectionately known as Rooster Sauce to some) breathed a sigh of relief when a judge denied a temporary restraining order …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Keeping up with the Engineers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-keeping-up-with-the-engineers/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 09:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lejon Chua,Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-keeping-up-with-the-engineers/</guid>
        <description>Integrating Engineers: the way to reviving the CGCU brand
Geeky punnery aside, the City and Guilds College Union (better known as the CGCU) has bounced back this year - having spent a good while in relative “CGC-who?” obscurity. With a fresh-faced committee in place working towards a unified theme - …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The self-catering cheatsheet
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-the-self-catering-cheatsheet/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 19:55:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Y K Chung,Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-the-self-catering-cheatsheet/</guid>
        <description>Understandably everyone reading this article will have a different view or preference/budget when it comes to eating or food shopping. Even within Carol’s household, the boys prefer to bag everything from Sainsbury’s (everything’s in one location), whereas she doesn’t mind scouring the North End …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What does Gousto mean?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-8-what-does-gousto-mean/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2013 03:17:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-8-what-does-gousto-mean/</guid>
        <description>It’s not everyday that the Felix Food crew gets to review something that was featured and acclaimed on BBC’s Dragons’ Den. Back in August I was trawling through FEAST at Batter- sea Park with the just-as-much-of-a- foodie (if not more) boyfriend (in fact Battersea was his idea, I was busy revising …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Here is The Plan
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-here-is-the-plan/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 00:07:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-here-is-the-plan/</guid>
        <description>Keep yourselves free on the 9th/10th of March – Imperial College Union Malaysian Society returns with Malaysian Night 2013, the annual production that’s been entertaining audiences across the UK for years. With great moves, great laughs, great music (and amazing food after!), it promises to be an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>So, what’s the big deal?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-so-whats-the-big-deal/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 00:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-so-whats-the-big-deal/</guid>
        <description>It’s easy to see why pasta is touted as reliable student grub. It’s relatively cheap, almost foolproof (RTFI, people – we’re Imperialites!) and doesn’t take ages. It’s flexible – you can make it a simple bolognese affair, or slap on a complex sauce and bake it in some mythical way passed down to you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cubby away with the Fox
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-cubby-away-with-the-fox/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 23:52:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-cubby-away-with-the-fox/</guid>
        <description>When you’re a new establishment issuing a challenge to been-around-the-block GBK by proclaiming you’ve got better burgers than they do – and offering punters the chance to play bartender with the first self-serve beer wall in the UK – you’re sure to set a few tongues wagging. Tucked away from busy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Lunchbox Lowdown #02
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-the-lunchbox-lowdown-02/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 01:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-the-lunchbox-lowdown-02/</guid>
        <description> Intro I‘m picking up where my fellow Editor Sophia left off last week. If you’re stuck in a sandwich/pie rut but you’re still aiming to pack lunches to keep your wallet and waistline in check, look East for some inspiration. The Japanese have long been the purveyors of colourful, varied and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What’s In My Lunchbox? #01
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-whats-in-my-lunchbox-01/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 22:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-whats-in-my-lunchbox-01/</guid>
        <description> Ah, winter. The season when just about everything seems to drop: temperatures, number of daylight hours, moods, hemlines (well, depending.) It’s around this time of the year when us Food Editors face a dilemma when packing our lunches – we need more warm/hot sustenance, so our fallback of sarnies …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Steakday, bloody steakday
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-steakday-bloody-steakday/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 02:48:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-steakday-bloody-steakday/</guid>
        <description>Here during the Halloween season, we’re more than happy to cater to all levels of “vampirism” – and by that, we mean we’re going to scrutinize how to cook the perfect beef steak.
First up, pick your pieces. We don’t discriminate on cut, but one thing we’re certainly picky about is quality. With …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What’s for breakfast?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-whats-for-breakfast/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 21:19:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-whats-for-breakfast/</guid>
        <description>You don’t need me to rehash that old cliché about breakfast being the most important meal of the day, seeing as it’s been nattered on enough. Some of you who skip breakfast might even want to stab my eyeballs for even bringing it up. However, for the majority of you who skimp on it because you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Twix Cheesecake Bites
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-twix-cheesecake-bites/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 22:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-twix-cheesecake-bites/</guid>
        <description>These are seriously decadent crowd-pleasers. I’ve made them twice for two group gatherings of different sizes – we’re talking at least 15 people, and they get snapped up quite nicely (the latter actually had 30-odd people!) They need a little bit of pre-planning and forethought, though; because …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Academics to boycott Elsevier journals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-academics-to-boycott-elsevier-journals/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 00:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-academics-to-boycott-elsevier-journals/</guid>
        <description>Following a damning blog post by Cambridge mathematician Professor Tim Gowers, nearly 3,000 academics have signed an online pledge to cease all work with Elsevier, a Dutch journal publishing house responsible for many publications including The Lancet.
Elsevier have come under frequent criticism for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Julia Buckingham steps down as Pro-Rector
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-julia-buckingham-steps-down-as-pro-rector/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 21:54:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-julia-buckingham-steps-down-as-pro-rector/</guid>
        <description>Professor Julia Buckingham, current Pro-Rector for Education and Academic Affairs at Imperial College London, has been appointed as the next Vice-Chancellor and Principal for Brunel University. The first woman to be appointed to this position at Brunel, she will assume duties from Professor Chris …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Abu Dhabi Diabetes Centre walk on
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-abu-dhabi-diabetes-centre-walk-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 22:07:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Carol Ann Cheah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-abu-dhabi-diabetes-centre-walk-on/</guid>
        <description>An annual walkathon to promote healthy living, jointly hosted by the Imperial College London Diabetes Centre (ICLDC) in Abu Dhabi and The National Health Insurance Company Daman, took place at the Yas Marina Circuit (the venue for the Abu Dhabi Grand Prix) on November 25. Walk For Life, which is now …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
