<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Live on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/tags/live/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Live on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/tags/live/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Queens of the Stone Age flex their muscles</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-queens-of-the-stone-age-flex-their-muscles/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Emily Freeman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-queens-of-the-stone-age-flex-their-muscles/</guid>
        <description>These people want you to be calm, but I don’t want you to be calm – I want you to take your fucking trousers off” lead singer Josh Homme’s Californian drawl crooned to the 20,000 strong crowd at the O2 Arena last Tuesday. Queens of the Stone Age, the legendary heavy rock band, embarked on the UK leg …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cory Henry brought the funk back to London last week</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-cory-henry-brought-the-funk-back-to-london-last-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Pearson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-cory-henry-brought-the-funk-back-to-london-last-week/</guid>
        <description>Hosted at KOKO, the venue’s atmosphere was perpendicular to that of the typical Friday night. An empty smoking area and non-sticky floors paid tribute to the multi-layered theater environment as an ideal place to host a gig (though drinks prices were unfortunately the same as any regular Saturday, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nai Palm lights up London with a killer solo set</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-nai-palm-lights-up-london-with-a-killer-solo-set/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Montgomerie-Corcoran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-nai-palm-lights-up-london-with-a-killer-solo-set/</guid>
        <description>For the first time London had Haitus Kyote’s lead singer, Nai Palm, at Koko to perform her own solo music in a night which defined her new direction with music. It was amazing just to see her on stage, and to finally hear her voice properly; she truly is one of the most impressive singers around …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Future Hndrxx Tour: an enjoyable, if not all that memorable, performance</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-future-hndrxx-tour-an-enjoyable-if-not-all-that-memorable-performance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-future-hndrxx-tour-an-enjoyable-if-not-all-that-memorable-performance/</guid>
        <description>In February, Atlanta rapper Future surprised fans by releasing his eponymous fifth studio album with little advance warning. FUTURE is a seventeen-track trap offering that went straight to number one in its first week. However, although Future’s fans were satisfied, Future was not. A mere seven days …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>St. John Sessions: Laurel Halo and Lee Gamble</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-st-john-sessions-laurel-halo-and-lee-gamble/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Lawrence,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-st-john-sessions-laurel-halo-and-lee-gamble/</guid>
        <description>Hyperdub is odd. It’s always been odd. But it has knitted itself so tightly into the fabric of London’s musical culture that when two of its artists play experimental sets in an 18th century church, it somehow feels perfectly natural.
I arrived at the St. John Church in Hackney to find a substantial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Hydra x Barbican present: Gas &#43; Huerco S.</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-the-hydra-x-barbican-present-gas-huerco-s/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joshua Lawrence,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-the-hydra-x-barbican-present-gas-huerco-s/</guid>
        <description>Another night, another gig. This time at the temple of austere, brutalist beauty that is the Barbican. If you’re a fan of ambient music, this venue is a must – the sculpted wood of the concert hall reverberates with thick, earthy noise, immersing and inducing you into a trance-like state. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>J. Cole’s 4 Your Eyez Only tour</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-j-cole-s-4-your-eyez-only-tour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-j-cole-s-4-your-eyez-only-tour/</guid>
        <description>J. Cole’s 4 Your Eyez Only tour touched down in London town early this week, with the Dreamville front man selling out two nights at the O2 Arena. Cole was supported by his labelmates Ari Lennox, EARTHGANG (whose recent Rags-EP is worth a listen and whose Robots EP drops on Friday), and J.I.D. (who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Slowdive prove to be worth the wait</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-slowdive-prove-to-be-worth-the-wait/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Hannah Cudmore,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-slowdive-prove-to-be-worth-the-wait/</guid>
        <description>It feels as fun, and as relevant playing together now as it did when we first started” said Slowdive’s Neil Halstead about their much-anticipated single ‘Star Roving’ upon its release in January. This was the band’s first new material in 22 years. Slowdive, a shoegaze band from Reading known for …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
