<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/tad08/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/tad08/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Eurovision Song Contest: The pop and the politics*
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-7-eurovision-song-contest-the-pop-and-the-politics/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 08:55:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-7-eurovision-song-contest-the-pop-and-the-politics/</guid>
        <description> I once had the misfortune of watching Eurovision with only an Argentinian, a Mexican, and a Lebanese for company. If you’re not European (or Australian, apparently), Eurovision seems to be very confusing and completely un-understandable. For us Europeans, either on the mainland or stuck on little …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Words can help us understand this
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-7-words-can-help-us-understand-this/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 08:44:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-7-words-can-help-us-understand-this/</guid>
        <description>Under the strain of thousands of people seeking refuge in Europe, several countries including Germany began to restrict their borders, after decades of free travel within the continent and the Schengen Area.
As a result, my well­ planned and advance booked night train from Vienna to Munich, being a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cyclists don’t follow the same rules
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-7-cyclists-dont-follow-the-same-rules/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 08:41:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-7-cyclists-dont-follow-the-same-rules/</guid>
        <description>New year, new you; the only time of the year when there’s a dramatic increase in the number of cyclists on the roads – with the exception of during tube strikes, that is. As a cyclist, there’s a definite sense of safety in numbers, and more people taking up this underrated method of getting around …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Abuse is not a valid comment
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-abuse-is-not-a-valid-comment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:45:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-abuse-is-not-a-valid-comment/</guid>
        <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been writing and editing Comment for felix for years, and it’s my strongly held opinion that a student newspaper without opinion is not a student newspaper worth having. University is a time when we’re all growing up, finding ourselves and forming our beliefs, and a huge part of this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to dump someone (you met in Metric and subsequently fell in love with)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-how-to-dump-someone-you-met-in-metric-and-subsequently-fell-in-love-with/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 16:16:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Theresa Davey,Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-how-to-dump-someone-you-met-in-metric-and-subsequently-fell-in-love-with/</guid>
        <description> You were weak. Despite our foolproof guides on how to have a one night stand (in Metric), ‘How to have a one night stand (in Metric)’, and how not to fall in love with someone (from Metric), ‘How not to fall in love with someone (from Metric)’, you went ahead and fell in love with someone (from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An ode to Shepherd&#39;s Bush
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-an-ode-to-shepherds-bush/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 14:59:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-an-ode-to-shepherds-bush/</guid>
        <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve lived in various places all over London over the last eight years, but I always come back to Shepherd’s Bush. It&amp;rsquo;s not the geographical convenience or the relative cheapness that keeps me there, it’s the fact that Shepherd’s Bush feels like home.
I feel at home on the Green, with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Manifesto breakdowns
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-manifesto-breakdowns/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:59:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,Cale E Tilford,Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-manifesto-breakdowns/</guid>
        <description> This piece aims to break down the main party manifestos and summarise a few key policies. This is by no means a full and in-depth analysis of each party. Mainly because the manifestos are long and complex, and it’s exam season. [Insert tinfoil hat theory that the timing of the election coincides …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In defence of being flaky
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-in-defence-of-being-flaky/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:25:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-in-defence-of-being-flaky/</guid>
        <description>Be honest, we all have that friend who’s a complete flake. You know, you make plans with them only to have them cancel at the last minute. Maybe this happens repeatedly. They’re really fucking annoying, right? Maybe you don’t even want to bother to reschedule. Maybe they’re so flaky that you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are we medicalising personality?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-are-we-medicalising-personality/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 12:55:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-are-we-medicalising-personality/</guid>
        <description>None of my friends from home have mental health problems. This is in small-town, rural Wales, where knowing about the wider world isn&amp;rsquo;t really a thing, and buzzwords like self-care and mindfulness might as well be in a totally different language, or are laughed at from behind a veneer of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why do we stigmatise abortion?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-why-do-we-stigmatise-abortion/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 17:42:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-why-do-we-stigmatise-abortion/</guid>
        <description>I haven’t had an abortion. In fact, I only know two people who have and they personally told me of it. One was a girl I went to school with, who had an abortion aged 15, and lost a lot of friends who had never realised they were pro-life until that moment. The other is my mother, who speaks about it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are millennials too entitled or do we just deserve better?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-are-millennials-too-entitled-or-do-we-just-deserve-better/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 15:52:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-are-millennials-too-entitled-or-do-we-just-deserve-better/</guid>
        <description>The media is obsessed with millennials being more entitled than previous generations, what with all those years of praise, encouragement, and social media. It’s a great rhetoric: we’re all narcissistic nightmares, who are too obsessed with our personal brand and too lazy to put our heads down and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pokémon Go on a bike
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-pokmon-go-on-a-bike/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 15:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-pokmon-go-on-a-bike/</guid>
        <description>Do you remember that blissful moment in Pokémon Red, when after walking around at a snail’s pace for so long, you finally could get your bike in Cerulean City and glide effortlessly down Cycling Road to Fuchsia City (or indeed, to anywhere)? No, you probably don’t because now it’s been a long time …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Love is the drug you can’t get enough of
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-love-is-the-drug-you-cant-get-enough-of/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-love-is-the-drug-you-cant-get-enough-of/</guid>
        <description> Let’s be real. Love is a drug. It inhibits our ability to think clearly, turns us into terrible people, and makes us do stupid things. Face it, it’s far more harmful than a few hours gurning at the weekend. But just like with drugs, there are different kinds of highs, and so now, in honour of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Postgraduate study is wrought with classist undertones
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-postgraduate-study-is-wrought-with-classist-undertones/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 14:37:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-postgraduate-study-is-wrought-with-classist-undertones/</guid>
        <description>The UK has a vast historic class divide – only those from the upper-middle classes who are in severe denial about our country would go so far as to say that class does not remain a huge cultural barrier today. Education has traditionally been something for the rich, and our modern higher education …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You&#39;re putting me off my food
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-youre-putting-me-off-my-food/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 15:46:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-youre-putting-me-off-my-food/</guid>
        <description>I have a complicated relationship with food. I think every fat person does. That isn’t to say I don’t also think that every woman or man who is impacted by the pressure of beauty standards also does – I do – but for a fat person it is subtly different. Being fat is the reason that we are perceived …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How not to fall in love with someone (from Metric)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-how-not-to-fall-in-love-with-someone-from-metric/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Theresa Davey,Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-how-not-to-fall-in-love-with-someone-from-metric/</guid>
        <description> This is a follow up to our piece ‘How to have a one night stand (in Metric)’. For those of you who somehow missed it, we provided a tried-and-tested plan of action designed to get you laid after a night in Metric. This plan was meant to get you in and out without leaving any trace. But expectedly, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Southern Rail need to get their shit together
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-southern-rail-need-to-get-their-shit-together/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-southern-rail-need-to-get-their-shit-together/</guid>
        <description>There were train strikes this week, you might have heard. No, not the tube strikes, they happen like once a year; you can take a bus for a day, get over yourself, no one cares. I’m talking about Southern Rail, whose staff are on strike for three days this week, causing a genuine total shutdown of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to build Hogwarts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-how-to-build-hogwarts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 16:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-how-to-build-hogwarts/</guid>
        <description> 2009 | The first gingerbread We weren’t ambitious. We built a cute little gingerbread house. It only took one batch of gingerbread and a few sweets for decoration, and it disappeared remarkably quickly. How things were to change!
2010 | The castle This took two whole batches of gingerbread. We …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The people who travel on long-distance buses are all freaks
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-the-people-who-travel-on-long-distance-buses-are-all-freaks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 15:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-the-people-who-travel-on-long-distance-buses-are-all-freaks/</guid>
        <description>There are three types of people who take overnight coaches: the stupid, those trying to fulfil a stereotype, and the desperate.
This seems like a bold statement, I know, but let me explain. You see, I fall into one of these categories (stupid, certainly), lured in by Megabus’ £11 ticket to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Girls Can do without Sport Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-imperial-girls-can-do-without-sport-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 14:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-imperial-girls-can-do-without-sport-imperial/</guid>
        <description>There are a lot of things that Imperial girls can do, including studying science and engineering, leading clubs and societies, and, presumably, going through adolescence, meaning that by the time we’re at Imperial, we’re probably women, not girls. But one area where we seem to be lacking, according …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why is fat-shaming the last socially acceptable form of discrimination?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-10-why-is-fat-shaming-the-last-socially-acceptable-form-of-discrimination/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 11:41:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-10-why-is-fat-shaming-the-last-socially-acceptable-form-of-discrimination/</guid>
        <description>Being fat is seen as the worst thing that a person can be. Fat is often synonymous with lazy, slovenly, unattractive, and unhealthy, and becomes a reason to deny someone any semblance of humanity – fat people aren’t seen as worthy.
But why are fat people so stigmatised in this way? Fat has a greater …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ten things I hate about you
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-7-ten-things-i-hate-about-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 17:32:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Theresa Davey,Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-7-ten-things-i-hate-about-you/</guid>
        <description> We’ve come to the end of Freshers’ Week, and maybe you’ve had a bit too much fun. We’ve all been there, made mistakes, and done things that we live to regret with the bad-boy (or girl) hall senior who seems so mature and experienced. Regardless of how, when, or why, many people all over Imperial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to blag your way through politics
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-how-to-blag-your-way-through-politics/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 18:47:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-how-to-blag-your-way-through-politics/</guid>
        <description> Are you more won’t than woke when it comes to talking politics? Do you despair at any mention of David Cameron, tremble at the thought of Theresa May, or cower away from Corbyn?
Difficult grown-up conversations will inevitably occur during freshers’ week as you all try and convince your peers that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let me and Beyoncé feel our feelings
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-let-me-and-beyonc-feel-our-feelings/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:11:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-let-me-and-beyonc-feel-our-feelings/</guid>
        <description>A couple of months ago, I wrote an open letter in Felix. It was directed at my very recent ex-boyfriend, and in it I attempted to verbalise the pain I felt and some of the things I realised in the wake of our breakup. It wasn’t something that I wrote originally with the intention of publishing it in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A letter to...the man who broke my heart
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-a-letter-tothe-man-who-broke-my-heart/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 11:42:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-a-letter-tothe-man-who-broke-my-heart/</guid>
        <description>This article was published as part of FELIX&amp;rsquo;s Sex Survey launch. Do the survey here.
I learnt so much from you.
You taught me how to love like I’ve never loved before. You taught me how to cry more than I’ve ever cried before. You taught me how to voice my opinions, to argue, to debate. You …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The elections are a popularity contest
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-the-elections-are-a-popularity-contest/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 11:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-the-elections-are-a-popularity-contest/</guid>
        <description>Year on year, students put themselves forward as candidates for leadership positions in the Union because they feel strongly that things need to change, and they think that their ideas and their drive can help implement that. They campaign, putting their faces and ideas out there, and, in the case …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>12 Jar Jar Binks GIFs That Sum Up Your Life At Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-16-12-jar-jar-binks-gifs-that-sum-up-your-life-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 18:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,Felix Editor,Theresa Davey,Grace G Rahman,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-16-12-jar-jar-binks-gifs-that-sum-up-your-life-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description> 1. When You Arrive Sober At Your First ACC  2. When You Sit Your First Exam At Imperial    Tumblr   3. When You Can&amp;rsquo;t Decide Between Pieminister And The Salad Bar    Tumblr   4. When You Fall For Your Lab Partner    Tumblr   5. When It&amp;rsquo;s Five To Nine And You&amp;rsquo;re Desperate For The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bond leaves feminists shaken not stirred
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-bond-leaves-feminists-shaken-not-stirred/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 13:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-bond-leaves-feminists-shaken-not-stirred/</guid>
        <description>Last week, along with half the country, I decided to brave the crowded cinemas to see the newest James Bond film, Spectre. Some have described Spectre as gratuitous, but I thought that it was fantastic, both in terms of the cinematography, and the primal enjoyment in watching people get beaten to a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nigeria bans FGM, but how much still needs to change?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-12-nigeria-bans-fgm-but-how-much-still-needs-to-change/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2015 12:35:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-12-nigeria-bans-fgm-but-how-much-still-needs-to-change/</guid>
        <description>Female genital mutilation (FGM) has been performed on more than 130 million women and girls worldwide, and more than 20,000 girls under the age of 15 in the UK are considered at risk. It is often done using razors, sharpened rocks, glass or even fingernails as tools.
The partial or total removal of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why is it so taboo to be Tory?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-14-why-is-it-so-taboo-to-be-tory/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 22:35:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-14-why-is-it-so-taboo-to-be-tory/</guid>
        <description>The General Election has come and gone, and the United Kingdom has democratically elected the Conservative Party into power for the next five years. 36.9% of the country voted for them, but if you look at the articles being plastered all over the internet and social media, you would have no idea …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Plus-size fashion need not be boring and unadventurous
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-plus-size-fashion-need-not-be-boring-and-unadventurous/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 12:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-plus-size-fashion-need-not-be-boring-and-unadventurous/</guid>
        <description>It’s safe to say that the world of plus-size fashion is rapidly accelerating at an unprecedented rate. It’s not difficult to see why. Over the last few decades the average size of women (and men) has increased, and regardless of the reasons why they’re getting larger, people still need clothes.
So …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pioneers of Plus-Size
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-pioneers-of-plus-size/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 12:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-pioneers-of-plus-size/</guid>
        <description>Tess Munster, also known as Tess Holliday, has recently become the largest model ever to be signed to a major modelling agency, MiLK Model Management. Her size being a UK 22-24, and 5’5”, she describes herself as a “body-positive activist”, and is most well known for her #effyourbeautystandards …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Favourite Musician: Taylor Swift
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-my-favourite-musician-taylor-swift/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 11:49:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-my-favourite-musician-taylor-swift/</guid>
        <description>Anyone who knows me will know that I have a particular penchant for Taylor Swift.
Whether I’m posting new Swifty (while I realise that Swiftie is the tumblr-accepted spelling, I prefer it with a y, okay?) videos on people’s walls on Facebook with overexcited captions, OMG!!!1! ITS SO GOOD I DIDNT …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is Imperial changing for the better?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-is-imperial-changing-for-the-better/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 18:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-is-imperial-changing-for-the-better/</guid>
        <description>I’ve been at Imperial for seven years, which is quite a long time – longer than most. In that time, I’ve seen a lot of change. Some of these changes are ones I never imagined happening, like the loss of Evelyn Gardens, which was my home as a fresher, but they’re mostly overwhelmingly positive. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Should we boycott Fifty Shades of Grey?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-19-should-we-boycott-fifty-shades-of-grey/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2015 23:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-19-should-we-boycott-fifty-shades-of-grey/</guid>
        <description>Fifty Shades of Grey has opened the door for us to talk about sex candidly and honestly in a way that has never been done before, something that can only be a good thing. People are more open to discussing their desires and fantasies than ever, with millions of people exploring new sensations, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why all the fuss about Charlie Hebdo?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-16-why-all-the-fuss-about-charlie-hebdo/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 13:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-16-why-all-the-fuss-about-charlie-hebdo/</guid>
        <description>The news over the past week has been dominated by stories about the terrorist attacks in Paris, killing 17 people, with the satirical magazine Charlie Hebdo among the targets. Also reported, but to a far lesser extent, are attacks by Boko Haram extremists in Baga, Nigeria, resulting in thousands of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is Bob Geldof’s Band Aid out of touch?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-20-is-bob-geldofs-band-aid-out-of-touch/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 21:23:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-20-is-bob-geldofs-band-aid-out-of-touch/</guid>
        <description>Aside from the fact that it makes me feel old (It can’t have been ten years since the last one, I remember that coming out when I was doing my GCSEs&amp;hellip;), I have more problems with Band Aid and the song, ‘Do They Know It’s Christmas’ than I can possibly keep straight. Of course, there’s as big a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is it bad to be &#34;All About That Bass&#34;?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-24-is-it-bad-to-be-all-about-that-bass/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2014 13:16:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-24-is-it-bad-to-be-all-about-that-bass/</guid>
        <description>Meghan Trainor’s super-catchy ‘All About That Bass’ has been “getting flak” (as she puts it) from all angles, from people of all walks of life, all of whom seem to have something to say about this seemingly body-positive bubblegum pop song.
With the number of people jumping on the bandwagon of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Six Nations Round Up
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-six-nations-round-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 15:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonathan Pratt,Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-six-nations-round-up/</guid>
        <description> Six Nations: The Verdict In the aftermath of one of the most poetic endings to the Six Nations yet, familiar foes Jonny Pratt and Tessa Davey give their verdict on the best, and worst, of the Six Nations
JONNY&amp;rsquo;S WINNERS AND LOSERS
Player of the Tournament
Mike Brown
Try of the tournament
Rob …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In defence of Justin Bieber
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-in-defence-of-justin-bieber/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 17:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-in-defence-of-justin-bieber/</guid>
        <description>I love Justin Bieber. There, I said it, I outed myself as a Belieber. I am a self-confessed fan of The Biebs. I know that this proclamation generally elicits a fairly strong reaction, but let me defend this view before you cast me out to the place where Directioners go to die.
So I’ll start with his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to procrastinate at Christmas
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-how-to-procrastinate-at-christmas/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 04:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-how-to-procrastinate-at-christmas/</guid>
        <description>As a student at Imperial, the lead up to Christmas can seem like one of the busiest times of the year, a feeling compounded by the multitude of seasonal events that you just have to go to. No matter how overwhelmed you’re feeling, there are always some parties that you will just refuse to miss, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Saudi Arabia: Is driving a human right?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-4-saudi-arabia-is-driving-a-human-right/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 13:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-4-saudi-arabia-is-driving-a-human-right/</guid>
        <description>I’ve always been in love with driving. In school, when I was learning to drive, my Physics teacher told me that he wished that we were in Saudi Arabia, where women are banned from driving, because then at least I’d shut up about it in his lessons. I remember being outraged to learn this, and it’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tessa’s Top Ten Tips for Graduation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-20-tessas-top-ten-tips-for-graduation/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 02:38:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-20-tessas-top-ten-tips-for-graduation/</guid>
        <description>Commemoration Day at Imperial is pretty well labelled, signposted and explained, and it’s pretty difficult to fail to do any of the essential parts. But as with anything else, it’s good to be aware of any potential stumbling blocks so that you can streamline your day. And so as a voice of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Royal Conspiracy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-18-my-royal-conspiracy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 21:39:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-18-my-royal-conspiracy/</guid>
        <description>Kensington Palace finally revealed last week that the mysterious VVIP guest who’s attending the grand opening of the “new” Centre for Blast Injury Studies is none other than my favourite eligible bachelor, Prince Harry. As part of the opening, they’re holding a Network Event, a day full of talks …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Freshers&#39; Week: The great equaliser
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-freshers-week-the-great-equaliser/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 00:49:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-freshers-week-the-great-equaliser/</guid>
        <description>I’ve had a pretty typical freshers week. I’ve attended about a million welcome talks that go along the lines of “You’re the best. You’re going to have to work fucking hard. But YOLO!” I’ve spent days without a swipe card, struggling to tailgate into every building, because I’m avoiding the queue at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let the world hear your voice sing
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-let-the-world-hear-your-voice-sing/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 13:55:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-let-the-world-hear-your-voice-sing/</guid>
        <description>It’s not just the stories making international headlines that are important to Imperial students. As well as giving different viewpoints on current events, Comment showcases any other issues that are significant to your life. Whether you think that the food in the JCR is actually pretty good, or you …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
