<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/miles_gulliford/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/miles_gulliford/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>A Brief History of Jazz </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-brief-history-jazz/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-brief-history-jazz/</guid>
        <description>By the time this newspaper came into existence, jazz was already old – or at least middle aged. Louis Armstrong had defined improvisation, swing had already been and gone, replaced by frantic bebop, cool jazz and eventually fusion. Genres like rock and soul had begun to rear their heads, offshoots …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FKA Twigs - Live</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-FKA-twigs-live/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-FKA-twigs-live/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
FKA twigs’ gig didn’t start until 9:30, by which point a large portion of the audience frustrated, having waited for over 2 hours. The curtains raised bit by bit, riling the crowd further. “This show had better be good” muttered someone behind me, thankfully, it was.
Twigs’ vocals were …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Two New Tunes for You</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-two-new-tunes-for-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-two-new-tunes-for-you/</guid>
        <description>Last month LA based Funk group The Pendletons released their debut LP: 2 Steps Away. A delightful blend of tight grooves, thick bass and slick 70’s-style horn sections. The record as a whole draws heavily on its funk and disco influences, with a distrincly vintage compositional style, still taking …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FKA Twigs Makes Album - is Good</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-fka-twigs-makes-album-is-good/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-fka-twigs-makes-album-is-good/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
Tahliah Barnett, aka FKA Twigs quickly rose from ‘Video Girl’ to adored songstress in the mid 10’s, earning critical acclaim and a cult following from a series of releases including her 2014 record LP1. Here, atmospheric synthesisers and industrial drums left plenty of space for Twig’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>JESUS... This Record is Disappointing</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-jesus-this-record-disappointing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-jesus-this-record-disappointing/</guid>
        <description>1.5 stars
Kanye West needs no introduction. By the time this is published he will undoubtedly have kicked up a fresh onslaught of headlines that even dedicated fans must be jaded with at this point. In other news, research suggests that narcissists are more likely to be successful than people with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tammy and the T-Rex</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-tammy-t-rex/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-tammy-t-rex/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
Two years ago, a friend of mine first introduced me to Tammy and the T-Rex: “Dinosaurs? Romance? On YouTube?” I thought to myself. “This is too good to be true”.It was not.
We spent the next hour and a half watching Stewart Raffill’s incredible brainchild, a memory I recall with great …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Danny Brown Lets Us Down</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-danny-brown-lets-us-down/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-danny-brown-lets-us-down/</guid>
        <description>3 stars
Danny Brown has become something of a legend of the underground hip-hop circuit this decade, with the ability to rhyme almost anything, an imppecable wit and a penchant for insane beats. On epic albums like XXX and Atrocity Exhibition Brown explores his lifestyle as a drug dealer-turned drug …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fresh tracks!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-fresh-tracks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-fresh-tracks/</guid>
        <description>Lapalux laid the foundation of his discography on glitchy, rough, and voided ambient sounds. While not considered “experimental”, his style certainly didn’t draw in the more mainstream crowds. However, his most recent release demonstrates a calmer and more collected direction. This track is supposed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kendrick vs Kendrick: To Pimp A Butterfly or good kid m.A.A.d city?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-kendrick-vs-kendrick-to-pimp-a-butterfly-or-good-kid-m-a-a-d-city/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-kendrick-vs-kendrick-to-pimp-a-butterfly-or-good-kid-m-a-a-d-city/</guid>
        <description>Ten years ago today, the name Kendrick Lamar meant no more than anyone else’s. The now 31-year-old rapper was still going by K-Dot and would shortly receive a career-changing cosign from Lil Wayne. Today he is one of the best known and certainly most respected artists in music. With twelve Grammys …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>James Blake’s Assume Form doesn’t quite take shape</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-james-blake-s-assume-form-doesn-t-quite-take-shape/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-james-blake-s-assume-form-doesn-t-quite-take-shape/</guid>
        <description>With production for names including Kendrick Lamar, Travis Scott and Oneohtrix Point Never under his belt in 2018 one would expect Blake’s 4th effort to sound sublime, but after a few listens you might wonder if perhaps he’s spreading himself too thin. Whilst there is a lot on Assume Form to enjoy, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Earl Sweatshirt’s back at it with some rap songs</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-earl-sweatshirt-s-back-at-it-with-some-rap-songs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-earl-sweatshirt-s-back-at-it-with-some-rap-songs/</guid>
        <description>With his critically acclaimed debut Earl dropping at just 16, Thebe Kgositsile has a strong claim to the familiarity with his audience the title of his latest release - Some Rap Songs presumes. With a 24 minute run time (admittedly less surprising in 2018) and eerily blurred selfie as its cover, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Courtney Barnett tells us how she really feels</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-courtney-barnett-tells-us-how-she-really-feels/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-courtney-barnett-tells-us-how-she-really-feels/</guid>
        <description>Courtney Barnett has been crafting witty, mid-paced indie gems for half a decade; on a mild Wednesday evening she treated Brixton to a well-deserved outing of her latest material. After an all-Australian warm up roster, featuring the three-guitar jangle-juggernaut that is Rolling Blackouts Coastal …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
