<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ea3211/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ea3211/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>College gets collection points for Grenfell Tower fire victims
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-college-gets-collection-points-for-grenfell-tower-fire-victims/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:49:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-college-gets-collection-points-for-grenfell-tower-fire-victims/</guid>
        <description>Following the fire that engulfed Grenfell Tower in the early hours last Wednesday, claiming 17 lives and injuring many more, some critically, Imperial College set up clothes and bedding donation points at the main entrance to the South Kensington campus and in White City at the Gradpad Wood Lane …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It doesn&#39;t matter if you&#39;re queer or not, you need to support Gay Pride
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-it-doesnt-matter-if-youre-queer-or-not-you-need-to-support-gay-pride/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:43:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-it-doesnt-matter-if-youre-queer-or-not-you-need-to-support-gay-pride/</guid>
        <description>It doesn’t matter if you’re queer or not. You need to support Gay Pride.
It’s that rainbow month of the year again, when queers all around the world take to the streets to celebrate being alive and every bigoted dickhead gets the opportunity to rant about how they “don’t mind The Gays but do they …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>So long... and thank you for all the fish
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-so-long-and-thank-you-for-all-the-fish/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:25:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-so-long-and-thank-you-for-all-the-fish/</guid>
        <description>It’s the final issue. I’ve ranted for some 28 editions now and you guys have taken it like champs. In my last editorial I’d like to say one final thing before I fade into irrelevance. I want to talk about complaining.
I’m a great complainer. I bitch and moan about everything. I quit an online …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What a week
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-what-a-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:21:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-what-a-week/</guid>
        <description>What a week. Since last Friday, shit has hit the fan. Much like an evil mastermind in a superhero movie, Donald Trump has announced to the world his evil plan to fuck over the planet: quitting the Paris Agreement. The only differences are that he’s as thick (but slightly more orange) as mustard, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>(1) 666 number of the beast
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-1-666-number-of-the-beast/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:19:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-1-666-number-of-the-beast/</guid>
        <description>Fun fact: we originally had big plans for issue 1666. We were gonna do a ‘pagan issue’ dedicated to religion, with a graphic illustration of the Devil splashed across the front cover. But then in April, May announced a snap general election and we were like ‘God damn’. We forfeited the pagan issue …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Summer lovin’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-summer-lovin/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:15:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-summer-lovin/</guid>
        <description>Summer is officially here. You can tell by the hoards of panting students waiting to get served at FiveSixEight. You can also tell because felix has succumbed to society’s pressures and has dropped to half its original weight in preparation for the beach. For real though yesterday was so hot I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is news?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-what-is-news/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:13:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-what-is-news/</guid>
        <description>In fact let’s go deeper. What is a newspaper? If it’s a publication propelled by the propagation of news to its readers, then let me tell you; you’re in for a treat because this is the newsiest, newspaper we’ve ever made. I’m obviously referring to the twelve page (centrefold included) sex survey …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Divest this
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-divest-this/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:10:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-divest-this/</guid>
        <description>Is Imperial morally bankrupt? I first asked myself this question in 2011 when I started my Biology undergraduate. My department had just sacked most, if not all of its plant scientists. There was no money in the field. Have I come close to an answer since? Maybe. Sometimes I’ve looked at Imperial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We’re back. Pitches?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-were-back-pitches/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:06:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-were-back-pitches/</guid>
        <description>Yay! The Easter break is over! Yay&amp;hellip;”
Lef suddenly stopped typing, an overwhelming feeling of sadness taking over him. He thought of all those hours he’d idly spent in bed, no stupid print deadlines, no stupid paper distribution cutting his sleep short. He thought of all that nutritious …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Memememememememe
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-memememememememe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:57:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-memememememememe/</guid>
        <description>Chill. Happy thoughts. Breathe in, breathe out. This issue is about self-care, which ideally would have involved me taking a holiday and getting my tan on, maybe on a small, secluded beach in the Canary Islands. But obviously I can’t just leave you guys hanging. How are you supposed to do the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My manifesto
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-my-manifesto/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:55:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-my-manifesto/</guid>
        <description>Hello everyone. My name is Lef. Some of you might know me from my reign of terror as felix editor. Others might have spotted me making short sustenance runs to the union or the JCR (dem buns tho&amp;hellip;) and might have admired my luscious locks or strong eye-liner game. Regardless of your …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Elections should be fun
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-elections-should-be-fun/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:52:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-elections-should-be-fun/</guid>
        <description>Let’s be honest. Everything we do, we do in the name of fun. Sure you can use fancy lingo, such as pleasure, satisfaction, gratification, joy, and even gusto if you’re that kind of person, but at the end of the day, fun does the trick just fine.
The reason we make babies is because sex is fun. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Going green is hard
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-going-green-is-hard/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:50:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-going-green-is-hard/</guid>
        <description>Oh my god this issue is so green. SO GREEN I TELL YOU. Just reading it will make you healthier and add at least one year to your sad, Imperial-stunted life. You might wonder why. You might even vocally ask me on the off chance you spot me outdoors “why are you doing a Green Issue Lef? Caring about …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Love is love
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-love-is-love/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:47:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-love-is-love/</guid>
        <description>February is LGBT history month (yes, I know – I only just found out too) and my heart is filled with joy because for the first time ever I’m actually clued up. I also feel more a part of the queer community than I’ve ever felt before. I can’t really explain why, but it is what it is and I’m glad, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Feeeeeeeeeed meeeeeeee
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-feeeeeeeeeed-meeeeeeee/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:45:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-feeeeeeeeeed-meeeeeeee/</guid>
        <description>This issue is quite clearly dedicated to food. Whether you eat it, throw it up, get high on it, or get down and dirty with it (hey, we don’t judge) food is a fundamental part of the human existence. We carefully selected this week to talk about food, because Eating Disorder Awareness Week is coming …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Resistance is not futile. We think.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-resistance-is-not-futile-we-think/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:40:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-resistance-is-not-futile-we-think/</guid>
        <description>Well we honestly tried – you know, taking a break from the doom and gloom. With the end of 2016, we were eager to turn over a new leaf, start anew with starry eyes full of hope for the future. But since Trump’s inauguration last Friday, it’s just been an onslaught of bad news, dumb news, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hang in there kitties
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-hang-in-there-kitties/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:35:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-hang-in-there-kitties/</guid>
        <description>Blue Monday, alternatively known as the most depressing day of the year, came and went this week (Blue like hands without gloves flaunted at passing strangers on the street. Wait what?). By now you’ve come to terms with the fact that you probably spent way too much money over Christmas. You’ve also …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The post new year’s blues
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-post-new-years-blues/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:29:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-post-new-years-blues/</guid>
        <description>One of my friends recently pointed out I’m going through a quarter-life crisis, that we (our group of friends) all are. And I can see where he’s coming from. We’re all in our mid-twenties and we seem to permanently be at a crossroads. Transcending from adolescence into adulthood (it’s… a process) – …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>felix navidad
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-felix-navidad/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:24:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-felix-navidad/</guid>
        <description>It’s beginning to look a lot like Christmas. The tube is packed, the streets are clogged, shopping is a nightmare, and you keep embarrassing yourself, blurting out family secrets at dinners, to people you barely know.
Meanwhile, there are all these fake gifts everywhere: stupid, empty, gift-wrapped …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My head hurts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-my-head-hurts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:21:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-my-head-hurts/</guid>
        <description>This is a very special editorial, a very special issue even. Partly because I started writing it after smacking my head on the cold, hard asphalt just past Kensington Gardens (I know it looks cool to have your flowy hair trailing behind you as you cycle, but don’t do it kids. Don’t cycle without a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We’re almost there
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-were-almost-there/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:18:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-were-almost-there/</guid>
        <description>Another week, another quality paper. The holidays are fast approaching, and let me tell you I cannot wait. For a glorious three weeks I will not have to work like a madman and I can catch up on all the Westworld I’ve missed, and go through my inbox, print all my unread mail, put it in little …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The lady doth protest too much
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-lady-doth-protest-too-much/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:16:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-lady-doth-protest-too-much/</guid>
        <description>Warning: I’m really tired, I have a million things to do including packing a suitcase for a weekend escape (yay me), and this editorial has been a pain in the butt to write. So prepare yourself for some really wishy washy stuff, cause I’m on course to work 54 hours this week and at this point I just …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We’ve all got daddy issues
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-weve-all-got-daddy-issues/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:13:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-weve-all-got-daddy-issues/</guid>
        <description>Change is in the air. Imperial College has taken up recommendations to improve student satisfaction made by the Union, the Higher Education and Research Bill has just been amended, an education demo is taking place in London this weekend, and Donald Trump’s backtracking behaviour has captured the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It happened
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-it-happened/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 15:11:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-it-happened/</guid>
        <description>The dreaded day has come and gone. The world has changed. Donald Trump is a democratically elected world leader. I don’t think I’ve processed the tangible reality of the above sentence quite yet (and what a sentence: four years, eight years, or life?).
The man who inflamed an already polarised …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I’ve had it
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-ive-had-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 14:49:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-ive-had-it/</guid>
        <description>Three weeks in and I have nearly had it. Don’t get me wrong, editing a major cough newspaper is fun but it is exhausting. On Wednesday, I got an email from the printers at 19:51, ten minutes before leaving the office which wrote: “Hi Lef, If you run into trouble tonight pls call my home number on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Post freshers’ blues
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-post-freshers-blues/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 14:46:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-post-freshers-blues/</guid>
        <description>So. Here we are once again, two weeks in a row. One more week and it will have become an unhealthy habit, like smoking, binge-watching Netflix, or reassuming the leadership of UKIP.
This week everything sucks. For starters we’ve all got freshers’ flu, passing it on like a joint at a house party (the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to dump someone (you met in Metric and subsequently fell in love with)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-how-to-dump-someone-you-met-in-metric-and-subsequently-fell-in-love-with/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 16:16:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Theresa Davey,Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-how-to-dump-someone-you-met-in-metric-and-subsequently-fell-in-love-with/</guid>
        <description> You were weak. Despite our foolproof guides on how to have a one night stand (in Metric), ‘How to have a one night stand (in Metric)’, and how not to fall in love with someone (from Metric), ‘How not to fall in love with someone (from Metric)’, you went ahead and fell in love with someone (from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Keeping Track of Imperial’s Cross Country &amp; Athletics Club
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-keeping-track-of-imperials-cross-country-athletics-club/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:42:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-keeping-track-of-imperials-cross-country-athletics-club/</guid>
        <description>Saturday the 27th of May saw the final event in the London Universities and Colleges Athletics (LUCA) outdoors championship take place. The series of three athletics meets between the London universities had previously visited St. Mary’s and Woodford athletics tracks, and the destination for the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Ode to Sense8
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-an-ode-to-sense8/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:11:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-an-ode-to-sense8/</guid>
        <description>Three weeks ago I embarked on an emotional binge-watch of the 2015 Netflix original Sense8. Within two weeks I’d managed to watch the 23 near hour-long episodes of the first two seasons. Then a week later it was announced that sense8 would not be getting renewed, that episode 23 would be the last …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Diesel pollution poses serious risk for asthma sufferers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-diesel-pollution-poses-serious-risk-for-asthma-sufferers/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:00:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Rachel Baxter,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-diesel-pollution-poses-serious-risk-for-asthma-sufferers/</guid>
        <description>Forty million British people are living in cities and towns with illegally high air pollution levels. This alarming statistic is in part due to diesel exhaust, which according to new research can directly affect our lungs and make respiratory conditions worse.
An international team of scientists led …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union awards ceremony honours volunteers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-union-awards-ceremony-honours-volunteers/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 14:51:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-union-awards-ceremony-honours-volunteers/</guid>
        <description>Monday saw the Union thank its volunteers at the annual Union Awards.
During the event, which is meant to showcase the best of Imperial College Union and its membership, 69 (wink) students were awarded colours, a further 19 were awarded outstanding service and a final five students were given …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Consent Matters pilot launched
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-consent-matters-pilot-launched/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 14:49:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-consent-matters-pilot-launched/</guid>
        <description>Two terms since consent training became a subject of contention amongst Imperial students, the Consent Matters pilot has finally been launched. Consent Matters is an interactive course aiming at educating students on areas of sexual consent, communication and relationships, and bystander …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial academics on Trump and climate
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-imperial-academics-on-trump-and-climate/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 14:48:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-imperial-academics-on-trump-and-climate/</guid>
        <description>Last week Trump declared to the world that he’d be pulling the US out of the Paris Agreement. Within hours, Elon Musk resigned from the President’s Board of Advisors, American states such as California went rogue and protested the move, vouching to uphold their commitment anyway, and world leaders …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Party candidates come to Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-party-candidates-come-to-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:50:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-party-candidates-come-to-imperial/</guid>
        <description>A hustings of local parliamentary candidates was held yesterday in Blackett which saw Victoria Borwick (Conservatives), Cllr Alan De’Ath (Labour), Bridget Fox (LibDems), Richard Braine (UKIP), and finally Bill Cashmore (Green), engaging in a debate on Education, Public Health and Brexit.
Borwick, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Afterhours sessions in the Central Library
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-afterhours-sessions-in-the-central-library/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:29:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-afterhours-sessions-in-the-central-library/</guid>
        <description>How does one end up in the Library past midnight? Maybe you had a paper to submit tomorrow. You thought you had everything under control. You were halfway there but you made the mistake of taking a break and committing to an episode of the Great British Bake Off. Six hours later you get a text from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College increases security in wake of Manchester attack
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-college-increases-security-in-wake-of-manchester-attack/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 12:48:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-college-increases-security-in-wake-of-manchester-attack/</guid>
        <description>In a statement sent out by President Alice Gast and Provost James Stirling, Imperial students and staff were told that there will now be an increased presence of security at College’s campuses.
This announcement comes two days after 22 people were killed and dozens were injured at an Ariana Grande …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Central Library air-con cost £11m
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-central-library-air-con-cost-11m/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 12:47:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-central-library-air-con-cost-11m/</guid>
        <description>It might have taken a freedom of information request but we found out how much the new Central Library air-con is going to cost. And while we were at it we thought we’d ask for the cost of every single refurbishment the Library has undergone since 2004. Because nobody keeps secrets from felix (and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mentality launches new survey
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-mentality-launches-new-survey/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 12:46:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-mentality-launches-new-survey/</guid>
        <description>Two years after its launch, Mentality is conducting another survey to gain insight into stress and mental health at Imperial. The survey will close at the end of June, with results expected to be published by the end of term. According to Mentality chair Ariana Sadr-Hashemi, the previous report …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>EEE Library to close at the end of term
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-eee-library-to-close-at-the-end-of-term/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 12:45:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-eee-library-to-close-at-the-end-of-term/</guid>
        <description>The Electrical and Electronic Engineering library, one of only a handful of departmental libraries remaining in the South Ken Campus, will be turned into a study space over the course of the summer. Departmental Facilities Manager for the EEE department, Andy Paice told felix that following …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Engineering dominates Imperial awards
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-engineering-dominates-imperial-awards/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 12:44:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-engineering-dominates-imperial-awards/</guid>
        <description>The Union honoured Imperial staff last week at the annual Student Academic Choice Awards (SACAs for short) after sifting through a record breaking 831 nominations. The ceremony saw eight humans of Imperial getting recognised for their contributions in teaching.
Categories include supervision, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Election hustings to take place at Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-election-hustings-to-take-place-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 12:25:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-election-hustings-to-take-place-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Imperial will be hosting general election hustings on the 1st of June, inviting five speakers representing the Conservatives, Labour, UKIP, Lib Dems and Greens. Speakers were selected by picking the constituencies in which the most Imperial students live (Hammersmith, Kensington and the Cities of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mental health related drop-outs on the rise
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-mental-health-related-drop-outs-on-the-rise/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 12:23:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-mental-health-related-drop-outs-on-the-rise/</guid>
        <description>In only five years, the number of students who have dropped out from higher education has quadrupled according to data from the Higher Education Statistics Agency (HESA). The findings which were highlighted earlier last week by the Guardian, show that just in 2014-15 a record 1,180 students …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fuelling the resistance
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-19-fuelling-the-resistance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 15:03:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Naomi Pratt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-19-fuelling-the-resistance/</guid>
        <description>The greatest obstacle to action on climate change is the one most often missing from discourse: the fossil fuel industry. Since comprehension of anthropogenic global warming began, the fossil fuel industry has been ignored in negotiations and subsidised by governments. Much time and energy has been …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union to do more for freedom of speech
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-19-union-to-do-more-for-freedom-of-speech/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 15:00:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-19-union-to-do-more-for-freedom-of-speech/</guid>
        <description>The Union is moving towards taking a stronger stance on Freedom of Speech. Over the past few months a conversation has begun around the role of Imperial College Union in supporting students’ freedom of speech. The question of “Are we doing enough to promote dialogue and debate?” lies at the centre …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UCL leaks paper, finds out after exam
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-19-ucl-leaks-paper-finds-out-after-exam/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 14:59:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-19-ucl-leaks-paper-finds-out-after-exam/</guid>
        <description>Turns out Imperial isn’t the only London uni to routinely fuck up exams, neither is it the worst at it. Last week at UCL a mechanical engineering exam had to be rescheduled after the department realised it had accidentally leaked the paper.
Students were contacted by their department a day after …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Madama butterfly | A non-opera-goer&#39;s review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-madama-butterfly-a-non-opera-goers-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 16:21:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-madama-butterfly-a-non-opera-goers-review/</guid>
        <description>The Royal Opera House’s Madama Butterfly is a modern take on the operatic classic that showcases a jaw-dropping performance from Ermonela Jaho. Despite this, the newest rendition of Puccini’s ‘ode’ to Japan doesn’t quite pack the punch it needs to drag the piece out of its orientalist past.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Divestment Campaign resurrected
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-imperial-divestment-campaign-resurrected/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 17:05:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-imperial-divestment-campaign-resurrected/</guid>
        <description>The divestment campaigners at Imperial are on the move again. This week saw them taking to campus with various events and actions. On Wednesday students dropped a banner off the main union building in Beit Quad. The banner which wrote out in large black and orange letters “IMPERIAL DIVEST NOW!” was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bioengineering lecturer accidentally shares exam paper with students
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-bioengineering-lecturer-accidentally-shares-exam-paper-with-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 16:51:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-bioengineering-lecturer-accidentally-shares-exam-paper-with-students/</guid>
        <description>Last week a lecturer accidentally shared an upcoming exam paper with their first-year bioengineering students.
The unfortunate gaffe occurred during a revision lecture for Molecules, Cells and Processes. During the lecture, a student had a question that was not covered in the section of the revision …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union reels in £34,000 from Postgrad Graduation Day
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-union-reels-in-34000-from-postgrad-graduation-day/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 16:48:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-union-reels-in-34000-from-postgrad-graduation-day/</guid>
        <description>Remember last week’s postgrad graduation day? It made the Union of ton of dough. The largest graduation ceremony to date which saw a record of 9,400 guests attend, brought Union shops and outlets a total of £34,715. That’s about 13 grand more than last year and eight grand more than the record year …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mascotry saga draws to an end
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-mascotry-saga-draws-to-an-end/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 16:30:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-mascotry-saga-draws-to-an-end/</guid>
        <description>It only took about a year but the ‘heated’ topic of mascotry conduct seems to have finally been put to rest. Sort of. During the final council meeting of the spring term, the reworked mascotry paper was almost successfully passed. Almost, because following a mass exodus after the presentation of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>SPA awards shortlist announced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-spa-awards-shortlist-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 16:28:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-spa-awards-shortlist-announced/</guid>
        <description>UPDATE: We didn&amp;rsquo;t win anything, there is no god, and everything sucks
April saw felix getting shortlisted for four Student Publication Association Awards last month, with Editor Lef Apostolakis and Comment Editor/Millennials Queen/felix Vice Chair/Office Legend Tessa Davey each garnering two …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NUS votes in new president | NAS endorses candidate
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-nus-votes-in-new-president-nas-endorses-candidate/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 16:26:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-nus-votes-in-new-president-nas-endorses-candidate/</guid>
        <description>Nas Andriopoulos ICU President publicly endorsed Tom Harwood for NUS President. The endorsement was given despite the fact that Imperial College Union is not part of the NUS but also despite Andriopoulos’ track record of avoiding any discussion of his political leanings, particularly his stance on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Homeless Period hits Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-homeless-period-hits-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 16:23:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-homeless-period-hits-imperial/</guid>
        <description>ICU has opened a branch of The Homeless Period, an initiative lobbying government to provide a yearly allowance to homeless shelters for the provision of female hygiene products to shelter seekers. The founders of the initiative believe that just as access to condoms and razors is facilitated for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial bags distinctions over break
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-imperial-bags-distinctions-over-break/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 16:16:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-imperial-bags-distinctions-over-break/</guid>
        <description>Over the Easter break, Imperial has shockingly managed to bag not one but two distinctions leaving students to wonder whether this was an April Fool’s joke. First IC won the Student Experience prize at the Guardian University Awards 2017 and shortly after, it got recognised as a centre of excellence …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Dean new day new life for Engineering
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-new-dean-new-day-new-life-for-engineering/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 16:14:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-new-dean-new-day-new-life-for-engineering/</guid>
        <description>Starting this October, College will be welcoming Prof. Nigel Brandon as its new Engineering Dean. Though he is currently the Director of Imperial’s Sustainable Gas Institute (ha), Brandon’s love affair with Imperial dates back to the 70s, when he started his undergraduate degree and later did his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jazz and Rock fans still homeless
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-jazz-and-rock-fans-still-homeless/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 16:13:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-jazz-and-rock-fans-still-homeless/</guid>
        <description>The summer term might be here but Jazz and Rock fans don’t see no light in that long, long tunnel affectionately referred to as the Jazz and Rock redevelopment. Not yet anyway. The practice room was meant to have been delivered to students by the end of April but it seems the works are still …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chemical spill culprit confirmed
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-chemical-spill-culprit-confirmed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 15:40:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-chemical-spill-culprit-confirmed/</guid>
        <description>Remember that RSM chemical spill that sent three people to the hospital earlier in March? Turns out the culprit was escaped hydrochloric acid fumes generated by the polymerisation of a forgotten container of acryloyl chloride, according to an email circulated by Eddie Hartrick, Process Safety …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Relieved postgrads finally graduate
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-relieved-postgrads-finally-graduate/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 15:34:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-relieved-postgrads-finally-graduate/</guid>
        <description>Last Wednesday marked the day of the largest graduation ceremony at Imperial where more than 3000 doctors, engineers, scientist and “future business leaders” from 93 countries graduated. Watched by a record 9400 guests (which is surprising considering no one really wants to watch anyone graduate …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Controversial Tie Clubs paper passed
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-controversial-tie-clubs-paper-passed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 15:29:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-controversial-tie-clubs-paper-passed/</guid>
        <description>During the final Council Meeting of spring term, a paper was passed that will limit the presence of the Tie Clubs at the Union. The invite only ‘secret’ clubs have been accused of sexism, discrimination, and elitism among other things in the past and the Union has time and time again reiterated it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Drinking societies’ face tankard ban
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-drinking-societies-face-tankard-ban/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 13:06:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-drinking-societies-face-tankard-ban/</guid>
        <description>A paper is to be presented at next week’s Council meeting asking the Union to stop handing out tankards to the so-called ‘Tie Clubs’. These are invite-only ‘secret’ clubs, members of which can be easily identified on a night out as they adorn characteristic ties.
The paper presented by Andrew Olson, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Practice room due to re-open (maybe)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-practice-room-due-to-re-open-maybe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 13:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-practice-room-due-to-re-open-maybe/</guid>
        <description>As the Spring term draws to an end, so should the West Basement refurbishment which has seen numerous student media facilities intermittently being cordoned off over the course of the last few years. This last leg of the works should mark the end of a cumulative £1.27 million investment.
If all goes …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get brought LOW | Reading as relaxation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-get-brought-low-reading-as-relaxation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 13:43:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-get-brought-low-reading-as-relaxation/</guid>
        <description>&amp;ldquo;Life without art is not worth living”
I don’t often write reviews. I find it hard to judge someone’s work – partially because I never feel like I have the authority or knowledge to publicly share my personal criticism, and partially because I believe in making art for the sake of art, which …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Elections over and so is the spam
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-elections-over-and-so-is-the-spam/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 13:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-elections-over-and-so-is-the-spam/</guid>
        <description>Thank God it’s Friday. Voting for the Leadership elections ends at noon today, as does the constant online and offline harassment from your potential future leaders!
At the time of writing there’s been a 34.28% turnout which translates into 6,246 students out of Imperial’s ca 16,000 students …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>QS World Rankings by subject released
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-qs-world-rankings-by-subject-released/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 13:11:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-qs-world-rankings-by-subject-released/</guid>
        <description>The QS university rankings have just released a breakdown of ranking by subject and while UK universities remain global leaders in higher education it would appear that competition keeps getting more intense each year.
The latest instalment of the rankings takes into account 46 different Subjects …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chemical spill causes closure of RSM
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-chemical-spill-causes-closure-of-rsm/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 18:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-chemical-spill-causes-closure-of-rsm/</guid>
        <description>Earlier today the Royal School of Mines (RSM) building had to be closed off while a crew of firefighters investigated a potential chemical spill.
Emergency services were called to the site after a member of staff detected an unidentified smell in one of the labs following the movement of a bottle. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How many Union policies are still active?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-how-many-union-policies-are-still-active/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 14:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-how-many-union-policies-are-still-active/</guid>
        <description>The Union has fallen behind maintaining up to date policies responsible for managing a range of issues, from Equality of Opportunities to Club Society and Project (CSP) Equipment.
A felix investigation found that according to the Union website, out of the Union’s 70 policies, 36 are currently marked …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where did all the election candidates go?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-where-did-all-the-election-candidates-go/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 14:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-where-did-all-the-election-candidates-go/</guid>
        <description>A lukewarm candidate turnout marks the beginning of this year’s Leadership Elections, as revealed by the publication of the manifestos earlier last Monday, after nominations closed on Sunday.
Despite boasting over 700 candidates and “Britain’s most active student democracy”, representation for some …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Eating Disorder Awareness Week hits IC
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-eating-disorder-awareness-week-hits-ic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 13:45:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-eating-disorder-awareness-week-hits-ic/</guid>
        <description>As we’re entering this year’s national Eating Disorder Awareness Week, which takes place over the first week of March in the UK, Imperial College Union will be hosting events and launching a social media campaign in support.
A screening of eating disorder documentary THIN will kick off the events. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial to go smoke-free*
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-imperial-to-go-smoke-free/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 13:44:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-imperial-to-go-smoke-free/</guid>
        <description>  Smoking may be banned but vaping isn’t (sort of)  Smoking may be banned but vaping isn’t (sort of) Vaping360   It’s official: Imperial will implement a smoking ban on all College campuses and properties starting the 1st of August.
The move which has been in the making for quite some time now, is a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are sweet potato fries really worth it?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-are-sweet-potato-fries-really-worth-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 13:39:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-are-sweet-potato-fries-really-worth-it/</guid>
        <description>The Union has launched a new menu and is now a proud server of sweet potato fries. The new dish is another addition to the Union’s growing vegetarian and vegan options in support of Go Green Week (yes, sweet potato fries are vegan, we asked).
A side of dem sweet potato fries will set you back £2.50, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Alban Hall living conditions deemed poor
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-alban-hall-living-conditions-deemed-poor/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 14:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-alban-hall-living-conditions-deemed-poor/</guid>
        <description>Following the reveal of the poor housing conditions at Evelyn Gardens earlier last year, another Hall of Residence has been found guilty of offering sub-par accommodation, after numerous reports were brought to felix’s attention.
This time, students at Alban Hall have had to consistently deal with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Truvada | A cultural symbol
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-truvada-a-cultural-symbol/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 14:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-truvada-a-cultural-symbol/</guid>
        <description>Truvada is a household name in the gay community. It is the name of a small blue pill containing two antiretroviral compounds, emtricitabine and tenofovir, used to treat HIV. But Truvada does so much more that carry antiretroviral properties. It is charged with symbolism and packed with historic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union bars get new tills
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-union-bars-get-new-tills/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 13:37:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-union-bars-get-new-tills/</guid>
        <description>So you might have heard – or you might have gathered from seeing the long lines of students stretching from Beit all the way down Exhibition Road – that the Union has updated its tills. The brand new tills and the “fancy new yoyo scanners” which were installed on Monday, are promised to increase …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>King&#39;s lecturer apologises for offending Somali community
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-7-kings-lecturer-apologises-for-offending-somali-community/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 15:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-7-kings-lecturer-apologises-for-offending-somali-community/</guid>
        <description>Dr Adam Perkins, the King’s lecturer who last week sparked public outrage after a series of offensive tweets were brought to the attention of King’s Intersectional Feminist Community, has issued a public apology on twitter.
In his apology which was reportedly sent to King’s Intersectional Feminist …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students take to the streets to protest Trump | Are the days of political apathy over?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-students-take-to-the-streets-to-protest-trump-are-the-days-of-political-apathy-over/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 15:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-students-take-to-the-streets-to-protest-trump-are-the-days-of-political-apathy-over/</guid>
        <description>Donald Trump has consistently been on the collective consciousness for a while. Though Trump’s presidency could globally affect climate change and human rights, to name only a few areas of concern, amongst some journalistic circles, there’s the additional concern that the international focus on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>King’s lecturer sparks racism row
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-2-kings-lecturer-sparks-racism-row/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 23:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-2-kings-lecturer-sparks-racism-row/</guid>
        <description>KCL’s feminist intersectional society has condemned a lecturer at King’s College London after he released a series of tweets which were described as “racist and incredibly insulting remarks directed at the Somali community”.
Dr. Adam Perkins, a lecturer in the Neurobiology of Personality took to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Protesting Trump | The Women’s March through the eyes of Imperial students
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-protesting-trump-the-womens-march-through-the-eyes-of-imperial-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 14:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-protesting-trump-the-womens-march-through-the-eyes-of-imperial-students/</guid>
        <description>    Indira Mallik   Ana Villanueva | felix reader I asked myself a question the first time I heard about the Women’s March: Is it necessary? The answer is yes. I joined tens of thousands of people because I needed to share a message too. It was not a complaint. We advocated tolerance and respect for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union launches 2017-20 strategy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-union-launches-2017-20-strategy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 14:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-union-launches-2017-20-strategy/</guid>
        <description>The Union launched a new three year strategy last week in Metric, at an event that was the culmination of a six month effort to meet (or at the very least express) the needs and wants of Imperial students. Despite vigorous consultation though, student reaction was luke-warm.
The strategy is a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mental Health Officer joins Union roles
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-mental-health-officer-joins-union-roles/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 14:13:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-mental-health-officer-joins-union-roles/</guid>
        <description>Union Council has voted to introduce a new liberation officer, representing students struggling with mental health issues. Appropriate steps will be taken for the position to be created in time for the elections in March. Liberation officers exist in order to represent and campaign for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Student calls out Career Services
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-student-calls-out-career-services/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 14:11:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-student-calls-out-career-services/</guid>
        <description>The Union has resolved to put pressure on Imperial College to Improve Career Services. The decision came after Eric Suen, a third year medic raised the issue during Council last Tuesday.
Suen acted on results from a survey he carried out with help from Officer Trustees and Union staff, which …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How not to fall in love with someone (from Metric)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-how-not-to-fall-in-love-with-someone-from-metric/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Theresa Davey,Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-how-not-to-fall-in-love-with-someone-from-metric/</guid>
        <description> This is a follow up to our piece ‘How to have a one night stand (in Metric)’. For those of you who somehow missed it, we provided a tried-and-tested plan of action designed to get you laid after a night in Metric. This plan was meant to get you in and out without leaving any trace. But expectedly, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Head of Sport Imperial resigns
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-head-of-sport-imperial-resigns/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 14:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-head-of-sport-imperial-resigns/</guid>
        <description>Grant Danskine, Head of Sport Imperial, has resigned amidst resurfaced criticism of the organisation’s treatment of female athletes. Although the criticism – which resurfaced after Imperial published its institutional culture report – is unrelated to Danskine’s direction of Sport Imperial, it did …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Central Library to get air con
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-central-library-to-get-air-con/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 14:54:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-central-library-to-get-air-con/</guid>
        <description>Happy days. Imperial College will finally be taking steps to solve issues with temperature regulation at the Central Library. Probably.
According to a teasing announcement from Library Services just before Christmas, “early indications are that a project to improve the temperature at Central Library …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial to face LSE at City Varsity
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-imperial-to-face-lse-at-city-varsity/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 14:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-imperial-to-face-lse-at-city-varsity/</guid>
        <description>Imperial will be taking on LSE this year during a showcase event to take place in March. The event, christened the City Varsity, will mark the first time in a long time that Imperial plays against another University. (Though earlier last year the first e-sports varsity was launched at Gfinity Arena …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Prayer room refurbishment completed
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-prayer-room-refurbishment-completed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 13:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-prayer-room-refurbishment-completed/</guid>
        <description>The Brother’s Prayer Room was successfully refurbished over the winter break. Earlier last year, felix revealed many maintenance issues that had plagued the IC Islamic Society managed prayer room for six years. The issues included a dirty carpet emitting a strong smell, damp on the walls, peeling …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Firefighters swarm the Science Museum
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-firefighters-swarm-the-science-museum/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 13:52:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-firefighters-swarm-the-science-museum/</guid>
        <description>Just before noon last Wedensday, hundreds of visitors were evacuated from the Science Museum. As the visitors collected outside the museum on Exhibition Road, three firefighter squads arrived and created a perimeter around the historical building, amounting to a total of seven fire engines with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>National Student Survey open for 2017
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-national-student-survey-open-for-2017/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 13:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-national-student-survey-open-for-2017/</guid>
        <description>It’s that time of year again when final year students across the country are invited to fill in the National Student Survey (NSS), also known as Imperial’s bane of existence. Last year’s remarkably low student satisfaction scores saw Imperial dropping in ranking from number ten to 21 out of 24 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Report sheds light on Imperial culture
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-report-sheds-light-on-imperial-culture/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 23:46:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-report-sheds-light-on-imperial-culture/</guid>
        <description>Results of a report investigating Imperial’s institutional culture were recently released to the public, revealing a troubling picture behind the shining facade of academic excellence. The report was commissioned after felix brought to the public’s attention a series of incidents that took place …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Transphobic incident in Reynolds Bar
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-transphobic-incident-in-reynolds-bar/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 23:45:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-transphobic-incident-in-reynolds-bar/</guid>
        <description>A transphobic incident reportedly took place last week at the women’s restroom of the Reynolds Bar at Charing Cross Hospital, against a member of women’s rugby.
The trans student involved was grabbed by the arms in an attempt to forcefully eject them from the women’s restroom. Thankfully one of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Evelyn Gardens | Halls from hell?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-evelyn-gardens-halls-from-hell/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 23:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-evelyn-gardens-halls-from-hell/</guid>
        <description>Several students currently housed at Evelyn Gardens are reporting being unhappy with the quality of the accommodation they are receiving, with complaints coming in ranging from issues with pest control, to problems with plumbing and electrical works.
The recently refurbished residencies of Holbein, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Islamic Society Charity Week success
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-islamic-society-charity-week-success/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 23:41:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-islamic-society-charity-week-success/</guid>
        <description>For the first time, this year’s Charity Week hit and smashed through the £1,000,000 ceiling, as students from around the globe managed to collectively raise a total of £1,057,220.12 in donations.
The initiative which traditionally takes place over the final week of October sees students in London …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A year of Shazams and this is what I found
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-a-year-of-shazams-and-this-is-what-i-found/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 15:43:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-a-year-of-shazams-and-this-is-what-i-found/</guid>
        <description>So it’s Sunday; I’m tending to some life admin, such as paying rent, doing laundry, binge-watching Gilmore Girls, you know, the usual. All of a sudden an amazing cover of I Drove All Night (originally by legendary Céline Dion) comes up on the radio and I just have to know who it’s by. So I whip out …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>felix talks NSS and Imperial’s teaching strategy plans with VP for Education
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-felix-talks-nss-and-imperials-teaching-strategy-plans-with-vp-for-education/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 15:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-felix-talks-nss-and-imperials-teaching-strategy-plans-with-vp-for-education/</guid>
        <description>So I guess we should probably start by welcoming you to Imperial. How are you finding it so far?
It’s amazing, I’m having a great time. It’s the best job I’ve had ever I think, at least that’s what it feels like right now, it’s only been four months. There’s a lot that needs to be done, which of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Smelves take over Union during ACC
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-smelves-take-over-union-during-acc/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 12:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-smelves-take-over-union-during-acc/</guid>
        <description>The union was quite literally painted blue last week after another successful ACC. The makeover was a result of blue face and body paint runoff which was part of the costumes men’s rugby had selected for the occasion.
The rugby players, who attended as ‘Smelves’ (the hybrid of a smurf and an elf, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Keep your hands off our mascots
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-keep-your-hands-off-our-mascots/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 11:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-keep-your-hands-off-our-mascots/</guid>
        <description>A controversial paper was presented at Union Council last Wednesday which suggested the creation of a Masctotry Policy that would protect the student body from violence that occasionally manifests itself during mascot stealing raids.
The paper presented by Council Ordinary Member (Undergraduate …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Crying epidemic hits Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-crying-epidemic-hits-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 11:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-crying-epidemic-hits-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Imperial students have finally cracked under the pressure of university life, if the South Kensington mass crying events that have been popping up on facebook are anything to go by.
As of yet, over 4,000 students have exhibited interest in attending at least one of the three mass sob sessions that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2015 bursary scheme criticised at Council
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-2015-bursary-scheme-criticised-at-council/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 11:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-2015-bursary-scheme-criticised-at-council/</guid>
        <description>Union Council voted to put pressure on College to investigate the legitimacy of the 2015-2016 bursary scheme which has been criticised for not providing adequate funding to students of higher income brackets.
The decision was made based on findings presented by second year physicist Rhidian Thomas. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Life Sciences: ‘College says sexual assault = bad’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-life-sciences-college-says-sexual-assault-bad/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 13:49:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-life-sciences-college-says-sexual-assault-bad/</guid>
        <description>An email was sent out on Wednesday, to the Department of Life Sciences, informing recipients of a serious incident of sexual assault taking place last year between members of the department.
The email was signed off by Professor Murray Selkirk (Head of Department), Professor Neil, Fairweather …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Islamic Society prayer room to finally get refurbishment
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-islamic-society-prayer-room-to-finally-get-refurbishment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 13:48:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-islamic-society-prayer-room-to-finally-get-refurbishment/</guid>
        <description>Plans to restore the Brothers’ Prayer Room to an acceptable condition are underway after the issue was brought to the attention of DP Finance and DP Clubs and Societies at the beginning of term. The prayer room is managed by IC’s Islamic Society, and located at 9B Princes Gardens.
The prayer room …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jailbreakers return breaking past records
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-jailbreakers-return-breaking-past-records/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 13:43:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-jailbreakers-return-breaking-past-records/</guid>
        <description>As another year nears its conclusion so does another Jailbreak challenge. This year’s annual travelling competition, organised by IC RAG, broke the previously held record for participation, as well as for distance travelled by a single team. The winners Ayush Dharap and Rohan Prasad from team …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
