<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/alex_large/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/alex_large/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Ariana Grande’s thank u, next is a mature and conscientious pop classic</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-ariana-grande-s-thank-u-next-is-a-mature-and-conscientious-pop-classic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Large,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-ariana-grande-s-thank-u-next-is-a-mature-and-conscientious-pop-classic/</guid>
        <description>I thoroughly enjoyed Ariana Grande’s last album, Sweetener. With a majority of the production handled by Pharrell, the project had an eccentric and colourful atmosphere, and was far more interesting than your standard pop album. And it didn’t just sound great; considering the context of the release …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Noonday Dream revisited: How one gig opened my eyes to the full beauty of Ben Howard’s latest album</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-noonday-dream-revisited-how-one-gig-opened-my-eyes-to-the-full-beauty-of-ben-howard-s-latest-album/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Large,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-noonday-dream-revisited-how-one-gig-opened-my-eyes-to-the-full-beauty-of-ben-howard-s-latest-album/</guid>
        <description>Ben Howard has had an interesting change in sound throughout his releases. His debut, Every Kingdom, was full of uplifting indie-folk songs with sing-along choruses and a (generally) carefree tone. His next release, The Burgh Island EP, marked a change in mood hinted at by the cover art; these songs …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bad luck for Ben Howard fans</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-bad-luck-for-ben-howard-fans/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Large,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-bad-luck-for-ben-howard-fans/</guid>
        <description>It’s easy to forget that Ben Howard released an album last year. It came and went, with no hit singles and an understated sound almost unrecognisable compared to the cheery beach-folk of his debut. The nature of this quiet and underdiscussed release is what makes the decision to perform these new …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hands up if you like being absolutely scared shitless</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-hands-up-if-you-like-being-absolutely-scared-shitless/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Large,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-hands-up-if-you-like-being-absolutely-scared-shitless/</guid>
        <description>Preface to this review: I’ve never been into heavy music, but I love horror films. It’s undeniably a bit insane to subject yourself to two hours of fear (I recently saw Hereditary in the cinema and thought I was going to die), but the visceral emotion good horror elicits is what makes it so …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pieces of a Man is introspective, indulgent, and inaccessible</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-pieces-of-a-man-is-introspective-indulgent-and-inaccessible/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex Large,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-pieces-of-a-man-is-introspective-indulgent-and-inaccessible/</guid>
        <description>Two years after his ambitious but inconsistent and occasionally preachy release The Healing Component, Mick Jenkins has dropped a new album, Pieces of a Man. Four singles were released prior to the album’s unveiling, but the best two of these were inexplicably not included on it. This is …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
