<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jf413/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jf413/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The Looming Climate Crisis, COP 21, and the Will to Survive
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-the-looming-climate-crisis-cop-21-and-the-will-to-survive/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 15:37:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jawaad Farooq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-the-looming-climate-crisis-cop-21-and-the-will-to-survive/</guid>
        <description>This week a positive 20°C air temperature anomaly has been recorded over the Arctic Ocean. With sea temperatures averaging around 4°C higher than is usual for October and November, it looks like we are set to see more extreme effects of climate change in the near future. With these alarming …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Trump Effect | Is Political correctness to blame?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-the-trump-effect-is-political-correctness-to-blame/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 13:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jawaad Farooq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-the-trump-effect-is-political-correctness-to-blame/</guid>
        <description>It has been argued that political correctness has created a culture where people are afraid of expressing their views. This culture has been exacerbated by far left labelling and clamping down on opinions it deems do not fit into the liberal narrative. This apparently has led to the feeling of those …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Overpopulation | Is it a myth? Is it inevitable? Should we be worried?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-overpopulation-is-it-a-myth-is-it-inevitable-should-we-be-worried/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 16:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jawaad Farooq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-overpopulation-is-it-a-myth-is-it-inevitable-should-we-be-worried/</guid>
        <description>On watching Dan Brown’s Inferno this weekend, the question of how we would survive overpopulation struck a chord with me. It may have been a slightly dull film at times but the theme nevertheless was a relevant and intriguing one. Essentially, a billionaire concerned with overpopulation creates a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Writing as a release
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-writing-as-a-release/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 09:43:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jawaad Farooq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-writing-as-a-release/</guid>
        <description>Off the back of the Met office announcement on Monday that the climate is about to pass the one-degree threshold for global warming, I sat at my desk trying to write a coherent piece about the subject. As I typed away on my laptop, making notes from articles and reading up on the subject I asked …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Discover Islam Week!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-26-discover-islam-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 12:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jawaad Farooq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-26-discover-islam-week/</guid>
        <description>Do you ever wonder why we are here? Does it make sense that everything around us has a purposeful order to it and we are the anomalies? Will our lives ever matter in the grand scheme of things, or are we just material beings, that can feel pleasure because of chemicals in the brain? ‘Who’ is it that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>To the Power of Ten: Charity Week is back!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-to-the-power-of-ten-charity-week-is-back/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 01:08:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jawaad Farooq,Hazem El-Turk,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-to-the-power-of-ten-charity-week-is-back/</guid>
        <description>Charity Week officially starts this Saturday 26th, it’s a week that will leave you with some of your fondest memories of your time at Imperial, as well as many lifelong friendships.
It really says it all in the name. Charity Week (CW) is a week of student led non-stop action to help raise money for …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
