<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ur13/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ur13/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>New antibodies could treat dengue fever
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-6-new-antibodies-could-treat-dengue-fever/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 17:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Utsav K Radia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-6-new-antibodies-could-treat-dengue-fever/</guid>
        <description>Researchers from the Department of Medicine at Imperial have identified a new class of antibodies that is effective against the virus that causes dengue fever.
Dengue is a mosquito-borne viral infection found primarily in tropical and sub-tropical regions around the world. However, in recent years, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All-nighters might not be such a good idea
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-9-all-nighters-might-not-be-such-a-good-idea/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 19:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Utsav K Radia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-9-all-nighters-might-not-be-such-a-good-idea/</guid>
        <description>It’s coming up to that time of year again where a lot of us start to panic and furiously try to catch up with all the lectures we’ve been procrastinating in since last October. However, is pulling all-nighters for the last few weeks leading up to exams really worth our while?
Researchers from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Having Trouble Sleeping?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-having-trouble-sleeping/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 01:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Utsav K Radia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-having-trouble-sleeping/</guid>
        <description>In the UK, 1 in 4 people suffer from some form of sleep disorder resulting in excessive daytime sleepiness. Researchers at Imperial College London, led by Professors William Wisden and Nicholas Franks of the Department of Life Sciences and Dr Mick Hastings’ group at the MRC Laboratory of Molecular …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Learning in lectures whilst sleeping – a dream come true?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-learning-in-lectures-whilst-sleeping-a-dream-come-true/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 22:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Utsav K Radia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-learning-in-lectures-whilst-sleeping-a-dream-come-true/</guid>
        <description>Scientists at the University of Cambridge and the Ecole Normale Superieure Paris working on a joint research project have discovered a new phenomenon of the human brain: the ability to perform automated tasks even whilst the subject is unconscious.
The study, led by Dr Sid Kouider and published in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Boosting your brainpower?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-boosting-your-brainpower/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 02:05:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Utsav K Radia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-boosting-your-brainpower/</guid>
        <description>The London 2012 Olympics was not just a very fruitful and lucrative opportunity for the UK economy, which benefitted from a £9.9bn boost in trade and investment. It also placed a huge responsibility on the analytical chemists who had the job of identifying the drug cheats and keeping the Games fair. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A trip down memory lane
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-a-trip-down-memory-lane/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 17:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Utsav K Radia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-a-trip-down-memory-lane/</guid>
        <description>Have you ever wondered why we tend to remember some things more than others? Our nervous system is a highly organised, complex system of neurones (units that communicate via electrical signals), their dendrites (highly branched outgrowths) and support cells called glia (involved in processes such as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Diagnosing Down’s Syndrome
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-diagnosing-downs-syndrome/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 09:36:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Utsav K Radia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-diagnosing-downs-syndrome/</guid>
        <description>A new antenatal blood test, developed by Professor Kypros Nicolaides and his team of researchers at King’s College London in collaboration with University College London Hospital, with the potential to diagnose Down’s Syndrome in developing foetuses, is being considered for trial in the NHS. Down’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Breakthrough towards curing Alzheimer’s...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-18-breakthrough-towards-curing-alzheimers/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 21:12:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Utsav K Radia,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-18-breakthrough-towards-curing-alzheimers/</guid>
        <description>The MRC Toxicology Unit research team, led by Professor Giovanna Mallucci at the University of Leicester, has managed to successfully control the progression of Prion disease, a neurodegenerative disorder, in mice. The study, published in Science Translational Medicine, shows great promise for human …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
