<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ffilm/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ffilm/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Your favourite films of 2016
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-your-favourite-films-of-2016/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 14:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-your-favourite-films-of-2016/</guid>
        <description> Alex Heib, Max Lewis-Clarke and Meryl Anil 1. Arrival Intelligent sci-fi films are rare, with ones involving aliens rarer still. Arrival uses these foreign beings to examine how language shapes our view of the world, how it can be the source of conflict but also how it can be the solution. This …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Winter All-Nighter 2014
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-11-winter-all-nighter-2014/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 20:59:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-11-winter-all-nighter-2014/</guid>
        <description>As is Imperial tradition, once again it is time for the hallowed All-Nighter where once a term we put on all the films you’ve been dying to see, all in one go and for ridiculous prices! With one of our best lineups to date, what more could you ask for?
Lineup (16/12/14 - 17/12/14):
18:00: Gone Girl …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get Ready For All Night At The Oscars
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-7-get-ready-for-all-night-at-the-oscars/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 12:47:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-7-get-ready-for-all-night-at-the-oscars/</guid>
        <description>As we near the end of another exhausting term at our favourite university, the return of the hallowed Imperial cinema All-Nighter also rapidly approaches. In a year of unusually high caliber for Oscar nominated films, we’ve selected the crème de la crème of the Oscar crop just for you. You’ll laugh, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Iron Monster at ICU Cinema
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-an-iron-monster-at-icu-cinema/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 16:04:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-an-iron-monster-at-icu-cinema/</guid>
        <description> ANNOUNCEMENT FRESHERS: FREE ICE CREAM and cinema screenings too! Imperial cinema-your student cinema- is putting on a double bill during freshers’ week of two summer blockbusters during freshers’ week. Wanna learn how to use your Imperial science skillz to become like Tony Stark or to use your …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2013 Cannes Film Festival
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-28-2013-cannes-film-festival/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2013 13:50:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-28-2013-cannes-film-festival/</guid>
        <description>The world’s most prestigious film festival came to a close last Sunday, with renowned filmmakers, actors, models, singers and Cheryl Cole all making an appearance on the fancy red carpet – there were highs, lows, and some downright bizarre films in competition, as with every year, and Felix Film …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Billion Dollar Babies
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-the-billion-dollar-babies/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 21:43:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-the-billion-dollar-babies/</guid>
        <description>Congratulations are in order for Iron Man 3 and its associated Marvel Universe, as within 3 weeks of its international release date, the third Tony Stark picture has already generated more than one billion dollars at the worldwide box office. Robert Downey Jr.’s latest effort joins a surprisingly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A tale of two all nighters
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-a-tale-of-two-all-nighters/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 02:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-a-tale-of-two-all-nighters/</guid>
        <description>Along time ago, in a Union room far, far away an intrepid young fresher decided to attend her first all-nighter. Young and innocent, this girl did not know what to expect and this is the magical, mystifying tale of what she found there&amp;hellip;
Well maybe magical and mystifying aren’t quite the right …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nicholas Sparks: vom-inducing one-trick pony (spoiler alert)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-28-nicholas-sparks-vom-inducing-one-trick-pony-spoiler-alert/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 23:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-28-nicholas-sparks-vom-inducing-one-trick-pony-spoiler-alert/</guid>
        <description> Message in a Bottle - 1999 The Photogenic Couple: Kevin Costner and Robin Wright
The Plot: She is the journalist who discovers intriguing messages in a bottle (duh) in the sand and tracks down the writer of these letters, a widower mourning the death of his wife. They meet and start to fall in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Talkin&#39; bout sex baby
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-12-talkin-bout-sex-baby/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 20:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-12-talkin-bout-sex-baby/</guid>
        <description>“Let’s talk about sex baby, let’s talkabout you and me, let’s talk about all the good things, all the bad things that may be, let’s talk about sex!”&amp;hellip;hardly something you would expect to hear in a choir that consists of retired pensioners but with the OAPZ (Old Age PensionerZ), formality isn’t …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wrecking em up
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-12-wrecking-em-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 20:24:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-12-wrecking-em-up/</guid>
        <description>A Toy Story for the video-game generation, instead of having cuddly little toys that come to life when no-one is around to look, we have a bunch of arcade game characters who are free to roam around their own little world via intricately designed trains and the “Grand Central Station”.
Ralph …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>4 stars for 4ty
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-12-4-stars-for-4ty/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 18:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-12-4-stars-for-4ty/</guid>
        <description>A follow-up to Knocked Up without actually holding onto any of its main characters, we instead have a closer look at how aged, mature relationships work, and in this case, how the “happily ever after” is much easier said than done.
Debbie (Mann) is 40 now although she would never admit it. Impromptu …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Not too cold
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-12-not-too-cold/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 18:29:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-12-not-too-cold/</guid>
        <description>You may think you know all about the zombie genre. They’re dead, they walk about aimlessly, bumping into things, and as soon as they smell living flesh, they will not stop until they get their share of raw human meat/organs in their mouths. But have you ever seen a zombie fall head over heels in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2013 January Preview: for your consideration...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-2013-january-preview-for-your-consideration/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 23:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-2013-january-preview-for-your-consideration/</guid>
        <description> The New Year is here – which can only mean one thing: the exciting, glittery Oscar season is well under way. Films that carry their studios’ high expectations are rolled out in late December over in the States, which means over here in England, we see their releases throughout January. Sick of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What we watched over Christmas
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-what-we-watched-over-christmas/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 23:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-what-we-watched-over-christmas/</guid>
        <description> The Impossible Reese Witherspoon, an Oscar-winner herself, sent a fan letter to Naomi Watts recently, praising her “brutal physical performance,” “the ferocity of [her] mothering spirit” and “soul touching moments.” And Ms. Witherspoon is spot-on when describing Watts’ contribution to the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Top Fifteen Films of 2012
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-top-fifteen-films-of-2012/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 14:53:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-top-fifteen-films-of-2012/</guid>
        <description>15) Brave
Pixar seems to strike gold with every film they produce and their 2012 effort is no exception to this rule. The tale of a young, red-head princess (voiced by the feisty Kelly Macdonald) is a charming, sweet treat full of action, comedy and heart.
14) Looper
An emotionally charged, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2012 Felix Film Awards
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-2012-felix-film-awards/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 14:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-2012-felix-film-awards/</guid>
        <description> Best Actor: Joaquin Phoenix
The Master
 Wide-eyed, hunched over and completely disturbed and damaged to the very core, Phoenix is bang on in the middle of Paul Thomas Anderson’s incredibly challenging, dense drama. His extremely volatile nature is a tour-de-force of a performance, one that grabs …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Size Doesn&#39;t Matter
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-size-doesnt-matter/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 23:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-size-doesnt-matter/</guid>
        <description>13 December 2012. This is a date that should be imprinted into everyone’s mind – from those who know that by divine law, Olórin is not allowed to use his magic directly against orcs to those who only know him as Gandalf.
For it is on this day that The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey will finally be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The best Bond film of all time
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-29-the-best-bond-film-of-all-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 18:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-29-the-best-bond-film-of-all-time/</guid>
        <description> Moonraker (1979)  The most embarrassing entry. Roger Moore goes to space to fight some bad guys firing tacky looking laser guns. They couldn’t even come up with a new villain, and creating a love story for Jaws was the silliest, most unnecessary move this franchise has ever made.
 A View to a Kill …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Which Bond is the best?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-29-which-bond-is-the-best/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 18:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-29-which-bond-is-the-best/</guid>
        <description> 6. Roger Moore  It’s about quality, not quantity, which is why, even after 7 films, more than any actor has so far managed, Moore finds himself on the bottom of our “Best Bond” list. He lacked the suave charisma of Connery, and
 &amp;hellip; turned the franchise into a bit of a camp joke&amp;hellip; he has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>56th BFI London Film Festival
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-56th-bfi-london-film-festival/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:26:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-56th-bfi-london-film-festival/</guid>
        <description>You Are God
Lily Le
In 1998 Poland, rapper Magik forms three-piece rap group Paktfonica (apparently meaning “the pact next to the sound of the speakers”). The film is based on his story, from getting them together, troubles in getting noticed and signed, why you should not cheat on your wife and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What we watched in September
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-what-we-watched-in-september/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 12:15:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-what-we-watched-in-september/</guid>
        <description>Anna Karenina (7th Sept) 4 stars
Joe Wright’s bold, visually focused re-interpretation of a story that’s been told many, many times before starts off flawlessly, with colourful, slick set pieces and an intimate, theatrical ambiance, combined with a strong lead performance from Wright’s regular …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kate Winslet - Titanic EGO
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-kate-winslet-titanic-ego/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 12:09:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-kate-winslet-titanic-ego/</guid>
        <description>Powerful debut: Heavenly Creatures (1994):
After bit parts in British television, Winslet made her film debut in Peter Jackson’s dark and stylishly gripping Heavenly Creatures. She received wide critical acclaim in her first motion picture appearance, and won several awards (including the Empire …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Shut up and deal: Shirley MacLaine’s AFI glory
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-7-shut-up-and-deal-shirley-maclaines-afi-glory/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 19:48:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-7-shut-up-and-deal-shirley-maclaines-afi-glory/</guid>
        <description>Jack Lemmon is in love. He runs to his apartment to declare his feelings to the one lady who means everything to him. And there she is, sitting on his couch, getting ready to play their card game. He says: “I absolutely adore you.” How sweet&amp;hellip; but her response? “Shut up and deal.” And with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In brief: what we watched over Easter
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-in-brief-what-we-watched-over-easter/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 18:25:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-in-brief-what-we-watched-over-easter/</guid>
        <description>21 Jump Street
American teen comedy isn’t dead after all. Two rookie cops (Channing Tatum, Jonah Hill) are assigned an undercover mission in a high-school to track down the supplier of a deadly new drug. Hilarity ensues as the two thirty-something year-olds try to fit in whilst realising that the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to: Survive the iCU Cinema All-Nighter
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-how-to-survive-the-icu-cinema-all-nighter/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 20:59:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-how-to-survive-the-icu-cinema-all-nighter/</guid>
        <description>It has returned. It’s coming to the end of term and just when you thought you might look forward to a bit of shut-eye, BAM! iCU Cinema phwacks you in the gut with an All-Nighter. Six films, back-to-back, from the early evening to 6am the next morning, or until the projectionist goes insane and feeds …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Legs, laughs, and Oscar highlights
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-legs-laughs-and-oscar-highlights/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 22:36:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-legs-laughs-and-oscar-highlights/</guid>
        <description>After a struggle to grab the interest of viewers the last couple of years, the 84th Oscars may have created a positive future for the show. Billy Crystal kept the night running smoothly with his humorous skits, and all the attendees were charismatic and optimistic. Although comedy was present …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Silent film The Artist and 3D film Hugo dominate on Oscar night
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-silent-film-the-artist-and-3d-film-hugo-dominate-on-oscar-night/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 22:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-silent-film-the-artist-and-3d-film-hugo-dominate-on-oscar-night/</guid>
        <description>The 84th Annual Academy Awards ceremony was presented Sunday night, hosted by comedian and actor Billy Crystal. After last year’s rather disappointing ceremony with hosts Anne Hathaway and James Franco, in an attempt to reach a younger demographic, Crystal returned to host the ceremony for the ninth …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Time to place your bets and win big at the Oscars
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-time-to-place-your-bets-and-win-big-at-the-oscars/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 20:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-time-to-place-your-bets-and-win-big-at-the-oscars/</guid>
        <description>Best Picture: The Artist
Who knew a black and white silent film could be this charming, crowd-pleasing and moving? In this advanced day and age of sound, colour and computer graphics, Michel Hazanavicius (director) grasped the hearts of audiences worldwide by taking cinema back to its roots. It’s a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Love, Lust, Sex, Passion, Warmth, Beauty, Desire
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-love-lust-sex-passion-warmth-beauty-desire/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 21:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-love-lust-sex-passion-warmth-beauty-desire/</guid>
        <description>The 1930s: Queen Christina
If you want to watch a love story where a monarch gives up a throne for love, don’t watch Madonna’s latest, W.E., which is a bland, dull retelling of this century’s greatest romance. Watch instead the divine, majestic Greta Garbo’s Queen Christina, in which she plays a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Some films to avoid on a date
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-some-films-to-avoid-on-a-date/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 21:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-some-films-to-avoid-on-a-date/</guid>
        <description>The Human Centipede 2: Full Sequence
If you’ve seen the first Human Centipede film, you may well have been pretty disgusted. It wasn’t nice, was it? But this one is worse. This story follows Martin Lomax, a depraved maniac obsessed with the first film, and his insane urge to create a twelve-person …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Film Awards – celebrating this year’s best films
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-felix-film-awards-celebrating-this-years-best-films/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 21:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-felix-film-awards-celebrating-this-years-best-films/</guid>
        <description>Actor of the Year: Michael Shannon (Take Shelter)
What makes _Take Shelter _such a harrowing experience is not down to its marvellously restrained special effects. Instead, Shannon’s intense performance as the unstable, paranoid family man is what grips us from start to finish. These alarming …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let&#39;s talk about mummy&#39;s little monster
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-lets-talk-about-mummys-little-monster/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 22:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-lets-talk-about-mummys-little-monster/</guid>
        <description>We Need to Talk About Kevin
Director Lynne Ramsay
Screenwriters Lynne Ramsay, Rory Kinnear, Lionel Shriver (novel)
Cast Tilda Swinton, Ezra Miller, John C. Reilly
I can’t say that I walked into We Need to Talk About Kevin expecting a trippy, synaesthetic nightmare. But that’s what I got, and it was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brett Ratner resigns as Oscar Producer
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-brett-ratner-resigns-as-oscar-producer/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 22:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-brett-ratner-resigns-as-oscar-producer/</guid>
        <description>The American producer/director Brett Ratner, known for such films as Rush Hour, Red Dragon and newly-released Tower Heist, has stepped down from his prominent position as producer of the 2012 Oscars.
His resignation follows a string of inappropriate comments in a number of recent media appearances, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Five films to watch on Halloween (if you&#39;re a massive wuss)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-five-films-to-watch-on-halloween-if-youre-a-massive-wuss/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 22:02:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-five-films-to-watch-on-halloween-if-youre-a-massive-wuss/</guid>
        <description>So, it’s Halloween and your friends suggest you have a group trip to the cinema to watch Paranormal Activity 3. There’s just one problem: last time you watched a scary film, it was The Ring when it came out on DVD ten years ago, and despite watching it in the middle of the day you still shat …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Only three minutes of Gwyneth... the rest&#39;s OK
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-only-three-minutes-of-gwyneth-the-rests-ok/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 21:29:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-only-three-minutes-of-gwyneth-the-rests-ok/</guid>
        <description>Contagion
Director Steven Soderbergh Screenwriter Scott Z. Burns Cast Matt Damon, Gwyneth Paltrow, Marion Cotillard, Kate Winslet, Jude Law, Laurence Fishburne
It’s rare for a disaster scenario to make for a decent film let alone a great one, so it is with a sense of relief that I report that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Who can spy on the spies?”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-who-can-spy-on-the-spies/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 09:44:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-who-can-spy-on-the-spies/</guid>
        <description>Tinker Tailor Soldier Spy
Director Tomas Alfredson Screenwriter Bridget O’Connor, Peter Straughan Cast Gary Oldman, John Hurt, Colin Firth
After a summer of upbeat comedy in the cinemas (with films like The Inbetweeners Movie and The Hangover Part II), this wonderfully stark adaptation of John le …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Precious Review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-precious-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 15:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-precious-review/</guid>
        <description>Reviewed by Jade Hoffman
This film is incredibly grim. That&amp;rsquo;s a word that&amp;rsquo;s been used to describe Precious quite frequently and, looking over the synopsis, that&amp;rsquo;s definitely what you get from it. Clareece Precious Jones is an overweight, illiterate sixteen-year old girl living in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Road Review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-the-road-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 15:29:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-the-road-review/</guid>
        <description>Reviewed by John Park
The cause of the mass destruction is never explained and the audience is never encouraged to care. The point is everything has died. No plants or animals have existed for the past few years. It&amp;rsquo;s only the humans who have survived, and since all we make is trouble, this …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
