<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/er310/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/er310/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The dangers of being strange
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-the-dangers-of-being-strange/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 09:46:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-the-dangers-of-being-strange/</guid>
        <description>Imagine a white hot day blazing around you, created by blinding and numbing sunlight, all colours scrubbed cleaner and brighter and the air too hot to breathe. As I read L’etranger – usually translated as either The Stranger or The Outsider – a similar atmosphere appeared to surround me, created by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best of Henry James
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-best-of-henry-james/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 00:27:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-best-of-henry-james/</guid>
        <description>In Henry James’ The Figure in the Carpet, several unlucky people become obsessed with painstakingly unearthing the meaning concealed – literally – in the works of a brilliant novelist. The story plays easily with the reader; it dangles a something sweet – the promise of ultimate knowledge – in front …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Snowdonia landscape colours Sherfield green
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-21-snowdonia-landscape-colours-sherfield-green/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 20:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-21-snowdonia-landscape-colours-sherfield-green/</guid>
        <description>With each passing year, the Artsfest annual exhibition increases in importance. This show is the result of a collaboration between two of the largest arts societies on campus: Leonardo Fine Arts society and Photographic society. Last week, Rocio Molina gave us an insight into the trials and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Back to collage
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-back-to-collage/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-back-to-collage/</guid>
        <description>Kurt Schwitters was a key influence on the development of pop-art, one of the most important movements of the 20th century, but if you have never heard his name before, do not fear. Tate Britain is having a major retrospective of his work and, in any case, it is a catchy name, with a tingling ring …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Privates On Parade – A review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-privates-on-parade-a-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 00:13:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-privates-on-parade-a-review/</guid>
        <description>Privates on Parade, a musical farce rife with semi-gratuitous nudity and camp song-and-dance numbers, is not the sort of play one would expect Michael Grandage to stage. A star-studded Shakespeare production would have been the obvious choice as his new company takes to the London stage for the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Putting the camp back into campaign
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-putting-the-camp-back-into-campaign/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 00:11:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Thomas,Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-putting-the-camp-back-into-campaign/</guid>
        <description>Meredith and I went down to the Noël Coward Theatre in the West End in order to interview a young actor, Sam Swainsbury, involved in one of the most exciting theatre companies playing currently in London.
Swainsbury plays a cocky flight sergeant with no combat time in Privates on Parade. He answered …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bad belles bring the bard behind bars brilliantly
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-bad-belles-bring-the-bard-behind-bars-brilliantly/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 00:37:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-bad-belles-bring-the-bard-behind-bars-brilliantly/</guid>
        <description>At the Donmar Warehouse, I have always found my way into the parallel reality that theatre should create. With Phillipa Lloyd’s new production of Julius Caesar, one can simultaneously find oneself in not one, but two different realities.
There was no real need to set an all-female production of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Whatcha doin? Just Roman around
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-23-whatcha-doin-just-roman-around/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2012 00:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-23-whatcha-doin-just-roman-around/</guid>
        <description>The luminous setting, sand trickling from the ceiling onto the stage into pools of light, was melancholy and serenity personified. The existence of the characters, who would soon be participating in the tragedy, was mirrored, somehow with tenderness,in the environment that had been created. It was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Frieze Art Fair 10
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-frieze-art-fair-10/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:09:24 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,Charles Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-frieze-art-fair-10/</guid>
        <description>WTF is Frieze?
Frieze Art Fair, for those of you who have missed the press coverage, is big. It attracts over 60,000 visitors a year and generates enough acres of print to cover the enormous canopy in Regents Park housing the whole circus. Tickets sell out well in advance of the fair, which only …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Exquisite corpses
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-exquisite-corpses/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 11:28:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-exquisite-corpses/</guid>
        <description>It was a wonderful quality of Leonardo da Vinci’s, that he had the abilities, both mental and practical, necessary to reach the minutiae of a subject such as to become almost an expert in fields that were not his own. Trained in painting early on in life, but with an inexhaustible fascination for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Poet - Kadhim Shubber
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-the-poet-kadhim-shubber/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 20:48:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-the-poet-kadhim-shubber/</guid>
        <description>Eva - You were Felix editor last year, you organise Felix Music Nights, have a show on IC Radio, set up Kensington poetry nights&amp;hellip; why did you decide to get so involved in the arts at Imperial?
Kadhim - It kind of started with Felix. I learned last year that it’s quite straightforward to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Interaction Designers - Simon Bond &amp; Tom Sidall
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-the-interaction-designers-simon-bond-tom-sidall/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 20:16:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-the-interaction-designers-simon-bond-tom-sidall/</guid>
        <description>I run into Simon Bond on the second floor landing of their Dean St. office and, assuring me that yes, the unworkable doorbell often plays up, he directs me into the studio.
Bond is a co-founder of Physical Pixels, a company coupling technology and design to create installations that act like …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Phoenix 2012
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-phoenix-2012/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 19:53:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Eleanor Vincent,Eva Rosenthal Mena,Charles Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-phoenix-2012/</guid>
        <description>Editorial
Spotlight: The Designer
Spotlight: The Interaction Designers
Spotlight: The Game Designer
Spotlight: The Artist
Spotlight: The Illustrator
Moonlighters: The Musician
Moonlighters: The Fashion Designer
Moonlighters: The Poet
Summer Lightning
Backlight
Lightbox: Henry Bennie
Lightbox: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>GILBERT &amp; GEORGE IN LONDON TAKEOVER
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-gilbert-george-in-london-takeover/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 20:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-gilbert-george-in-london-takeover/</guid>
        <description>Gilbert &amp;amp; George, an eccentric duo even by the standards of the London art world, establish the ultimate vision of a dark, murky, sort-of-foggy London. As the ghostly reporters of the ghastliest news stories to hit the capital in the past years, with the London Pictures they have created a body …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hip to Bee square
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-hip-to-bee-square/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 10:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-hip-to-bee-square/</guid>
        <description>The ease with which Ido, protagonist of The Bee, morphs from law-abiding and rather boring businessman – of the kind who present their sons with calculators for their 6th birthday – to terrorising monster is stupefying but altogether not far removed from reality. After all, murderers lead at least …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hockney’s biggest splash yet?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-hockneys-biggest-splash-yet/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 22:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-hockneys-biggest-splash-yet/</guid>
        <description>Herman Hesse, the German novelist and poet, wandered for some time through the Swiss countryside – and wrote as a result the aptly named Wandering. His book is about many things, one of them being a communion with nature. Hesse tells his reader “Trees are sanctuaries. Whoever knows how to speak to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Free House Verse
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-free-house-verse/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 20:20:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-free-house-verse/</guid>
        <description>The first poetry evening I attended left me with the somewhat sour taste of disappointment, enhanced, no doubt, by the dashed hopes I’d been harbouring all week. Instead of great poetry, I was faced by something resembling slapstick stand-up comedy.
For that reason, I turned up to Fluent on Paper …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can’t be artsed: Will and Eva consider
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-cant-be-artsed-will-and-eva-consider/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 21:39:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,William Prince,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-cant-be-artsed-will-and-eva-consider/</guid>
        <description>It is always difficult, for unfathomable reasons, to make it to even the best of cultural events taking place in your own city. As a tourist, rushing around during a fleeting visit to the newest European cultural capital, visiting every museum in sight is merely second nature. But at home, with time …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rhyme, gentlemen please
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-rhyme-gentlemen-please/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 21:34:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-rhyme-gentlemen-please/</guid>
        <description>Fluent on Paper, apparently the first poetry night to take place in South Kensington, has been set up by last year’s Felix editor Kadhim Shubber, and will likely feature amateur poets from the university. It must take some courage to get up in front of an audience of your peers and read words that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nothing stormy about Trevor Nunn&#39;s Tempest
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-nothing-stormy-about-trevor-nunns-tempest/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 21:39:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-nothing-stormy-about-trevor-nunns-tempest/</guid>
        <description>Despite evidence pointing to the contrary, the name Ralph Fiennes is not synonymous with that of Lord Voldemort. Fiennes, who made his name at the Royal Shakespeare Company, is in fact a seasoned Shakespearean actor and proves his worth playing Prospero in Trevor Nunn’s production of The Tempest.
In …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Shots of Art
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-shots-of-art/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 11:25:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-shots-of-art/</guid>
        <description>The National Gallery opens late on Friday evenings. It is the perfect moment to visit, the rooms being relatively empty and peaceful. This is very conducive to a careful, and thus more interesting viewing of the National Gallery’s splendid collection. However there are few students, excepting those …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Frieze: A Preview of the Madness
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-16-frieze-a-preview-of-the-madness/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2011 14:31:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-16-frieze-a-preview-of-the-madness/</guid>
        <description>The talk of the day at Frieze Art Fair, from some grasped snippets of conversation, was a Yacht. It was, quite literally just a yacht that the artist Christian Jankowski was going to sign. Apparently this sort of thing is called “ready made art” and “the viewer gets to decide onwhether or not to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Royal Ballet is alive and well
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-16-the-royal-ballet-is-alive-and-well/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2011 14:27:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-16-the-royal-ballet-is-alive-and-well/</guid>
        <description>Watching a ballet from the wings is an experience akin to glancing through an open window into the life of a stranger. A voyeuristic experience perhaps. Dancers on a stage appear as magical and ethereal creatures, even in the most human of roles. They are perfectly poised, every movement apparently …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gilbert &amp; George wish you were here
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-gilbert-george-wish-you-were-here/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 19:39:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-gilbert-george-wish-you-were-here/</guid>
        <description>A seemingly endless tapestry of postcards greets visitors to the latest Gilbert &amp;amp; George exhibition at White Cube. The aesthetic quality of the show is tangible from the start, even when one is not quite sure of the content of the pictures. The overall effect is that of giant, multicoloured …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Poetry unplugged. And unwanted
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-poetry-unplugged-and-unwanted/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 20:24:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-poetry-unplugged-and-unwanted/</guid>
        <description>The Poetry Café is a sweet little place with a rather unattractive poetry night, Poetry Unplugged, on Tuesday evenings. Poetry Unplugged gives anyone the opportunity to read poetry in public. Amateur poets can read their poetry in public to an accepting audience. Unfortunately, the mix of amateur …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Marclay’s 24hr masterpiece
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-marclays-24hr-masterpiece/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 18:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-marclays-24hr-masterpiece/</guid>
        <description>Time will run away with you. It will skip, jump, come to a standstill, and even explode in front of your very eyes in Christian Marclay’s ‘The Clock’. Marclay has made a twenty-four hour film using snippets from movies that involve clocks and references to time. Every single minute of the day is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial does The Ugly One
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-imperial-does-the-ugly-one/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 19:16:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-imperial-does-the-ugly-one/</guid>
        <description>Beauty does not bring true happiness. Marius von Mayenburg’s &amp;lsquo;The Ugly One&amp;rsquo;, produced by the Drama Society, discusses this theme in a comedic and slightly ridiculous approach whilst never letting us forget the tragedy of trying to conform to social norms.
Lette is a man who finds out …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
