<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/cm5314/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/cm5314/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to a world of ups and downs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-welcome-to-a-world-of-ups-and-downs/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 19:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chrysostomos Meli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-welcome-to-a-world-of-ups-and-downs/</guid>
        <description>Silicon Valley has for some time now declared an all-out war on our non-electronic habits, changing them to fit around their technology. It has been a gradual process but thinking about it, we certainly don’t read books the way we used to. Writing an essay barely involves a pen anymore, we can go …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Microsoft: stepping back into the future
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-microsoft-stepping-back-into-the-future/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 13:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chrysostomos Meli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-microsoft-stepping-back-into-the-future/</guid>
        <description>Since the explosion of the smartphone, Microsoft has been facing an ever-increasing uphill struggle. With the introduction of iOS and Android, Windows is no longer the only viable OS option out there. iPads and Android tablets might not be the productivity powerhouses that Windows is, but they have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wearable technology – watch this space
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-wearable-technology-watch-this-space/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 22:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chrysostomos Meli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-wearable-technology-watch-this-space/</guid>
        <description>Tech-companies want to expand their product portfolio outside of smartphones, and with iPad and tablet sales falling quarter after quarter and all the variety in screen sizes pretty much exhausted, where do they go from here?
For some, the answer to that question seems to be wearable technology. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A breath of fresh air in an old and stale industry
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-a-breath-of-fresh-air-in-an-old-and-stale-industry/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 20:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chrysostomos Meli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-a-breath-of-fresh-air-in-an-old-and-stale-industry/</guid>
        <description>You don’t have to be a petrolhead to know that the automobile industry hasn’t been the most innovative over the years. Since the introduction of the Model T in 1908, the car has remained largely unchanged. It might have become faster, more reliable and more efficient over those 100 years but no …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
