<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/stephennaulls/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/stephennaulls/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s time to be online honestly</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-it-s-time-to-be-online-honestly/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Naulls,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-it-s-time-to-be-online-honestly/</guid>
        <description>In a modern world, our interactions with one another are often shaped by the explosive and revolutionary impact of social media. For most of us, Facebook, Instagram, Snapchat, and Twitter can be a pleasant escape – a way to keep in contact with our friends, or share fond memories of good times in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How high can student loan interest rates go?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-how-high-can-student-loan-interest-rates-go/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 15:31:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Naulls,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-how-high-can-student-loan-interest-rates-go/</guid>
        <description>You probably missed the memo, buried deep under a pile of revision notes but the fact remains: The cost of your degree has just increased.
Interest rates on student loans have risen by around a third – up from 4.6% to 6.1%. The reason for the increase stems from changes first introduced in 2012 to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can students bear London’s housing crisis?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-can-students-bear-londons-housing-crisis/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 14:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Naulls,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-can-students-bear-londons-housing-crisis/</guid>
        <description>It’s that time of year again. The ‘Private Housing Event’ invitation has appeared on Facebook, your housemates are suspiciously quiet about that looming deadline to renew your tenancy, and the thought of going through the whole process again makes you even more nauseous than that seventh snakebite …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The NHS is in a humanitarian crisis
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-the-nhs-is-in-a-humanitarian-crisis/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Naulls,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-the-nhs-is-in-a-humanitarian-crisis/</guid>
        <description>The Society of Acute Medicine has revealed that the NHS currently has “third world levels of staffing and third world levels of beds”. For the Red Cross, our NHS is in the midst of a ‘humanitarian crisis’. This language may sound vitriolic, but a crisis of this magnitude is something medical …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Public meeting to save Charing Cross
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-public-meeting-to-save-charing-cross/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 12:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Naulls,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-public-meeting-to-save-charing-cross/</guid>
        <description>A packed public meeting was attended by hundreds of Hammersmith and Fulham residents this week, in support of the campaign to save Charing Cross Hospital.
“There is nothing that makes me prouder to be British than those three words: national health service”. This was the rallying call sent out by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Save Charing Cross Hospital
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-save-charing-cross-hospital/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 14:28:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Stephen Naulls,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-save-charing-cross-hospital/</guid>
        <description>Plans to demolish Charing Cross hospital have ramped up in the past week, with a public meeting being held on November 29th a pivotal moment in the future of healthcare provision in North West London. The meeting, to be held by Hammersmith &amp;amp; Fulham Council is likely to be key in gauging public …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
