<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/pjb09/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/pjb09/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Action Against Acton
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-action-against-acton/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 01:37:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paul J Beaumont,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-action-against-acton/</guid>
        <description>What’s the point of widening participation and encouraging the brightest minds to apply to Imperial – if they’re then not going to be able to afford to come. Or worse, can just afford to come but get placed in ahall in North Acton?
For the last six months, I and the Deputy President (Welfare), Becky …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Manifesto Review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-17-the-manifesto-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 23:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paul J Beaumont,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-17-the-manifesto-review/</guid>
        <description> As the 2012&amp;frasl;13 academic year flies by (this time last year, I was already saying ’14 weeks til exams’ in an attempt to motivate myself…) there are a number of developments to update everyone on. For final years, the National Student Survey is back; for the whole student body we have, what I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NUS: A pottered history
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-nus-a-pottered-history/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 22:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paul J Beaumont,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-nus-a-pottered-history/</guid>
        <description>Personally, I have a great deal of respect for Liam Burns. I should imagine he has an incredibly difficult job attempting to mire the two ends of the tertiary education system: Higher Education (Universities) and Further Education (more vocational courses). The two systems – in my opinion -have very …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICSM VS RCSU
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-icsm-vs-rcsu/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 22:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Suzanne C Rayner,Paul J Beaumont,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-icsm-vs-rcsu/</guid>
        <description> Disclaimer: If you read this as anything other than a bit of banterous free advertising for our joint event, then you read too hard.
RCSU IS BETTER: Paul Beaumont, RCSU Vice President (Operations)
I run the inherent risk of making myself unpopular in writing this: and so I shall endeavour to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Unexpected guest at RCSU Ball
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-27-unexpected-guest-at-rcsu-ball/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 00:27:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paul J Beaumont,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-27-unexpected-guest-at-rcsu-ball/</guid>
        <description>Last Tuesday, the Royal College of Science Union (RCSU) held its annual Spring Ball in aid of Raising and Giving (RAG).
The evening – attracting two hundred and fifty ticket sales – will have raised somewhere in the region of £450 for RAG, the charity-raising Management Group of the Central Union, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dinner in the House of Lords, anyone?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-dinner-in-the-house-of-lords-anyone/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 20:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paul J Beaumont,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-dinner-in-the-house-of-lords-anyone/</guid>
        <description>This Wednesday the Royal College of Science Union (RCSU) announced via email to the Faculty of Natural Sciences that it will be holding the Science Challenge 2012 Final in the House of Lords. The Science Challenge is the RCSU’s annual essay competition and this year, entrants will be given four …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Friends of the Mirth
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-friends-of-the-mirth/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 22:32:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paul J Beaumont,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-friends-of-the-mirth/</guid>
        <description>Me being me, and this being only my second ever comedy gig, I was a little sceptical about certain aspects of last Friday’s line-up at The Hammersmith Apollo. A childrens’ entertainer? Musicians telling jokes? Charity?! Retrospectively, however, my aversion to live comedy was wholly unfounded. I …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
