<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/henry_hart/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/henry_hart/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial on top of London Once Again!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-Imperial-on-top-of-London-once-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Hart,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-Imperial-on-top-of-London-once-again/</guid>
        <description>Going into Mitcham, the second cross country fixture of the season, Imperial were engaged in a battle to be the top club in London with none other than St. Mary’s University, Twickenham. Mary’s, the University of Mo Farah and a National Lottery funded British Athletics Program, was going to be a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Eliud Kipchoge Ran a Sub-2h Marathon</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-18-10-how-eliud-kipchoge-ran-sub-2h-marathon/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Hart,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-18-10-how-eliud-kipchoge-ran-sub-2h-marathon/</guid>
        <description>Sub-2 has happened, and it still hasn’t sunk in completely. Yes, the conditions were VERY optimised and it is not record eligible, and we’ll get to that later, but the enormity of such an effort is almost unbelievable. Prior to this time last year, only one man had run under 2:03 in a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Surprise success for Imperial at the Teddy Hall Relays </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-surprise-success-for-imperial-at-the-teddy-hall-relays/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Hart,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-surprise-success-for-imperial-at-the-teddy-hall-relays/</guid>
        <description>In the aftermath of the successful 2019 edition of ICXCAC’s Hyde Park Relays, a merry band of Imperial runners headed out to Oxford for the ‘away’ fixture: Oxford’s Teddy Halls Relays. With runners wearily boarding the convenient Oxford Tube at Notting Hill or Shepherd’s Bush, the banter slowly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hyde Park Relays returns with aplomb</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-hyde-park-relays-returns-with-aplomb/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Hart,Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-hyde-park-relays-returns-with-aplomb/</guid>
        <description>On Saturday 9th February, the much anticipated 70th annual edition of the Hyde Park Relays, hosted by Imperial College Cross Country and Athletics, smashed onto the scene.
With over 80 teams and nearly 500 participants, it was once again a roaring success for the club.
This event holds a special …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get your running shoes on, it’s the Hyde Park Relays!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-get-your-running-shoes-on-it-s-the-hyde-park-relays/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Hart,Aymeric Regnier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-get-your-running-shoes-on-it-s-the-hyde-park-relays/</guid>
        <description>The Hyde Park Relays are the largest annual student relays in the UK and have seen over 500 competitors take to the paths of the iconic Hyde Park in Central London every year since 1949 to complete 5km laps in men’s or mixed teams of 6 and women’s teams of 4. This year’s edition is set to be even …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cross Country Runs for Parliament (Hill)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-cross-country-runs-for-parliament-hill/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Hart,Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-cross-country-runs-for-parliament-hill/</guid>
        <description>The first few weeks of October always seem to have surprisingly good weather to put the new freshers at ease, but eventually the first day of rain comes.
For years, engineers and scientists have been trying to refine the Navier-Stokes equations enough to be able to predict weather accurately. One …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Henry Hart accuses Sport Imperial of fraud</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-15-henry-hart-accuses-sport-imperial-of-fraud/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Hart,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-15-henry-hart-accuses-sport-imperial-of-fraud/</guid>
        <description>Fraud: Wrongful OR criminal deception intended to result in financial or personal gain. At least that’s the definition google gives me. It perfectly describes the situation that Sport Imperial has created with its new scheme to increase Ethos fees to £30 a year. Yes, I could hardly help but hear you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The bull climbs the stairs</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-the-bull-climbs-the-stairs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Hart,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-the-bull-climbs-the-stairs/</guid>
        <description>Stock markets rise and rise up until the point the bull jumps out of the window. US stock markets have been more expensive than now only twice in history: Black Tuesday of 1929, and the Dot Com bubble of 2000. Needless to say, both of those bubbles burst in spectacular fashion, and nothing helps to …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
