<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/egk08/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/egk08/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Classic Cinema: On The Waterfront
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-classic-cinema-on-the-waterfront/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 18:52:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edmund Knock,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-classic-cinema-on-the-waterfront/</guid>
        <description>The Italians dominated social commentary cinema in the fifties and with the British kitchen sink dramas and French New Wave in their infancies, this gritty genre of cinema was their playground until the Americans caught up a couple of decades later. However, amongst the gaudy visuals of Technicolor …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Superhero overload
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-superhero-overload/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 18:43:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edmund Knock,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-superhero-overload/</guid>
        <description>I’ll be honest, I’m not the biggest comic book fan. Sure, I used to watch X-Men and Spiderman cartoons in my pajamas during the now distant nineties but as far as turning the pages of actual comics, my only memories are of the occasional Beano – if I had enough change from my pocket money. Many …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Give me my Oscar!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-give-me-my-oscar/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 20:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edmund Knock,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-give-me-my-oscar/</guid>
        <description>The Best Picture Award is the most coveted prize at the Academy Awards and is awarded to the the film that Hollywood views as the greatest accomplishment of the past year. It is apparently given to the film that has the greatest script, performances, cinematography, editing and direction but if we …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Read me my last rites
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-read-me-my-last-rites/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 21:04:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edmund Knock,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-read-me-my-last-rites/</guid>
        <description>Any film about exorcism will always be compared to William Friedkin’s unintentionally hilarious 1973 classic The Exorcist but Mikael Håfström’s attempt to circumnavigate any comparisons with the latter in his latest horror The Rite inevitably fails. Although we’re informed that the story is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The King’s Speech triumphs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-the-kings-speech-triumphs/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 20:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edmund Knock,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-the-kings-speech-triumphs/</guid>
        <description>It’s always a joy when one film doesn’t clean up all the statuettes at The Oscars and this year was one of the most balanced distribution of gongs in recent years. However amongst the most predictable wins there were a few obvious surprises, notably The King’s Speech. Honestly I did not anticipate …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bicycle Thieves
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-bicycle-thieves/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 19:23:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edmund Knock,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-bicycle-thieves/</guid>
        <description>A man searching for his bike hardly sounds like a great plot for one of the most beloved films of all time, but Vittorio De Sica&amp;rsquo;s 1948 masterpiece is a beautifully crafted portrayal of suffering and poverty in post war Rome. Being the definitive Italian Neorealist film, Bicycle Thieves has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The late, great John Barry remembered.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-the-late-great-john-barry-remembered/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 19:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edmund Knock,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-the-late-great-john-barry-remembered/</guid>
        <description>It’s the most famous title sequence in cinema; A white circle bobs across the screen, the camera reveals we’re looking down a gun barrel before 007 strides across the frame shooting the unfortunate owner and as the blood drips down the screen, those famous swinging orchestral chords blast out rising …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mean Streets
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-mean-streets/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 19:48:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edmund Knock,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-mean-streets/</guid>
        <description>On the surface, New York City appears to be the physical embodiment of the American Dream. The wide, leafy spaces of Central Park nestled amongst the glittering spires of the skyscrapers that house the largest financial district in the world project a symbol of prosperity and success across the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kill ‘em All at Fabric with the legendary Erol Alkan
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-kill-em-all-at-fabric-with-the-legendary-erol-alkan/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 20:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edmund Knock,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-kill-em-all-at-fabric-with-the-legendary-erol-alkan/</guid>
        <description>Last Friday saw the promotors Kill em All hijack the club’s hallowed halls and the music policy was strictly four to floor, ranging the whole spectrum from disco and electro to pounding techno. Filthy Dukes set the tone of the night, a rendition of Green Velvet’s classic ‘It’s Time for the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Gutsy” Black Swan should get Best Picture
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-gutsy-black-swan-should-get-best-picture/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 20:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edmund Knock,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-gutsy-black-swan-should-get-best-picture/</guid>
        <description>It’s all too was easy to say that this year’s Oscars is going to be exciting but I do believe that the 51st Academy Awards are going to be a bit special. Whereas previous years have been dominated by a few strong contenders ( There Will be Blood and No Country For Old Men 2007) or a weak field …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Director Profile: Danny Boyle
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-director-profile-danny-boyle/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 19:53:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edmund Knock,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-director-profile-danny-boyle/</guid>
        <description>The creative void of the ‘80s in cinema did not leave British cinema unaffected. The ‘Carry on…’ films and Hammer Horror series had fizzled out aons ago and the legacy of Ken Loach and Lindsay Anderson’s Kitchen Sink dramas still left a stale aftertaste of gritty misery on British filmmaking. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Micmacs Review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-micmacs-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 15:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edmund Knock,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-micmacs-review/</guid>
        <description>Micmacs starts very sombrely; a soldier crouching over a landmine, gingerly sweeping the dirt off its surface amongst the cruel barenness of the desert. The camera cuts to a longshot and the mine suddenly explodes in the soldiers face throwing him high into the air. This sounds like a step into …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Prophet Review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-28-a-prophet-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 15:52:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edmund Knock,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-28-a-prophet-review/</guid>
        <description>Reviewed by Stefan Zeeman
A Prophet is the latest masterpiece that has emerged from France. The story focuses on Malik El Djebena, a 19 year old Arabic man who is given a 6 year sentence in a corrupted French jail. He enters the prison with no family, no religion, and no friends. His only …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nine Review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-21-nine-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 14:03:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edmund Knock,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-21-nine-review/</guid>
        <description>Reviewed by John Park
Among the never-ending stream of modern musical films, there were some hits, (Moulin Rouge, Hairspray) complete critical/financial flops (2009&amp;rsquo;s Fame and Rent) and those in between. (Evita, The Phantom of the Opera) But before you say “Oh no, not another flashy, camp, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Avatar Review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-13-avatar-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2010 20:55:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edmund Knock,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-13-avatar-review/</guid>
        <description>‘I’m the King of the World!’ declared James Cameron after the box-office smashing, Oscar hauling behemoth of a film that was Titanic. With Hollywood wrapped around his little finger, Cameron looked poised to produce many a hit-film from his throne but quicker than you can say Terrence Mallick, he …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
