<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/felix/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/felix/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Fellwanderers Easter Tour
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-imperial-fellwanderers-easter-tour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:59:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Emma McCracken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-imperial-fellwanderers-easter-tour/</guid>
        <description>Following an early flight at 7am from Gatwick to Aberdeen, we arrived in the scenic village Braemar in the Cairngorms national park at around 1pm. Kate, the provider of Rucksacks accommodation, greeted us as we sleepily got off the bus. Luckily Braemar was the end of the line, as otherwise we …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The failings of the Conservatives
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-failings-of-the-conservatives/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:42:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Ansh Bhatnagar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-the-failings-of-the-conservatives/</guid>
        <description>Theresa May went for a power grab. She wanted to wipe out Labour while her party was polling with almost 20 points ahead of them. With a fragmented opposition and Corbyn’s poor approval ratings, everyone assumed it was going to be a landslide election. So how did this all backfire and end up in a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>k bye.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-k-bye/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-k-bye/</guid>
        <description>Finally, the last issue (of term). I have been waiting for this moment for too long. While I’m going to miss putting together this wonderful publication for the next few weeks, I’ll be honest with you, I’m super excited to lay back and relax, maybe get a massage, definitely re-balance my sleep and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The election and the NHS
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-the-election-and-the-nhs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 14:25:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Dan Faehndrich,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-the-election-and-the-nhs/</guid>
        <description>Since the surprise of 7th May 2015, the NHS has fallen into its darkest times since its inception. As a medical student, seeing my colleagues here and across the whole medical profession has, frankly, made becoming a doctor look the least appealing it’s looked since 14 year-old me decided it was the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why I’m voting Labour
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-why-im-voting-labour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 14:16:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-why-im-voting-labour/</guid>
        <description>Soft on security, denying the deficit, and incapable of addressing concerns over immigration. These sound like the sort of accusations the Conservatives levelled at the last Labour government not too long ago, and yet after seven years in government, these are all areas in which the Conservative …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Afterhours sessions in the Central Library
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-afterhours-sessions-in-the-central-library/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:29:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-afterhours-sessions-in-the-central-library/</guid>
        <description>How does one end up in the Library past midnight? Maybe you had a paper to submit tomorrow. You thought you had everything under control. You were halfway there but you made the mistake of taking a break and committing to an episode of the Great British Bake Off. Six hours later you get a text from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Xavier Dolan | In praise of popular art
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-xavier-dolan-in-praise-of-popular-art/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 17:21:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Leo Diaz,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-xavier-dolan-in-praise-of-popular-art/</guid>
        <description>Xavier Dolan is not your average director. What first sets him apart is that he is extremely young: 28 at the time of writing, he’s already released six full-length features. He directed his first, I Killed My Mother, when he was just 20, and his 2014 Mommy received the Jury Prize at Cannes, along …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The case for divestment at Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-the-case-for-divestment-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 16:00:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Sarah Barfield Marks,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-the-case-for-divestment-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Here at Imperial, any mention of divestment from fossil fuels is largely met with one of two responses. The first is a supportive but disheartened reply along the lines of, “yeah, it’s a nice idea but it will never happen”. The second offers a complete aversion to the subject entirely, by changing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Divestment has worked before, and will work again
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-divestment-has-worked-before-and-will-work-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 15:57:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Conor O&#39;Riordan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-divestment-has-worked-before-and-will-work-again/</guid>
        <description>As the threat of climate change continues to loom large over society, activists are turning to more creative methods to encourage the large-scale change that we urgently need. Where traditional political methods have failed, divestment is now making serious progress on university campuses, in city …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Could 2017 be the year of indie?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-could-2017-be-the-year-of-indie/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 17:06:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Joseph O&#39; Connell-Dannes,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-could-2017-be-the-year-of-indie/</guid>
        <description>Last year, was almost unquestionably the year of hip-hop; the genre saw a huge influx of new artists and the drop of some absolutely massive albums from established names (From Chance the Rapper’s Colouring Book and A Tribe Called Quest’s We Got It From Here… Thank You 4 Your Service to Kendrick …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>There&#39;s no place at Imperial for elitist &#39;secret&#39; clubs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-theres-no-place-at-imperial-for-elitist-secret-clubs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 17:01:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Andrew D Olson Gallardo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-theres-no-place-at-imperial-for-elitist-secret-clubs/</guid>
        <description>Everyone studying at Imperial is aware that this place is not perfect. Yes, there are problems with student engagement, mental health, even sexism. But despite these issues, I feel it is the place which has mainly contributed at making me who I am today; the fantastic wardening team in my halls in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial to get HEFCE Funding
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-imperial-to-get-hefce-funding/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 13:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Abigail E de Bruin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-imperial-to-get-hefce-funding/</guid>
        <description>Imperial has been selected as one of 64 institutions to receive up to £50,000 of HEFCE Catalyst funding from the Student Safeguarding fund. This is part of the £2.45 million released by HEFCE for projects addressing sexual harassment on campus following the report from Universities UK’s Harassment …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The felix sex survey 2017 #callmedaddy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-16-the-felix-sex-survey-2017-callmedaddy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2017 19:22:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,Felix Editor,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-16-the-felix-sex-survey-2017-callmedaddy/</guid>
        <description>The 2017 felix sex survey is now LIVE! Fill it out here
</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>KenDO or KenDONT ? You be the judge
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-kendo-or-kendont-you-be-the-judge/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 14:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Gabriel Ng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-kendo-or-kendont-you-be-the-judge/</guid>
        <description>Last weekend on the 4th and 5th of March, the annual UK Kendo University Championships took place in Cambridge, where Imperial College took home several awards, including winning the kyu grade team competition.
Kendo is a Japanese martial art, similar to European fencing, where the objective in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The 2017 IC Cinema Spring All-Nighter
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-the-2017-ic-cinema-spring-all-nighter/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 14:37:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Sophie Sagawe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-the-2017-ic-cinema-spring-all-nighter/</guid>
        <description>This year’s Spring All-Nighter will take place on Tuesday the 21st of March at 6pm, ending at approximately 7.45am the next day. For those who are inexplicably out of the loop with this beloved Imperial College tradition: it’s a whole night of films, shown back to back, on a screen 8 meters wide, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let’s talk about Drugs #realtalk
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-lets-talk-about-drugs-realtalk/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 14:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,David Charchoglyan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-lets-talk-about-drugs-realtalk/</guid>
        <description>Do you know why some drugs are called ‘Drugs’ with a capital D? Or why your school was so eager to drill into you that some things are bad no-questions-asked-because-I-said-so during those insufferable PSHE lessons? Why some substances are kept completely out of our reach and have a seven year …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ugly Lies the Bone | VR therapy and emotional trauma
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-ugly-lies-the-bone-vr-therapy-and-emotional-trauma/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 13:43:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Vaishnavi Gnanananthan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-ugly-lies-the-bone-vr-therapy-and-emotional-trauma/</guid>
        <description>Ugly Lies the Bone follows the story of Jess, a young woman returning home following 3 tours in Afghanistan, which have left her with severe burns after an IED. Struggling to fit back into her old life in her declining Florida home town, and struggling to cope with her disability and chronic pain, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC American Football | Divison champs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-ic-american-football-divison-champs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 16:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Gatis Ogle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-ic-american-football-divison-champs/</guid>
        <description>After a season-long fight, it all boiled down to the last Sunday of the regular season. To be or not to be, it’s now or never: all three play-off qualifiers (Imperial Immortals, Cambridge Pythons and Kent Falcons) could come out top of the division if the day went their way.
While our play-off …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Trump&#39;s cabinet is cleverer than you think
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-trumps-cabinet-is-cleverer-than-you-think/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 14:41:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Alexander Luisi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-trumps-cabinet-is-cleverer-than-you-think/</guid>
        <description>The language of the Trump administration fascinates me. The daily barrage of comments, tweets and press conferences reveals something quite fundamental about the way that the government is operating, and how it will operate. It’s hard to believe that the administration is not in utter chaos, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Confused Nursery exhibition
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-the-confused-nursery-exhibition/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 15:34:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Tom Mutimer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-the-confused-nursery-exhibition/</guid>
        <description>Friday of last week, I had the pleasure of attending the Blyth gallery for the opening of a joint exhibition between Leonardo Fine Arts and PhotoSoc, titled ‘Confused Nursery’.
The space is a time machine that will take you back to days you hardly remember and juvenile feelings that you forgot …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My eating disorder
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-my-eating-disorder/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 13:48:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Conchi Hermida Sánchez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-my-eating-disorder/</guid>
        <description>As part of Eating Disorders Awareness Week, I would like to share my personal experience and hopefully help someone out there.
“You are going to get fat.” ”Don’t let yourself go as I did.” “Remember: a moment on the lips is a lifetime on the hips”. These are all expressions I have been hearing at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial rugby down RUM(s)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-imperial-rugby-down-rums/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 16:22:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,David Nielson-Scot,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-imperial-rugby-down-rums/</guid>
        <description>Still buzzing after their triumph last week, Imperial were roaring to get at a UCL Medical School (RUMS) side which had evaded defeat in the past five meetings, including a 49-10 drubbing earlier this season. With RUMS 2nd top and IC 2nd from bottom in our league, the scene was set for a tough …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hit me up, homeslice
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-hit-me-up-homeslice/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Alice Davage,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-hit-me-up-homeslice/</guid>
        <description>The hipster revolution is upon us. No food is safe. The humble burger has been embellished with a bright green avocado bun. If you haven’t tried kale or quinoa (pronounced “keen-wah”, trust me, I have been corrected multiple times), frankly, where have you been? Although the occasional twists on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are we killing the planet in style | Sustainable Fashion
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-are-we-killing-the-planet-in-style-sustainable-fashion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:47:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Eloise Hunt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-are-we-killing-the-planet-in-style-sustainable-fashion/</guid>
        <description>At the thought of pollution, we imagine raw sewage pumped into rivers, open-caste mines and oil spills. We don’t often think of our fluffy unicorn slippers or plaid shirts. But the overall impact the fashion industry has on our planet is shocking. The production of clothing has been estimated to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Romeo and Juliet | Updated and abridged
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-romeo-and-juliet-updated-and-abridged/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Helen Money-Kyrle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-romeo-and-juliet-updated-and-abridged/</guid>
        <description>Regardless of whether you&amp;rsquo;re madly in love, or frankly you&amp;rsquo;ve had enough of it this week, there&amp;rsquo;s still something inherently appealing about the tragic tale of Romeo and Juliet.
Squeezed into a running time of just one hour, the National Theatre’s interpretation sets a shortened …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Helping out a bee in need
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-helping-out-a-bee-in-need/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Olivia Barber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-helping-out-a-bee-in-need/</guid>
        <description>Over the past few years, discussion of the rapid decline of bee populations has intensified. Every week there seems to be another alarming headline implying that honeybee population decline is something we should care about. Do bees truly impact the world as we know it? Wouldn’t we do just fine …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The challenges facing early career sustainable scientists
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-the-challenges-facing-early-career-sustainable-scientists/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Alexandra Hicken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-the-challenges-facing-early-career-sustainable-scientists/</guid>
        <description>As a director on the executive board of the Network of Sustainable Scientists and Engineers (NESSE) and a PhD student in the Chemistry Department funded via the Grantham Institute, it may appear as though my future career path in sustainable science is all but decided. This, however, is far from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Being Black and Muslim in the UK
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-being-black-and-muslim-in-the-uk/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 14:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Omer G Mohamed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-being-black-and-muslim-in-the-uk/</guid>
        <description>The US is what most of us think of when we think of Black Civil Rights, which is where the movement was the most prominent, but seldom do we realise or remember what people in our own communities go through. The recent race row at Oxford University, in which students received an email from staff …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Query your consumerism
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-query-your-consumerism/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 14:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Valerie Wischott,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-query-your-consumerism/</guid>
        <description>I buy these flip-flops from H&amp;amp;M for every summer – after one year, they’re broken. But it doesn’t matter, they’re only €7.” “I already booked my journey back home for Christmas holidays – got a flight for €10!” All of you have probably said something along these lines at some point. These quotes …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You have no excuse for not recycling
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-you-have-no-excuse-for-not-recycling/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 14:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Giulia Costa,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-you-have-no-excuse-for-not-recycling/</guid>
        <description>Have you ever spent a long time staring at the coloured bins wondering where your everything should go? Wondering if someone is judging your bin choice? Well good, because recycling is important.
The global population is rapidly increasing and our lifestyles generate huge amounts of waste. In the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Climate change is a political problem
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-climate-change-is-a-political-problem/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 14:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Rhidian Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-climate-change-is-a-political-problem/</guid>
        <description>As political descriptors go, the humble watermelon is perhaps predictably an unconventional one: it is not wheeled out too often as a way of making a point. It’s a charge often levelled at politicians like Caroline Lucas, who are accused of being green on the outside but red (that is, socialist) on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Talk dirty to me | Banana Tree
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-talk-dirty-to-me-banana-tree/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 16:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Shanzeh Khurshid,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-talk-dirty-to-me-banana-tree/</guid>
        <description> Where to go On their way to the Royal Albert Hall, my friends and I caught up in Banana Tree in Bayswater. I suggested the restaurant because it’s about 30 minutes walking distance from campus, and only 20 minutes from Wilson House and Pembridge. Ever since she went on a yoga trip to Vietnam, one …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s a queer gal to do/see/watch/listen to? Our guide to your gal-pal culture fix
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-whats-a-queer-gal-to-doseewatchlisten-to-our-guide-to-your-gal-pal-culture-fix/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 15:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-whats-a-queer-gal-to-doseewatchlisten-to-our-guide-to-your-gal-pal-culture-fix/</guid>
        <description> Film Appropriate Behaviour
Desiree Akhavan directs and stars in this comedy about an American-Iranian bisexual going through a breakup. It’ll make you feel worse about your recent breakup but then, strangely, better. It’s pretty funny and feels quite real. The protagonist also struggles with coming …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fuck Valentine’s Day | Asexual and aromantic
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-fuck-valentines-day-asexual-and-aromantic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 14:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-fuck-valentines-day-asexual-and-aromantic/</guid>
        <description>The first two weeks in February are an infernal nightmare of constant bombardment with advertisements for jewellery, chocolates, and lingerie – all for that ‘special someone’. People in relationships presumably don’t mind. Single people complain incessantly about it. For aromantics however, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science won’t be Trumped
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-science-wont-be-trumped/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 14:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Agnes Donnelly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-science-wont-be-trumped/</guid>
        <description>The past three weeks have meant that the previously enjoyable activity of looking at Facebook has instead become a daily battle of emotions as I brace myself to learn of another Trump shocker. A travel ban on 7 countries, banning organizations from speaking to the public and a petty fight over who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Romanian protests are an unlikely beacon of democracy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-the-romanian-protests-are-an-unlikely-beacon-of-democracy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 13:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Claudia Mihai,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-the-romanian-protests-are-an-unlikely-beacon-of-democracy/</guid>
        <description>A brief glance at the main headlines and you can see that the past month has been filled with protests, discontent, and outrage. While the world is watching the United States, Eastern Europe is facing its own demons as formerly communist country Romania is seeing its largest protest since the fall …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The LGBT community is a dichotomy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-the-lgbt-community-is-a-dichotomy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 13:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Elizabeth Windo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-the-lgbt-community-is-a-dichotomy/</guid>
        <description> I found a home in the LGBT community The LGBT community is the first place that I found people like me. For so many years of my life, I lived in a state of confusion. To finally discover people that shared the same interests and passions was incredible. I’ve been able to make the lifelong friends …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You&#39;re misrepresenting the facts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-youre-misrepresenting-the-facts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 13:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Saul Coleman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-youre-misrepresenting-the-facts/</guid>
        <description>Opening last week’s issue of felix, I was greeted on page three by an article entitled “Israeli ambassador’s secret visit to Imperial”. And I’m pleased to say that, on the whole, the article was a very balanced read, just as the event was very civil. The sensitive nature of the discussion had …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial students launch campaign to make medical curriculum LGBT-inclusive
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-imperial-students-launch-campaign-to-make-medical-curriculum-lgbt-inclusive/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 13:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Michael Wilkinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-imperial-students-launch-campaign-to-make-medical-curriculum-lgbt-inclusive/</guid>
        <description>The founding principles of the NHS were that it should meet the needs of everyone, be free at the point of delivery, and be based on clinical need, not ability to pay. Those of us watching BBC’s Hospital last week, were reminded of the importance of these values, as we witnessed overseas patients …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I heard you like... food?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-i-heard-you-like-food/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 18:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,B. C. Maile,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-i-heard-you-like-food/</guid>
        <description> Have you ever found yourself aroused by the thought of having a cream pie pushed into your face or cracking eggs over someone’s chest? Of course you have. Well, you’re not alone. This fringe phenomenon is called ‘Wet and Messy Fetishism’, often abbreviated to WAM or simply called sploshing. Fans of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bake sale
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-bake-sale/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 17:07:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Harry Wilkinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-bake-sale/</guid>
        <description>Among other smaller, less internationally important incidents, it seems to me that 2016 will be remembered primarily as the year that the BBC lost the Great British Bake Off to Channel 4. In what is ostensibly just a show about people making cakes, you find a lot of what British culture is all …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Percolate | Mind Fundraiser
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-percolate-mind-fundraiser/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 17:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Philipp Antonas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-percolate-mind-fundraiser/</guid>
        <description>Any excuse to visit one of my favourite venues in London is welcomed by me, so much more the better when that excuse is me donating to an amazing charity and getting a great, music-heavy evening in return.
The Oval Space is small and intimate, overlooking an industrial side of the city which adds to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ghost in the Shell
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-ghost-in-the-shell/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 16:52:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Peter Shatwell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-ghost-in-the-shell/</guid>
        <description>If you wish to dive into the world of Japanese animation, you cannot miss Mamoru Oshii’s profound 1995 cyberpunk film Ghost in the Shell. It stands as a science-fiction classic and has gone on to inspire other films such as The Matrix, Surrogates, and Avatar. But why am I talking now about a film …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I turned vegan four months ago – am I allowed to preach yet?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-i-turned-vegan-four-months-ago-am-i-allowed-to-preach-yet/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 15:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Alex Chaundri,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-i-turned-vegan-four-months-ago-am-i-allowed-to-preach-yet/</guid>
        <description>A year ago, after mostly avoiding meat for several months, I decided to make the commitment to being fully vegetarian. My decision for this was mostly driven by a concern for the planet. The Food and Agriculture Organisation of the UN estimates that 14.5% of global greenhouse gas emissions come from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Leave Trident alone
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-leave-trident-alone/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 15:54:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-leave-trident-alone/</guid>
        <description>Trident was announced as the UK’s new deterrent back in 1980, and patrols with the missile began in 1994. The renewal of trident was debated in July 2016, to replace the current submarines with the newer Dreadnought Class by 2028. The estimated cost of the upgraded weapons system is around £31 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Zero tolerance policy gets scrapped
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-zero-tolerance-policy-gets-scrapped/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 15:04:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Matt Rego,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-zero-tolerance-policy-gets-scrapped/</guid>
        <description>Last Tuesday, during Union Council, Student Deputy President of Education, Luke McCrone announced a repeal to the university’s zero-tolerance late submission policy.
According to McCrone’s report given at the meeting, the zero tolerance policy will be replaced by a new policy, allowing grades capped …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hallelujah Money
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-hallelujah-money/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 16:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Sam Wood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-hallelujah-money/</guid>
        <description>Gorillaz are back – and this time they are as political as they are whacky. Having teased a new album through Instagram and SoundCloud releases over the past few months, Gorillaz released the brand new track Hallelujah Money (ft. Benjamin Clementine) on the eve of Trump’s inauguration. The Damon …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cunts in conversation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-cunts-in-conversation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lucille Calmon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-cunts-in-conversation/</guid>
        <description>I bet you&amp;rsquo;re worried. I was worried. I was worried about vaginas. I was worried about what we think about vaginas, and even more worried that we don&amp;rsquo;t think about them” wrote Eve Ensler in the introduction of The Vagina Monologues, a compilation of over 200 women’s feelings about their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Taking a leaf out of Tove Jansson&#39;s book
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-taking-a-leaf-out-of-tove-janssons-book/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:28:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Jenny Shelley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-taking-a-leaf-out-of-tove-janssons-book/</guid>
        <description>For many, the Moomins hold nothing more than the nostalgia of childhood. While some have no idea what they are, for others the word conjures up a vague image of a hippo-esque creature that adorns cutesy bottles and notepads. There is no particular reason to go any deeper than these associations, but …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bro do you even lift?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-bro-do-you-even-lift/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:08:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Aran Shaunak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-bro-do-you-even-lift/</guid>
        <description>Fact: The strongest living thing on the planet is gonorrhea.
Neisseria gonorrhoeae (the bacterium that causes gonorrhea) is a force to be reckoned with, given it can pull with a force over 100,000 times its own body weight. For a human to compete, you’d have to shift over ten million kilos, which …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is it stupid to take smart drugs?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-is-it-stupid-to-take-smart-drugs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Anjeline Joegi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-is-it-stupid-to-take-smart-drugs/</guid>
        <description> It’s the night before the final exam, but you haven’t studied. If you had a small white pill which promised greater focus and productivity would you take it? The Tab website conducted a survey of 2000 UK university students and discovered that 1 in 5 have taken the drug ‘Modafinil’. Many students …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Head of Sport Imperial resigns
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-head-of-sport-imperial-resigns/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 14:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-head-of-sport-imperial-resigns/</guid>
        <description>Grant Danskine, Head of Sport Imperial, has resigned amidst resurfaced criticism of the organisation’s treatment of female athletes. Although the criticism – which resurfaced after Imperial published its institutional culture report – is unrelated to Danskine’s direction of Sport Imperial, it did …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Central Library to get air con
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-central-library-to-get-air-con/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 14:54:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-central-library-to-get-air-con/</guid>
        <description>Happy days. Imperial College will finally be taking steps to solve issues with temperature regulation at the Central Library. Probably.
According to a teasing announcement from Library Services just before Christmas, “early indications are that a project to improve the temperature at Central Library …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial to face LSE at City Varsity
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-imperial-to-face-lse-at-city-varsity/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 14:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-imperial-to-face-lse-at-city-varsity/</guid>
        <description>Imperial will be taking on LSE this year during a showcase event to take place in March. The event, christened the City Varsity, will mark the first time in a long time that Imperial plays against another University. (Though earlier last year the first e-sports varsity was launched at Gfinity Arena …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Monster Calls
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-a-monster-calls/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Fred S Fyles,Meryl Chittethazhathu Anil,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-a-monster-calls/</guid>
        <description>Storytellers are a threat,” wrote Chinua Achebe, “they threaten all champions of control, usurpers of the right-to-freedom of the human spirit”. It is this power, that of a simple story well-told, that director J. A. Bayona is trying to tap with his latest feature A Monster Calls, an adaptation of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Southern Rail need to get their shit together
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-southern-rail-need-to-get-their-shit-together/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-southern-rail-need-to-get-their-shit-together/</guid>
        <description>There were train strikes this week, you might have heard. No, not the tube strikes, they happen like once a year; you can take a bus for a day, get over yourself, no one cares. I’m talking about Southern Rail, whose staff are on strike for three days this week, causing a genuine total shutdown of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rhodes must stay
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-rhodes-must-stay/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 13:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Divyen Vanniasega,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-rhodes-must-stay/</guid>
        <description>In recent months, the ‘Rhodes Must Fall’ campaign has gained significant traction not only at Oriel college, Oxford but at several institutions in the UK and abroad. The campaign has attempted to have the statue of Cecil Rhodes removed due to his strong support for the apartheid movement in South …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Prayer room refurbishment completed
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-prayer-room-refurbishment-completed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 13:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-prayer-room-refurbishment-completed/</guid>
        <description>The Brother’s Prayer Room was successfully refurbished over the winter break. Earlier last year, felix revealed many maintenance issues that had plagued the IC Islamic Society managed prayer room for six years. The issues included a dirty carpet emitting a strong smell, damp on the walls, peeling …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Firefighters swarm the Science Museum
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-firefighters-swarm-the-science-museum/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 13:52:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-firefighters-swarm-the-science-museum/</guid>
        <description>Just before noon last Wedensday, hundreds of visitors were evacuated from the Science Museum. As the visitors collected outside the museum on Exhibition Road, three firefighter squads arrived and created a perimeter around the historical building, amounting to a total of seven fire engines with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>National Student Survey open for 2017
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-national-student-survey-open-for-2017/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 13:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-national-student-survey-open-for-2017/</guid>
        <description>It’s that time of year again when final year students across the country are invited to fill in the National Student Survey (NSS), also known as Imperial’s bane of existence. Last year’s remarkably low student satisfaction scores saw Imperial dropping in ranking from number ten to 21 out of 24 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jiu Jitsu advances to the next level in style
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-jiu-jitsu-advances-to-the-next-level-in-style/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 16:26:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Cloe Fradin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-jiu-jitsu-advances-to-the-next-level-in-style/</guid>
        <description>Last Saturday saw London host the Jiu Jitsu grading. If competitions are scary, then gradings are a halloween movie marathon with the lights off and the creepy neighbour wearing his Freddy Krueger outfit staring through the window.
A grading is the opportunity for any member of a Jitsu club (from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICSM Netball get crafty
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-icsm-netball-get-crafty/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 16:23:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Ifrah Hussain,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-icsm-netball-get-crafty/</guid>
        <description>The start of the summer saw planning and preparations for the upcoming academic year get underway at ICSM Netball. With an ever-expanding club, we decided to shift some focus to the development of the club off-court whilst maintaining team progression on-court. One particular area of focus was club …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Crowning Glory | The Crown
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-crowning-glory-the-crown/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 15:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-crowning-glory-the-crown/</guid>
        <description>The Crown isn’t just one of the most anticipated shows of the year, but if the rumors of its budget of £100 million an episode are true, it’s also one of the most expensive. This is Netflix’s attempt at trying out something more traditional yet different (at least by Netflix standards) at the same …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Through the Wall
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-through-the-wall/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 14:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lawrence Good,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-through-the-wall/</guid>
        <description>I’m tired of being alone – I just want to love, and to be loved” laments Michal (Noa Kooler), voicing a complaint that many Imperial students share. Yet instead of just drowning her sorrows like the rest of us, Michal resolves to marry in 22 days’ time, trusting in God to find her a husband. From …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Harnessing bacterial defences to disrupt infectious biofilms
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-harnessing-bacterial-defences-to-disrupt-infectious-biofilms/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 14:34:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Rachel Gillespie,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-harnessing-bacterial-defences-to-disrupt-infectious-biofilms/</guid>
        <description>Pseudomonas aeruginosa is a bacterium of considerable medical importance. It is the archetypal “multi-drug resistant (MDR) pathogen”, known for its extreme antibiotic resistance, broad host range, and an association with serious illnesses including sepsis and hospital-acquired infections, prominent …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The real disgrace of executive pay
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-the-real-disgrace-of-executive-pay/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 14:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Shaul Rosten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-the-real-disgrace-of-executive-pay/</guid>
        <description>Theresa May announced this week that she intends to force companies to “justify” executive pay in response to reports that, at times, executives earn 140 times more than the average worker. High executive pay has been thrust into the headlines recently amidst the furore of the BHS collapse, and the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Report sheds light on Imperial culture
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-report-sheds-light-on-imperial-culture/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 23:46:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-report-sheds-light-on-imperial-culture/</guid>
        <description>Results of a report investigating Imperial’s institutional culture were recently released to the public, revealing a troubling picture behind the shining facade of academic excellence. The report was commissioned after felix brought to the public’s attention a series of incidents that took place …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Transphobic incident in Reynolds Bar
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-transphobic-incident-in-reynolds-bar/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 23:45:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-transphobic-incident-in-reynolds-bar/</guid>
        <description>A transphobic incident reportedly took place last week at the women’s restroom of the Reynolds Bar at Charing Cross Hospital, against a member of women’s rugby.
The trans student involved was grabbed by the arms in an attempt to forcefully eject them from the women’s restroom. Thankfully one of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Evelyn Gardens | Halls from hell?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-evelyn-gardens-halls-from-hell/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 23:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-evelyn-gardens-halls-from-hell/</guid>
        <description>Several students currently housed at Evelyn Gardens are reporting being unhappy with the quality of the accommodation they are receiving, with complaints coming in ranging from issues with pest control, to problems with plumbing and electrical works.
The recently refurbished residencies of Holbein, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Islamic Society Charity Week success
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-islamic-society-charity-week-success/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 23:41:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-15-islamic-society-charity-week-success/</guid>
        <description>For the first time, this year’s Charity Week hit and smashed through the £1,000,000 ceiling, as students from around the globe managed to collectively raise a total of £1,057,220.12 in donations.
The initiative which traditionally takes place over the final week of October sees students in London …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Unknown Girl ties everything up in the end
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-the-unknown-girl-ties-everything-up-in-the-end/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 15:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Steve Bohnel,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-the-unknown-girl-ties-everything-up-in-the-end/</guid>
        <description>For about the first 90 minutes of The Unknown Girl, I sat rather unimpressed in my leather chair in one of the small theaters at Soho Screening Rooms. Then, as the last half hour unfolded, directors Jean-Pierre and Luc Dardenne tied together multiple plot lines like a beautiful bow on a Christmas …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Documentary Corner | Citizenfour
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-documentary-corner-citizenfour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 15:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-documentary-corner-citizenfour/</guid>
        <description>Sometimes a perfect opportunity can just present itself to a director. Citizenfour is a film whose mere existence is incredible. Based on the drama of Edward Snowden’s whistleblowing on the mass surveillance being performed by the NSA in America, Citizenfour is the final film in director Laura …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Moana
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-moana/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 15:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-moana/</guid>
        <description>In the world’s current situation, a film that can make you laugh, cry, and leave with a warm, fuzzy feeling is desperately needed. The newest Disney princess film, Moana, is the answer.
The storyline follows Moana Waialiki (Auli’i Cravalho), daughter of Chief Tui (Temuera Morrison). Growing up on a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A year of Shazams and this is what I found
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-a-year-of-shazams-and-this-is-what-i-found/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 15:43:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-a-year-of-shazams-and-this-is-what-i-found/</guid>
        <description>So it’s Sunday; I’m tending to some life admin, such as paying rent, doing laundry, binge-watching Gilmore Girls, you know, the usual. All of a sudden an amazing cover of I Drove All Night (originally by legendary Céline Dion) comes up on the radio and I just have to know who it’s by. So I whip out …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>felix talks NSS and Imperial’s teaching strategy plans with VP for Education
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-felix-talks-nss-and-imperials-teaching-strategy-plans-with-vp-for-education/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 15:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-felix-talks-nss-and-imperials-teaching-strategy-plans-with-vp-for-education/</guid>
        <description>So I guess we should probably start by welcoming you to Imperial. How are you finding it so far?
It’s amazing, I’m having a great time. It’s the best job I’ve had ever I think, at least that’s what it feels like right now, it’s only been four months. There’s a lot that needs to be done, which of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Smelves take over Union during ACC
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-smelves-take-over-union-during-acc/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 12:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-smelves-take-over-union-during-acc/</guid>
        <description>The union was quite literally painted blue last week after another successful ACC. The makeover was a result of blue face and body paint runoff which was part of the costumes men’s rugby had selected for the occasion.
The rugby players, who attended as ‘Smelves’ (the hybrid of a smurf and an elf, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ongoing investigation into Acton stabbing
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-ongoing-investigation-into-acton-stabbing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 11:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Steve Bohnel,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-ongoing-investigation-into-acton-stabbing/</guid>
        <description>The Metropolitan police are still searching for a minicab driver they believe played a role in the fatal stabbing of 18-year-old Khalid Safi on December 1st – which occurred near Woodward Buildings, one of Imperial College’s residence halls.
Safi, who was living in Southwark, was stabbed in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Keep your hands off our mascots
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-keep-your-hands-off-our-mascots/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 11:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-keep-your-hands-off-our-mascots/</guid>
        <description>A controversial paper was presented at Union Council last Wednesday which suggested the creation of a Masctotry Policy that would protect the student body from violence that occasionally manifests itself during mascot stealing raids.
The paper presented by Council Ordinary Member (Undergraduate …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Crying epidemic hits Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-crying-epidemic-hits-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 11:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-crying-epidemic-hits-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Imperial students have finally cracked under the pressure of university life, if the South Kensington mass crying events that have been popping up on facebook are anything to go by.
As of yet, over 4,000 students have exhibited interest in attending at least one of the three mass sob sessions that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2015 bursary scheme criticised at Council
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-2015-bursary-scheme-criticised-at-council/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 11:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-2015-bursary-scheme-criticised-at-council/</guid>
        <description>Union Council voted to put pressure on College to investigate the legitimacy of the 2015-2016 bursary scheme which has been criticised for not providing adequate funding to students of higher income brackets.
The decision was made based on findings presented by second year physicist Rhidian Thomas. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The ultimate fan girl’s account of women’s eastern regionals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-the-ultimate-fan-girls-account-of-womens-eastern-regionals/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 16:54:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,May Kyaw,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-the-ultimate-fan-girls-account-of-womens-eastern-regionals/</guid>
        <description>On the 19th and 20th of November, I participated in the Women’s Eastern Regionals for Ultimate Frisbee. While I could just list the outcomes of matches, I think it’s time the sports section of felix discussed what goes the behind the scenes of an ultimate tournament – particularly from the lens of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Octopush show diving isn’t always bad in sport
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-octopush-show-diving-isnt-always-bad-in-sport/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 16:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Esme Hoston Moore,Sam Maser,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-octopush-show-diving-isnt-always-bad-in-sport/</guid>
        <description>Underwater hockey (or Octopush as it is often called) is a competitive sport combining hockey and snorkelling, played on the bottom of a swimming pool. The rules are similar to hockey, but with shorter sticks (about a foot long), meaning players must dive to the bottom of the pool to flick the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Paralympians achieve legendary status but who was there to witness history in the making ?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-paralympians-achieve-legendary-status-but-who-was-there-to-witness-history-in-the-making-/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 16:48:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Beng Tan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-paralympians-achieve-legendary-status-but-who-was-there-to-witness-history-in-the-making-/</guid>
        <description>The partying and fireworks on a wet, rainy night in and around the Maracanã Stadium marked the grand finale of the biggest sporting showpiece of the year and brought a happy ending to two weeks full of sweat, grit, determination, tension, sportsmanship, joy, tears, more sportsmanship and the very …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Yacht club’s Far-Eastern adventure
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-yacht-clubs-far-eastern-adventure/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 16:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Alex Eckl,Bob Xu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-yacht-clubs-far-eastern-adventure/</guid>
        <description>From the 27th to 31st of October 2016, the 10th China Cup International Regatta was hosted in Shenzhen, attracting over 140 teams from all over the world including Russia, the USA, Australia and Germany, amongst others. Imperial College Yacht Club (ICYC) sent out Team Imperial, comprised of students …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is it a bird? Is it a plane?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-is-it-a-bird-is-it-a-plane/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 16:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Amy Whistlecroft,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-is-it-a-bird-is-it-a-plane/</guid>
        <description>How long can you stay in the air without an engine? In a glider, anything is possible.
On a fresh Sunday morning in November, eight members of the Imperial College Gliding Club, both new and experienced, set off on an expedition to a new airfield. Meeting at university at 6:30am on a Sunday was a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Documentary Corner | James Marsh Special
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-documentary-corner-james-marsh-special/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 14:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Benjamin Collier,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-documentary-corner-james-marsh-special/</guid>
        <description>I often hear people sing the praises of director James Marsh and his two supposed classics Project Nim and Man on Wire. Having recently seen both films, I thought it would be interesting to present my reviews this week in tandem. The reason for this is that I noticed a lot of similarities in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A foundation in fractals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-a-foundation-in-fractals/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 14:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Zofia Strzelecka,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-a-foundation-in-fractals/</guid>
        <description>Fractals are everywhere we look. Clouds, snowflakes, broccoli – even mountains are full of them. Simply put, a fractal is a never-ending pattern that can be defined as ‘a rough or fragmented geometric shape that can be subdivided in parts, each of which is a reduced-size copy of the whole’. This …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>When I was three I wanted to be...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-when-i-was-three-i-wanted-to-be/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 14:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Aran Shaunak,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-when-i-was-three-i-wanted-to-be/</guid>
        <description>Fact: A 10-year old girl discovered a new molecule in her chemistry lesson.
Anyone who did chemistry at school will remember those ball-and-stick molecule toys that teachers used to try and get everyone enthusiastic about covalent bonding. But 10 year old Clara Lazen decided she knew more than her …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>£5 for top quality animal fat
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-5-for-top-quality-animal-fat/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 14:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Ben Sharpless,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-5-for-top-quality-animal-fat/</guid>
        <description>Introduced in September of this year, the revamped £5 bank notes are designed to be more robust and last longer than the previous edition. Already seen in countries like Australia, Canada and Indonesia, these polymer bank notes are designed not to be torn, therefore increasing their lifespan by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial doesn’t need your money
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-imperial-doesnt-need-your-money/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 13:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Alexandre Adler,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-imperial-doesnt-need-your-money/</guid>
        <description>A spectre is haunting Imperial: the spectre of tuition fees. Six years ago now, the conservative-led government tripled fees, expanding on a policy started by New Labour. Students around the country rose up in protest, but to no avail. Since then, young Britons have depended on government loans, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Life Sciences: ‘College says sexual assault = bad’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-life-sciences-college-says-sexual-assault-bad/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 13:49:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-life-sciences-college-says-sexual-assault-bad/</guid>
        <description>An email was sent out on Wednesday, to the Department of Life Sciences, informing recipients of a serious incident of sexual assault taking place last year between members of the department.
The email was signed off by Professor Murray Selkirk (Head of Department), Professor Neil, Fairweather …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Islamic Society prayer room to finally get refurbishment
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-islamic-society-prayer-room-to-finally-get-refurbishment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 13:48:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-islamic-society-prayer-room-to-finally-get-refurbishment/</guid>
        <description>Plans to restore the Brothers’ Prayer Room to an acceptable condition are underway after the issue was brought to the attention of DP Finance and DP Clubs and Societies at the beginning of term. The prayer room is managed by IC’s Islamic Society, and located at 9B Princes Gardens.
The prayer room …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jailbreakers return breaking past records
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-jailbreakers-return-breaking-past-records/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 13:43:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-jailbreakers-return-breaking-past-records/</guid>
        <description>As another year nears its conclusion so does another Jailbreak challenge. This year’s annual travelling competition, organised by IC RAG, broke the previously held record for participation, as well as for distance travelled by a single team. The winners Ayush Dharap and Rohan Prasad from team …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>American Football make Pirates walk plank
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-american-football-make-pirates-walk-plank/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 14:52:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Imraj Singh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-american-football-make-pirates-walk-plank/</guid>
        <description>It has been a rough road for the IC Immortals, recently relegated from the highest tier of American Football in the country, to Division one. Immortals have now had the sweet taste of victory that had been missed so dearly.
After a close overtime defeat, Immortals were fearful of a repeat of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Thames gets seal of approval
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-thames-gets-seal-of-approval/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 13:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Emma Parkin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-thames-gets-seal-of-approval/</guid>
        <description>Over a pint in Clapham, my friend exclaimed that they, along with the entire top deck of the 345 bus, had seen a seal in the Thames on the way to college. At first I was sceptical. Whilst the odd whale has occasionally been known to take a wrong turn, how could anything, especially something as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tis the season to be... cryogenically frozen?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-tis-the-season-to-be-cryogenically-frozen/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 13:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Abigail Sawyer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-tis-the-season-to-be-cryogenically-frozen/</guid>
        <description>For starters, here’s a myth buster: Walt Disney was not actually cryogenically frozen. With news emerging this week concerning a terminally ill 14-year-old girl winning a court case against her father allowing her to be cryogenically frozen, I decided to explore exactly what this entails.
First of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>They want our data | The UK’s Internet Crisis
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-they-want-our-data-the-uks-internet-crisis/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 13:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Dan Slocombe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-they-want-our-data-the-uks-internet-crisis/</guid>
        <description>Edward Snowden said that “Arguing that you don’t care about the right to privacy because you have nothing to hide is no different than saying you don’t care about free speech because you have nothing to say.” And, while we may have nothing to hide here at felix, we have plenty to say.
Theresa May …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What went down at the Education demo
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-what-went-down-at-the-education-demo/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 13:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-what-went-down-at-the-education-demo/</guid>
        <description>Saturday saw thousands of students and academics take to the streets to protest government cuts and education reforms.
The procession started near Hyde Park and progressed through central London with students holding signs and shouting chants such as ”no ifs, not buts, no education cuts” For its …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>VP Education kicks off teaching consultations
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-vp-education-kicks-off-teaching-consultations/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 13:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-vp-education-kicks-off-teaching-consultations/</guid>
        <description>Imperial launched its College-wide consultation on the Learning and Teaching Strategy this Wednesday with a Town Hall meeting which saw Vice-Provost of Education, Simone Buitendijk, address the issues raised by Imperial’s disappointing NSS scores. “All of us know that student experience isn’t …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Road accident hospitalises medical students
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-24-road-accident-hospitalises-medical-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2016 16:44:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-24-road-accident-hospitalises-medical-students/</guid>
        <description>Three Imperial students were among the four pedestrians injured last night during a car collision on North End Road. The accident occurred shortly before 18:45 when it is believed, according to Metropolitan Police reports, that a black Audi A3 crashed into the pedestrians.
The three medical …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
