<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/artur_donaldson/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/artur_donaldson/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>No Silent Spring with Extinction Rebellion</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-no-silent-spring-with-extinction-rebellion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-no-silent-spring-with-extinction-rebellion/</guid>
        <description>The past nine months have seen the birth of Extinction Rebellion in the UK, the global school strike for climate movement and, of course, the weekly Sustainability column in Felix. Before the newspaper goes on hiatus until October, it seems only fitting to report on the events which, to a large …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Review of Petals of Blood</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-a-review-of-petals-of-blood/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-a-review-of-petals-of-blood/</guid>
        <description>In a sentence, Petals of Blood is a story of change through the eyes of those oppressed. The author, Ngũgĩ wa Thiong’o, uses the murder, by arson, of three prominent figures in an emerging town to frame the narrative of the transformation of a backward (or unblemished?) village into a prospering (or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Today China has consumed more natural resources than it can replenish</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-today-china-has-consumed-more-natural-resources-than-it-can-replenish/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-today-china-has-consumed-more-natural-resources-than-it-can-replenish/</guid>
        <description>For each year since 1970, the first year that humanity began to consume more resources than the Earth can replenish in a year, the Global Footprint Network (a non-profit think tank) has calculated the date when humanity exhausts its budget of natural resources for the year. The calculation of this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flying regularly not crucial for success in academia</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-flying-regularly-not-crucial-for-success-in-academia/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-flying-regularly-not-crucial-for-success-in-academia/</guid>
        <description>Science is quite rightly celebrated for being an international enterprise, and academics often feel required or obliged to fly frequently and over long-distances in order to conduct their work or maintain professional relationships. But how important is long-distance travel to a scientific career, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In response to Big Daddy Oil</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-in-response-to-big-daddy-oil/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-in-response-to-big-daddy-oil/</guid>
        <description>A recent article in Felix, “Big Daddy Oil outearns Apple and Google, wants more”, reported on records seen by the Financial Times which assert that the state-owned oil company Saudi Aramco has a greater net income than any other company worldwide. Since many of the graduates of this university, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don’t call your country “developed” </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-don-t-call-your-country-developed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-don-t-call-your-country-developed/</guid>
        <description>Is the UK developed or developing? What about Vietnam - developed or developing?
The World Bank no longer uses the terms “developed” or “developing” and I couldn’t agree more. The distinction of “developed” and “developing” countries date to the period just after the Second World War, when …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Not yet (bothered to be) recycled</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-not-yet-bothered-to-be-recycled/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-not-yet-bothered-to-be-recycled/</guid>
        <description>From crisps to coke, and pears to pizzas, almost everything we buy today is wrapped, boxed or bottled in plastic. Disposable packaging is, by definition, used just once yet, according to the government recycling agency WRAP, they make up 40% of all plastic used in the UK. A key part to changing this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kobala Revisited: Afriquoi storm XOYO</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-kobala-revisited-afriquoi-storm-xoyo/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-kobala-revisited-afriquoi-storm-xoyo/</guid>
        <description>Afriquoi describe themselves simply as an “afro supergroup” who perform “live African dance music fusing Congolese guitar + Gambian kora virtuosity with UK electronic sensibilities”. Its band members: Andre Marmot (on percussion), Jally Kebba Susso (kora), Fiston Lusambo (guitar), Andre Espeut …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Going on in the world this week</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-going-on-in-the-world-this-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-going-on-in-the-world-this-week/</guid>
        <description>Brazil – This week Brazil’s government announced that it will no longer be hosting the UN global summit on climate change next year citing costs. The conference could cost Brazil up to $100 million. Brazil spent $4.6 billion on the 2015 Olympic games and it is expected that $33 trillion worth of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Going on in the world </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-going-on-in-the-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-going-on-in-the-world/</guid>
        <description>Monday sees the beginning of the COP 24 conference in Katowice, Poland. Previous conferences include 2015’s COP 21, in which 190 nations committed to limiting the rise in global temperatures to 1.5°C above pre-industrial levels.
In other news, Felix sees the beginning of a new column on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don’t Be a Mug – Bring a Mug</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-don-t-be-a-mug-bring-a-mug/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-don-t-be-a-mug-bring-a-mug/</guid>
        <description>On Monday 5th November, Taste Imperial introduced a 15p charge on disposable coffee cups across its outlets on all campuses. The environmentally-conscious initiative is part of the Greening Imperial campaign which has already seen the removal of single-use plastic cups from water dispensers and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Free this weekend? Go to MozFest!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-free-this-weekend-go-to-mozfest/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-free-this-weekend-go-to-mozfest/</guid>
        <description>This weekend will mark the biggest party on the World Wide Web not on the World Wide Web – Mozilla Festival or “MozFest”.
Organized by Mozilla, the creators of that web browser with the fire-tailed fox as its logo, Mozilla Festival is a festival like no other. Mozilla Festival will be split into six …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>GDPR is a good start, but it’s up to us to protect our online privacy</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-gdpr-is-a-good-start-but-it-s-up-to-us-to-protect-our-online-privacy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-gdpr-is-a-good-start-but-it-s-up-to-us-to-protect-our-online-privacy/</guid>
        <description>Even if you didn’t read Kapilan’s article in last week’s Felix, the new General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) will not have escaped your attention thanks to the barrage of emails you will have received over the past few weeks.
GDPR could have a profound influence on the future of the World Wide …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why Facebook “Protect” is all but protection</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-05-why-facebook-protect-is-all-but-protection/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-05-why-facebook-protect-is-all-but-protection/</guid>
        <description>This week, WIRED reports that Facebook has been trialling a new feature for the iOS Facebook app, called “Protect”. The little blue shield directs you to the App Store where you will be prompted to download “Onavo Protect”, an app Facebook bought in 2013. This supposed safety-enhancing app is a VPN …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
