<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/tech/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Tech Headlines: 9th December 2019</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-tech-headlines-9th-december-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sudarshan Sreeram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-tech-headlines-9th-december-2019/</guid>
        <description>Qualcomm XR2 - 5G Ready AR Glasses
At a special event in Maui, Hawaii, Qualcomm announced its new AR platform - XR2 5G, which succeeds the company’s older XR1 platform that still powers a number of VR and AR experiences. According to Qualcomm, the XR2 is the world’s first 5G-supported extended …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Augmented Reality and Intelligence Automation</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-augmented-reality-intelligence-automation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sudarshan Sreeram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-augmented-reality-intelligence-automation/</guid>
        <description>Everyone’s heard of artificial intelligence, more commonly known as AI, but have you heard of intelligence augmentation, or IA? No, it’s not an illegal substance that alters your thinking capabilities to make you highly intelligent; though, it does come close!
IA is closely linked with AI, but it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tech Headlines: 29th November 2019</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-tech-headlines-29th-november-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sudarshan Sreeram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-tech-headlines-29th-november-2019/</guid>
        <description>Cybertruck Unveil
Elon Musk announced Tesla’s new electric pickup truck - Cybertruck. The physical appearance of the truck sure caught everyone off guard. With a low-poly inspired futuristic aesthetic, this truck challenges the conventional design of modern vehicles in general, let alone pickup …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tech Headlines: 22nd November 2019</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-tech-headlines-22nd-november-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sudarshan Sreeram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-tech-headlines-22nd-november-2019/</guid>
        <description>Above: The Ford Mustang Mach-E
Audi E-Tron Sportback
At the LA motor show, Audi unveiled its second electric vehicle, the Audi E-Tron Sportback. Powered by a dual motor setup and with a range of of up to 446 kilometres, this car uses the same base drivetrain and battery as its older brother, the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Huawei Ban</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-the-huawei-ban/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sudarshan Sreeram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-the-huawei-ban/</guid>
        <description>Sci-fi based movies and television series often show a person or a group of people in their mid to late 20s cut off power to an entire city by hacking into a power grid or steal data from a ‘target’ by hacking their internet connected devices. A well-known example of this is CW’s “The Flash”, where …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Automation and Virtual Assistants</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-automation-virtual-assistants/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sudarshan Sreeram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-automation-virtual-assistants/</guid>
        <description>The past decade has seen the rise of digital virtual assistants and a big boom in the home automation industry. If you’ve seen the movies “Flubber” (1997) or “Chitty Chitty Bang Bang” (1968), you’ll know what I’m talking about; from machines that cook you a breakfast meal to a virtual assistant that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Gamification of Apps</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-gamification-apps/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-gamification-apps/</guid>
        <description>Gamification may be the best way to maximise revenue and grow the userbase of your app. It’s a well-known technique these days, the darling of UX developers everywhere, and a fundamental part of design. Once a niche, it has become the standard – integrated from the very conception of an app idea. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Form Factor of Modern Smartphones</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-form-factor-modern-smartphones/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sudarshan Sreeram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-form-factor-modern-smartphones/</guid>
        <description>Smartphones, and mobile phones in general, are nothing but merely an extension of the human mind; to put it simply, these devices serve as external information banks and keep us connected with the outside world. Always adapting and evolving to meet the needs of the consumer, the form-factor (i.e. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Impromptu Part V - Detailing Impromptu</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-impromptu-part-v-detailing-impromptu/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sahir Khurshid,Tom Burgoyne,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-impromptu-part-v-detailing-impromptu/</guid>
        <description>Hello again, Felix readers! Congrats on finishing your exams! Our prior instalments have touched on some of the general do’s and dont’s of setting up a tech start up, and also our personal journey. In this final issue of the term, Tom and I detail Impromptu.
The inspiration for the app stems from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Impromptu Part IV - Our Own Story</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-impromptu-part-iv-our-own-story/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sahir Khurshid,Tom Burgoyne,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-impromptu-part-iv-our-own-story/</guid>
        <description>Hello Felix readers! This week Tom and I move into more personal territory, touching on the beginning of our journey as entrepreneurs. This will be followed next week by a final piece detailing Impromptu itself.
The inspiration for our decision to create an app stems from our time as PhD students in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Impromptu Part III - Realising your Ideas</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-impromptu-part-iii-realising-your-ideas/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sahir Khurshid,Tom Burgoyne,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-impromptu-part-iii-realising-your-ideas/</guid>
        <description>Welcome back Felix readers, time for our third instalment! Having laid the correct framework for your ideas and performed your background research, we now discuss how you realise your ideas in practical terms&amp;hellip;.
Funding
Having validated your idea, your primary concerns will be economic. Where …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Impromptu Part II - How to Get Off the Ground</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-impromptu-part-ii-how-to-get-off-the-ground/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sahir Khurshid,Tom Burgoyne,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-impromptu-part-ii-how-to-get-off-the-ground/</guid>
        <description>Background research
This is where a background in an analytical discipline comes up trumps. Think of this as a research project. Is there a demand for your proposed idea? Look into how unique your idea is, what your selling points are and how viable your idea is. Will it be possible to monetise your …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Impromptu Part I - Getting the Basics Right</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-impromptu-part-i-getting-the-basics-right/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sahir Khurshid,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-impromptu-part-i-getting-the-basics-right/</guid>
        <description>Hello Felix readers! We are Sahir and Tom, and over the course of the next few weeks we will be writing regular articles about the trials and tribulations of creating a tech start-up.
You may ask why we are doing this. We currently have our own app, Impromptu, in development and we are really …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>HP #WomeninTech Roundtable</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-hp-womenintech-roundtable/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-hp-womenintech-roundtable/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday 10th April, Felix attended a roundtable discussion on the perceived barriers of women in the UK to joining the tech industry.
The event was jointly hosted by HP and The Fawcett Society, the UK’s leading organisation campaigning for equality between women and men, and drew upon an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Should we subsidise pre-schools?’ - a debate between man and AI</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04--should-we-subsidise-pre-schools-a-debate-between-man-and-ai/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Krithika Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04--should-we-subsidise-pre-schools-a-debate-between-man-and-ai/</guid>
        <description>Earlier this month, IBM Research and Intelligence Squared U.S. sponsored an event where Project Debater, IBM’s AI debating machine, and Harish Natarajan, a debating expert, discussed whether pre-schools should be subsidized. Both sides had fifteen minutes to prepare on the topic given on the spot. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are we nearing the last stages of the Apple wave?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-are-we-nearing-the-last-stages-of-the-apple-wave/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Krithika Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-are-we-nearing-the-last-stages-of-the-apple-wave/</guid>
        <description>Apple - the one phone brand everybody knows. Even if you haven’t owned an Apple product in the past decade, you have probably seen somebody in Hyde Park taking a selfie with their new iPhone XR or the person sitting next to you in the library on their MacBook Air. Ever since 2007, Apple has enjoyed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A power shift? </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-a-power-shift/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sharada Joshi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-a-power-shift/</guid>
        <description>Once upon a time, around 30 years ago, the oil industry was at the forefront of technological innovation, pushing boundaries with creations borne out of necessity, such as digital well logs, electrical submersible pumps and 3D seismic imaging tools, which use sound waves to create a 3D image of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Medical Devices under the Spotlight</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-medical-devices-under-the-spotlight/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aline Buat,Krithika Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-medical-devices-under-the-spotlight/</guid>
        <description>Technology has dramatically changed every aspect of life as we know it, with medicine being one of the most important aspects. Medicine has been revolutionized through medical imaging, drugs, implants and more. What happens, however, when the medical device industry fails? The International …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Network - the new student exclusive application that  is rethinking the university experience</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-network-the-new-student-exclusive-application-that-is-rethinking-the-university-experience/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Erald Veliaj,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-network-the-new-student-exclusive-application-that-is-rethinking-the-university-experience/</guid>
        <description>Network, a student exclusive application founded by Erald Veliaj, launched this summer at Goldsmiths, University of London and has now opened up for Imperial. The application automatically connects students based on information such as the course they’re taking, what country they’re from and who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A new way to say ‘Hello!’ to the World of coding</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-a-new-way-to-say-hello-to-the-world-of-coding/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aline Buat,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-a-new-way-to-say-hello-to-the-world-of-coding/</guid>
        <description>Programming is, for those who don’t know anything about it, a mysterious and intimidating subject. However, at any point in our careers, we might be placed in a situation where some coding knowledge is needed. And not only there: it is enough to look at the media, or more specialized websites to be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Too distracted by your phone to study? The Hold App is here to help you out</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-too-distracted-by-your-phone-to-study-the-hold-app-is-here-to-help-you-out/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aline Buat,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-too-distracted-by-your-phone-to-study-the-hold-app-is-here-to-help-you-out/</guid>
        <description>It has been one and a half months since the end of summer break, and I guess many of our students already feel submerged by the workload and are willing to be more efficient. However, simple observations from the classroom show us that using our phones during class or revision affects our focus. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is Elon Musk Making the Biggest Crypto-Giveaway in the World?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-is-elon-musk-making-the-biggest-crypto-giveaway-in-the-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Krithika Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-is-elon-musk-making-the-biggest-crypto-giveaway-in-the-world/</guid>
        <description>This Monday, more than a dozen verified accounts were hacked into by scammers impersonating Elon Musk. The scammers claimed that they were giving away 10,000 Bitcoin(BTC) after resigning from the job of being the director of Tesla.
“I’m giving 10 000 bitcoin (BTC) to all community! I left the post …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Artificial Intelligence for Social Good</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-artificial-intelligence-for-social-good/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Haaris Asghar,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-artificial-intelligence-for-social-good/</guid>
        <description>Google.org is an arm of Google that aims to support nonprofits through grants and contributing employee volunteer hours. The $25 million pool announced recently aims to support any ideas of situations where AI could be realistically applied. Winning organisations would not only receive funding, but …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcoming the most powerful iPad Pro yet</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-welcoming-the-most-powerful-ipad-pro-yet/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Krithika Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-02-welcoming-the-most-powerful-ipad-pro-yet/</guid>
        <description>Another iPad was introduced this week - the iPad Pro. It isn’t, however, just another iPad as this is said to have the biggest changes ever and will push the functionality of these devices farther than ever before.
This model has a 11-inch and 12.9-inch Liquid Retina displays to the edges of iPad …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Free this weekend? Go to MozFest!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-free-this-weekend-go-to-mozfest/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-free-this-weekend-go-to-mozfest/</guid>
        <description>This weekend will mark the biggest party on the World Wide Web not on the World Wide Web – Mozilla Festival or “MozFest”.
Organized by Mozilla, the creators of that web browser with the fire-tailed fox as its logo, Mozilla Festival is a festival like no other. Mozilla Festival will be split into six …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your hours are numbered – Emit style!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-your-hours-are-numbered-emit-style/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Krithika Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-your-hours-are-numbered-emit-style/</guid>
        <description>Be honest with me - how many times did you pull an all-nighter last year? How many times did you start an assignment at the last minute, this questionable decision justified by saying that “diamonds are made under pressure”? We are three weeks into college and some of us have already found that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wishing You an Appy New Year in London</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-wishing-you-an-appy-new-year-in-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-wishing-you-an-appy-new-year-in-london/</guid>
        <description>Whether you are new to London or you’ve always lived here, the collecton of apps in this article consists of apps many Londoners use daily, and many more you may be unaware of. Either way, they are sure to help you out if you haven’t used them before.
Citymapper
If you are new to London or even if …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Volkswagen – you are one SaaSy car!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-your-filename/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Krithika Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-your-filename/</guid>
        <description>Volkswagen (VW) has recently signed a deal with Microsoft to use their Azure cloud-based system. This gives them the portal to the highly sought after world of Software as a Service (SaaS).
“The Volkswagen Automotive cloud will be built from the ground up on top of Microsoft’s Azure cloud and IoT …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Apple announces new iPhones and a watch this fall</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-apple-announces-new-iphones-and-a-watch-this-fall/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kapilan M,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-apple-announces-new-iphones-and-a-watch-this-fall/</guid>
        <description>Following Apple’s 10th anniversary iPhone X that was announced last fall, the now trillion-dollar company returns to announce a slew of new devices that fully embrace the notch-life; with the three new iPhone models, the home button is now officially dead and new devices going forward will start …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What did we miss?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-what-did-we-miss/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Mrazek,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-what-did-we-miss/</guid>
        <description>The light blinded me as I climbed out of my cave. For many, time essentially stopped around March and didn’t restart until their very last exam. I was one of those people, and until a few hours ago I was convinced that nothing happened in the world of tech for the past three months.
Holy crap was I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“We have updated our privacy policy” – a closer look into GDPR </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07--we-have-updated-our-privacy-policy-a-closer-look-into-gdpr/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kapilan M,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07--we-have-updated-our-privacy-policy-a-closer-look-into-gdpr/</guid>
        <description>Europe’s General Data Protection Regulation, otherwise known as GDPR, is a set of new regulations that has the potential to fundamentally flip the – increasingly strained – relationship between the massive technology companies that gather data and the users from whom they gather it.
The issue of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix reports: Wearable Technology Show 2018</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-felix-reports-wearable-technology-show-2018/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Krithika Balaji,Robert Jin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-felix-reports-wearable-technology-show-2018/</guid>
        <description> Virtual Reality – the shift from gaming to healthcare
 Current therapy for psychological phenomena like anxiety, depression, and addiction involves going to a therapist on a regular basis (maybe once a week) and talking with them about your progress. They would suggest treatment goals and tips that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A deep dive: Cambridge Analytica</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-a-deep-dive-cambridge-analytica/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Hubert Kaluzny,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-a-deep-dive-cambridge-analytica/</guid>
        <description>Cambridge Analytica have been successfully controlling the minds of thousands of people – if not hundreds of thousands – since 2013. Working for political parties for over 200 elections in the United States and the United Kingdom, as well as Argentina, the Czech Republic, Kenya, India, and Nigeria, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Amazon’s latest purchase – a ‘smart’ doorbell</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-amazon-s-latest-purchase-a-smart-doorbell/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Krithika Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-amazon-s-latest-purchase-a-smart-doorbell/</guid>
        <description>Recently, Amazon, an American electronic commerce and cloud-computing company, bought US firm Ring for more than $1 billion. The firm produces high-tech doorbells that records live videos of the customer’s doorstep and sends it to their smartphone. Ring hopes that working with Amazon will allow it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Applications of blockchain technology</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-applications-of-blockchain-technology/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Hubert Kaluzny,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-applications-of-blockchain-technology/</guid>
        <description>X but on the blockchain”, has become as much of a technological mantra as “Uber but for X” in these recent months. Apart from the sharp peaks and shallow troughs of the price of cryptocurrencies produced by a mutual belief of value, is there any practical use of blockchain technology?
Smart …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why Blackboard?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-why-blackboard/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Thushaan Rajaratjam,Annika Guez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-why-blackboard/</guid>
        <description>Blackboard. The main framework that manages all the course material and information for most departments, and yet it still remains flawed. It is currently the principal exchange platform between professors and their respective students when it comes to sharing notes, tutorials, and all other …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pioneering treatments for healing chronic wounds</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-05-pioneering-treatments-for-healing-chronic-wounds/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xiuchen Xu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-05-pioneering-treatments-for-healing-chronic-wounds/</guid>
        <description>Chronic wounds differ from normal acute wounds, because they do not go through the normal healing process of inflammation, proliferation, and remodelling; instead they stop at the inflammation stage, and the healing process is stopped completely. Chronic wounds often require amputations, and may …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why Facebook “Protect” is all but protection</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-05-why-facebook-protect-is-all-but-protection/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Artur Donaldson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-05-why-facebook-protect-is-all-but-protection/</guid>
        <description>This week, WIRED reports that Facebook has been trialling a new feature for the iOS Facebook app, called “Protect”. The little blue shield directs you to the App Store where you will be prompted to download “Onavo Protect”, an app Facebook bought in 2013. This supposed safety-enhancing app is a VPN …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sweat analysis – a new direction for wearables</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-sweat-analysis-a-new-direction-for-wearables/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Krithika Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-sweat-analysis-a-new-direction-for-wearables/</guid>
        <description>Northwestern University professor John A. Rogers last Friday published, along with other scientists, his research on a wearable microfluidics sweat analytics device in the journal Science Advances. He is now collaborating with many partners such as Gatorade, the Seattle Mariners, and the U.S. Air …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Falcon Heavy: looking past a brilliant publicity stunt </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-falcon-heavy-looking-past-a-brilliant-publicity-stunt/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Mrazek,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-falcon-heavy-looking-past-a-brilliant-publicity-stunt/</guid>
        <description>Finally. There’s late, and then there’s this rocket. Conceived in 2004, Falcon Heavy was in the works before I could ride a bike or reliably spell the word “rocket”. Sure, expecting a timely release from Elon Musk would be simply ludicrous, but this is a bit much even by future-leader-of-Mars’ …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC Hack 18 – a first timer’s perspective</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-12-ic-hack-18-a-first-timer-s-perspective/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kapilan M,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-12-ic-hack-18-a-first-timer-s-perspective/</guid>
        <description>Let’s admit it, pizza at midnight is the real driving force behind the technological advances of the past few years. The Hackathon is essentially the culture that built the technological titans of today - Facebook, Google and Microsoft. And the annual hackathlon organised by DocSoc keeps up that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Audio Focus: An introduction to over-ear IEMs</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-12-the-audio-focus-an-introduction-to-over-ear-iems/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Robert Jin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-12-the-audio-focus-an-introduction-to-over-ear-iems/</guid>
        <description>If you frequently turn up the volume on your earbuds to overcome external noise, you are at a high risk of noise induced hearing loss over time. The average hearing threshold for a young adult lies between 18 to 20 kHz, but can fall to as low as 15 to 16 kHz due to long exposure to sound above 85 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The future of medicine – edible QR codes?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-12-the-future-of-medicine-edible-qr-codes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Krithika Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-12-the-future-of-medicine-edible-qr-codes/</guid>
        <description>If you are ill, chances are you would book an appointment with your doctor. They would listen to your heartbeat, do some tests and then prescribe some medicines based on your symptoms. A trip to your local pharmacy would result in a bag full of medications, some of which being the ones that your …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Organs-on-Chips – A catalyst for drug testing?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-organs-on-chips-a-catalyst-for-drug-testing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Krithika Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-organs-on-chips-a-catalyst-for-drug-testing/</guid>
        <description>According to the World Health Organization (WHO), antibiotic resistance in bacteria is one of the biggest threats to global health today. Bacteria gaining resistance is a natural process, but this has been accelerated by the misuse of medicines. The consequence of this is that bacteria remain …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Should we trust governments with our faces?  </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-should-we-trust-governments-with-our-faces/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Hubert Kaluzny,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-should-we-trust-governments-with-our-faces/</guid>
        <description>London is one of the world’s most surveilled cities. Recently, China has begun using facial recognition to keep track of one of their district’s Muslim populations. Ethically speaking, I believe we can all agree that, this is one of the worst uses of modern technology we have seen to date. At the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Some of the biggest tech announcements of 2017 </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-some-of-the-biggest-tech-announcements-of-2017/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ignatius-Roy Hillcoat-Nalletamby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-some-of-the-biggest-tech-announcements-of-2017/</guid>
        <description>March 2017 saw the phoenix that is Nintendo rise from its ashes with the release of its new console the Nintendo Switch. Marketed as a truly versatile game console, the Switch can be played in three modes – TV mode for the traditionalists who like a big TV, tabletop mode for when a big TV screen …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why your toothpaste, a Toyota Prius, and a McLaren F1 car have more in common than you think</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-why-your-toothpatse-a-toyota-prius-and-a-mclaren-f1-car-have-more-in-common-than-you-think/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Mrazek,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-why-your-toothpatse-a-toyota-prius-and-a-mclaren-f1-car-have-more-in-common-than-you-think/</guid>
        <description>Steel disc brakes, like many other technologies that make today’s cars so safe and efficient were developed nowhere other than on the racetrack. Until a revised version of the Jaguar C-Type first took to the track in 1953, drum brakes were considered the only practical way of stopping a car. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tesla’s Semi announcement is really just a distraction   </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-tesla-s-semi-announcement-is-really-just-a-distraction/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Mrazek,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-tesla-s-semi-announcement-is-really-just-a-distraction/</guid>
        <description>What came first, the Model 3 or the Falcon Heavy?
What’s the first word that comes to mind when I say Tesla? Performance, ecology? What about delays? If you’ve followed Tesla or SpaceX, you’re undoubtedly aware of a mysterious time zone known as Elon Standard Time™. Symptoms include thinking the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The James Dyson Award – upgrading the world one clever project at a time </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-the-james-dyson-award-upgrading-the-world-one-clever-project-at-a-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ignatius-Roy Hillcoat-Nalletamby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-the-james-dyson-award-upgrading-the-world-one-clever-project-at-a-time/</guid>
        <description>In September 2017, shortlisted entries for this year’s Dyson Award were announced. For those of you who don’t know, the Dyson Award is an international award for current and recently graduated design engineering students, coordinated by the James Dyson Foundation. The main purpose of the award is to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gene Drives – A technology capable of changing entire species</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-gene-drives-a-technology-capable-of-changing-entire-species/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xiuchen Xu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-gene-drives-a-technology-capable-of-changing-entire-species/</guid>
        <description>Gene drive technology allows humans to introduce genetical modifications to species that are always passed on to the next generation, which allows a characteristic to become prevalent in a species over very few generations. The technology is powerful enough to wipe out whole species, and has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The October 4th Google Event: Pixel 2 and More</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-the-october-4th-google-event-pixel-2-and-more/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ignatius-Roy Hillcoat-Nalletamby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-30-the-october-4th-google-event-pixel-2-and-more/</guid>
        <description>Google announced a host of new products in San Francisco on the 4th of October this year. Everyone eagerly awaited the announcement, particularly the unveiling of the company’s second flagship smartphone, the Pixel 2. However, in true Google fashion, there were a few surprises in the announcement …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is Elon Musk Big Brother?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-is-elon-musk-big-brother/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Mrazek,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-is-elon-musk-big-brother/</guid>
        <description>Our story begins with the jellyfish, the first animal to have a nervous system – or rather a nervous net. An animal without a nervous net can’t respond to its environment, so its odds of survival could be likened to flipping a coin. Having one was a real breakthrough. Later on, the flatworm …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Engineering the Hyperloop prototype
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-engineering-the-hyperloop-prototype/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 14:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Osama Awara,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-3-engineering-the-hyperloop-prototype/</guid>
        <description>It was in 2012 that the restless entrepreneur Elon Musk first announced his idea for a high speed transport system – the Hyperloop. Described by the magnate as ‘a cross between a Concorde, a railgun and an air hockey-table,’ this next-generation train system aims to transport people at speeds of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The art of war for faceless people
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-the-art-of-war-for-faceless-people/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 18:09:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Osama Awara,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-the-art-of-war-for-faceless-people/</guid>
        <description>The previous few weeks have seen a surge in cyber warfare like no other. From the Sony Pictures hacking over The Interview – a satire film depicting the assassination attempt of Kim Jong-Un, to the ISIS hacking of US Central Command Twitter account. The hacktivist group Anonymous have vowed to take …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Taking another step into the smartphone world
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-taking-another-step-into-the-smartphone-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 18:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-taking-another-step-into-the-smartphone-world/</guid>
        <description>This week Felix released the latest version of its app for iPhone. It includes a major revamp of the way it works, adding benefits both in its user interface and in its engine for the user. Today Felix Technology takes a look at what we should expect from the latest addition to _Felix_’s digital …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Millions injured in worst Friday since Rebecca Black
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-millions-injured-in-worst-friday-since-rebecca-black/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 19:29:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>James Dutton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-millions-injured-in-worst-friday-since-rebecca-black/</guid>
        <description>Horror at Currys PC World Workington branch as millions of people flocked to the store to pick up excellent deals on the best and latest technology, ranging from 2.5mm microphone cables to ruby-encrusted vibrators.
The opening was just like any day but the first people to arrive were literally …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to a world of ups and downs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-welcome-to-a-world-of-ups-and-downs/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 19:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chrysostomos Meli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-welcome-to-a-world-of-ups-and-downs/</guid>
        <description>Silicon Valley has for some time now declared an all-out war on our non-electronic habits, changing them to fit around their technology. It has been a gradual process but thinking about it, we certainly don’t read books the way we used to. Writing an essay barely involves a pen anymore, we can go …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Microsoft: stepping back into the future
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-microsoft-stepping-back-into-the-future/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 13:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chrysostomos Meli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-microsoft-stepping-back-into-the-future/</guid>
        <description>Since the explosion of the smartphone, Microsoft has been facing an ever-increasing uphill struggle. With the introduction of iOS and Android, Windows is no longer the only viable OS option out there. iPads and Android tablets might not be the productivity powerhouses that Windows is, but they have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Commercialisation in creative technology
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-commercialisation-in-creative-technology/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 12:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Xuan Chen,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-commercialisation-in-creative-technology/</guid>
        <description>The release of the iPad in the UK in the early summer of 2010 was a watershed moment which forever changed the way we interact with application technology. It was only a matter of time before a number of social entrepreneurs decided to weave the creative talent together in the form of conventions, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s no Razr, but Motorola are back on the map
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-its-no-razr-but-motorola-are-back-on-the-map/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 12:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Paul Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-24-its-no-razr-but-motorola-are-back-on-the-map/</guid>
        <description>The Moto 360 is one of the first Android Wear devices to launch this year, amongst the LG G Watch and Samsung Gear variants. Sporting a round face and elegant design, it is one of this year’s most highly desired gadgets. At £199 it’s also one of the more expensive, but the combination of Google’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wearable technology – watch this space
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-wearable-technology-watch-this-space/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 22:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chrysostomos Meli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-wearable-technology-watch-this-space/</guid>
        <description>Tech-companies want to expand their product portfolio outside of smartphones, and with iPad and tablet sales falling quarter after quarter and all the variety in screen sizes pretty much exhausted, where do they go from here?
For some, the answer to that question seems to be wearable technology. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Microsoft hope 3 is the magic number
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-microsoft-hope-3-is-the-magic-number/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 22:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Osama Awara,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-microsoft-hope-3-is-the-magic-number/</guid>
        <description>The third generation of Windows tablets, or Lablets as I like to call them, have been released by Microsoft. They claim that the Surface Pro 3 is not only a tablet, but a laptop as well, potentially replacing both of those devices in your home. After owning one for several weeks, I can honestly back …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A breath of fresh air in an old and stale industry
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-a-breath-of-fresh-air-in-an-old-and-stale-industry/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 20:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chrysostomos Meli,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-a-breath-of-fresh-air-in-an-old-and-stale-industry/</guid>
        <description>You don’t have to be a petrolhead to know that the automobile industry hasn’t been the most innovative over the years. Since the introduction of the Model T in 1908, the car has remained largely unchanged. It might have become faster, more reliable and more efficient over those 100 years but no …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Yearly Review: The Big ones
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-19-yearly-review-the-big-ones/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 18:45:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-19-yearly-review-the-big-ones/</guid>
        <description> Microsoft A year when the redmond based company only really got into the news because of the numerous U-turns they did, as well as falling really far behind to Sony in the next-gen console devices. However, dropping of the kinect device as well as a lowering of the price, allows the XBone to be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>KILLER ROBOTS
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-19-killer-robots/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 18:44:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-19-killer-robots/</guid>
        <description>Recently a new breakthrough was achieved in the field of robotics. Pepper, a robot from Japan, is now able to read emotions from its human masters.
Furthermore, it can change its behaviour according to this information. However, most horrifically, is the fact that pepper will be able to dance, joke …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Programming: Easy, Peasy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-11-programming-easy-peasy/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 21:37:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-11-programming-easy-peasy/</guid>
        <description> It is now summer (for most of us at least!). If you have nothing lined up for you, and would like to learn something new or do something productive, why not consider learning how to program?
Why learn to program? Have you ever tried to rename hundreds of files, or tried to organise some data files …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>OS X, iOS and full-frontal Apple
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-11-os-x-ios-and-full-frontal-apple/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 21:33:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-11-os-x-ios-and-full-frontal-apple/</guid>
        <description> In recent times I have become quite disillusioned with Apple. The keynotes were kinda boring, and there was nothing really interesting. I usually tuned in to the keynotes just because I felt that I should. In fact, it got to the point that this time around, I almost missed the keynote. When I did …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Google: Now the ultimate innovators?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-google-now-the-ultimate-innovators/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 01:48:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cornelius M O Makanjuola,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-google-now-the-ultimate-innovators/</guid>
        <description>Google announced a few weeks ago via a Google+ post that it has plans to create its very own smartwatch. No concrete details on the wearable device are known as of yet, but the sources across the netscape indicate that it could build on already established partnerships with HTC, Asus, LG and others. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to get into Ghostblogging!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-how-to-get-into-ghostblogging/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 01:46:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-how-to-get-into-ghostblogging/</guid>
        <description>Choosing a platform
As soon as I had finished installing Ghost on a cloud virtual server, my good friend Luke G-B pointed out the existence another awesome blogging/CMS platform called WagtailCMS.
WagtailCMS is a Django-powered Content Management System created by Torchbox, a web design consultancy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>August EP650 Headphones
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-august-ep650-headphones/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 15:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-26-august-ep650-headphones/</guid>
        <description>Almost a year and a half ago I stumbled across the wonderful world of Bluetooth headphones. For those of you who might remember, back then a naïve tech writer I had just decided to splash out on a pair of 20 quid headphones from Amazon, namely the SX-907. To date this still remains my most popular …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial’s own smartwatch
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-11-imperials-own-smartwatch/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2014 17:42:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Serge Vasylechko,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-11-imperials-own-smartwatch/</guid>
        <description>A few of months ago a couple of Imperial College students set out on an adventure to create the world’s most versatile smartwatch – BLOCKS. Since then the team, expanded to 8 people, entered Imperial Create Lab’s £20,000 challenge and are getting ready to “Pitch at St James’ Palace” event in April. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Mt Gox Bitcoin Debacle
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-the-mt-gox-bitcoin-debacle/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 06:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-the-mt-gox-bitcoin-debacle/</guid>
        <description>The fledgling cryptocurrency Bitcoin suffered one of its biggest setbacks this past week when the (formerly) largest exchange Mt. Gox filed for bankruptcy protection. The beleaguered exchange has been marred by a string of management problems before it filed for bankruptcy protection. Yet, the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Future of Social Media
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-future-of-social-media/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 03:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Osama Awara,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-future-of-social-media/</guid>
        <description>When you hear the term social media, what comes to mind? Facebook? Twitter? Or perhaps even that embarrassing video you were tagged in by your friends last night. Of the modern age of technology, social media has perhaps had the most profound effect on our lives, reaching out with its addictive grip …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Future of Social Media
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-19-future-of-social-media/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 21:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Osama Awara,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-19-future-of-social-media/</guid>
        <description>When you hear the term social media what comes to mind? Facebook? Twitter? Or perhaps even that embarrassing video you were tagged in by your friends last night. Of the modern age of technology, social media has perhaps had the most profound effect on our lives, reaching out with its addictive grip …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Find the egg-laying chicken #yoyonotyolo
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-12-find-the-egg-laying-chicken-yoyonotyolo/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 12:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-12-find-the-egg-laying-chicken-yoyonotyolo/</guid>
        <description>ME: Introduce yourself:
MR: My name is Michael Rolph, I am the co-founder of Yoyo which has launched very recently here at Imperial.
ME: What is the history of Yoyo, how did you guys start out?
MR: I’ve got a personal background which is very much from the payment space. Ex-Barclaycard business, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tired of all those Wires?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-5-tired-of-all-those-wires/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 10:22:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-5-tired-of-all-those-wires/</guid>
        <description>I hate wires. Every time I look at the back of my PC and I see the bunch of wires, my OCD kicks in. Luckily, I can usually sit at my desk and pretend the wires are not there.
Not for the mobile phone. When you need to charge it, transfer data, or listen to music, you have to pluck some bloody cables …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Return to paper?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-5-return-to-paper/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 10:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-5-return-to-paper/</guid>
        <description>Yes, Facebook, has turned 10. Ten years this giant has been sucking out our souls, killing our times and generally trying to inject itself into every aspect of our lives. Now they have introduced their next strategy in their multi-pronged attack to make themselves virtually indispensible, a reader …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix on the move!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-29-felix-on-the-move/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 16:24:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kunal M L Wagle,Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-29-felix-on-the-move/</guid>
        <description>ME: Introduce yourself!
KW: I am a first year Computing student from London. I currently reside in the Southside Halls of Residence.
ME: What is your position in Felix?
KW: I am the sports editor. I follow most sports, particularly football, cricket and tennis, so I felt that when the opportunity …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Paying in style: #yoyonotyolo
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-29-paying-in-style-yoyonotyolo/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 16:19:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-29-paying-in-style-yoyonotyolo/</guid>
        <description>You must have seen it around these days, the proliferation of pink flyers littering imperial’s walkways. Flyers that seem to have the word yolo written on them. However fear not my dear students, our university has not descended into a swag-palace. No these flyers actually say yoyo on them, and what …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Consumer Electronics Show
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-consumer-electronics-show/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 04:24:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Osama Awara,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-consumer-electronics-show/</guid>
        <description>The Consumer Electronics Show (CES) is an annual technology and consumer products show held every January in Las Vegas. Being the global stage that attracts next generation innovations and electronics, CES is the largest of its kind, showcasing over 3000 exhibitors from computer hardware …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Steelseries 9H Tournament Headset
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-steelseries-9h-tournament-headset/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 04:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Technology,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-steelseries-9h-tournament-headset/</guid>
        <description>Steelseries. It’s a name all gamers are familiar with, and it’s a company which deals with all aspects of a gamers needs by providing good quality peripherals and accessories. The Steelseries 9H is a top range headset from the H series of tournament grade headsets provided by Steelseries and has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fancy shmancy tech from Santa
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-fancy-shmancy-tech-from-santa/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 16:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-fancy-shmancy-tech-from-santa/</guid>
        <description> Every year, as Christmas nears, I would like to think that I have some really rich and wealthy relative who is a Lord somewhere, perhaps some Lord of the Silicon. I would then write up a list of five items I would really like to have and then present it to them, knowing that I would probably get …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tech for X-Mas
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-tech-for-x-mas/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 16:23:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Osama Awara,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-tech-for-x-mas/</guid>
        <description> Samsung KN55S9C OLED TV If you’ve ever thought that HD pictures were not enough, fear no more, the Samsung OLED TV that uses organic self-emitting pixels would blow your mind away this Christmas giving you the best quality, surpassing even the best LCD TVs. This TV doesn’t come cheap, expect to be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who doesn&#39;t need a Roomba?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-who-doesnt-need-a-roomba/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 16:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-who-doesnt-need-a-roomba/</guid>
        <description>iPhone 5S
Considering how much of an apple fan I am, I think this is a bit of an obvious one. At the moment I have an iPhone 5, and I don’t see the 5S as enough of an upgrade to pay out that much money. I mean sure the 64-bit processor and the fingerprint scanner are all really nice, but do I want …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Encryption moving forward
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-27-encryption-moving-forward/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 16:04:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-27-encryption-moving-forward/</guid>
        <description>The recent spate of NSA tapping data and storing huge amount of internet traffic has been rather worrying. The exposé courtesy of Edward Snowden has made end-users more aware of the need for encryption, and accelerated the process of enhancing the security between end users and the service providers …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Ultimate Luxury Tech List
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-13-the-ultimate-luxury-tech-list/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2013 22:57:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Osama Awara,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-13-the-ultimate-luxury-tech-list/</guid>
        <description> Alienware laptops: If you ever imagined what a laptop in the future might look like, just take a look at these gaming laptops; the must-have gadget for any hard-core gamer. When you compare the specs of the Alienware to your average PC world or Curry’s laptops, it is light-years ahead. Carrying the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>5 Things Tablets are/have killing/ed
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-13-5-things-tablets-arehave-killinged/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2013 22:53:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-13-5-things-tablets-arehave-killinged/</guid>
        <description> Elegance of making a photo: In our day and age everything has a camera attached to it. Your phone, your mp3 player, my god, even your fridge could have a camera for all we know. Therefore it is not a surprise that your tablet has a camera. How many times have you seen someone with their tablet in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>CRTALT/CHANGEing the world
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-13-crtaltchangeing-the-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2013 22:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aaron Ng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-13-crtaltchangeing-the-world/</guid>
        <description>There is no doubt that technological advancements over the past few decades have had immense impact on our society. Those of us living comfortable lives in developed countries celebrate the latest gadgets and how they have made our lives even simpler. But meanwhile, there are still many people out …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Google Releases the Nexus 5
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-6-google-releases-the-nexus-5/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 17:22:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-6-google-releases-the-nexus-5/</guid>
        <description>After many weeks of speculations, leaks, and overwhelming anticipation, Google has finally taken the wraps off their new flagship phone, the Nexus 5. The Nexus 5 is, like the Nexus 4, manufactured by LG and modelled after one of their flagship phones, and comes in black and white colours. The Nexus …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>10 Things Smartphones Slaughtered
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-6-10-things-smartphones-slaughtered/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 17:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-6-10-things-smartphones-slaughtered/</guid>
        <description> After last weeks Osama Awara’s “10 things the Internet has slaughtered”, I decided to write something in a similar vein, except of course exchanging one vital invention (internet) of our lives for something equally important (smartphones). So here goes (in no particular order).
Dedicated hand-held …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Steve Wozniak at Apps-World 2013
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-30-steve-wozniak-at-apps-world-2013/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 16:10:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>William F N Daubney,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-30-steve-wozniak-at-apps-world-2013/</guid>
        <description>Steve Wozniak, known by many as Woz was the keynote speaker of Apps-World 2013 at Earls Court, London. As a member of the press via my website, I was invited and given a press pass. The whole day was a very surreal experience, basically being treated like a member of royalty as each exhibitor tries …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>10 things the internet has slaughtered
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-30-10-things-the-internet-has-slaughtered/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 16:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Osama Awara,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-30-10-things-the-internet-has-slaughtered/</guid>
        <description> 1. Movie Stores Long gone are the days of popping in to your local Blockbusters and buying that VHS tape or DVD that had you sorted for the night. With the boom of wireless internet from your Ming Dynasty era dial-up connection, streaming movies/shows online has never been quicker or easier. With …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Apple’s New Keynote and What it Means for You
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-30-apples-new-keynote-and-what-it-means-for-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 15:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-30-apples-new-keynote-and-what-it-means-for-you/</guid>
        <description>As mentioned in last weeks news bubble Apple had a key note last tuesday. That day confirmed most rumours on the internet as well as some pleasant surprises. However if you are looking at the news, scratching your head and wondering how this will affect anything in your life, read on dear reader and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cyber black market is no more
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-cyber-black-market-is-no-more/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 00:59:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Osama Awara,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-cyber-black-market-is-no-more/</guid>
        <description>Known and loved by its many users and advocates as the Silk Road Marketplace, this underground website dubbed as the ‘amazon.com’ and ‘e-bay’ of illegal drugs has officially been shut down by the FBI. Seizing what is believed to be $3.6 million dollars in bitcoins, a small fraction of their $80 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NSA: Peeling the skin off TOR users
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-16-nsa-peeling-the-skin-off-tor-users/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 14:00:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Osama Awara,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-16-nsa-peeling-the-skin-off-tor-users/</guid>
        <description>The NSA known for its privacy breaching of internet users across the globe has been found ‘peeling’ the encryption that Tor provides for its users’ information sent online, in order to gain access to sensitive information. Tor is a piece of software, ironically funded by the US government, which …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get rich quick, Youtube style!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-16-get-rich-quick-youtube-style/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 13:56:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-16-get-rich-quick-youtube-style/</guid>
        <description>All of you spend a significant amount of your life on youtube, be it watching handy tutorial videos, lets-plays, music videos and/or videos of cute-ass kittens (the last being the most time intensive). However have you ever wondered why some of these Youtubers, more often than not just average …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The crippling effect of Technology
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-the-crippling-effect-of-technology/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 23:50:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maximilian Eggl,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-the-crippling-effect-of-technology/</guid>
        <description>This is a very interesting question I found myself talking about with a friend recently. Is technology really making us weaker, mentally and physically? If you consider that technology is part of the human condition, then you would disagree and I would be on your side. All the brilliant things that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>3-D Printers take off!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-3-d-printers-take-off/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 19:38:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Osama Awara,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-3-d-printers-take-off/</guid>
        <description>Launching a rocket into space is in itself a tricky business; well after all it is rocket science! Being able to repair one or a space station for that matter is a different ball game altogether. NASA has plans to launch their very own 3-D printer by next year, and for those of you who aren’t …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Torrid State of the Onion
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-the-torrid-state-of-the-onion/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 19:32:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-the-torrid-state-of-the-onion/</guid>
        <description>It was something like a 90s cyberpunk’s dream: an anonymous, hidden marketplace on the “deep web” where everything from research psychedelics to stolen credit card details could be bought. The Silk Road, considered by some a bold experiment in libertarianism, by others the biggest online hotbed of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nexus 7 Review!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-nexus-7-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 19:30:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Yong Wen Chua,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-nexus-7-review/</guid>
        <description>The Nexus series of devices released by Google is now a staple amongst many Android users’ arsenal of devices. Initially touted as a benchmark setting niché series of devices, the Nexus series has spawned off its own fanbase for users who are interested in always having the latest version of Android …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
