<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sa1908/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sa1908/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>FIG grows by finding eleven more businesses to invest in
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-fig-grows-by-finding-eleven-more-businesses-to-invest-in/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 20:36:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sina Ataherian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-fig-grows-by-finding-eleven-more-businesses-to-invest-in/</guid>
        <description>Read part one
In 2009, James King founded Find Invest Grow (FIG). FIG is a young company that funds and supports promising enterprises started-up by university students, including from Imperial College. James currently serves as its CEO. The firm is involved with fifteen different student-led …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The economy and small businesses
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-the-economy-and-small-businesses/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 05:51:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sina Ataherian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-the-economy-and-small-businesses/</guid>
        <description>The third business in our week on start-ups is Find Investment Grow (FIG). James King, its founder and CEO, gave his first Felix interview in October 2009, when he had just started his student-focused venture capital firm. In the year and a half since, his family of start-up businesses has grown …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How they started up: introducing a week of interviews with real entrepreneurs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-how-they-started-up-introducing-a-week-of-interviews-with-real-entrepreneurs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 19:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sina Ataherian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-how-they-started-up-introducing-a-week-of-interviews-with-real-entrepreneurs/</guid>
        <description>Throughout the year, largely due to reader interest, the business section has a strong emphasis on finance. This fits with many Imperial students’ desire to learn more about the industry, in order to stay informed and help with their career choices. This being an undergraduate newspaper, this seems …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lehman loses law suit in US against Barclays
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-lehman-loses-law-suit-in-us-against-barclays/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 19:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sina Ataherian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-lehman-loses-law-suit-in-us-against-barclays/</guid>
        <description>The estate of Lehman Brothers lost a law suit on Wednesday against Barclays over the sale of its investment banking and brokerage businesses to Barclays. The sale was made in September 2008 in the same week that Lehman filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy. The company received $1.85 billion and was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Will the BoE raise its rates?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-will-the-boe-raise-its-rates/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 19:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sina Ataherian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-will-the-boe-raise-its-rates/</guid>
        <description>A mid growing concern over the Bank of England’s focus on and commitment to keeping its inflation targets, one more committee member joined calls to raise interest rates. According to minutes from the latest monetary policy meeting, three members now find “the case for removing some monetary …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Midterm elections: what do they mean for US businesses?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-midterm-elections-what-do-they-mean-for-us-businesses/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 18:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sina Ataherian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-midterm-elections-what-do-they-mean-for-us-businesses/</guid>
        <description>As the Republicans retake the House of Representatives, analysts debate whether they will they ease the burden on businesses or let them down like it’s 1994
Tuesday saw the US midterm elections, ending months of speculation about the extent of predicted Democrat loses. These elections were seen as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Two miners rumble in the Congo
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-two-miners-rumble-in-the-congo/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 19:33:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sina Ataherian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-two-miners-rumble-in-the-congo/</guid>
        <description>Last year, the Government of the Democratic Republic of Congo terminated the mining license of First Quantum Minerals, the Canadian owner of Kolwezi copper mine. This was a considerable blow for First Quantum, which spent US$750m developing the mine, a move that generated over a quarter of the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
