<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/vmh14/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/vmh14/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The vital importance of being mediocre
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-the-vital-importance-of-being-mediocre/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 18:39:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Vivien Hadlow,Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-the-vital-importance-of-being-mediocre/</guid>
        <description>University is a time for learning new things. By the time you leave you’ll (hopefully) be able to make nutritionally passable food, complete group projects without stabbing anyone, and compose the perfect passive aggressive group chat message about washing up. But, arguably apart from the content of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can men advise on how to respond to sexual harassment?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-can-men-advise-on-how-to-respond-to-sexual-harassment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 09:51:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vivien Hadlow,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-can-men-advise-on-how-to-respond-to-sexual-harassment/</guid>
        <description>Picture the scene: A friend of yours has just told you about an experience of theirs, one in which they experienced discrimination, and they’re pissed off. Why did they tell you? So you could explain to them how their reaction to the situation was wrong, right?
It’s not news that many women have to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All I want for Christmas is the truth
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-15-all-i-want-for-christmas-is-the-truth/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 12:47:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vivien Hadlow,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-15-all-i-want-for-christmas-is-the-truth/</guid>
        <description>Every year, a strange phenomenon occurs: trees are decorated, gifts are exchanged, and the world decides that it is again time to deceive millions upon millions of impressionable children.
Whenever someone discovers that I’ve never believed in Santa, the customary reaction is to lament my poor, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My period is not a luxury
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-30-my-period-is-not-a-luxury/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 12:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vivien Hadlow,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-30-my-period-is-not-a-luxury/</guid>
        <description>As a student, the list of items I would define as “luxury” is quite long. Branded chocolate, new razors, shoes without holes in – for all these things there is a feasible, if less appealing, alternative.
So, when HMRC classify sanitary products as part of this list, what alternative could they …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
