<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mguenot/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mguenot/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Sh!t Sc!ence
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-sht-scence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 09:20:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marianne L Guenot,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-sht-scence/</guid>
        <description>At Sh!t Sc!ence, we’ve been trying to provide evidence that the scientific method that is in place is an effective filter, and that as such, there is no such thing as ‘shit science’. But as it is the end of the year, and you might be going off to glorious academic careers, here are a few things you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sh!t Sc!ence
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-sht-scence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 08:26:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marianne L Guenot,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-sht-scence/</guid>
        <description>At Sh!t Sc!ence, we want to show that every science paper is a drop of water that, in its small way, helps fill up the aquarium of human knowledge, so that us little humans can float around happily oxygenated by the water of cognition. This week, you may have guessed, we are talking about fish.
Have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sh!t Sc!ence
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-sht-scence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 09:18:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marianne L Guenot,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-sht-scence/</guid>
        <description>At Sh!t Sc!ence, we like to show how all science is special, a little bouncing 1-UP that your character runs towards to let it continue through the game. This version of Sh!t Sc!ence is a little different. Because this week, I’m not going to be talking about research that sounds silly, or useless. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sh!t Sc!ence
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-sht-scence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 09:08:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marianne L Guenot,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-sht-scence/</guid>
        <description>At Sh!t Sc!ence we like to defend the lil’ science, the science that gets bullied, the science that gets wedgies from the bigger sciences when it tries to speak up, because we believe that every science, no matter how puny, has value and should be respected. This week: archaeology. Need I say more? …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sh!t Sc!ence
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-sht-scence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 09:02:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marianne L Guenot,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-sht-scence/</guid>
        <description>At Sh!t Sc!ence, we like to defend research that may seem insignificant or futile. We believe that all research projects go through a complicated selection process during which a group of learned intellectuals congregate and decide what particular pieces of research need to be conducted in order to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sh!t Sc!ence
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-sht-scence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 09:55:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marianne L Guenot,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-sht-scence/</guid>
        <description>At Sh!t Sc!ience, we believe that all science, no matter how stupid it sounds, has a purpose and adds to the sum of human knowledge. This week: the science of gingerness.
You’ll have seen this story. From Prince Harry to Julianne Moore, the honorary heads of the ginger committee are strewn across …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sh!t Sc!ence
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-sht-scence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 11:49:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marianne L Guenot,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-sht-scence/</guid>
        <description>At Sh!t Sc!ence, we try to show that all science, preposterous as it may sound, is useful to humanity and increases the sum of human knowledge. That is, even when the research seems to investigate something that is so bleeding self-evident, it makes you want to cry.
This week’s study, published in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sh!t Sc!ence
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-sht-scence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 11:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marianne L Guenot,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-sht-scence/</guid>
        <description>At Sh!t Sc!ence, we believe that all science has a purpose, and helps us better understand the fascinating world we all live in. Especially when scientists spend some time exposing the sexual deviances of Quebeckers.
Quebec: an anomaly in itself. A french bastion buried in the frozen confines where …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sh!t Sc!ence
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-sht-scence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 11:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marianne L Guenot,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-sht-scence/</guid>
        <description>At Sh!t Sc!ence, we argue that all research, no matter how outrageously ridiculous-sounding, has a purpose and contributes to widen our knowledge of the world. Even when it is a study of how fish can be left-handed.
Well… not left-handed, per se. It turns out that a specific type of fish called the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sh!t Sc!ence
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-sht-scence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 11:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marianne L Guenot,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-sht-scence/</guid>
        <description>At Sh!t Sc!ence, we argue that all research, no matter how ridiculous, has a purpose and brings us all closer to the truth.
This week: penguins. You thought you knew just how adorable they were, but that was until you heard the news that makes them frigging awesome. Fat penguins are scientifically …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sh!t Sc!ence
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-sht-scence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 11:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Marianne L Guenot,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-sht-scence/</guid>
        <description>Cockroaches are despised by everyone. With the whole human race out to squash them into oblivion, you’d think they’d have died out by now. But instead, they thrive, popping up in the most random places, and miraculously surviving the most vigorous squashing. Scientists have therefore spent months …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
