<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Photos on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/highlights/photos/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Photos on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/highlights/photos/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Colour and Light: Degas&#39; mastery of pastels
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-25-colour-and-light-degas-mastery-of-pastels/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 12:41:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-25-colour-and-light-degas-mastery-of-pastels/</guid>
        <description>Glasgow’s Burrell Collection, which was amassed by shipping magnate William Burrell, is closed until 2020 for refurbishment; a loss, perhaps, for Glasgow, but a boon for Londoners, who are able to view the Collection’s celebrated Degas works, which have never travelled before as a group. It is these …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Getting to the truth of Jasper Johns
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-22-getting-to-the-truth-of-jasper-johns/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 18:56:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-22-getting-to-the-truth-of-jasper-johns/</guid>
        <description>On the way out of the press viewing of the Royal Academy&amp;rsquo;s latest exhibition, Jasper Johns: ‘Something Resembling Truth’, an immense monograph of the titan of 20th century American art, I overhear a fragment of a conversation: “and when did he die?”
Johns is still going strong, but it is an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cassini bids farewell in its Grand Finale
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-15-cassini-bids-farewell-in-its-grand-finale/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 12:09:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kenza Tazi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-15-cassini-bids-farewell-in-its-grand-finale/</guid>
        <description>Before 1:00 PM (GMT) today, the Cassini spacecraft will bid us a final farewell. We will take a closer look at this mission, the furthest orbiting space operation from Earth, and what we can expect in the last moments of Cassini’s life.
On October 15th 1997, Cassini was launched from Cape Canaveral, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Waiting for Godot has its definitive homecoming at the Arts Theatre
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-12-waiting-for-godot-has-its-definitive-homecoming-at-the-arts-theatre/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 09:25:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-12-waiting-for-godot-has-its-definitive-homecoming-at-the-arts-theatre/</guid>
        <description>Billed as its “definitive homecoming” Samuel Beckett’s tragicomedy Waiting for Godot returns to the Arts Theatre after the first English-language production premiered there in 1955.
Nick Devlin and Patrick O’Donnell are delightfully childish and mercurial as vagabonds Didi and Gogo, who seem to love …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Xenia Hall&#39;s management to be taken over by Salvation Army Housing Association
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-1-xenia-halls-management-to-be-taken-over-by-salvation-army-housing-association/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 09:14:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-1-xenia-halls-management-to-be-taken-over-by-salvation-army-housing-association/</guid>
        <description>Chapter 1, the charity that owns and manages Xenia hall, is to be merged with the Salvation Army Housing Association (Saha) at the end of September.
The hall, which is located in Waterloo, accommodates 149 Imperial students. Saha, “a leading provider of residential centres for single and homeless …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brainsnatchers: Microbes that change the way we behave
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-31-brainsnatchers-microbes-that-change-the-way-we-behave/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 10:57:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maya Kaushik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-31-brainsnatchers-microbes-that-change-the-way-we-behave/</guid>
        <description>Friday night, work finally done, I sit down in my favourite pub and order a pint. I’m tired, maybe a bit grumpy. A couple of pints in and I’m happy, my energy levels are up, I’m chatting to everyone vibrantly. A couple more pints and I’m dragging myself home somewhat stupefied.
Alcohol is just one …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cooked breakfast removed from SCR menu amid wide-ranging changes to campus services
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-26-cooked-breakfast-removed-from-scr-menu-amid-wide-ranging-changes-to-campus-services/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2017 14:02:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-26-cooked-breakfast-removed-from-scr-menu-amid-wide-ranging-changes-to-campus-services/</guid>
        <description> On the 31st July, the Senior Common Room (SCR) served its last cooked breakfast to Imperial College London staff and students. From the 1st August, the SCR has removed cooked breakfasts from its menu as part of a wide-ranging series of changes to campus services, affecting a number of areas.
As …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>National Student Survey results reveal wide ranges in student satisfaction
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-25-national-student-survey-results-reveal-wide-ranges-in-student-satisfaction/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 10:26:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-25-national-student-survey-results-reveal-wide-ranges-in-student-satisfaction/</guid>
        <description> The results from the National Student Survey (NSS), which saw a number of universities omitted following a boycott, show a divide among Imperial students, with a wide range in satisfaction rates between undergraduate courses.
The survey, which is given to all final-year undergraduates, showed that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your Name: Freaky Friday by way of Kierkegaard
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-20-your-name-freaky-friday-by-way-of-kierkegaard/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 18:26:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-20-your-name-freaky-friday-by-way-of-kierkegaard/</guid>
        <description>In his latest amine film Your Name, which has broken box-office records in Japan and beyond, director Makoto Shinkai chooses a plot-line which has a long pedigree: body swapping. Shuffling characters’ consciousnesses around is a trope that stretches back to the 19th Century and beyond. In Your Name, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial student halls fail fire safety tests on cladding
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-9-imperial-student-halls-fail-fire-safety-tests-on-cladding/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 09:48:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-9-imperial-student-halls-fail-fire-safety-tests-on-cladding/</guid>
        <description>The cladding system used in Woodward Buildings, one of Imperial College London’s newly-built student halls, has failed governmental fire safety testing. Sources from inside the hall also report multiple failures to adhere to fire safety policy, Felix can reveal.
The results of the tests were …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Eurovision Song Contest: The pop and the politics*
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-7-eurovision-song-contest-the-pop-and-the-politics/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 08:55:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-7-eurovision-song-contest-the-pop-and-the-politics/</guid>
        <description> I once had the misfortune of watching Eurovision with only an Argentinian, a Mexican, and a Lebanese for company. If you’re not European (or Australian, apparently), Eurovision seems to be very confusing and completely un-understandable. For us Europeans, either on the mainland or stuck on little …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>XU | the brainchild of BAO is a beautiful addition to the London food scene
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-xu-the-brainchild-of-bao-is-a-beautiful-addition-to-the-london-food-scene/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 17:10:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-xu-the-brainchild-of-bao-is-a-beautiful-addition-to-the-london-food-scene/</guid>
        <description>Two years into this half-university-student-half-food-blogger life of mine and I already have a lifetime’s worth of cringe worthy moments – mostly encountered during blogger events and restaurant invites. Imagine: turning up to the door of a launch event to know that my name had never been added to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>E3 2017 | Follow up
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-e3-2017-follow-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 17:06:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Qasim Mahmood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-e3-2017-follow-up/</guid>
        <description>Microsoft had a few more reveals, including PlayerUnknown’s Battlegrounds, State of Decay 2, Minecraft in 4K and DragonBall FighterZ. They then proceeded to an extended look at Sea of Thieves, Rare’s open-world pirate game, which featured treasure hunting, riddle solving and a large-scale naval …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Fellwanderers Easter Tour
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-imperial-fellwanderers-easter-tour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:59:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Emma McCracken,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-imperial-fellwanderers-easter-tour/</guid>
        <description>Following an early flight at 7am from Gatwick to Aberdeen, we arrived in the scenic village Braemar in the Cairngorms national park at around 1pm. Kate, the provider of Rucksacks accommodation, greeted us as we sleepily got off the bus. Luckily Braemar was the end of the line, as otherwise we …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Soul of a Nation | A searing portrait of the Civil Rights Era
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-23-soul-of-a-nation-a-searing-portrait-of-the-civil-rights-era/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 12:13:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-23-soul-of-a-nation-a-searing-portrait-of-the-civil-rights-era/</guid>
        <description>“Is there a black aesthetic, and if there is, what form does it take?” is the question that concerns the artists assembled for Soul of a Nation. For some, like the Spiral collective, the answer lay in monochrome paintings with a strong political message. In Norman Lewis’ America the Beautiful, a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Summer Exhibition at the Royal Academy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-15-the-summer-exhibition-at-the-royal-academy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 15:17:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-15-the-summer-exhibition-at-the-royal-academy/</guid>
        <description>There aren’t many galleries in which you might expect to see a multimillion pound creation by a Turner prize winning artist exhibited on equal footing with an oil by Joe Bloggs from Surrey, but that is exactly what the Royal Academy’s Summer Exhibition offers. Each year, tens of thousands of works …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Keeping Track of Imperial’s Cross Country &amp; Athletics Club
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-keeping-track-of-imperials-cross-country-athletics-club/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:42:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Fergus Johnson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-keeping-track-of-imperials-cross-country-athletics-club/</guid>
        <description>Saturday the 27th of May saw the final event in the London Universities and Colleges Athletics (LUCA) outdoors championship take place. The series of three athletics meets between the London universities had previously visited St. Mary’s and Woodford athletics tracks, and the destination for the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The great age of the 3DS
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-the-great-age-of-the-3ds/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:25:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-the-great-age-of-the-3ds/</guid>
        <description> The 3DS has been the go-to portable games machine of its time, testified by the sales of over 65 million units, and is a shining example of how to make a perfect handheld console. Its only other portable rival, the Playstation Vita is as good as dead these days, and mobile games don’t even come …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Manifesto breakdowns
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-manifesto-breakdowns/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:59:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,Cale E Tilford,Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-manifesto-breakdowns/</guid>
        <description> This piece aims to break down the main party manifestos and summarise a few key policies. This is by no means a full and in-depth analysis of each party. Mainly because the manifestos are long and complex, and it’s exam season. [Insert tinfoil hat theory that the timing of the election coincides …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An idiot’s guide to the UK general election
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-an-idiots-guide-to-the-uk-general-election/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:57:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-an-idiots-guide-to-the-uk-general-election/</guid>
        <description>Ding ding ding, it’s election time again. No, you haven’t woken up from that nap in 2020, they’ve called an early election. Do you have no idea who you’re voting for? Well, you’re in luck my friend, because we’ve got a whole pull-out complete with manifesto breakdowns, and personal views on who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Afterhours sessions in the Central Library
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-afterhours-sessions-in-the-central-library/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:29:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-afterhours-sessions-in-the-central-library/</guid>
        <description>How does one end up in the Library past midnight? Maybe you had a paper to submit tomorrow. You thought you had everything under control. You were halfway there but you made the mistake of taking a break and committing to an episode of the Great British Bake Off. Six hours later you get a text from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The counselling service does not work as advertised
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-19-the-counselling-service-does-not-work-as-advertised/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 15:05:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-19-the-counselling-service-does-not-work-as-advertised/</guid>
        <description>Everyone gets stressed at uni at some point. If you don’t, I applaud your Jedi level of inner peace. But for the rest of us mere mortals, it hits at some point. Because it affects everyone, I just assumed that what I was feeling was normal, that my course was always going to be a tough one and it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fuelling the resistance
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-19-fuelling-the-resistance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 15:03:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Naomi Pratt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-19-fuelling-the-resistance/</guid>
        <description>The greatest obstacle to action on climate change is the one most often missing from discourse: the fossil fuel industry. Since comprehension of anthropogenic global warming began, the fossil fuel industry has been ignored in negotiations and subsidised by governments. Much time and energy has been …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Forests have been hiding in plain sight
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-forests-have-been-hiding-in-plain-sight/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 17:33:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-forests-have-been-hiding-in-plain-sight/</guid>
        <description>Scientists have been missing the forest for the trees; literally, it turns out. A team of international scientists have found that dryland forest cover could be 40% to 47% higher than previously estimated. This corresponds to 467 million hectares (Mha) of forest that have never been reported before …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Xavier Dolan | In praise of popular art
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-xavier-dolan-in-praise-of-popular-art/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 17:21:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Leo Diaz,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-xavier-dolan-in-praise-of-popular-art/</guid>
        <description>Xavier Dolan is not your average director. What first sets him apart is that he is extremely young: 28 at the time of writing, he’s already released six full-length features. He directed his first, I Killed My Mother, when he was just 20, and his 2014 Mommy received the Jury Prize at Cannes, along …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Worthy of Worship | American Gods
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-worthy-of-worship-american-gods/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 17:14:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-worthy-of-worship-american-gods/</guid>
        <description>After a tumultuous five years in development hell, Neil Gaiman’s post-modern blend of Americana and folklore has finally found its way to TV courtesy of Starz and Amazon. American Gods, an adaptation of Gaiman’s 2001 novel by the same name, is at its heart an examination of faith and the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Madama butterfly | A non-opera-goer&#39;s review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-madama-butterfly-a-non-opera-goers-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 16:21:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-madama-butterfly-a-non-opera-goers-review/</guid>
        <description>The Royal Opera House’s Madama Butterfly is a modern take on the operatic classic that showcases a jaw-dropping performance from Ermonela Jaho. Despite this, the newest rendition of Puccini’s ‘ode’ to Japan doesn’t quite pack the punch it needs to drag the piece out of its orientalist past.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Divestment Campaign resurrected
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-imperial-divestment-campaign-resurrected/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 17:05:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-12-imperial-divestment-campaign-resurrected/</guid>
        <description>The divestment campaigners at Imperial are on the move again. This week saw them taking to campus with various events and actions. On Wednesday students dropped a banner off the main union building in Beit Quad. The banner which wrote out in large black and orange letters “IMPERIAL DIVEST NOW!” was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Partenope | A brilliantly off-piste version of a little-performed classic
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-22-partenope-a-brilliantly-off-piste-version-of-a-little-performed-classic/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 17:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-22-partenope-a-brilliantly-off-piste-version-of-a-little-performed-classic/</guid>
        <description>Can 18th century humour still be relevant today? This is the question the ENO are attempting to answer, with the first reprisal of Christopher Alden’s production of Partenope. First performed in 1730, Partenope is an opera not often found on the operatic stage today. Opera in the early 18th century …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The National Wedding Show is decadent and depraved
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-the-national-wedding-show-is-decadent-and-depraved/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 17:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theo Farah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-the-national-wedding-show-is-decadent-and-depraved/</guid>
        <description>As I walked along Hammersmith Road to the convention centre, Kensington Olympia, a faltering bundle of nerves, I scanned my brain for excuses not to enter the palatial structure. Fortified by a cocktail of stimulants, I still felt lacking in brass for my foray behind enemy lines. Twenty-one and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>There&#39;s no place at Imperial for elitist &#39;secret&#39; clubs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-theres-no-place-at-imperial-for-elitist-secret-clubs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 17:01:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Andrew D Olson Gallardo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-theres-no-place-at-imperial-for-elitist-secret-clubs/</guid>
        <description>Everyone studying at Imperial is aware that this place is not perfect. Yes, there are problems with student engagement, mental health, even sexism. But despite these issues, I feel it is the place which has mainly contributed at making me who I am today; the fantastic wardening team in my halls in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial students react to the ECJ&#39;s motion on the banning of religious symbols
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-imperial-students-react-to-the-ecjs-motion-on-the-banning-of-religious-symbols/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 16:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-imperial-students-react-to-the-ecjs-motion-on-the-banning-of-religious-symbols/</guid>
        <description> Banning religious symbols is discrimination Hafiza Irshad discusses the recent ruling by the European Court of Justice The triple penalty that Muslim women face – for being a woman, for being a Muslim and often for being of an ethnic minority group – has never been more prominent. Muslim women are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>So you want to run an Elections 2018 campaign?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-so-you-want-to-run-an-elections-2018-campaign/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 15:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandre Adler,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-so-you-want-to-run-an-elections-2018-campaign/</guid>
        <description>Campaigning for a position in the student elections is the least Imperial-like thing imaginable: you have to talk to strangers while sober. Some coped by campaigning online, thereby retreating safely behind a Facebook page or Twitter account dedicated to their glory, but most of us ended up doing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London Varsity 2017 | Gymnastics on a Pole
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-london-varsity-2017-gymnastics-on-a-pole/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 14:43:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Beng Tan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-london-varsity-2017-gymnastics-on-a-pole/</guid>
        <description>The first thing that comes to mind when you mention pole dancing is pretty obvious. The sexual connotation it carries will remain for as long as clubs continue to offer such services, but there is a sporting aspect to it as well that, though rather well-known as well, is almost certainly not the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Treasures from the Levant
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-treasures-from-the-levant/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 14:02:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanjay Bhattacharya,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-treasures-from-the-levant/</guid>
        <description>To look on at the birth of a new restaurant is always exciting – I’ve been a part of it, having seen the place I worked at in Oxford rise from the ashes of a mediocre Italian cocktail bar, and realising that I really wanted to be a part of that. Teething problems ranged from gutters that drained …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Games to feel good
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-games-to-feel-good/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 13:56:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-games-to-feel-good/</guid>
        <description> Truck Simulator | Or any simulator When you first hear about it, Truck Simulator sounds like a pretty boring game. You’re a truck driver and your job is to make deliveries from one city to another. You’re not even supposed to drive crazily; you’re supposed to obey the traffic laws and you actually …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The best picks for some cinematic self-care
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-the-best-picks-for-some-cinematic-self-care/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 13:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-the-best-picks-for-some-cinematic-self-care/</guid>
        <description> Frances Ha (2012) If there’s one scene that encompasses the exuberant joie-de-vivre present in Noah Baumbach’s Frances Ha, it’s the titular character – played brilliantly by Greta Gerwig, who also co-wrote the screenplay – running and dancing along a Manhattan street to David Bowie’s ‘Modern Love’. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Life with Archie | Riverdale
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-life-with-archie-riverdale/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 15:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-life-with-archie-riverdale/</guid>
        <description>You can now add Riverdale to the increasing list of media adaptations of various forms of literature. Like most recent adaptations, Riverdale also goes for a darker and edgier feel; however in this case, this approach pulls off and actually works spectacularly well. Riverdale is based upon the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Labour has a one way ticket to Switzerland
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-labour-has-a-one-way-ticket-to-switzerland/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 14:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-labour-has-a-one-way-ticket-to-switzerland/</guid>
        <description>T he by-elections in both Stoke and Copeland were both called recently, due to their respective MPs resigning. As I’m sure you are aware, Labour lost the Copeland seat and held on to the Stoke seat, but suffered a reduction in the proportion of votes compared to 2015. This is viewed by many, myself …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can students bear London’s housing crisis?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-can-students-bear-londons-housing-crisis/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 14:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Naulls,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-can-students-bear-londons-housing-crisis/</guid>
        <description>It’s that time of year again. The ‘Private Housing Event’ invitation has appeared on Facebook, your housemates are suspiciously quiet about that looming deadline to renew your tenancy, and the thought of going through the whole process again makes you even more nauseous than that seventh snakebite …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Confused Nursery exhibition
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-the-confused-nursery-exhibition/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 15:34:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Tom Mutimer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-the-confused-nursery-exhibition/</guid>
        <description>Friday of last week, I had the pleasure of attending the Blyth gallery for the opening of a joint exhibition between Leonardo Fine Arts and PhotoSoc, titled ‘Confused Nursery’.
The space is a time machine that will take you back to days you hardly remember and juvenile feelings that you forgot …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ten of the best</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-ten-of-the-best/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 15:23:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-ten-of-the-best/</guid>
        <description> 1 | Dirty Bones Shoreditch Fried chicken on waffles for brunch? Definitely. Hit up Dirty Bones for their boozy brunch menu with mac ‘n’ cheese burgers, short rib crumpets and more heart attack-worthy dishes!
   Christy Lam   2 | Café Loren Looking for a homey, warming breakfast? Café Loren in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>And the Best Picture Award goes to...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-and-the-best-picture-award-goes-to/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 14:19:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-and-the-best-picture-award-goes-to/</guid>
        <description> Arrival | Cale Tilford&amp;rsquo;s pick With Arrival, Denis Villeneuve has turned a tedious and uninteresting topic – the translation of an alien language – into science-fiction spectacle. From its meticulous sound design to its subdued lighting, the whole film looks and sounds otherworldly. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial to go smoke-free*
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-imperial-to-go-smoke-free/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 13:44:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-imperial-to-go-smoke-free/</guid>
        <description>  Smoking may be banned but vaping isn’t (sort of)  Smoking may be banned but vaping isn’t (sort of) Vaping360   It’s official: Imperial will implement a smoking ban on all College campuses and properties starting the 1st of August.
The move which has been in the making for quite some time now, is a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ballin’ on a budget #studentlyfe
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-ballin-on-a-budget-studentlyfe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 18:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shanzeh Khurshid,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-ballin-on-a-budget-studentlyfe/</guid>
        <description> Location, location, location Whilst religiously completing my daily routine of procrastination, I happened to view my friend’s, who seems to have a lot of money to spend on food, snapchat story. She always puts up gourmet looking pictures, but whenever I google the restaurants their prices are so …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Drug Bible | Modafinil 101
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-drug-bible-modafinil-101/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 16:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-drug-bible-modafinil-101/</guid>
        <description> What it does Modafinil is used to increase the alertness of the user. Whilst it is normally used to treat narcolepsy and other sleep disorders, it is also commonly used as a study drug. Once taken, expect to feel more awake and typically less prone to frustration, allowing you to become more …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is porn hurting your brain?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-is-porn-hurting-your-brain/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:54:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-is-porn-hurting-your-brain/</guid>
        <description>Last night I masturbated. That’s not particularly exciting in itself – a pretty standard Thursday night – but when I found myself alone in bed looking for some me-time, I automatically reached for my phone for some inspiration. Realising that I didn’t know when I got in this habit, so I decided to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Robots | All hail our benevolent mechanical overlords
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-robots-all-hail-our-benevolent-mechanical-overlords/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Agnese Abrusci,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-robots-all-hail-our-benevolent-mechanical-overlords/</guid>
        <description>Robots, the Science Museum’s shiny newly-opened exhibition, is a real treasure trove of delights: featuring over 100 robots models it spans 500 years of humanity&amp;rsquo;s quest to recreate itself in the form of a machine, a process historically shaped by religion, industrial innovation, and popular …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hockney makes a splash at this Tate Britain retrospective
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-hockney-makes-a-splash-at-this-tate-britain-retrospective/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adam Gellatly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-hockney-makes-a-splash-at-this-tate-britain-retrospective/</guid>
        <description>Logistically alone, the new David Hockney exhibition at Tate Britain is a marvel. Nearly 150 pieces spanning the breadth of Hockney’s career – paintings, sketches, photography, video, and drawings – have been assembled in a thirteen-room experience. Many of the pieces have been borrowed from David …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Revolution: Russian Art 1917 – 1932 | A terrible festival of dead leaves
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-revolution-russian-art-1917-1932-a-terrible-festival-of-dead-leaves/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-revolution-russian-art-1917-1932-a-terrible-festival-of-dead-leaves/</guid>
        <description>The Royal Academy’s ambitious new exhibition chronicles a troubled period in Russian history, from the overthrowing of the tsarist regime in 1917, through the years of civil war, to the consolidation of power by Stalin after death. In this window of time, art in Russia experienced a brief burgeoning …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>20 th Century Women | All hail Annette Bening
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-20-th-century-women-all-hail-annette-bening/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-20-th-century-women-all-hail-annette-bening/</guid>
        <description>As part of the promotional material for 20th Century Women, director Mike Mills’ latest work, there’s a website called ‘My Mother Before Me’, where users can upload pictures of what their mother looked like before they had children. The shots, which are hazy and saturated, each come with a brief …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Helping out a bee in need
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-helping-out-a-bee-in-need/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Olivia Barber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-helping-out-a-bee-in-need/</guid>
        <description>Over the past few years, discussion of the rapid decline of bee populations has intensified. Every week there seems to be another alarming headline implying that honeybee population decline is something we should care about. Do bees truly impact the world as we know it? Wouldn’t we do just fine …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Putin has a huge power hard on
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-putin-has-a-huge-power-hard-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 14:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-putin-has-a-huge-power-hard-on/</guid>
        <description>From his images in National Media (and yes, those do require capital letters), it’s clear that Vladimir Vladimirovich Putin has a hard on for one man: himself. Whether he’s shirtless fishing, riding a horse, or killing a bear with his bare hands, Putin’s got a thing for being the manliest manly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Alban Hall living conditions deemed poor
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-alban-hall-living-conditions-deemed-poor/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 14:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-alban-hall-living-conditions-deemed-poor/</guid>
        <description>Following the reveal of the poor housing conditions at Evelyn Gardens earlier last year, another Hall of Residence has been found guilty of offering sub-par accommodation, after numerous reports were brought to felix’s attention.
This time, students at Alban Hall have had to consistently deal with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bored of the classic waffle? Me too!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-bored-of-the-classic-waffle-me-too/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 16:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-bored-of-the-classic-waffle-me-too/</guid>
        <description>You should never make a comment about a restaurant before you’ve tried it.”
That was a strong lesson from a man, a total stranger, sitting at the table next to me, which ended our morning debate over the much hyped-about The Breakfast Club a few months back. For him, it was his holy grail breakfast …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Talk dirty to me | Banana Tree
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-talk-dirty-to-me-banana-tree/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 16:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Shanzeh Khurshid,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-talk-dirty-to-me-banana-tree/</guid>
        <description> Where to go On their way to the Royal Albert Hall, my friends and I caught up in Banana Tree in Bayswater. I suggested the restaurant because it’s about 30 minutes walking distance from campus, and only 20 minutes from Wilson House and Pembridge. Ever since she went on a yoga trip to Vietnam, one …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Criminally short | The Benefits of Gusbandry
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-criminally-short-the-benefits-of-gusbandry/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 15:56:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-criminally-short-the-benefits-of-gusbandry/</guid>
        <description>Built from the ground up by creator Alicia J. Rose, this series of ten-ish minute shorts chronicles the ever-evolving relationship between 40-something Oregonite Jackie, and her so-called ‘gay husband’, River. Now, to the uninitiated (as I was) this may conjure up images of cringe-worthy sitcom …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>¡Caliente! Burning up the stage with Tango Fire
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-caliente-burning-up-the-stage-with-tango-fire/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 15:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-caliente-burning-up-the-stage-with-tango-fire/</guid>
        <description>Tango – the word alone conjures images of passion, seduction, and power play. German Cornejo and his sizzling dance crew return to London with Tango Fire to set the stage ablaze. The first part of the show harks back to tango’s roots in the milongas of Buenos Aires. Impossibly glamorous, the five …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reading Drawings
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-reading-drawings/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 15:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-reading-drawings/</guid>
        <description>    Courtauld Gallery   Marginalia are the annotations one finds scribbled in the margins of a text; they can be insightful, witty or rude depending on the commentator in question. Reading Drawings is a new collection at the Courtauld Gallery that aims to showcase the equivalent in drawings – …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s a queer gal to do/see/watch/listen to? Our guide to your gal-pal culture fix
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-whats-a-queer-gal-to-doseewatchlisten-to-our-guide-to-your-gal-pal-culture-fix/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 15:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-whats-a-queer-gal-to-doseewatchlisten-to-our-guide-to-your-gal-pal-culture-fix/</guid>
        <description> Film Appropriate Behaviour
Desiree Akhavan directs and stars in this comedy about an American-Iranian bisexual going through a breakup. It’ll make you feel worse about your recent breakup but then, strangely, better. It’s pretty funny and feels quite real. The protagonist also struggles with coming …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>British short films take us around the globe
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-british-short-films-take-us-around-the-globe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 15:21:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-british-short-films-take-us-around-the-globe/</guid>
        <description>If there is a theme of the nominees for the BAFTAs for Best British Short Film and Best British Short Animation, it would probably be ‘journey’. Across the eight shorts, we are catapulted from one corner of the globe to the next, dealing with themes both big and small. One of the most engaging …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>China charges ahead environmentally
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-china-charges-ahead-environmentally/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 14:04:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sara Hamilton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-china-charges-ahead-environmentally/</guid>
        <description>I can’t speak for everyone, but when I think of China in relation to the environment, an image of coal and smog-full Beijing, with millions of citizens running around in protective anti-pollution masks, springs to mind. Henry Wang, in his talk Energy and Environment Growth Strategies hosted by the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>King&#39;s lecturer apologises for offending Somali community
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-7-kings-lecturer-apologises-for-offending-somali-community/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 15:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-7-kings-lecturer-apologises-for-offending-somali-community/</guid>
        <description>Dr Adam Perkins, the King’s lecturer who last week sparked public outrage after a series of offensive tweets were brought to the attention of King’s Intersectional Feminist Community, has issued a public apology on twitter.
In his apology which was reportedly sent to King’s Intersectional Feminist …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Starving anxiety into submission | Anorexia
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-starving-anxiety-into-submission-anorexia/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 18:07:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-starving-anxiety-into-submission-anorexia/</guid>
        <description>I thought the only way I could dull my anxiety was starving it. If I was dizzy and needed to concentrate hard on staying upright, there was no space left to worry. Before long I’d reach a comfortable haze, unable to carry a thought for more than a few seconds. The emptiness inside my stomach made …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ten of the best
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-ten-of-the-best/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 17:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-ten-of-the-best/</guid>
        <description> 1 | Bleecker Burger The Bleecker Black is probably the best burger in London, with two juicy patties with a layer of black pudding in the middle.
   Christy Lam   2 | Where the Pancakes Are A cute little pancake house serving delicious, homemade pancakes at the back of a bustling food market. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Want some fish in that taco?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-want-some-fish-in-that-taco/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 17:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-want-some-fish-in-that-taco/</guid>
        <description>There’s this one question I always get asked: how do I have the time to fit in lectures in the morning, project-work in the afternoon, while managing an Instagram story saturated with #bloggermail, press events and bearded baristas in tiny independent cafés in god-knows-where?
The answer is – I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bake sale
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-bake-sale/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 17:07:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Harry Wilkinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-bake-sale/</guid>
        <description>Among other smaller, less internationally important incidents, it seems to me that 2016 will be remembered primarily as the year that the BBC lost the Great British Bake Off to Channel 4. In what is ostensibly just a show about people making cakes, you find a lot of what British culture is all …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Resist through cinema!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-resist-through-cinema/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 16:55:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-resist-through-cinema/</guid>
        <description> if&amp;hellip; (1968) Notable both as one of the UK’s only Palme d’Or-winning films, and the work that catapulted Malcolm McDowell to international stardom, Lindsay Anderson’s if&amp;hellip; explores a violent insurrection that takes place at a British public school. As the discipline imposed by the school …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Christine | On the outside looking in
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-christine-on-the-outside-looking-in/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 16:48:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-christine-on-the-outside-looking-in/</guid>
        <description>The television, with its ability to repeatedly display the images of those who have long since departed, can act as an electronic graveyard, conjuring up spirits from the past. It is fitting, therefore, that Christine – the latest film by Antonio Campos, which deals with the on-air suicide of news …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Making my life great again
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-making-my-life-great-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 15:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jian Chew,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-making-my-life-great-again/</guid>
        <description>As I watched Trump’s inauguration ceremony at fivesixeight, where I work, and observed exuberant Americans celebrating with champagne, I got thinking about my life. It’s been in a rut lately, just doing my tutorial sheets, coursework, revising, cooking my meals, feeling homesick over Chinese New …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students take to the streets to protest Trump | Are the days of political apathy over?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-students-take-to-the-streets-to-protest-trump-are-the-days-of-political-apathy-over/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 15:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-students-take-to-the-streets-to-protest-trump-are-the-days-of-political-apathy-over/</guid>
        <description>Donald Trump has consistently been on the collective consciousness for a while. Though Trump’s presidency could globally affect climate change and human rights, to name only a few areas of concern, amongst some journalistic circles, there’s the additional concern that the international focus on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>King’s lecturer sparks racism row
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-2-kings-lecturer-sparks-racism-row/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 23:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-2-kings-lecturer-sparks-racism-row/</guid>
        <description>KCL’s feminist intersectional society has condemned a lecturer at King’s College London after he released a series of tweets which were described as “racist and incredibly insulting remarks directed at the Somali community”.
Dr. Adam Perkins, a lecturer in the Neurobiology of Personality took to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Avocado for breakfast? So #2k16
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-avocado-for-breakfast-so-2k16/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 17:38:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-avocado-for-breakfast-so-2k16/</guid>
        <description>Mezze. A word meaning a selection of small appetizers. And a word that I have recently started noticing following a sharing plates trend that has finally hit the London food scene. After some hearty meals, I have adjusted my taste buds (and stomach) to this wonderful dining culture home to Turkey, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The rising chorus of South Asian voices
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-the-rising-chorus-of-south-asian-voices/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 17:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-the-rising-chorus-of-south-asian-voices/</guid>
        <description>Last Saturday, Aziz Ansari continued his meteoric rise to prominence by being the first person of South Asian descent to host SNL. In his speech, he highlights the rise of a so-called ‘lower-case KKK’; the subtle resurgence and renormalisation of white supremacy. Now more than ever, he suggests, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Terrains of the Body is a bold but beguiling show
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-terrains-of-the-body-is-a-bold-but-beguiling-show/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 17:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-terrains-of-the-body-is-a-bold-but-beguiling-show/</guid>
        <description>Hellen van Meene’s works combine this unsteady storyline with a heady mix of sensual textures and colours. Her works are celebrations of surface, with Vermeer-light like dappling across her subjects, bringing an incredible sense of tactility. Janaina Tschape’s work shares this obsession with tone, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Most anticipated hip-hop albums of 2017
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-most-anticipated-hip-hop-albums-of-2017/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 16:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-most-anticipated-hip-hop-albums-of-2017/</guid>
        <description> 10. Lil Wayne | Tha Carter V Cast your mind back to June 2008. Lil Wayne and Birdman were still best mates and Wayne had just dropped his critically acclaimed sixth studio album, including four top 20 singles, and went on to be Wayne’s most successful to date, selling 3.6 million copies and winning …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hallelujah Money
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-hallelujah-money/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 16:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Sam Wood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-hallelujah-money/</guid>
        <description>Gorillaz are back – and this time they are as political as they are whacky. Having teased a new album through Instagram and SoundCloud releases over the past few months, Gorillaz released the brand new track Hallelujah Money (ft. Benjamin Clementine) on the eve of Trump’s inauguration. The Damon …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Our Academy Award #hottake
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-our-academy-award-hottake/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 16:46:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-our-academy-award-hottake/</guid>
        <description>The announcement of the nominees for the 89th Academy Awards this week marked the beginning of the end of the year-long awards process, which begins with the Cannes Film Festival in May, and ends with the Oscars, 8 months later. As usual, the list of nominees contains few surprises, with the Academy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Protesting Trump | The Women’s March through the eyes of Imperial students
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-protesting-trump-the-womens-march-through-the-eyes-of-imperial-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 14:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-protesting-trump-the-womens-march-through-the-eyes-of-imperial-students/</guid>
        <description>    Indira Mallik   Ana Villanueva | felix reader I asked myself a question the first time I heard about the Women’s March: Is it necessary? The answer is yes. I joined tens of thousands of people because I needed to share a message too. It was not a complaint. We advocated tolerance and respect for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union launches 2017-20 strategy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-union-launches-2017-20-strategy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 14:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-union-launches-2017-20-strategy/</guid>
        <description>The Union launched a new three year strategy last week in Metric, at an event that was the culmination of a six month effort to meet (or at the very least express) the needs and wants of Imperial students. Despite vigorous consultation though, student reaction was luke-warm.
The strategy is a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How not to fall in love with someone (from Metric)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-how-not-to-fall-in-love-with-someone-from-metric/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Theresa Davey,Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-how-not-to-fall-in-love-with-someone-from-metric/</guid>
        <description> This is a follow up to our piece ‘How to have a one night stand (in Metric)’. For those of you who somehow missed it, we provided a tried-and-tested plan of action designed to get you laid after a night in Metric. This plan was meant to get you in and out without leaving any trace. But expectedly, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An immaculate conception?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-an-immaculate-conception/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-an-immaculate-conception/</guid>
        <description>Best friend in town? You just have to take them to one of the best restaurants in town and order three times your normal portion of food – and roll out of the restaurant with a six-month food baby hoping to ‘walk’ it off with a tube journey to the next.
So when my friend came down to London all the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Taking a leaf out of Tove Jansson&#39;s book
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-taking-a-leaf-out-of-tove-janssons-book/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:28:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Jenny Shelley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-taking-a-leaf-out-of-tove-janssons-book/</guid>
        <description>For many, the Moomins hold nothing more than the nostalgia of childhood. While some have no idea what they are, for others the word conjures up a vague image of a hippo-esque creature that adorns cutesy bottles and notepads. There is no particular reason to go any deeper than these associations, but …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rob’s Sad Playlist
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-robs-sad-playlist/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Robert Garside,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-robs-sad-playlist/</guid>
        <description> Disintegration Moving onto the more melodramatic side of sad, The Cure take us into the wilderness that is Disintegration. With the disconcerting glass smashing samples, unwavering drum machine and self indulgent vocals, the song is weirdly mesmerising. If you like this sort of thing but fancy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Problematic faves | J Cole and Jesse Hughes
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-problematic-faves-j-cole-and-jesse-hughes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:21:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-problematic-faves-j-cole-and-jesse-hughes/</guid>
        <description>Alas, poor Jermaine. Forest Hills Drive was a huge success, the wider public had recognised your musical and lyrical talent, and you were being mentioned in the same breath as the likes of Kendrick; you’d made it big. Why did you have to sabotage it all by taking shots at Yeezy? Now, beef is nothing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rebooted | A Series of Unfortunate Events
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-rebooted-a-series-of-unfortunate-events/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-rebooted-a-series-of-unfortunate-events/</guid>
        <description>The catchy theme song of this Netflix adaptation advises you to look away, warning you of a story that is dark and has no happy ending. If you actually listen to that advice, it would be an unfortunate event in of itself, as you would be missing out on a well-made, dark and incredibly self-aware …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A series of final problems | Sherlock
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-a-series-of-final-problems-sherlock/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-a-series-of-final-problems-sherlock/</guid>
        <description>In 2010 when Sherlock was first introduced to the world as Arthur Conan Doyle’s great detective being brought into the 21st century, co-creator Steven Moffat explained his motivations in making the series to Premium Hollywood thus: “This wasn’t a case of, ‘Let’s grab that off the shelf and update …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is it stupid to take smart drugs?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-is-it-stupid-to-take-smart-drugs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Anjeline Joegi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-is-it-stupid-to-take-smart-drugs/</guid>
        <description> It’s the night before the final exam, but you haven’t studied. If you had a small white pill which promised greater focus and productivity would you take it? The Tab website conducted a survey of 2000 UK university students and discovered that 1 in 5 have taken the drug ‘Modafinil’. Many students …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The university meme page revolution
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-the-university-meme-page-revolution/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 15:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,Paul Balaji,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-the-university-meme-page-revolution/</guid>
        <description>T his strange world of memes which we currently find ourselves in – one where a president can be catapulted to the White House with the help of online fascists and Pepe the Frog – is terrifying. There was an undercurrent of darkness in the memes that defined 2016: we celebrated Harambe’s death as if …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Breakfast, Hong Kong style
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-breakfast-hong-kong-style/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-breakfast-hong-kong-style/</guid>
        <description>Plonk.
It was the sound of a quarter-inch thick china cup hitting the glass-topped wooden table, as my milk tea lands before me just three seconds after the waiter took my order.
My mind snapped out from my fuzzy morning daydream of fluffy bunnies jumping over lush green grass back into full …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Most anticipated games of 2017
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-most-anticipated-games-of-2017/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:51:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-most-anticipated-games-of-2017/</guid>
        <description> Mass Effect: Andromeda The Mass Effect series was iconic and well deserving of all its recognition. Its ending may have been polarising but it did not take away from the hours of rich game play and world building. It was a thrill to learn that another entry in the series was coming. Although not …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This term in Arts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-this-term-in-arts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-this-term-in-arts/</guid>
        <description> It’s safe to say that 2016 wasn’t kind to the world of culture. In a year of blow after blow to the pantheon of iconic cultural stars, the passing of two more bright lights – Carrie Fisher and her mother Debbie Reynolds – left the arts world reeling once more. 2017 brings with it a new hope that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Spring term picks | felix’s film editors let you know their top films to look out for
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-spring-term-picks-felixs-film-editors-let-you-know-their-top-films-to-look-out-for/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:37:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-spring-term-picks-felixs-film-editors-let-you-know-their-top-films-to-look-out-for/</guid>
        <description> Christine | Released 27th January Christine tells the harrowing story of Christine Chubbuck, a Florida news anchor who killed herself live on air in 1974. Rebecca Hall takes on the titular character in a powerhouse performance that mines the depths of Chubbuck’s self-destructive tendencies; due to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Silence
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-silence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Theo Farah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-silence/</guid>
        <description>Following on from the messy hedonism of The Wolf of Wall Street – a three hour orgy of casual violence, over-sexualisation, and easy profanity – it is clear that Martin Scorsese is searching for a kind of ‘mea culpa’ with Silence, a mix of asceticism, endurance, and proselytism. It’s a hard pill to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s a kind of magic | psychedelic mushroom trip soothes depression in terminally ill patients
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-its-a-kind-of-magic-psychedelic-mushroom-trip-soothes-depression-in-terminally-ill-patients/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rachel Gillespie,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-its-a-kind-of-magic-psychedelic-mushroom-trip-soothes-depression-in-terminally-ill-patients/</guid>
        <description>It was like a space shuttle launch…that gives way to the weightlessness and majesty of space…” These are the words of Patrick Mettes, a participant in a recent clinical trial looking into the effects of psilocybin – the active component of aptly named ‘magic’ mushrooms – on depression and anxiety in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Artificial Intelligence | fears and future
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-artificial-intelligence-fears-and-future/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lizzie E Riach,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-artificial-intelligence-fears-and-future/</guid>
        <description>Last Wednesday I attended a talk comprised of five leading experts in the fields of machine learning and artificial intelligence (AI), mediated by the calming voice of Brian Cox. It was an enlightening evening. I hadn’t really thought too much about AI, but what struck me was how much of what I did …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The NHS is in a humanitarian crisis
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-the-nhs-is-in-a-humanitarian-crisis/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Stephen Naulls,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-the-nhs-is-in-a-humanitarian-crisis/</guid>
        <description>The Society of Acute Medicine has revealed that the NHS currently has “third world levels of staffing and third world levels of beds”. For the Red Cross, our NHS is in the midst of a ‘humanitarian crisis’. This language may sound vitriolic, but a crisis of this magnitude is something medical …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Firefighters swarm the Science Museum
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-firefighters-swarm-the-science-museum/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 13:52:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-firefighters-swarm-the-science-museum/</guid>
        <description>Just before noon last Wedensday, hundreds of visitors were evacuated from the Science Museum. As the visitors collected outside the museum on Exhibition Road, three firefighter squads arrived and created a perimeter around the historical building, amounting to a total of seven fire engines with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tossing fruit salad
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-tossing-fruit-salad/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 16:21:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-tossing-fruit-salad/</guid>
        <description> I know that times are tough when you go back home for the holidays. You’ve got used to having your freedom and privacy during term time, and maybe even got used to having a bae that keeps the sexual frustration at bay. Maybe you’ve got used to being able to use that corn-on-the-cob shaped vibrator …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to build Hogwarts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-how-to-build-hogwarts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 16:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-how-to-build-hogwarts/</guid>
        <description> 2009 | The first gingerbread We weren’t ambitious. We built a cute little gingerbread house. It only took one batch of gingerbread and a few sweets for decoration, and it disappeared remarkably quickly. How things were to change!
2010 | The castle This took two whole batches of gingerbread. We …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
