<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/bwh12/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/bwh12/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>No dash for gas: Activist group protests at Royal School of Mines
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-4-no-dash-for-gas-activist-group-protests-at-royal-school-of-mines/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2015 23:12:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Howitt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-4-no-dash-for-gas-activist-group-protests-at-royal-school-of-mines/</guid>
        <description>The Royal School of Mines (RSM) entrance was occupied on Monday 1st June by a group of students and members of the public representing the activist group ‘Reclaim the Power’.
The protest consisted of the presentation of a degree in Petroleum Geophysics to “brainwashed student #5102”, which claimed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Campaigning is hard work...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-19-campaigning-is-hard-work/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 23:52:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Abigail E de Bruin,Benjamin Howitt,Tom Rivlin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-19-campaigning-is-hard-work/</guid>
        <description>Tom Rivlin: Deputy President (Clubs and Societies) candidate, 2015
Let’s get one thing out of the way first: yes, I did just lose in the Big Elections. Yes, I am extremely bitter about this. Yes, you can read the whole article as just a sore loser whining about losing sorely if you want.
That said I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Favourite Musical – Next To Normal
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-6-my-favourite-musical-next-to-normal/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 13:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Howitt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-6-my-favourite-musical-next-to-normal/</guid>
        <description>Next to Normal, with book and lyrics by Brian Yorkey and music by Tom Kitt, follows Diana, a bipolar depressive with a dead son, a rock star psychiatrist, a daughter she describes as “a freak” (and her stoner boyfriend)&amp;hellip; and Dan, her husband.
When it was on Broadway during 2009-11, the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ArtsFest: A Very Vocal Evening 3.0
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-20-artsfest-a-very-vocal-evening-30/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 00:19:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Howitt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-20-artsfest-a-very-vocal-evening-30/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday night I had the pleasure of attending my first ArtsFest event of the year – A Very Vocal Evening (3.0), presented by The A Cappella and Musical Theatre societies. All four established A Cappella groups gave performances, and various solos and duets were performed by members of both …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Art Explosion tops off ICSM RAG Week
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-13-art-explosion-tops-off-icsm-rag-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2015 14:52:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Howitt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-13-art-explosion-tops-off-icsm-rag-week/</guid>
        <description>The Imperial College School of Medicine Students’ Union (ICSMSU) presented an Arts Revue last Sunday, 8th February, to conclude what has been, by all accounts, a very successful Raising and Giving (RAG) week.
The show was performed in the Union Concert Hall and featured acts from various Medics’ …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Starting a new club at Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-9-starting-a-new-club-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 18:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Howitt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-9-starting-a-new-club-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Union boasts over 340 societies, and that number grows every month, with new societies proposed including Wine Tasting, Airsoft and three different applications for weightlifting societies.
The creation of new clubs, societies and projects is run by the New Activities Committee …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“How dare you accuse us of being communist?”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-9-how-dare-you-accuse-us-of-being-communist/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 18:04:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Howitt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-9-how-dare-you-accuse-us-of-being-communist/</guid>
        <description>The Socratic Society (SocSoc) became a full society in December of last year, as a revival of the previously inactive Philosophy Society.
I met up with two members from the committee, Amelia Rath (Vice Chair, Nietzsche) and Abhinav Varma (Treasurer, Marx) to find out where they came from and what …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Society Funding in Review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-2-society-funding-in-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 14:36:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Howitt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-2-society-funding-in-review/</guid>
        <description>The Union has, according to the 2014 Impact Report, a turnover of just over £4.4 million. When you take out the bar and retail outlets, as well as staffing, overheads etc, that leaves approximately £1.4 million running through the clubs’ coffers on a yearly basis – as reported last year at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Week in the Life of: Felix
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-2-a-week-in-the-life-of-felix/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 14:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Howitt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-2-a-week-in-the-life-of-felix/</guid>
        <description>We decided to ‘start strong’ with Felix, under the assumption that we could write most of this over the break.
I started writing on Monday morning .
Saturday/Sunday
The Union staff have already been back for a week, and the news that’s come in over Christmas means we have things to reprt on other …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Send in the Clowns — A Return to Traditional Circus
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-31-send-in-the-clowns-a-return-to-traditional-circus/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2015 19:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Howitt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-31-send-in-the-clowns-a-return-to-traditional-circus/</guid>
        <description>We arrived at the Royal Albert Hall for the Friday matinee performance of Cirque du Soleil’s Kooza, and almost immediately began a mission to find somewhere to buy the programme and video recording. It turns out that the Londoner’s assumption of “oh, they’ll probably take card” does not extend to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Cappella comes to Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-a-cappella-comes-to-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 00:42:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Howitt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-a-cappella-comes-to-imperial/</guid>
        <description>The semi-finals of the International Championship of Collegiate A Cappella (ICCA) will be held this Saturday at Imperial College. The competition is presented by Varsity Vocals, in conjunction with the Union’s A Cappella Society, which is also sending three groups to compete against a range of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Carrying the Banner: Coffee, Newspapers &amp; Jazzhands
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-11-carrying-the-banner-coffee-newspapers-jazzhands/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 21:23:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Howitt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-11-carrying-the-banner-coffee-newspapers-jazzhands/</guid>
        <description>The Musical Theatre Society (MTSoc) ended their Autumn season last week with an all-singing, all-dancing musical revue. _Carrying The Banner _featured numbers from a spectrum of different musicals and cabaret acts, including Wicked and Avenue Q.
This is the third consecutive year in which MTSoc has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Swingers hit the mark
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-11-imperial-swingers-hit-the-mark/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 21:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Howitt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-11-imperial-swingers-hit-the-mark/</guid>
        <description>Over the weekend of Saturday 15th November, Imperial’s dance societies combined forces to run a Pineapple style open day, offering classes ranging from Salsa and Swing Dancing through to Hiphop, Break and Belly Dance.
The event saw over 100 different students attending classes over the two days, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial: Prepare to get Pitch slapped
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-imperial-prepare-to-get-pitch-slapped/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 00:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Howitt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-28-imperial-prepare-to-get-pitch-slapped/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College A Cappella Society has been chosen to host the UK semi-finals of the International Championship of Collegiate A Cappella (ICCA), presented by Varsity Vocals. The competition, now in its 20th year, was featured in the 2012 film Pitch Perfect, which introduced the world to the now …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial deletes tweet after ‘shirtstorm’ backlash
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-21-imperial-deletes-tweet-after-shirtstorm-backlash/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2014 13:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Howitt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-21-imperial-deletes-tweet-after-shirtstorm-backlash/</guid>
        <description>The clothing choice of an Imperial graduate has been extensively lambasted throughout the media in the wake of the Philae landing, the culmination of over a decade’s work. Such scrutiny was not limited to the actions of the social media team of Imperial, who removed a tweet celebrating the success …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial receives £65k of lottery funding for casual sport initiative
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-20-imperial-receives-65k-of-lottery-funding-for-casual-sport-initiative/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 22:05:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Howitt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-20-imperial-receives-65k-of-lottery-funding-for-casual-sport-initiative/</guid>
        <description>Sport Imperial have launched a new initiative, aimed at people who want to play casual sport without the pressure of being a part of a sports club or the atmosphere of being in Ethos for a fitness class or gym session.
Imperial College has been recognised as the top university for sport in the South …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UCH redev &#34;rather better than expected&#34;
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-17-uch-redev-rather-better-than-expected/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 15:00:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benjamin Howitt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-17-uch-redev-rather-better-than-expected/</guid>
        <description>In January 2014, Felix reported on the award of a £220,000 Harlington grant to redevelop the Union Concert Hall, where Imperial Cinema and various performing arts societies present shows, films and concerts. We interviewed George Goldberg from Imperial Cinema about the redevelopment, who …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
