<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/hj408/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/hj408/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Norman Finkelstein on Hamas, boycotts and liberty
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-norman-finkelstein-on-hamas-boycotts-and-liberty/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 21:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Hassan Joudi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-norman-finkelstein-on-hamas-boycotts-and-liberty/</guid>
        <description>You’ve said previously that there is a possibility of resolving the Arab-Israeli conflict and it’s not an eternal conflict that can’t be resolved. What keeps you so optimistic?
First of all you have to see if there are basic principles which people can agree on to resolve the conflict. On the basic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A gimmick or new era of transparency?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-a-gimmick-or-new-era-of-transparency/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2010 21:18:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Hassan Joudi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-a-gimmick-or-new-era-of-transparency/</guid>
        <description>Earlier this month, David Cameron launched a new government “transparency” website as part of his Big Society plans for Britain.
Visitors to www.number10.gov.uk/transparency will be welcomed by three live items: “Business plans”, “Who does what in Whitehall” and “Who ministers are meeting.” The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Debate whether Lib Dems betrayed voters continues
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-debate-whether-lib-dems-betrayed-voters-continues/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 19:06:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Hassan Joudi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-debate-whether-lib-dems-betrayed-voters-continues/</guid>
        <description>The accusations that the Liberal Democrats have compromised or “betrayed” their principles has constantly been levelled at them since their rise to shared power in May 2010. These have only intensified with the recent comprehensive spending review and the announcement of a higher cap on university …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It ain’t all numbers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-7-it-aint-all-numbers/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 22:51:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Hassan Joudi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-7-it-aint-all-numbers/</guid>
        <description>One downside to life at Imperial is the lack of variety of students you meet. You won’t find any undergraduates studying full degrees in English Literature, Languages, Law, History or any other excuse to spend three years writing essays.
We’re all here at this “technical” university to study our …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
