<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mg2109/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mg2109/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>How we find faces
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-how-we-find-faces/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 20:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Madhura Ghosh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-how-we-find-faces/</guid>
        <description>Babies have a tendency to attend to face and “face-like” stimuli (such as a triangle on a point as opposed to on a base). With faces practically hard-wired into our systems from a young age, it makes sense that there is a part of the brain dedicated to recognising faces in opposition to non faces – …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An interview with Medic President Suzie Rayner
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-an-interview-with-medic-president-suzie-rayner/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 21:23:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,Madhura Ghosh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-an-interview-with-medic-president-suzie-rayner/</guid>
        <description>Felix: How do you think the medical school has changed since this time last year (with respect to the Daily Mail article highlighting the binge-drinking culture of ICSM)? Suzie Rayner (SR): The changes made [after] the Daily Mail article last January have caused some necessary changes to bar …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Alcohol: why should you care?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-alcohol-why-should-you-care/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 21:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Katherine Bettany,Madhura Ghosh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-alcohol-why-should-you-care/</guid>
        <description> It’s that time of year again when we all start to make, and consequently break, all those well-meant resolutions we dreamt up over the Christmas break. But one resolution that couldn’t afford to be broken was that made by Imperial College School of Medicine (ICSM) this time last year: its …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cna yuo raed tihs snentece?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-cna-yuo-raed-tihs-snentece/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 21:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Madhura Ghosh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-cna-yuo-raed-tihs-snentece/</guid>
        <description>Throughout the history of neuroscience, we have often been amazed by the brain’s capability and workings. Instances like the ability to read the jumbled headline above intrigue us – how is a mess of letters comprehensible?
We have long known that skilled readers do not need to read individual …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hall survey delayed
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-hall-survey-delayed/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 19:42:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Madhura Ghosh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-hall-survey-delayed/</guid>
        <description>Imperial halls of accommodation were the subject of much heated debate this week following the Union’s announcement of a survey to see how the rent for Halls could be reduced. In particular Union President Alex Kendall’s comments about the halls amenities fund, which is paid from rents and used to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial to charge £9,000
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-imperial-to-charge-9000/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 18:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Madhura Ghosh,Katherine Bettany,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-imperial-to-charge-9000/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College has this week revealed that it plans to charge the maximum £9,000 tuition fee rate for 2012 entry. The move is an unsurprising one, with the universities of Cambridge and Oxford signalling earlier this month that higher fees would be necessary to fill a deficit created by government …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
