<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/martin_flerin/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/martin_flerin/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>How Computers Took our Music Away</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-how-computers-took-our-music-away/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-how-computers-took-our-music-away/</guid>
        <description>Putting the history of a whole genre of music to paper is a mammoth task, especially for a genre as fluid and diverse as electronic music, so please forgive any oversight I may have made in trying to accomplish it. It is a story of technical innovation, experimentation, and of people coming …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Surrealist Superstars</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-surrealist-superstars/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-surrealist-superstars/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
Brussels’s Place Royale is a mecca of art, like a small, art-oriented brother to the museums surrounding our beautiful campus. The Royal Museums that flank it comprise some of the finest works of the European canon, from the Flemish masters to the modern genius of Magritte. The latter’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Arrival: Two Brothers Reunited</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-the-arrival-two-brothers-reunited/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-the-arrival-two-brothers-reunited/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
Samad (Irfan Shamji) and Tom (Scott Karim) have lived very different lives. Different upbringings, different parents, different friends, different schools. Social, geographic and cultural barriers have divided them for over thirty years. But they have one thing in common, they are brothers, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>1/3 analogue, 1/3 digital, 1/3 nature: Dominik Eulberg</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-third-analogue-third-digital-third-nature-dominik-eulberg/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-third-analogue-third-digital-third-nature-dominik-eulberg/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
Dominik Eulberg, the 41-year-old recluse birdwatcher, who happens to also make some of the best German techno, says that he feels drawn to the animalistic aspects of the genre. The sweating, the entranced dancing, the rapture when the crescendo lifts your feet off the ground. He brought all …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Denis Sulta takes us to the Xanadu of dance</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-denis-sulta-takes-xanadu-dance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-denis-sulta-takes-xanadu-dance/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
We turn the corner, the gray lake at Canada Water still at the back of our minds. It’s pouring it down, and the group consensus is that we won’t miss the outside world for the next 10 hours. We’re going into the void. That is how every new Printworks adventure feels.
I’m not explicitly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sick Boy Lookalike Bringing the Disco Vibes</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-sick-boy-lookalike-bringing-disco-vibes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-sick-boy-lookalike-bringing-disco-vibes/</guid>
        <description>The white hair, the Scottishness, the pomp he brings to his sets – a lot of the elements of 26-year-old Hector Barbour’s alter ego point to the man from Trainspotting. But while the difficult path that Hector was on may well have led him to the same kind of sorry existence that his on-screen …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Decimal Man Still CRUSHing it After Over Four Years</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-decimal-man-still-crushing-after-four-years/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-decimal-man-still-crushing-after-four-years/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
Floating Points is a man with a PhD from UCL. Now, I wouldn’t want to set the bar TOO high but FP’s friend Dan Snaith, a.k.a. Caribou, a.k.a. Daphni, has a PhD from Imperial, as does Brian May. Looking at musicians with doctorates from the most (un?)prestigious London universities, that is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Soviet Still Life in Eight Chapters - Theatre of Nations</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-soviet-still-life-eight-chapters-theatre-nations/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-soviet-still-life-eight-chapters-theatre-nations/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
The themes of the stories are centred mostly on the everyday aspects of social life. The characters are not extraordinary in their feats of achievement but shine through with their touching realness. When the curtains part, a bench is revealed, which takes up most of the stage, and will …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Live it Up with the Modernists at Barbican’s New Show</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-live-up-with-modernists-barbicans-new-show/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-live-up-with-modernists-barbicans-new-show/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
In contrast to last year’s wildly popular Modern Couples, which offered an intimate view into how interpersonal relationships of artists shaped their work, this offers a different view. It portrays some of the most influential artists of modernism as entertainers: uproarious and devilish …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A big fish in an even bigger pond</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-a-big-fish-in-an-even-bigger-pond/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-a-big-fish-in-an-even-bigger-pond/</guid>
        <description>This March, Australia will be the centre of gravity for psych rock and Formula 1 fans alike. But no matter how hot Ferrari are looking, in my heart I doubt that the action on the black asphalt of Albert Park will be able to overshadow what’s hiding in the grooves of the new Pond LP. Here’s why.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is the haze craze kushing a tad too far?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-is-the-haze-craze-kushing-a-tad-too-far/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-is-the-haze-craze-kushing-a-tad-too-far/</guid>
        <description>Marijuana users all over rejoiced earlier this month when Canada became the first big Western democracy to legalize free use of cannabis. Canadians actually rejoiced so much that the country is now facing a weed shortage. It seems like the world is finally ready to move on from the question of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>European museum of the year resting on its laurels</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-european-museum-of-the-year-resting-on-its-laurels/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-european-museum-of-the-year-resting-on-its-laurels/</guid>
        <description>In May of this year, the design museum, that resides a mere 15-minute walk away from our South Kensington campus, won the award for European museum of the year. Sat between a Byron burgers and the peacocks of Holland park, it became the 7th British museum to do so in the 41 years that the prize has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Everybody wants to change the world:  Looking at the White Album’s Legacy 50 Years on</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-everybody-wants-to-change-the-world-looking-at-the-white-album-s-legacy-50-years-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-everybody-wants-to-change-the-world-looking-at-the-white-album-s-legacy-50-years-on/</guid>
        <description>Exactly fifty years ago, the year 1968 was to be the beginning of the end for the Beatles. Lennon had finally escaped the clutches of chronic acid tripping, partly due to his burgeoning love for Yoko Ono, partly due to the retreat the band made to Rishikesh where they were meant to have sworn off …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Hippo in the room: toxic masculinity </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-the-hippo-in-the-room-toxic-masculinity/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-the-hippo-in-the-room-toxic-masculinity/</guid>
        <description>Following up a debut LP as well-received and enjoyable as Landmark was bound to be a tough job for Hippo Campus. The American Midwest’s breeziest indie rock band have not shied away from the pressure though, and have just released a record that – despite not being a big departure from their previous …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Beware the man who has everything</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-beware-the-man-who-has-everything/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-beware-the-man-who-has-everything/</guid>
        <description>As a book lover, it was a wonderful thing to discover Father John Misty. It is simply impossible to get past the brilliant lyrics this man has continuously pumped out on all four albums released under this moniker. When listening to the stories he has to tell, you are completely immersed in a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Beach House return with lucky number 7</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-beach-house-return-with-lucky-number-7/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-beach-house-return-with-lucky-number-7/</guid>
        <description>When the new Beach House album, 7, came out on Friday, the first thing I did in the morning was take a walk through Hyde park and listen to it. Back home, Beach house was THE band I would listen to on long and moody walks through the forest, and I thought it fitting that I give 7 a whirl in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>MGMT: transformed, transfigured, transcendental</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-mgmt-transformed-transfigured-transcendental/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Martin Flerin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-mgmt-transformed-transfigured-transcendental/</guid>
        <description>It is fair to say that MGMT have had some trouble reconciling their own musical vision and their fans’ auditory desires. But perhaps their new album, Little Dark Age, is proof that abstract expressionist Barnett Newmann’s view - that the encounter between art and audience can be considered as a …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
