<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/vj05/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/vj05/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Coffee on campus
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-27-coffee-on-campus/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 14:05:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vicky Jeyaprakash,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-27-coffee-on-campus/</guid>
        <description>I was going to dazzle you all with a review of a restaurant this week but seeing the almost prolific response we received to our coffee article last week I thought I would join in with the conversation. It seems when it comes to our caffeinated sustenance we all have rather exacting standards and I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best in Class: Teen
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-best-in-class-teen/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 21:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vicky Jeyaprakash,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-best-in-class-teen/</guid>
        <description>There is no shame, only greatness and beautiful people. At least that’s the cover I’m hiding under. Teen Drama has a bad reputation and for good reason; the word teen conjures up an image of a thirteen year old girl painting her nails and blue tacking pictures of some floppy haired, half clothed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Our HBO-fest continues
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-our-hbo-fest-continues/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 20:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vicky Jeyaprakash,Navid Nabijou,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-our-hbo-fest-continues/</guid>
        <description>The Sopranos
“A rich exploration of the paradoxes of modern life that will leave an impression on all who give it a chance.”
Perhaps no other series to date has had a greater impact on television as The Sopranos, writes Navid Nabijou. Exploding onto the airwaves in 1999, it came as a massive shock; …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>National Television Awards
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-national-television-awards/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 20:29:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vicky Jeyaprakash,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-national-television-awards/</guid>
        <description>Tis’ the season. Award ceremonies are everywhere as the ultimate narcissists congratulate themselves on just how wonderful they are.
I don’t know about you but that’s my idea of a fun night in. I love the red carpet, the utter rubbish people say about how grateful they are for the free booze and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>So you think you can eat? Meet the meat challenge
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-so-you-think-you-can-eat-meet-the-meat-challenge/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 18:52:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vicky Jeyaprakash,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-so-you-think-you-can-eat-meet-the-meat-challenge/</guid>
        <description>Meat. That quintessential ingredient of all meals. The point of any fare. Or so I’ve been told. I love food; lunch, brunch, pudding, tea, tapas and amuse-bouche are all held in fond regard. I could however easily forgo meat. I’m not a vegetarian. I would definitely not want to be part of that fringe …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>10 O’Clock Live premier: Confused
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-10-oclock-live-premier-confused/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 20:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Vicky Jeyaprakash,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-10-oclock-live-premier-confused/</guid>
        <description>In the last month Channel 4’s marketing department has done well in bombarding us all with anchormanesque billboards and amusing adverts for 10 O’Clock Live, their new topical comedy show. I suspect, however, that the hype and anticipation created is where their downfall will lie. All of us were far …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
