<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/he915/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/he915/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Revelling in the chaos of American politics</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-revelling-in-the-chaos-of-american-politics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-revelling-in-the-chaos-of-american-politics/</guid>
        <description>The midterms are nearly upon us, and this is no fun for anybody. And before you get excited about a possible radical change in the US federal government, take a dose of reality, bud. Shit slides slowly. But, with luck, shit will slide the right way.
Quick refresher for those of you not knowledgeable …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kavanaugh: The aggressor or the victim?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-kavanaugh-the-aggressor-or-the-victim/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,Theodor Videnberg,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-kavanaugh-the-aggressor-or-the-victim/</guid>
        <description>The legal system works under the principle that one is innocent until proven guilty,
Three weeks ago Henry Eshbaugh wrote an article titled “Stuck in my Kava-craw” about US supreme court nominee Brett Kavanaugh. In the rather polemical piece he called Kavanaugh “non-human”, “a nympho who raped …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fresh albums: Thee Oh Sees, Gregory Alan Isakov</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-fresh-albums-thee-oh-sees-gregory-alan-isakov/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-fresh-albums-thee-oh-sees-gregory-alan-isakov/</guid>
        <description>The new Isakov album is out today&amp;hellip;
And I haven’t listened to it yet because I’m writing this piece on a Wednesday. But it’s spawned enough singles to be recommended to me on Spotify anyhow as an EP, “Dark, Dark, Dark,” after the lead single on the album. And boy howdy, isn’t he dreamy?
Isakov …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Every Microsoft Windows startup sound, ranked</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-every-microsoft-windows-startup-sound-ranked/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-every-microsoft-windows-startup-sound-ranked/</guid>
        <description>The Windows boot sounds are unknown gems of the music world. Brian Eno was a collaborator!
12. Windows 98 Plus!
Legitimately awful. I can’t believe the marketing theme thought this was a good idea. If I heard this noise out of my computer, I’d try to put it out with a fire extinguisher.
11. Windows …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New term, hoo dis? The 2018 album prospectus</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-new-term-hoo-dis-the-2018-album-prospectus/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-new-term-hoo-dis-the-2018-album-prospectus/</guid>
        <description>It’s no secret that music is released. But figuring out what’s coming out, and when, can be a bit of a chore. I’ve curated a list of albums over the horizon our readers might care to listen to (if only for jokes).
Coheed and Cambria.
Vaxis – Act I: The Unheavenly Creatures.
2015’s The Color Before …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stuck in my Kava-craw</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-stuck-in-my-kava-craw/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-stuck-in-my-kava-craw/</guid>
        <description>Well, here’s a little Kavfefe that’s been dominating the US news cycle recently (anyone remember those kids in concentration camps? They’re still there for the record). Brett Kavanaugh, potential appointee to the Supreme Court of the United States, has had a rough few weeks. The media circus was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to the pleasuredome</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-welcome-to-the-pleasuredome/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adrian LaMoury,Henry Eshbaugh,Asad Raja,Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-welcome-to-the-pleasuredome/</guid>
        <description>My friend Kunal from Singapore calls me the grime guy. I like the way that sounds so I don’t correct him. In truth, as far as grime or UK rap goes, I consider myself a semi-casual listener (you won’t catch me listening to anyone less niche than, like, Ghetts). Though I stay open to most genres, US …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>While you were away...</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-while-you-were-away/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Asad Raja,Henry Eshbaugh,Adrian LaMoury,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-while-you-were-away/</guid>
        <description>Family of Aliens
The third full-length effort by this indie pop quartet packs all the wholesome family-friendly goodness that fans have come to expect, but not without a wicked sense of humour and a quirky, sci-fi inflected glaze. A new crisply produced electronic vibe replaces their traditionally …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What do we talk about when we talk about music?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-what-do-we-talk-about-when-we-talk-about-music/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-what-do-we-talk-about-when-we-talk-about-music/</guid>
        <description>What motivates the musician? Compulsive enjoyment of frissive frequencies rattling together in perfect harmony? Melodies meandering through modes and motifs, each refrain serving as a signifier, a stand-in for human speech – the connotations built by our musical traditions there to hint at some …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The revision soundtrack you wish you had this year</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-the-revision-soundtrack-you-wish-you-had-this-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Henry Eshbaugh,Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-the-revision-soundtrack-you-wish-you-had-this-year/</guid>
        <description>Right in time for the end of exam season, the usual suspects rec some LPs that you should’ve been listening to all along. Sucks you don’t have a time machine, or you could’ve had that many more hours of pleasant revision coasting emotionally on the bangin’ tunes we tell you to like. Well, there’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Breaking: R. Kelly is still a revolting human being</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-breaking-r-kelly-is-still-a-revolting-human-being/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-breaking-r-kelly-is-still-a-revolting-human-being/</guid>
        <description>This article is sensitive, and discusses extreme violence against women. Reader discretion is advised.
R. Kelly is back in the news – as in, he’s being sued for sexual slavery. His conduct is deeply immoral – sick and hideous behavior. And it’s been going on for 20 fucking years.
Those familiar with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Shô! it’s come to this: jazz fusion from Marseille </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-sh-it-s-come-to-this-jazz-fusion-from-marseille/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-sh-it-s-come-to-this-jazz-fusion-from-marseille/</guid>
        <description>There’s this guy on YouTube called Marcel the Drunkard, and he does really spiffy speed watercolor paintings. He does them to fusion/neosoul albums, then uploads the video and the music to go along with it. The guy’s neat, and the albums are abshô!lutely splendid. His latest video featured a jazz …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A wrong, mostly short history of punk rock, part III</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-a-wrong-mostly-short-history-of-punk-rock-part-iii/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-04-a-wrong-mostly-short-history-of-punk-rock-part-iii/</guid>
        <description>To all of my readers waiting for this a month ago – sorry, the end of term got messy, and I never finished the article. Not that you (as in, my readers) exist, I just thought I’d take the opportunity to flatter myself. Now, on to history.
Despite all the over-eager commenters throughout the years …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A brief, mostly wrong history of punk rock, part II</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-a-brief-mostly-wrong-history-of-punk-rock-part-ii/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-a-brief-mostly-wrong-history-of-punk-rock-part-ii/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to the history of punk rock, part 2. Part 1 was in the last edition of Felix - get caught up online. Now, history.
Anarcho-punk emerged in the UK in the late 70s and early 80s. Crass was one of the foremost bands (“Do they owe us a living? / of course they fucking do!”). Bands like The Mob …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A short, mostly wrong history of punk rock, part I</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-a-short-mostly-wrong-history-of-punk-rock-part-i/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-a-short-mostly-wrong-history-of-punk-rock-part-i/</guid>
        <description>Punk is hard to pin down; it’s not a particular genre or style marked by any particular technical approach to writing music. In fact, most of the time, it’s not very technical at all. It’s sort of a patched-together set of reactions to a number of musical lineages, which entangled to form the angry, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New GoGo Penguin: A Humdrum Star is anything but</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-new-gogo-penguin-a-humdrum-star-is-anything-but/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-new-gogo-penguin-a-humdrum-star-is-anything-but/</guid>
        <description>Manchester-based jazztronica band GoGo Penguin has made more jazztronica. The group, noted especially for previous efforts Man Made Object and the Mercury-nominated v2.0, have continued to refine their unique sound on the latest effort. Not too much changes in the way of tone or songwriting; you can …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A brief, mostly wrong history of the lo-fi aesthetic</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-a-brief-mostly-wrong-history-of-the-lo-fi-aesthetic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-a-brief-mostly-wrong-history-of-the-lo-fi-aesthetic/</guid>
        <description>In a world far before the age of high-fidelity recording, there was the gramophone. Recordings from the era are near-inaudible; the band plays as loudly as possible, so as to make the recording as clear as can be. The sound is marked by tinniness and an unmistakable crackling sound, as the needle …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Modern Lore is an instant classic</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-modern-lore-is-an-instant-classic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-modern-lore-is-an-instant-classic/</guid>
        <description>Thirty years into his life, twenty-five years into his guitar-playing career, and two years into his time as a bandleader, Julian Lage has returned with his most mature album yet. Playing the darling Telecaster that gave Arclight its wonderful fuzzy feel, and supported by bassist Scott Colley and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Today’s Empires, Tomorrow’s Ashes is still relevant</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-today-s-empires-tomorrow-s-ashes-is-still-relevant/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-today-s-empires-tomorrow-s-ashes-is-still-relevant/</guid>
        <description>Margaret Thatcher famously referred to herself as practicing “conviction politics” in the months before her 1979 rise to the office of Prime Minister. She holds no candle to Winnipeg-based thrash-punk band Propagandhi, an all-vegan band so dedicated to environmentalism that they organize tours to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The rowdiest gig the beacon theatre ever hosted</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-the-rowdiest-gig-the-beacon-theatre-ever-hosted/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-the-rowdiest-gig-the-beacon-theatre-ever-hosted/</guid>
        <description>Streetlight is a band that’s impossible to categorise. I’ve heard ska-punk, world, prog jazz, hardcore folk, and a dozen other descriptors chucked their way, none sticking in any sense of the word (best I’ve seen is “mariachi band from hell”).
But if there’s one word descriptor agreeable to the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>They’ve only gone and bloody done it</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-12-they-ve-only-gone-and-bloody-done-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-12-they-ve-only-gone-and-bloody-done-it/</guid>
        <description>As avid readers of the Best Music Section On Earth TM might already be aware, The Gizz made a legendary attempt to stick five albums out last year (the fourth of which, Polygondwanaland, was reviewed herein). We awaited with baited breath to see whether Stu &amp;amp; Co would deliver their fifth - as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Top albums of 2017: Henry’s picks</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-top-albums-of-2017-henry-s-picks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-top-albums-of-2017-henry-s-picks/</guid>
        <description>7 Sleep Well Beast The National
An album that’s nothing less than a return to form for the band. The National are a well-known New York-based post-rock band (up Interpol’s alley), known best for their two magnificent albums Crocodile and Boxer. So the story goes, a group of friends from Ohio moved …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I, for one, hail our faceless corporate overlords</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-i-for-one-hail-our-faceless-corporate-overlords/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-i-for-one-hail-our-faceless-corporate-overlords/</guid>
        <description>Now That’s What I Call Music! is a cross-label series of compilation albums of the biggest songs of the year (or, at least, whatever they could get the rights to). Now, historically, I haven’t really been their biggest fan, but I found Now That’s What I Call Music! 98 to be one of the most moving …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In praise of Hobgoblin, the Swiss Army beer</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-in-praise-of-hobgoblin-the-swiss-army-beer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-in-praise-of-hobgoblin-the-swiss-army-beer/</guid>
        <description>It’s just gone 11 AM, your head is fuzzy, and you roll onto your side to find a half-finished can of Stella. Your body screams for hydration but your head rails against the prospect of drinking lukewarm piss, flat, tasteless, and sticky. Oh, fates! Defeated, you slump back into bed, clutching your …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>King Gizzard takes a field trip to Polygondwanaland</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-king-gizzard-takes-a-field-trip-to-polygondwanaland/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-king-gizzard-takes-a-field-trip-to-polygondwanaland/</guid>
        <description>The Gizz is back with their fourth effort of the year, and it sounds like they’ve been listening to too much Tool.
Fans of the the proggy indie hard rock outfit (like the B52s on crack) went into this year fresh off their fantastic effort Nonagon Infinity, in eager anticipation of the announced …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Weezer wheezes out another fucking travesty...</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-weezer-wheezes-out-another-fucking-travesty/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-weezer-wheezes-out-another-fucking-travesty/</guid>
        <description>Oh, Rivers. What an absolute shame, the mess you’ve ended up in. Weezer was hot shit in the ‘90s. The Blue Album spoke to a generation of individuals who felt introverted and alone. It was a dorky, confessional, energetic mess – and never once did the heart fail to shine through. Then, the story …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Diverse influences make for a remarkable LP</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-diverse-influences-make-for-a-remarkable-lp/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-diverse-influences-make-for-a-remarkable-lp/</guid>
        <description>Wolf Alice is a band with a diverse set of influences. There are detectable traces of shoegaze, pop, folk, punk, grunge, and indie, to name just a few components of the musical palette brought to bear on this album.
There is never a dull minute as Ellie Roswell &amp;amp; co. leap from phrase to phrase, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Off-kilter prog-funk is one for the superfans</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-off-kilter-prog-funk-is-one-for-the-superfans/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-off-kilter-prog-funk-is-one-for-the-superfans/</guid>
        <description>Bass legend Les Claypool returns with the only band to earn its own ID3 genre tag. The band is known for off-kilter prog-funk with metal roots. Trademark syncopated riffs return with newfound minimalism. This album conceptually focuses on the “desaturating seven”, a band of goblins who chase …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>QC anarchy is for me</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-qc-anarchy-is-for-me/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-qc-anarchy-is-for-me/</guid>
        <description>GY!BE has earned itself a seat in the post-rock pantheon, and for good reason. The Montreal collective, led by guitarist/composer Efrim Menuck, has a score of classic post-rock albums. The band is marked by a bleak, ragged, distorted sound, always aggressively limping to a heroic climax, which …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Relatively un-miraculous</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-relatively-un-miraculous/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-relatively-un-miraculous/</guid>
        <description>This psych-pop album is neither particularly psychedelic nor particularly poppy, instead preferring fairly unimaginative composition and over-reliance on production.
I mean, there’s nothing /wrong/ with it. The band members are objectively skilled musicians, who play clearly and effectively …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Another year, another Death Grips leak
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-another-year-another-death-grips-leak/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 09:58:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-another-year-another-death-grips-leak/</guid>
        <description>The most avant-garde of avant-garde rap groups has leaked yet another album: Bottomless Pit. And it’s exactly what you’d expect. It’s so good it’s bad. It’s so bad it’s good. And it’s self-aware. We’ve reached peak irony, and I for one love it.
The band is hard to pin down stylistically. Clearer …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FELIX’s Mercury Prize picks
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-felixs-mercury-prize-picks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 09:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,Peter Munton,Robert Garside,Fred S Fyles,Cale E Tilford,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-felixs-mercury-prize-picks/</guid>
        <description> _In Colour_Jamie xx Oh Jamie, you can do no wrong. Not in my eyes, the eyes of anyone who went outdoors this summer who was inundated with your invariably uplifting ‘Good Times’, and presumably, not in the eyes of the Mercury Music Prize people.
The flabbergasting combo of Jamie Smith, dance hall …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ratatat funkify Brixton
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-ratatat-funkify-brixton/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 14:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-ratatat-funkify-brixton/</guid>
        <description>As those of you who speak to me on a regular basis know, I went to see Ratatat live in Brixton the other day. I couldn’t help pouring gloat after gloat out my face-hole. Eat it, Josh! I was on the guest list!
Ratatat is serious business. Their sense of groove is among the best in the industry. Since …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Protomartyr’s return holds no surprises
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-protomartyrs-return-holds-no-surprises/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 11:49:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-protomartyrs-return-holds-no-surprises/</guid>
        <description>Golly gee, am I an angsty emo. The only clothing I own is black. Black like my soul – my heart, which screams constantly in writhing agony about the horrors of the human condition and the bleakness and depravity of our dismal existence. Sometimes, when I’m really moody, I walk to the park and let …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
