<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/cmt09/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/cmt09/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Serpentine Double Whammy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-serpentine-double-whammy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 04:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-serpentine-double-whammy/</guid>
        <description>What: Wael Shawky: al-Qurban &amp;amp; Jake and Dinos Chapman: Come and See Where: Serpentine &amp;amp; Serpentine Sackler Gallery, Hyde Park, SW6 When: 29 Nov 2013 – 9 Feb 2014 Price: FREE
Visiting the Serpentine Gallery, situated in the middle of Hyde Park, usually constitutes a pleasant lunchtime …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>E-lighting up
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-e-lighting-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 23:41:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Frank Machin,Charles Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-e-lighting-up/</guid>
        <description>Others in the Felix Office will vouch for this. My first words on smoking my allocated e-cigarette were, “this tastes like smoking a dusty egg in a sauna”. In my all too numerous returns to the device I never managed to elucidate a more pithy nor precise description of the experience. As you can …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Beauty and the beholder’s eye
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-5-beauty-and-the-beholders-eye/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 19:00:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-5-beauty-and-the-beholders-eye/</guid>
        <description>I met Jennifer Louise Martin in the food hall at Selfridges. To get there I had to walk through the cosmetics hall. Through the haze of perfume, immaculate girls stared out with twinkling eyes, watching my progress as I picked my way though counters stacked with foundation, mascara and lipsticks. I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Berlin walls have years
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-4-30-berlin-walls-have-years/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 14:26:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-4-30-berlin-walls-have-years/</guid>
        <description>Berlin is a city that weeps with history. Decades after unification it has a skyline like a broken jaw. Buildings conspicuous by their absence are found next to bullet riddled vestiges of the Wiemar years. Soviet space-age architectural excesses and grim utilitarian atrocities now sit alongside …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>There is something in the air
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-there-is-something-in-the-air/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 00:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-there-is-something-in-the-air/</guid>
        <description>College seems to be on the anti-smoking warpath again. Bins and ashtrays are mysteriously disappearing from places like the RSM entrance and my inbox is filling up with passive-aggressive emails. Interfering busy-bodies have made it their mission to enforce the ridiculous ‘smoke-free’ zones around …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Killer rob-arts attack
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-28-killer-rob-arts-attack/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 23:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-28-killer-rob-arts-attack/</guid>
        <description>There is an underground space near Baker Street that feels a lot like a baroque sci-fi future. The half-light is illuminated by occasional flashes of neon. Blue and green lasers strafe the ceiling and an eerie soundscape of ambient electronic squawks and whirring servos greets the intrepid. Skulls …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Putting the camp back into campaign
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-putting-the-camp-back-into-campaign/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 00:11:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Thomas,Eva Rosenthal Mena,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-1-putting-the-camp-back-into-campaign/</guid>
        <description>Meredith and I went down to the Noël Coward Theatre in the West End in order to interview a young actor, Sam Swainsbury, involved in one of the most exciting theatre companies playing currently in London.
Swainsbury plays a cocky flight sergeant with no combat time in Privates on Parade. He answered …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Not a face for radio
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-not-a-face-for-radio/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 22:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-not-a-face-for-radio/</guid>
        <description>The Boy with Tape on his Face aka Sam Wills has been causing something of a splash in recent year. From street performances in Covent Garden he has shot up the comedy league tables with hits at the Fringe, the Melbourne Comedy Festival and, in 2011, the Royal Variety Show. His unique brand of comedy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Minotaurs and major excursions
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-minotaurs-and-major-excursions/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 02:24:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-minotaurs-and-major-excursions/</guid>
        <description>The Architect is Shunt’s first production in three years and it was well worth the wait. Shunt is an unusual collective centred round an experimental theatre company. The group have had a presence around East London for years. Some readers might just remember the astonishing club they ran in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fusion achieved at last in Huxley
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-fusion-achieved-at-last-in-huxley/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 13:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-fusion-achieved-at-last-in-huxley/</guid>
        <description>I met Geraldine Cox in a windy garet on the roof of the physics building. The abandoned weather station is an octagonal room half-open to the elements and filled with drying clothes, bits of mouldering, esoteric looking equipment and empty beer bottles. It was an appropriately idiosyncratic setting …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Art studio opens in College
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-art-studio-opens-in-college/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:49:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-art-studio-opens-in-college/</guid>
        <description>The Blyth Centre has announced the opening of a new facility catering for student and staff artists. A large room in Weeks Hall has been refurbished to function as an art studio. Access to the space and materials will be made available to members of the studio. This can be purchased for £10 for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Frieze Art Fair 10
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-frieze-art-fair-10/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:09:24 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Rosenthal Mena,Charles Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-frieze-art-fair-10/</guid>
        <description>WTF is Frieze?
Frieze Art Fair, for those of you who have missed the press coverage, is big. It attracts over 60,000 visitors a year and generates enough acres of print to cover the enormous canopy in Regents Park housing the whole circus. Tickets sell out well in advance of the fair, which only …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Superhuman
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-superhuman/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 20:28:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-superhuman/</guid>
        <description>What do dildos, wheelchairs and steroids have in common? There are probably only two places in London you will find these three things in conjunction. One of them is not suitable for a family newspaper, the second is the Wellcome Collection. In the latter case their justification for sharing a room …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brief History of Phoenix
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-brief-history-of-phoenix/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 21:05:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-brief-history-of-phoenix/</guid>
        <description>In the 125 years since its inception Phoenix has changed its name, format and remit. In fact, in almost every way this issue would be completely alien (aliens being something of a preoccupation) to the man who founded the magazine in 1887. However it is just possible to trace a thread of continuity …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Fashion Designer - Emma Amoafo
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-the-fashion-designer-emma-amoafo/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 20:44:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-the-fashion-designer-emma-amoafo/</guid>
        <description>Emma Amoafa is a third year medic. After a day on the ward most students can only think about bedsheets but Emma has another fabric on her mind. Her embryonic label Friday Born splashes colour across the streets of London in a life-saving injection of Ghanaian vibrance.
Meredith – How long have you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Musician - Jyi Sim
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-the-musician-jyi-sim/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 20:39:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-the-musician-jyi-sim/</guid>
        <description>Jyi Sim is a bubbly 3rd year aero with a enthusiasm that goes beyond the day job. Her passion for music and what it meant to her became clear as we talked. Jyi’s self produced first album Postcards from Unity draws heavily on her upbringing in Malaysia and the shock of moving to the UK. Recording …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Illustrator - Mithila Shafiq
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-the-illustrator-mithila-shafiq/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 20:33:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-the-illustrator-mithila-shafiq/</guid>
        <description>Mithili Shafiq was the archetypal scientist with a creative itch. By the end of her PhD she had decided that the itch needed to be scratched. Now she has retrained as an illustrator and is making a new life for herself in Bristol. I caught up with her over Skype after several abortive attempts to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Editorial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-editorial/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 20:02:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-editorial/</guid>
        <description>On the auspicious 125th anniversary of this magazine one is more conscious than normal of the burden history places on the editorial yoke of such venerable publications as Phoenix. I was initially impressed with all the doubts and uncertainties you might imagine when embarking on this foreword. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Phoenix 2012
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-phoenix-2012/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 19:53:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Eleanor Vincent,Eva Rosenthal Mena,Charles Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-phoenix-2012/</guid>
        <description>Editorial
Spotlight: The Designer
Spotlight: The Interaction Designers
Spotlight: The Game Designer
Spotlight: The Artist
Spotlight: The Illustrator
Moonlighters: The Musician
Moonlighters: The Fashion Designer
Moonlighters: The Poet
Summer Lightning
Backlight
Lightbox: Henry Bennie
Lightbox: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A step towards cross-f***ing
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-a-step-towards-cross-fing/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 22:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-a-step-towards-cross-fing/</guid>
        <description>It is very difficult to retain a historical perspective of the present. Artistic movements only acquire recognition and an associated nomenclature once they are well established, or in many cases once they have peaked. However, I am going to stick my neck out to predict that art histories yet to be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Artifact
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-artifact/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 20:40:47 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-artifact/</guid>
        <description>An artist and a scientist walk into a bar. They find each other incomprehensible and mysterious and fail to have a meaningful conversation. They leave vowing never to move out of their comfort zone again. Not really funny is it? Before I continue, I must declare an interest in writing this article. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your memorable Valentine
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-your-memorable-valentine/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 20:58:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charles Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-your-memorable-valentine/</guid>
        <description>This story starts with clenched, muscular buttocks. The buttocks in question comprise the cover art of the latest Scissor Sisters album Night Work and while they certainly deserve a second glance you would not grasp their full significance unless you had also knew of the man who took that …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
