<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/slb210/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/slb210/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The hidden secrets of coral reefs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-the-hidden-secrets-of-coral-reefs/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 22:47:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Byrne,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-the-hidden-secrets-of-coral-reefs/</guid>
        <description>Coral reefs are one of the wonders of the marine world: vast underwater structures supporting a large and diverse ecosystem of marine species. It’s surprising then that until recently we knew very little about exactly how they form.
Corals are colonies of small marine invertebrates, and it is their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Underground networking
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-underground-networking/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 22:08:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Byrne,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-underground-networking/</guid>
        <description>You probably think humans invented communication networks. However according to recent research, plants might have got there first, communicating with each other through extensive underground fungal networks.
Most soil-based fungi grow as hyphae: long, branching fibres that form spreading …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What happens when we tell stories about science?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-what-happens-when-we-tell-stories-about-science/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 21:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Byrne,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-what-happens-when-we-tell-stories-about-science/</guid>
        <description>What does happen when we tell stories about science? That was the question the panel of academics attempted to answer at the LSE/Imperial Literary Festival event last Wednesday evening. The aims described at the beginning were both ambitious and a bit vague. We were going to examine the relationship …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rats get infrared ‘sixth sense’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-21-rats-get-infrared-sixth-sense/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 20:43:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Byrne,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-21-rats-get-infrared-sixth-sense/</guid>
        <description>Researchers at Duke University have given lab rats the ability to ‘see’ infrared light, in research published in Nature Communications last week.
The story was reported widely as the rats getting a ‘sixth sense’. The term is an exaggeration, implying some unexplained or paranormal effect. But the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stem cells aid recovery from stroke
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-stem-cells-aid-recovery-from-stroke/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 23:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Byrne,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-stem-cells-aid-recovery-from-stroke/</guid>
        <description>he effects of a stroke can be devastating, with the initial loss of blood supply to part of the brain setting in motion a series of biochemical events called the ‘ischaemic cascade’. This causes cumulative damage to brain cells and blood vessels during the first few hours after the stroke, often …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Protein-building nanomachines
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-protein-building-nanomachines/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 23:24:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Byrne,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-protein-building-nanomachines/</guid>
        <description>Inside every cell, tiny biological machines are hard at work, constructing the proteins that will perform vital roles as enzymes, hormones, and a wide variety of other structural and biochemical functions. These molecular machines, called ribosomes, translate our genetic code into a protein …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don’t let your heart rule your head
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-dont-let-your-heart-rule-your-head/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 01:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Byrne,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-dont-let-your-heart-rule-your-head/</guid>
        <description>Cognitive decline is often accepted as an inevitable part of aging. Even aside from specific conditions such as Alzheimer’s disease, poor short term memory and impaired reasoning abilities can be among the problems that come with older age, and for many people they can be severe enough to interfere …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Silwood Park hope for British ash population
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-silwood-park-hope-for-british-ash-population/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 21:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Byrne,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-silwood-park-hope-for-british-ash-population/</guid>
        <description>The European ash tree is a familiar sight across the UK’s gardens, parks and countryside, and has been part of the landscape for many centuries, the common name even deriving from Old English.
However earlier this year a serious fungal disease affecting ash trees, Chalara fraxinea, was found in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New drug could hold the key to pancreatic cancer
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-new-drug-could-hold-the-key-to-pancreatic-cancer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 02:29:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Byrne,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-new-drug-could-hold-the-key-to-pancreatic-cancer/</guid>
        <description>The thunder god vine, or Lei Gong Teng, is a herb used in traditional Chinese medicine and believed by some to be of use in a variety of ailments from arthritis to kidney disease. The plant contains multiple active compounds, and one of the most promising of these is triptolide, previously shown to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Good news, bad news
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-good-news-bad-news/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:20:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Byrne,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-good-news-bad-news/</guid>
        <description>Do you want the good news or the bad news first? The bad news is that we are all hopeless optimists; but on the positive side, research published in PNAS last month suggests we can be cured.
Previous research had shown that we tend to process positive and negative information differently. When …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stem cells help stop biological clock
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-stem-cells-help-stop-biological-clock/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 20:07:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Byrne,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-stem-cells-help-stop-biological-clock/</guid>
        <description>Most women will at some point in their lives encounter the ticking biological clock: the realisation that their fertile years are limited, and if they wish to start a family, they cannot wait much longer. This is because we have only the supply of oocytes or egg cells we are born with, and when …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Historic social networks
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-historic-social-networks/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 19:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Byrne,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-historic-social-networks/</guid>
        <description>We normally think of social networks as a modern-day phenomenon: Facebook, Twitter etc. come to mind. But according to recent research published in Nature, ancient societies may have been organised along much the same lines.
It is a popular belief that the evolution of human behaviour is all about …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fleming’s fungus finally identified
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-flemings-fungus-finally-identified/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 19:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Byrne,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-flemings-fungus-finally-identified/</guid>
        <description>Moulds are perhaps the least celebrated of organisms, with the notable exception of the one that led to Alexander Fleming’s discovery of penicillin in 1928. The story is well-known: the fungal spores were accidentally allowed to contaminate a petri dish, Fleming observed that the mould was killing …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
