<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ygr12/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ygr12/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The FELIX Sex Survey 2016
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-the-felix-sex-survey-2016/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 09:01:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-the-felix-sex-survey-2016/</guid>
        <description>Here it is, for the sixth year running, the infamous FELIX Sex Survey results. Thank you so much to everyone who trusted us with your deepest, darkest, and occasionally unrealistic and obviously made-up secrets (we deleted those responses from our data). Six hundred or so of you took the time to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s harder to get into Imperial if you&#39;re black
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-its-harder-to-get-into-imperial-if-youre-black/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 08:50:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-its-harder-to-get-into-imperial-if-youre-black/</guid>
        <description>UCAS has released data that shows Imperial is one of the country’s worst offenders in terms of giving fewer offers to black and poorer students.
UCAS’ data shows that in 2015, 2014 and 2012, there was a statistically significant difference between the offer rate for black applicants and the average …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Next year our sabbs become the highest paid in the country
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-next-year-our-sabbs-become-the-highest-paid-in-the-country/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 08:23:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-next-year-our-sabbs-become-the-highest-paid-in-the-country/</guid>
        <description>Next year’s sabbs, who were elected in March and take up their roles officially this August, will, on paper, become the best-paid full-time sabbatical officers in the country. They’ll have jumped from fourteenth highest-paid sabbs to the highest, beating last year’s highest, LSE, who pay a modest …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Student caught in housing scam
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-student-caught-in-housing-scam/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 08:16:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-student-caught-in-housing-scam/</guid>
        <description>A student was caught out by scammers this week after paying a deposit on a flat that turned out not to be for rent.
The student saw the flat, which was just off the King’s Road, advertised on one of the union’s fresher Facebook groups. After speaking with the person who posted the ad, the student …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dog therapy for stressed students
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-dog-therapy-for-stressed-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 08:12:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-dog-therapy-for-stressed-students/</guid>
        <description>The City and Guilds union offered a novel way of recovering from exam stress relief last week – playing with dogs.
The dogs, who were brought in by the dog re-homing charity All Dogs Matter, sat in a room in CGCU, and students filed in all afternoon to play with them. They also had a few walks …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mech Eng head tells students he’s voting remain
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-mech-eng-head-tells-students-hes-voting-remain/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 08:12:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-mech-eng-head-tells-students-hes-voting-remain/</guid>
        <description>On Sunday, the head of the department of mechanical engineering sent an email to all of his students and staff, addressing concerns about a post-Brexit fee status for EU students, and telling them that he was “strongly in favour of remaining in the EU” and so would be “voting accordingly”.
In the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Our sabbs will now be paid £29,800 a year
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-our-sabbs-will-now-be-paid-29800-a-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 08:11:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-our-sabbs-will-now-be-paid-29800-a-year/</guid>
        <description>This year’s change in sabb pay, despite looking like a £10,000 pay rise on paper, may actually leave sabbs worse off financially than ever.
In an investigation by FELIX, comparing this year’s cohort pay packet and remuneration arrangements (i.e. offer of ‘free’ halls that goes with the job) to next …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How much does the Rector get paid?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-how-much-does-the-rector-get-paid/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 09:06:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-how-much-does-the-rector-get-paid/</guid>
        <description>The college’s Rector does a very important job. They go on Radio 4 for us, they sign open letters in newspapers, and if you’re lucky and they’re not having a round off, they shake your hand at graduation. The amount these members of staff get paid is always a point of contention.
This week, we took …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial academics warn against Brexit
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-imperial-academics-warn-against-brexit/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 08:38:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-imperial-academics-warn-against-brexit/</guid>
        <description>Professors and readers in public health at Imperial have published a letter in this month’s Journal of the Royal Society of Medicine on how staying in the EU would help safeguard the health of British people.
The letter, signed by 17 academics, points to the economic downturn predicted by the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial starts joint venture with Nestlé
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-imperial-starts-joint-venture-with-nestl/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 08:32:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-imperial-starts-joint-venture-with-nestl/</guid>
        <description>Imperial has signed a deal with the food and drink giant Nestlé to launch research into nutrition together.
The research will focus specifically on the gut’s bacterial make-up, the microbiome, and digestive metabolites’ influence on both physical and mental health.
Nestlé will invest £6.5 million in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial staff pensions invested in tobacco firms
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-imperial-staff-pensions-invested-in-tobacco-firms/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 08:29:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-imperial-staff-pensions-invested-in-tobacco-firms/</guid>
        <description>After FELIX’s scoop last week on Imperial’s £2.4 million investment in the tobacco industry, the Guardian has revealed that a university pensions provider has £211 million invested in British American Tobacco.
The Universities Superannuation Scheme (USS) is the pension fund for academic staff at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Imperial endowment fund – what are we investing in?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-the-imperial-endowment-fund-what-are-we-investing-in/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 08:43:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-the-imperial-endowment-fund-what-are-we-investing-in/</guid>
        <description>Imperial’s investment portfolio is a well-known part of the college’s assets. Much like a savings account, a board decides where we invest year on year, to make the most of our stacks of cash and earn us interest. This is done by most universities, and whereas Oxford and Cambridge’s endowments are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Petition to air con in the library hits 1000 signatures
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-petition-to-air-con-in-the-library-hits-1000-signatures/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 08:41:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-petition-to-air-con-in-the-library-hits-1000-signatures/</guid>
        <description>Sign the petition here.
FELIX’s petition to get air conditioning in the library has had a strong opening week, reaching 1000 signatures on its third day, showing how keen students are for better revision conditions.
Comments from miffed students on why they signed the petition range from the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>David Nutt talks drugs, alcohol and research funding
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-david-nutt-talks-drugs-alcohol-and-research-funding/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 08:39:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-david-nutt-talks-drugs-alcohol-and-research-funding/</guid>
        <description>David Nutt, the chair of Imperial’s Centre for Neuropsychopharmacology, advocate for drug reform, and former chair of the Advisory Council on the Misuse of Drugs before he was sacked by the government in 2009 for saying alcohol was more harmful than illegal drugs, spoke to students and staff last …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial places 7th in the Guardian’s league table
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-imperial-places-7th-in-the-guardians-league-table/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 08:38:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-imperial-places-7th-in-the-guardians-league-table/</guid>
        <description>Imperial has placed seventh in the Guardian’s league table of British universities, coming behind Durham, Surrey and Loughborough.
Imperial usually takes third place in league tables of UK universities but in this league table, St Andrews comes straight in after Cambridge and Oxford.
The Guardian’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial gets 20% of its research money from the EU
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-imperial-gets-20-of-its-research-money-from-the-eu/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 08:37:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-imperial-gets-20-of-its-research-money-from-the-eu/</guid>
        <description>Imperial receives just over 20% of its research funding from the EU, according to a report by a research software firm.
Over the last ten years, the EU has given Imperial grants in the region of £342 million.
The research hints towards the idea that if the public vote for Brexit in June’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial has £2.3 million invested in tobacco firms via endowment
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-imperial-has-23-million-invested-in-tobacco-firms-via-endowment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 08:36:24 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-imperial-has-23-million-invested-in-tobacco-firms-via-endowment/</guid>
        <description>This week FELIX revealed that the college has significant investments in several tobacco firms, as part of its endowment portfolio.
Overall, Imperial has invested just under £2.4 million across several tobacco firms, via several equity and hedge funds.
Our findings, made via a Freedom of Information …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FELIX investigates study drugs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-felix-investigates-study-drugs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 09:02:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-felix-investigates-study-drugs/</guid>
        <description>Like all good things in life, this article starts with a disclaimer: FELIX is by no means advocating the use of these so-called study drugs. I don’t know about you, but shitting every hour doesn’t scream productive work mode to me, – each to their own. We’re just giving you some facts and student …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fraudsters target students in scam outside halls
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-fraudsters-target-students-in-scam-outside-halls/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 08:49:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-fraudsters-target-students-in-scam-outside-halls/</guid>
        <description>This week, a student was conned into handing over cash to fraudsters on Prince Consort Road.
Two men in a white Audi stopped the student near Beit, pretending to be Armani salesman.
They got chatting, and persuaded the student that they had leather jackets to give away. The fraudsters told the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Petition started to get air conditioning in library
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-petition-started-to-get-air-conditioning-in-library/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 08:46:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-petition-started-to-get-air-conditioning-in-library/</guid>
        <description>Sign the petition here.
A petition, launched by FELIX, asking college to pay for air conditioning in the central library has nearly 1000 signatures after being launched on Friday.
The college got planning permission for air conditioning units on the library’s roof two years ago, but little has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Aero students invited to will.i.am gig because director liked their boiler suits
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-aero-students-invited-to-william-gig-because-director-liked-their-boiler-suits/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 08:45:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-aero-students-invited-to-william-gig-because-director-liked-their-boiler-suits/</guid>
        <description>Twenty first year aeronautics students were given free tickets to a will.i.am gig at the Royal Albert Hall gig last week, after being spotted in their boiler suits taking an end of year picture outside the venue earlier that day.
Apparently impressed by the group’s aesthetic, the concert’s director …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial President sends mass email on EU stance
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-imperial-president-sends-mass-email-on-eu-stance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 08:43:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-imperial-president-sends-mass-email-on-eu-stance/</guid>
        <description>On Monday, Imperial President, Alice Gast, and Provost, James Stirling, sent an email to all staff and students, encouraging us to vote and reminding us of their stance on the EU.
After encouraging recipients to register to vote in the June referendum, Professor Gast described how Imperial had …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Student’s political dreams shattered
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-students-political-dreams-shattered/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 08:49:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-students-political-dreams-shattered/</guid>
        <description>An Imperial student with dreams of becoming a councillor was beaten by two Conservative candidates to join Kensington and Chelsea council.
The winners were Sarah Ann Louise Addenbrooke and Anne Barbara Cyron, who gained 1716 and 1470 votes respectively.
The final year physics student did come in at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial to spread medic bursaries out across all six years
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-imperial-to-spread-medic-bursaries-out-across-all-six-years/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 08:48:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-imperial-to-spread-medic-bursaries-out-across-all-six-years/</guid>
        <description>Yesterday it was announced that Imperial’s bursaries for medics will be spread out over all six years of study instead of just the first four. This is in a bid to ease the financial hardship that notoriously occurs in the final years of a medical degree.
Currently, medical students can get up to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sigma cancels Summer Ball appearance
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-10-sigma-cancels-summer-ball-appearance/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 13:11:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-10-sigma-cancels-summer-ball-appearance/</guid>
        <description>FELIX has learnt that Sigma, the DJ duo who were due to play the ICU Summer Ball, have cancelled and will be replaced by DJ Fresh. Despite the fact that a contract had already been signed, Sigma told the union last week that they would not be playing the Summer Ball on the 18th of June, presumably …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Laing O’Rourke awarded another Imperial contract
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-laing-orourke-awarded-another-imperial-contract/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 09:45:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-laing-orourke-awarded-another-imperial-contract/</guid>
        <description>This week it was announced that the contract for the large tower to be constructed at the Imperial West campus will be given to Laing O’Rourke.
The £76 million project will be to build a 34-storey block that will include 192 apartments, with 59 of those reserved for “Imperial key workers”. According …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I just got my PhD, will you marry me?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-i-just-got-my-phd-will-you-marry-me/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 09:42:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-i-just-got-my-phd-will-you-marry-me/</guid>
        <description>Adorable or terrible? At Wednesday’s postgraduate graduation ceremony a student who, judging from his gown, had just completed a PhD, proposed to his girlfriend onstage at the Royal Albert Hall. Cameras are set up that project close ups of those crossing the stage up onto a screen behind it for the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students sign up to three year £125,000 housing contract by accident
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-students-sign-up-to-three-year-125000-housing-contract-by-accident/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 09:41:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-students-sign-up-to-three-year-125000-housing-contract-by-accident/</guid>
        <description>This week, college is coming to the aid of three Imperial students who accidentally signed a three year tenancy agreement for a flat on Queen’s Gate that they can’t afford.
The house, which has three bedrooms, was advertised at £800 per week in total, which amounts to a hefty £267 per student per …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Exam mishap as students given test with answers attached
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-exam-mishap-as-students-given-test-with-answers-attached/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 09:40:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-exam-mishap-as-students-given-test-with-answers-attached/</guid>
        <description>In a classic example of exam season drama, first year geophysics students were given a paper with the answers at the bottom.
Students quickly realised the error and told the invigilators, who allowed the students to leave the room without starting the exam.
The test, which took place on the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What’s your degree worth now?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-whats-your-degree-worth-now/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:34:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-whats-your-degree-worth-now/</guid>
        <description>We’re constantly being told that degrees aren’t as valuable as they used to be. And fair enough. Your mate from home’s 2:2 in film and media studies might not expect to be as valuable as your mum’s desmond in computing from the 80s, but an Imperial degree is an Imperial degree, right?
Perhaps not. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NUS votes to allow student media to comment on union elections
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-nus-votes-to-allow-student-media-to-comment-on-union-elections/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:06:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-nus-votes-to-allow-student-media-to-comment-on-union-elections/</guid>
        <description>At last week’s NUS conference, a motion was passed which should allow student media organisations to cover union elections in more detail.
Most unions insist student newspapers only publish election material okayed by the candidates. Students who wrote the motion argued that ‘propaganda’ like …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ex-student Trevor Philips says Muslims in Britain “do not want to participate”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-ex-student-trevor-philips-says-muslims-in-britain-do-not-want-to-participate/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:03:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-ex-student-trevor-philips-says-muslims-in-britain-do-not-want-to-participate/</guid>
        <description>Ex-ICU President and broadcaster, Trevor Philips, appeared in a Channel 4 documentary called “What do Muslims really think?” The controversial show, which aired in the Easter break, reflected on a poll which had quizzed Muslims on their thoughts on issues like homosexuality, sharia law and human …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We’re having a Mayor-off
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-20-were-having-a-mayor-off/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 14:54:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-20-were-having-a-mayor-off/</guid>
        <description> Next Thursday, Londoners go to the polls to vote in their new Mayor of London. Twice-elected Conservative Boris Johnson has moved onto bigger and better things, and now Labour’s Sadiq Khan and the Conservative Zac Goldsmith are going head to head below in this: our comparison of the two …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>38% increase in Imperial students seeking counselling
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-38-increase-in-imperial-students-seeking-counselling/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 11:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-38-increase-in-imperial-students-seeking-counselling/</guid>
        <description>There has been a 38% increase in students seeking counselling services from college over the last three years, despite only a 5% increase in students over the same period.
Last year’s figures were also up 12% from the year before.
In the 2014&amp;frasl;15 academic year, 3.7% of the student population, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The women of Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-the-women-of-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 11:34:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-the-women-of-imperial/</guid>
        <description>The odds are good, but the goods are odd, or so goes the saying on the ‘talent’ at our beloved university. It’s an oft-referred trope of Imperial: on open days, we’re warned that there’s no shortage of dudes, and forced conversations during freshers’ week often resort to, “Wow, there are loads of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What’s happening to union council?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-whats-happening-to-union-council/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 11:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-whats-happening-to-union-council/</guid>
        <description>At this week’s union council a paper was tabled&amp;hellip; on the problems faced by union council.
Only two meetings so far this academic year have been quorate, rendering the democratic outlet for students ultimately useless.
The paper, entitled ‘Solving Council’s Quorum Crisis’, proposed to discount …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>King’s Student has niqab ripped off
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-kings-student-has-niqab-ripped-off/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 11:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-kings-student-has-niqab-ripped-off/</guid>
        <description>Afemale Muslim student had her niqab pulled off by two men outside the King’s Strand campus last Friday.
Bystanders said the men, not thought to be students, approached the students’ stall and started using racially aggravated language before throwing leaflets over their stall. They then asked why …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>International Women’s Day at Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-international-womens-day-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 11:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-international-womens-day-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>International Women’s Day on Tuesday was marked by college’s ‘Women@Imperial’ week.
Over the week, Imperial’s official Twitter and Facebook pages churned out images and interviews from women working around Imperial.
An exhibition celebrating women has been up in the Business School entrance all …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Basketball team told by Ethos they’re not a “commercial asset”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-basketball-team-told-by-ethos-theyre-not-a-commercial-asset/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 11:20:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-basketball-team-told-by-ethos-theyre-not-a-commercial-asset/</guid>
        <description>Last weekend Imperial’s 1st Basketball team were told as they arrived for a tournament they had organised that their court booking had been given away to a birthday party.
The group had spent hours organising the tournament, that involved multiple matches, teams and referees. The tickets cost £4 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Renovated Evelyn Gardens halls will cost up to £225 per week
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-renovated-evelyn-gardens-halls-will-cost-up-to-225-per-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 11:18:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-renovated-evelyn-gardens-halls-will-cost-up-to-225-per-week/</guid>
        <description>Three halls in Evelyn Gardens, Holbein, Southwell and Willis Jackson, which college closed at the end of last year, will reopen this September to second and third year undergraduates only.
Standard singles will range from £182 to £200 per week, in comparison to Beit’s £192. Ensuite singles range …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Presidential candidates boycott radio debate after “aggressive” emails and “extreme dissatisfaction&#34;
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-9-presidential-candidates-boycott-radio-debate-after-aggressive-emails-and-extreme-dissatisfaction/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 19:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-9-presidential-candidates-boycott-radio-debate-after-aggressive-emails-and-extreme-dissatisfaction/</guid>
        <description>A debate between Union President Candidates that was due to be held on IC Radio last night was scuppered after four candidates decided to boycott the show an hour before it went on air.
The show, which initially raised eyebrows after one presenter had been on one candidate’s campaign team, was later …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Election fever sweeps campus
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-election-fever-sweeps-campus/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 11:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-election-fever-sweeps-campus/</guid>
        <description>Voting opens today for the Leadership Elections, which have seen a record number of students come forward for the roles of President and Deputy President (Welfare). No one put themselves forward for the Deputy President (Finance and Services) role.
The current DPFS, Chris Kaye, commented on Twitter …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Meet the Candidates broadcast with nine Presidents
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-meet-the-candidates-broadcast-with-nine-presidents/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 11:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-4-meet-the-candidates-broadcast-with-nine-presidents/</guid>
        <description> Loud cries of protest could be heard from the next room
 After some technical difficulties around kick off, ICTV and Imperial College London’s evening of candidate-grilling began.
Ex-Union President, Paul Beaumont, played Jeremy Paxman on the night. Most would agree his style was kind, despite …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cancelled RAG bungee jump green lit by college
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-cancelled-rag-bungee-jump-green-lit-by-college/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 11:27:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-cancelled-rag-bungee-jump-green-lit-by-college/</guid>
        <description>Despite knowing about it since November, college officials cancelled the jump just three days before it was due to take place, over health and safety concerns.
The RAG committee were contacted by senior college officials last Friday, who told them the bungee jump would not be happening.
The jump was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial President Alice Gast signs pro-EU letter
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-imperial-president-alice-gast-signs-pro-eu-letter/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 11:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-imperial-president-alice-gast-signs-pro-eu-letter/</guid>
        <description>Over one hundred leaders of UK universities, including the President of Imperial, Alice Gast, have signed an open letter published in the Sunday Times, asking the British public to reject a ‘Brexit’ and vote to stay in the European Union.
The letter says universities are better able to “collaborate …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College puts a stop to RAG bungee jump
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-22-college-puts-a-stop-to-rag-bungee-jump/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 18:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-22-college-puts-a-stop-to-rag-bungee-jump/</guid>
        <description>UPDATE 24/02/16 : FELIX has now learnt the bungee jump has been green-lit by college, although a new date is yet to be set.
RAG’s annual bungee jump has been cancelled just three days beforehand over health and safety concerns.
The RAG committee were contacted by senior college officials on Friday, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>More than one female toilet for RSM
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-more-than-one-female-toilet-for-rsm/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 11:08:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-more-than-one-female-toilet-for-rsm/</guid>
        <description>Women in the Goldsmith’s wing of the RSM building had a bit of a shock after coming back over the summer: all but a single female toilet had been converted to men’s only. This meant that women had to either queue to use one loo or walk to another building if it was out of order.
A survey into the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>RAG mag battle reaches national newspapers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-rag-mag-battle-reaches-national-newspapers/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 11:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-rag-mag-battle-reaches-national-newspapers/</guid>
        <description>This week, national newspapers covered the sexism row that has been raging since the union strongly advised RAG to bin 1600 copies of a satirical magazine they’d just printed. In an attempt to raise money for Great Ormond Street Hospital, the British Refugee Council and Porridge in Rice, which works …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>RAG Jailbreakers removed from flight to Turkey after terror suspicions
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-rag-jailbreakers-removed-from-flight-to-turkey-after-terror-suspicions/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 11:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-rag-jailbreakers-removed-from-flight-to-turkey-after-terror-suspicions/</guid>
        <description>One team in RAG’s jailbreak competition found themselves £400 down and a day behind after being pulled off of a flight to Istanbul by anti-terror police.
The group of students, who were raising money for several charities, had spent the first morning of the jailbreak fundraising around West London. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Could Imperial ever go on a rent strike?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-could-imperial-ever-go-on-a-rent-strike/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 11:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-could-imperial-ever-go-on-a-rent-strike/</guid>
        <description>We’ve had our fair share of housing disputes at Imperial.
If you think people don’t care, check out the ICTV’s ‘Imperial Questions Live’ debate on the subject of Weeks hall from last year. Think union council but with ironed shirts and better behaviour since it’s on YouTube for eternity and there …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>RAG mag battle becomes sexism row
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-rag-mag-battle-becomes-sexism-row/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 11:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-rag-mag-battle-becomes-sexism-row/</guid>
        <description>In this week’s FELIX, the Union President has spoken out on last week’s RAG mag controversy. Contents of the magazine, although technically not banned, caused the union to strongly advise RAG to dispose of the 1600 undistributed copies after the union had seen the contents. One page in particular …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rowers forced to pay hotel two grand in fines
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-rowers-forced-to-pay-hotel-two-grand-in-fines/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 11:10:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-rowers-forced-to-pay-hotel-two-grand-in-fines/</guid>
        <description>The rowing club have been forced to pay £2050 in reparations to the Ambassadors Hotel in Bloomsbury, where they held their annual dinner three weeks ago.
The payment came straight from the club’s own account of Self Generated Income, which will include money the club have raised from sponsorship and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>RAG mag accused of &#34;harassment and bullying&#34;
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-rag-mag-accused-of-harassment-and-bullying/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 11:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-rag-mag-accused-of-harassment-and-bullying/</guid>
        <description>Yesterday the union told RAG its magazine of adverts and satire was “beyond the acceptable bounds of satire or mockery”. RAG were also warned that the individuals involved in writing it could be faced with serious consequences from the college if they continued to distribute the magazine as this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rowers thrown out of hotel for partying too hard
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-rowers-thrown-out-of-hotel-for-partying-too-hard/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 08:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-rowers-thrown-out-of-hotel-for-partying-too-hard/</guid>
        <description>Last Saturday, Imperial College Boat Club’s annual party ended early when students were chucked out for bad behaviour.
In an email seen by FELIX sent from the venue’s management after the event, the students are accused of throwing food at members of staff, vomiting in corridors and staircases …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Medic boat club stopped on way to Belgium for being too drunk
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-22-medic-boat-club-stopped-on-way-to-belgium-for-being-too-drunk/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 12:42:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-22-medic-boat-club-stopped-on-way-to-belgium-for-being-too-drunk/</guid>
        <description>Last week’s ICSM Boat club’s annual trip to Belgium ended before it really even began – at the ferry port in Dover.
Current medics and alumni were prevented by P&amp;amp;O ferry staff from boarding the boat which would have taken them to mainland Europe, as they were too drunk.
The students tried to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Evelyn Gardens may open to non-freshers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-15-evelyn-gardens-may-open-to-non-freshers/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2016 11:23:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-15-evelyn-gardens-may-open-to-non-freshers/</guid>
        <description>At Tuesday night’s union council meeting it came to light that the Evelyn Gardens may become a hall reserved for second years.
The union is currently in talks with college to allow students to take up 51 week contracts in the halls. The rather tired accomodation would most likely be renovated before …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Medics support Junior Doctor strike action
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-15-medics-support-junior-doctor-strike-action/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2016 11:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-15-medics-support-junior-doctor-strike-action/</guid>
        <description> On Tuesday, junior doctors went on strike for 24 hours, in protest against the government’s proposed changes to their contracts. Doctors say these changes will involve both dangerously long working hours for them, which will in turn endanger patients, as well as an effective pay cut.
Peaceful …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial professor makes questionable comments on race in new book
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-13-imperial-professor-makes-questionable-comments-on-race-in-new-book/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 14:45:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-13-imperial-professor-makes-questionable-comments-on-race-in-new-book/</guid>
        <description>One of Imperial’s Emeritus professors has published a book on human diversity, in which he claims that London has “‘no-go’ areas at night for white people”.
He also wrote that having “one race” would “help a nation minimise internal and external conflicts”. Both comments are uncited, and appear in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>12 Jar Jar Binks GIFs That Sum Up Your Life At Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-16-12-jar-jar-binks-gifs-that-sum-up-your-life-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 18:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,Felix Editor,Theresa Davey,Grace G Rahman,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-16-12-jar-jar-binks-gifs-that-sum-up-your-life-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description> 1. When You Arrive Sober At Your First ACC  2. When You Sit Your First Exam At Imperial    Tumblr   3. When You Can&amp;rsquo;t Decide Between Pieminister And The Salad Bar    Tumblr   4. When You Fall For Your Lab Partner    Tumblr   5. When It&amp;rsquo;s Five To Nine And You&amp;rsquo;re Desperate For The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pig’s head found in Australian University mosque&#39;s bathroom
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-11-pigs-head-found-in-australian-university-mosques-bathroom/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 15:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-11-pigs-head-found-in-australian-university-mosques-bathroom/</guid>
        <description>  Last weekend, a student at the University of Western Australia discovered a decapitated pig’s head in the toilets adjacent the University’s Muslim prayer rooms.
Majdi Fal, a Tunisian PhD student, came across the gruesome object when preparing for prayer in the bathrooms near the prayer rooms. He …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial’s Charity Week raises over £61,000
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-4-imperials-charity-week-raises-over-61000/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 15:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-4-imperials-charity-week-raises-over-61000/</guid>
        <description>This week it was announced that Imperial College’s Islamic Society (ISoc) have managed to raise £61,648.31 for good causes as part of Charity Week.
The week included street collections, the ‘Smoky not Smudgy’ fashion event, a climb up Mount Snowdon, and the annual Charity Week dinner and auction. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Anne Robinson’s dismay at Kensington sculpture
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-4-anne-robinsons-dismay-at-kensington-sculpture/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 15:11:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-4-anne-robinsons-dismay-at-kensington-sculpture/</guid>
        <description>This week, plans to install a new sculpture on the roundabout just off Gloucester Road were damned by ex-presenter of The Weakest Link and Watchdog, Anne Robinson.
Robinson, whose infamous glare made her a TV staple in the noughties, said the £100,000 price tag was too much, considering the UK is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Beit basement project deemed &#39;inferior&#39;
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-4-beit-basement-project-deemed-inferior/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 15:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-12-4-beit-basement-project-deemed-inferior/</guid>
        <description>A report, commissioned on behalf of Imperial College Union, described work completed on Beit’s west basement as having created a facility “considered to be very much inferior to that which existed before, with a significant portion of it being unusable.”
It also referred to shortcomings in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union spends five grand on a desk
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-27-union-spends-five-grand-on-a-desk/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 11:52:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-27-union-spends-five-grand-on-a-desk/</guid>
        <description>This week it came to light that the union has spent something in the region of £20,000 on the refurbishment of its own office spaces, £5100 of which was spent on a new light-up reception desk. Other monumental costs included £1266 on the removal and disposal of the old reception desk, £4180 on the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>English universities are the most expensive in the world
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-27-english-universities-are-the-most-expensive-in-the-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 11:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-27-english-universities-are-the-most-expensive-in-the-world/</guid>
        <description>New research has uncovered that students working for degrees at English universities are paying more on average than those in China, Japan or the USA.
During the 2013&amp;frasl;14 year, those studying in Britain were paying an average of £6000 per year. The US was a close second with average annual fees …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FELIX’s Mercury Prize picks
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-felixs-mercury-prize-picks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 09:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Eshbaugh,Peter Munton,Robert Garside,Fred S Fyles,Cale E Tilford,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-20-felixs-mercury-prize-picks/</guid>
        <description> _In Colour_Jamie xx Oh Jamie, you can do no wrong. Not in my eyes, the eyes of anyone who went outdoors this summer who was inundated with your invariably uplifting ‘Good Times’, and presumably, not in the eyes of the Mercury Music Prize people.
The flabbergasting combo of Jamie Smith, dance hall …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union could be banned from lobbying
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-19-union-could-be-banned-from-lobbying/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2015 22:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-19-union-could-be-banned-from-lobbying/</guid>
        <description>This week’s union council meeting was rocked by the tabling of a paper to prevent the union from lobbying its own members.
A difficult read in itself, the paper proposes to ban the union from lobbying its members in either direction for general or by-elections, or in national referenda, such as the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial mourns
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-19-imperial-mourns/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2015 22:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-19-imperial-mourns/</guid>
        <description>Several hundred people gathered at the foot of Queen’s Tower on Monday for a minute’s silence to remember the 129 people killed in the Paris attacks. The crowd included students and staff, who joined a Europe-wide moment of reflection three days after the tragedy.
Students paused at 11am, and after …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Race row at Yale sparks protest
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-race-row-at-yale-sparks-protest/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 14:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-race-row-at-yale-sparks-protest/</guid>
        <description> After an email from a college administrator, telling them to “look away” if they were offended by racially insensitive Halloween costumes, Yale students have been protesting this week.
Shortly before Halloween, an initial email was sent to the whole student body from Yale’s ‘intercultural affairs …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chancellor introduces spending review from Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-chancellor-introduces-spending-review-from-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 14:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-chancellor-introduces-spending-review-from-imperial/</guid>
        <description>After tagging along on President Xi’s visit three weeks ago, George Osborne was back at Imperial on Monday, but this time slightly further out at our White City branch, AKA Imperial West.
Speaking from the unfinished campus, which overlooks the A40, the chancellor introduced the spending review. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College fees likely to rise under new plans
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-college-fees-likely-to-rise-under-new-plans/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 14:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-13-college-fees-likely-to-rise-under-new-plans/</guid>
        <description>Last Friday, the government released its ‘green paper’ on higher education.
Promising to put students “at the heart of higher education”, the 105 page document proposes huge changes to fees and the way universities are created.
The fees for home students at the moment are capped at £9000 per year, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial triumphs at royal start-up competition
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-imperial-triumphs-at-royal-start-up-competition/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 13:37:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-imperial-triumphs-at-royal-start-up-competition/</guid>
        <description>The Duke of York’s Pitch@Palace competition, held this year’s finals at St James’s Palace on Tuesday, with Imperial entrepreneurs taking home both first and third place.
Unmade, a 3D-printed knitwear startup came top, with Baby LifeBox, a low-cost baby incubator, taking third position.
Founded by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union replaces tree in Beit Quad
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-union-replaces-tree-in-beit-quad/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 13:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-union-replaces-tree-in-beit-quad/</guid>
        <description>One of the two large, established cherry trees dominating Beit quad has been completely removed, and replaced with a younger model. Many readers will be familiar with the trees’ knobbly roots which have lifted the paving around the union’s seating area, forming a trip hazard.
The combination of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial students attend fees and cuts demo
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-imperial-students-attend-fees-and-cuts-demo/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 13:32:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-imperial-students-attend-fees-and-cuts-demo/</guid>
        <description>Wednesday saw 10,000 students, including several from Imperial, march for free education. The protest was organised by the National Campaign Against Fees and Cuts. Kieran Ryan (pictured) organised the Imperial bloc, which included the union’s elected Deputy President of Welfare and campaigns …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICTV meet Top Gear host
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-30-ictv-meet-top-gear-host/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 14:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-30-ictv-meet-top-gear-host/</guid>
        <description>ICTV’s Jonathon Masters and Hasan Al-Habib managed to wangle a YouTube gem at the Spectre premiere: an interview with Chris Evans.
After being flagged down by Imperial College TV at the end of the red carpet, Evans paused to talk to the roving reporters.
He was handed a microphone by the rookies, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Several Imperial academics to boycott Israeli universities
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-30-several-imperial-academics-to-boycott-israeli-universities/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 12:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-30-several-imperial-academics-to-boycott-israeli-universities/</guid>
        <description>On Tuesday, a letter pledging an ‘academic boycott’ of Israeli universities was published in The Guardian, signed by 343 lecturers including three from Imperial.
The full page spread was entitled ‘A Commitment by UK Scholars to the rights of Palestinians’ and featured the names and institutions of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President Xi comes to Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-president-xi-comes-to-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 10:49:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-president-xi-comes-to-imperial/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday, Chinese President Xi Jinping stopped off at Imperial to celebrate collaboration between Chinese institutions and the College. Imperial proudly repeated the statistic that since 2003, the number of UK papers published in Nature with a co-author in China had jumped from 3% to 22%. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Hub lives to fight another day
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-16-imperial-hub-lives-to-fight-another-day/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 14:32:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-16-imperial-hub-lives-to-fight-another-day/</guid>
        <description>Imperial hub, the volunteering charity whose relationship with the union went sour over the summer, remains in action. In a statement released after Freshers Fair, the Hub gang said they were still committed to projects they had planned before the split, including the London Climate Forum, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Potential pay rise for union bar staff?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-16-potential-pay-rise-for-union-bar-staff/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 14:28:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-16-potential-pay-rise-for-union-bar-staff/</guid>
        <description>At last Monday’s Union Council meeting, the question was raised as to whether the union should be paying student bar workers the London Living Wage.
At the moment, student bar staff are paid the compulsory minimum wage for adults aged over twenty-one, regardless of the student’s age; this is £6.70 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Prince Andrew hosts entrepreneurial contest
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-16-prince-andrew-hosts-entrepreneurial-contest/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 14:05:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-16-prince-andrew-hosts-entrepreneurial-contest/</guid>
        <description>Wednesday saw the Duke of York come to Imperial, to host his Pitch@Palace entrepreneurial competition.
The royal, who is the Queen’s third child, stood down as the UK trade envoy after being criticised over his friendships with controversial figures, such as Azerbaijan’s president and Jeffrey …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hall seniors forced to move to Evelyn Gardens
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-9-11-hall-seniors-forced-to-move-to-evelyn-gardens/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2015 19:09:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-9-11-hall-seniors-forced-to-move-to-evelyn-gardens/</guid>
        <description>Felix has learnt that at least four Hall Seniors, who had been selected for places at Beit and Prince&amp;rsquo;s Gardens, have been assigned accommodation at the newly re-opened Evelyn Gardens halls without their consent.
As the Freshers received their offers of accommodation early last week, Hall …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College u-turn on Evelyn Gardens
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-8-29-college-u-turn-on-evelyn-gardens/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2015 16:33:47 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-8-29-college-u-turn-on-evelyn-gardens/</guid>
        <description>Imperial have announced that accommodation at Evelyn Gardens will indeed be offered to Imperial students joining this academic year.
This comes after the decision had been made to remove all halls at Evelyn Gardens from Imperial’s “accommodation portfolio”, arguably due to their worsening condition, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What did Imperial get up to this year?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-19-what-did-imperial-get-up-to-this-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 13:26:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,Philip Kent,Philippa M Skett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-19-what-did-imperial-get-up-to-this-year/</guid>
        <description>This year, Felix has covered a plethora of stories from all corners of the campus, covering stories relevant to staff and students alike. We recap the stories we’ve brought to you this year, and what to watch out for next year.
BUAV hit our front pages twice this year; firstly, the animal rights …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get on the zine
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-get-on-the-zine/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 12:11:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-get-on-the-zine/</guid>
        <description>Summer Camp released their third LP, Bad Love, this week, and as well as doing a handful of promotional in store performances, they brought out their second ever zine. Full of comics, poetry and prose from fans who are also friends, ‘Drive Past My House’ is a snazzy addition to any fan’s collection, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Live by the fringe. Die by the fringe.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-live-by-the-fringe-die-by-the-fringe/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 12:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-live-by-the-fringe-die-by-the-fringe/</guid>
        <description> Long before Kate Moss brought the fringe back into the mainstream in 2007, these indie babes were rocking some seriously vision-impairing styles. Forget Cara Delevingne; where we’re going there are no eyebrows. It’s not about seeing the audience anyway, as long as they can see your fringe and you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why I&#39;m voting for Ben Howitt for Deputy President (Clubs and Societies)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-why-im-voting-for-ben-howitt-for-deputy-president-clubs-and-societies/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 14:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-why-im-voting-for-ben-howitt-for-deputy-president-clubs-and-societies/</guid>
        <description>It’s that time of year again. Endless Facebook invites, Haribo flung at you down every corridor and people you’ve never heard of stopping you legging it from your last lecture by shouting terrible hashtags as you, so by the time you get to the JCR only the crap paninis are left.
If your mate’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Favourite Comic – Sex Criminals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-8-my-favourite-comic-sex-criminals/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 16:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-8-my-favourite-comic-sex-criminals/</guid>
        <description>I won’t lie, I don’t know shit about comics. I only started frequenting Soho’s GOSH! Comics for the sexy men and proximity to good record stores. Before I started lurking in the graphic novel section of Waterstones, I thought comics simply provided fuel for Marvel Studios to re-hash into a new …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Historic Soho venue’s license revoked for good
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-historic-soho-venues-license-revoked-for-good/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 19:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-historic-soho-venues-license-revoked-for-good/</guid>
        <description>Music fans were left mourning the loss of another one of London’s live music venues last week, after Westminster council permanently revoked the licence of Madame JoJo’s in Soho, after their appeal against the initial ruling failed. For years, this had been the home of White Heat, an indie night …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Band Aid 30: fastest selling single of 2014
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-20-band-aid-30-fastest-selling-single-of-2014/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 21:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-20-band-aid-30-fastest-selling-single-of-2014/</guid>
        <description>The first radio play of the rejuvenated Band Aid single, Do They Know It’s Christmas?, happened this week, following a first look at the music video on last Saturday’s X Factor. This is the fourth time in thirty years that the charity song has been recorded, but the first time the lyrics have been …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What’s on this week
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-whats-on-this-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 21:53:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-10-whats-on-this-week/</guid>
        <description>Saturday, 1st November: MØ @ O2 Shepherd’s Bush Empire.
You might have seen her supporting AlunaGeorge last year and her debut album, No Mythologies To Follow, sees a collaboration with Diplo. Despite being fresh from a controversial performance with Iggy Azealia on SNL, this is a chance to see MØ …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Benefits Britain and the ethics of TV-making
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-26-benefits-britain-and-the-ethics-of-tv-making/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 12:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-26-benefits-britain-and-the-ethics-of-tv-making/</guid>
        <description>As a self-confessed fan of Benefits Street, I was confused at the break in the series two weeks back, which was followed by an announcement that Channel 4 was capitalising further on the few weeks of column inches the show had earned them by staging a debate on benefits.
It promised to feature the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
