<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/srg03/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/srg03/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Rubberise your iPhone 4 with SecondSkin
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-rubberise-your-iphone-4-with-secondskin/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 19:38:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-rubberise-your-iphone-4-with-secondskin/</guid>
        <description>Silicon cases have been a dime-a-dozen ever since the original iPod. When you get to the iPhone 4, those same soft silicon cases haven’t really evolved very much. Sure they have cut outs now so you can access the buttons and the ports, but they’re still pretty poor.
The Cygnett SecondSkin for the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Got a laptop bag, how about a tablet bag?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-got-a-laptop-bag-how-about-a-tablet-bag/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 20:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-got-a-laptop-bag-how-about-a-tablet-bag/</guid>
        <description>You’ve got a laptop bag, but what about an iPad bag? It might seem like an odd concept to have a bag just for your iPad, when you can fit it in almost any bag you’re likely to be carrying. But that hasn’t deterred be.ez from releasing an iPad version of it’s LE rush line of laptop bags, the En …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Feather-light protection for your iPhone 4.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-feather-light-protection-for-your-iphone-4/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 20:21:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-feather-light-protection-for-your-iphone-4/</guid>
        <description>Incipio is pretty well known for its slimline iPhone cases. From the first generation through to the iPhone 4, Incipio has made some of the best minimal cases money can buy. So you could say Incipio’s latest, the feather for iPhone 4, has some big boots to fill.
Feather by name, feather by nature – …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>To protect and charge: the Juice Pack Air
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-to-protect-and-charge-the-juice-pack-air/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 20:34:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-to-protect-and-charge-the-juice-pack-air/</guid>
        <description>The iPod touch is an outstanding media player for the most part. Packing almost all the tech behind the wildly popular iPhone, save for the cell radio of course, and playing host to up to 64GB of storage, there’s a lot to love about Apple’s touchable media player.
Of course there’s one thing that’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ez laptop protection for those in LE Rush
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-ez-laptop-protection-for-those-in-le-rush/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 19:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-ez-laptop-protection-for-those-in-le-rush/</guid>
        <description>If you’ve ever carried a MacBook Pro out and about with you, you’ll know that a laptop bag is essential. Considering you’re carrying around the best part of £1000 at least, when it comes to a bag you’re going to want something well built and with decent padding, God-forbid you drop the thing. Be.ez …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Christmas Gift Guide
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-christmas-gift-guide/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 20:02:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-christmas-gift-guide/</guid>
        <description>£25 and Under
First up we’ve got the under £25 category, and while there’s quite a lot you can get for under a quarter of a ton, there’s not much better, and more useful, than a flash drive. Problem is flash drives are a dime a dozen these days, and while they come in all shapes and sizes most are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Eyeball 2 Eyeball
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-eyeball-2-eyeball/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 20:09:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-eyeball-2-eyeball/</guid>
        <description>Having loved the Blue Yeti a couple of weeks ago, we had high expectations for Blue’s latest webcam replacement, the Eyeball 2.0. Featuring Blue’s excellent USB microphone technology, and a retractable 2MP webcam, on paper the Eyeball 2.0 is an excellent upgrade to the stock web chat solution built …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Clear iPhone 4 protection
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-clear-iphone-4-protection/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 18:46:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-clear-iphone-4-protection/</guid>
        <description>The iPhone 4 is a svelte piece of product design, with immaculate lines and a glossy, beautiful finish. Like it or loathe it, no one can deny that it is a gorgeous piece of hardware and, with it costing up to £600, you probably want to keep it that way.
In steps Scosche with its take on the thin …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can you hear me now?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-can-you-hear-me-now/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 18:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-can-you-hear-me-now/</guid>
        <description>Not all microphones are born equal; some are infinitely more equal than others. That’s certainly the case with the THX certified Yeti from renowned USB microphone manufacturer Blue.
The £100 Yeti is the top of the range, all singing, all dancing USB microphone that claims to be able to do it all. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Alluring iPad case
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-an-alluring-ipad-case/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 18:57:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-an-alluring-ipad-case/</guid>
        <description>So you’ve got your shiny new iPad and you want to take it everywhere with you, but what about protecting your not inconsiderable investment? The back may be made from tough aluminium, but with that large pane of glass on the front, it’s just asking for trouble.
That’s where the LA robe Allure for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Technology Survival Guide 2010
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-1-imperial-technology-survival-guide-2010/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 22:00:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-1-imperial-technology-survival-guide-2010/</guid>
        <description>Welcome Freshers! You’ve made it to Imperial, a place where technology and life should go hand in hand. I’ll leave that up to you to decide whether that’s true, but here’s a quick guide to tech at college and the surrounding areas of London to see you through your first couple of weeks.
These days …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>WikiLeaks - Freedom of Information&#39;s Greatest Assett
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-6-16-wikileaks-freedom-of-informations-greatest-assett/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2010 19:49:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-6-16-wikileaks-freedom-of-informations-greatest-assett/</guid>
        <description>Where would you go if you had a government secret that you felt needed publishing? Just as there’s a wiki for encyclopaedia articles and another for dictionary entries, you might want to try the wiki for whistleblowers and activists, Wikileaks. Among its eclectic collection of leaks are a manual on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sort your journal library out with Papers for Mac
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-6-16-sort-your-journal-library-out-with-papers-for-mac/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2010 19:44:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-6-16-sort-your-journal-library-out-with-papers-for-mac/</guid>
        <description>Reading peer-reviewed journal articles is one of the most crucial parts of studying science. Whether you’re an undergraduate trying to write a literature review or a researcher trying to find a new method, journals are the primary way of sharing new information on research topics with both …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Google TV - WebTV all over again?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-5-28-google-tv-webtv-all-over-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 10:48:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-5-28-google-tv-webtv-all-over-again/</guid>
        <description>If you haven&amp;rsquo;t heard, Google launched its attempt to infiltrate the TV space with internet content this week. The Android based Google TV aims to bring not only video, but the whole internet onto the small screen. The search giant isn&amp;rsquo;t the first to attempt to do so however, as Microsoft …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Open Source Problem
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-5-28-the-open-source-problem/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 10:28:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-5-28-the-open-source-problem/</guid>
        <description>If you’re unfamiliar with the concept of open source software, you’re definitely not alone. In a market full of expensive consumer electronics that are locked down and bound to carriers and application stores, the concept of releasing the code to software that has taken you hundreds of hours to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Privacy paradigm shift leaves Facebookers open
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-5-21-privacy-paradigm-shift-leaves-facebookers-open/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 12:15:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-5-21-privacy-paradigm-shift-leaves-facebookers-open/</guid>
        <description>On May 12th, the New York Times published an infographic (right) that would have looked more at home in a science textbook - their breakdown of Facebook&amp;rsquo;s privacy options. The final count reached 50 settings containing 170 options in total, ranging from those related to the public availability …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lanchiya mi-football iPod dock review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-5-14-lanchiya-mi-football-ipod-dock-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2010 11:52:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-5-14-lanchiya-mi-football-ipod-dock-review/</guid>
        <description>The World Cup is on its way, about a month away now and everyone with a product to sell is jumping on the football bandwagon. We&amp;rsquo;ve got shirts, flags, footballs and even Pringles trying to get a slice of World Cup fever. It&amp;rsquo;ll come as no surprise that electronics manufacturers are also …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The World Cup in HD
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-5-7-the-world-cup-in-hd/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2010 11:50:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-5-7-the-world-cup-in-hd/</guid>
        <description>The World Cup is coming and it&amp;rsquo;s only 34 days away! That&amp;rsquo;s 32 of the best teams from around the world, battling it out over 30 days, through group stages and knockout games, all to get their hands on that elusive golden trophy. That&amp;rsquo;s a lot of quality football, and this year …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Microsoft Kin One and Two
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-4-30-microsoft-kin-one-and-two/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 11:42:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-4-30-microsoft-kin-one-and-two/</guid>
        <description>Microsoft, not to be left out of the party that was April, announced its first own-brand phones, the Kin One, a square slider and the Kin Two, a more traditional landscape slider. Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s aiming the Kin brand as a separate device category from the recently announced Windows Phone 7, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dell&#39;s Device Deluge
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-4-30-dells-device-deluge/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 11:39:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-4-30-dells-device-deluge/</guid>
        <description> ###
Dell&amp;rsquo;s been pretty busy behind the scenes over Easter and on April 21st, the mother of all leaks landed in the laps of the Engadget Crew. In the leak there were details and photos of no less than five previously unknown devices and more detail on two as yet unreleased gadgets. The bounty …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Apple&#39;s iPhone Prototype Leaked
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-4-30-apples-iphone-prototype-leaked/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 11:23:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-4-30-apples-iphone-prototype-leaked/</guid>
        <description>Love it or hate it, the iPhone is a pretty big part of the modern smartphone market, and as such is currently the phone to beat. Apple is expected to release a brand new iPhone in the summer, but normally it&amp;rsquo;s legendary culture of secrecy keeps leaks to an absolute minimum, leaving the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Apple&#39;s iPhone OS 4 unveiled
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-4-30-apples-iphone-os-4-unveiled/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 11:03:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-4-30-apples-iphone-os-4-unveiled/</guid>
        <description>Whilst the great majority of you were hitting the books, Apple has been quite busy. A week after the iPad release the fruity company sent out invites to an iPhone OS4 event titled &amp;lsquo;Get a sneak peak into the future of iPhone OS&amp;rsquo;. Now of course, this wasn&amp;rsquo;t really a surprise for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Apple&#39;s iPad Launch
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-4-30-apples-ipad-launch/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 10:47:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-4-30-apples-ipad-launch/</guid>
        <description>Whilst you were out, Apple launched a little thing called the iPad. You might have seen our feature on Mr. Jobs&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;magical&amp;rsquo; device last term, which was released in its WiFi only form to avid fans across the US on April 3rd. Is it as amazing as all Apple fanboys hoped and dreamed? …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Easter Break Tech Wrap Up
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-4-30-easter-break-tech-wrap-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 10:40:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-4-30-easter-break-tech-wrap-up/</guid>
        <description>Welcome back all you holidaying Imperialites. I hope you had a refreshing break or as so many of you were, your revision went well. It&amp;rsquo;s back to the daily grind from now until the end of the academic year with the summer term punctuated by exams and projects.
But enough of that, what did we …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>E-Ink&#39;s not ready for prime time
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-3-12-e-inks-not-ready-for-prime-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2010 16:54:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-3-12-e-inks-not-ready-for-prime-time/</guid>
        <description>One thing that has been a staple feature of science fiction stories since the late 50s is the death of printed books. If SF authors are to be believed, books are eventually going to be phased out in favour of eBooks, and in the 21st century, major publishers and content distributors seem to agree. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cut backs at the BBC hit web and DAB
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-3-4-cut-backs-at-the-bbc-hit-web-and-dab/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 13:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-3-4-cut-backs-at-the-bbc-hit-web-and-dab/</guid>
        <description>This week saw something I fundamentally disagree with: cut backs at the BBC in preparation for a Tory government.
OK, cutbacks because of budget deficits are one thing, unavoidable in times of poor profits and economic instability; but that&amp;rsquo;s just the thing, we&amp;rsquo;re talking about the BBC. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Keep your old phone, save some dosh
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-3-4-keep-your-old-phone-save-some-dosh/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 12:59:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-3-4-keep-your-old-phone-save-some-dosh/</guid>
        <description>OK, listen carefully guys, we&amp;rsquo;re going to try and save you some good money in felix this week. For many of us, our mobile phones are a vital part of our lives. However, we often pay well over the odds for them. For instance, did you know the cheapest iPhone 3GS contact comes to £729 (not to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jail time for Google over Italian autistic abuse video
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-3-4-jail-time-for-google-over-italian-autistic-abuse-video/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 12:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-3-4-jail-time-for-google-over-italian-autistic-abuse-video/</guid>
        <description>Would you indict a postal worker for delivering hate mail? Or jail an eyewitness to a crime for not having stopped it in the first place? To use the precedent set by a recent court ruling in Italy, you should.
In a shocking case of judicial incompetence, three Google employees who were involved in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Facebook Login search dimwits come unstuck
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-facebook-login-search-dimwits-come-unstuck/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 13:23:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-facebook-login-search-dimwits-come-unstuck/</guid>
        <description>This week saw the accidental birth of a new internet meme at the expense of some rather ignorant Facebook users. I say some, it&amp;rsquo;s more like thousands of Stalkerbook simpletons, and it all stems from their inability to understand a simple principle: Google is a search engine, not an address …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can you hear me?!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-can-you-hear-me/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 13:08:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-can-you-hear-me/</guid>
        <description>Let me make this abundantly clear, I don’t want to hear about your dog’s diarrhoea problems. It may sound harsh, but I don’t care if the poor sod is at death’s door, especially if it involves you describing his last meal and what it looked like coming out the other end. Ever been aurally assaulted …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Return of the Windows Phone
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-18-the-return-of-the-windows-phone/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2010 13:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-18-the-return-of-the-windows-phone/</guid>
        <description>This week has seen the annual Mobile World Congress take place in Barcelona. MWC is THE place where mobile device manufactures come to show off their latest wares and where journalists flock to attempt to chart what we can all expect for the mobile year.
This year Microsoft stole the show with what …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Consumer Electronics Show 2010
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-14-consumer-electronics-show-2010/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 16:18:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Samuel R S Gibbs,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-14-consumer-electronics-show-2010/</guid>
        <description>Transparent Displays
Onward the march of 3D! Not content only to smash its way back into the big screen, 3D is infiltrating our homes and poking its finger right into your face. Sony was there with its pretty incredible 24.5” OLED 3D Bravia boasting incredible blacks and colour vibrancy, even if the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
