<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/evacoles13/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/evacoles13/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Spotted | The seagull of nightmares
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-spotted-the-seagull-of-nightmares/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 12:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Coles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-spotted-the-seagull-of-nightmares/</guid>
        <description>For most, a visit to Hyde Park engenders feelings of tranquility and relaxation. Going for a walk in this urban wilderness at the heart of London would provide anyone with the “escape” that we city dwellers crave, whether we know it or not. As a biologist, I certainly identify myself as a regular …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Going back to the future in style
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-going-back-to-the-future-in-style/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 14:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Coles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-going-back-to-the-future-in-style/</guid>
        <description>It seems wearable tech is becoming somewhat of a fashion trend around the world. And many new products coming into play this year take their inspiration from the 1980s film franchise: Back to The Future. Nike were the first to stun the world with the first-ever line of self lacing trainers, The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Saving the world one tile at a time
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-saving-the-world-one-tile-at-a-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 12:47:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Eva Coles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-saving-the-world-one-tile-at-a-time/</guid>
        <description>Unless you’ve been living under a cave for the last few years, you will have heard of Elon Musk, the founder of Tesla Motors, SolarCity and SpaceX. This South African born engineer, inventor and progressive thinker is on a quest to save mankind from itself through renewable energy, space exploration …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>There should be more to foreign aid than emergency support
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-28-there-should-be-more-to-foreign-aid-than-emergency-support/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 15:16:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,CATNIP FELIX,Eva Coles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-28-there-should-be-more-to-foreign-aid-than-emergency-support/</guid>
        <description>If you were to hear mention of Haiti in a conversation, what would your initial thoughts be? Some of you would likely confuse it with Tahiti or have no clue as to what Haiti actually is. For most of you, though, I am sure the first thing to pop into your minds would be the devastating 7.0 magnitude …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
