<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ariana_sadr_hashemi/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ariana_sadr_hashemi/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s time to take five: Under Pressure is here!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-it-s-time-to-take-five-under-pressure-is-here/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ariana Sadr-Hashemi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-it-s-time-to-take-five-under-pressure-is-here/</guid>
        <description>Coming up on March 1st is University Mental Health Day; dedicated to promoting awareness for student wellbeing across the country. Without a doubt, studying at Imperial is incredibly stressful, which can take a serious toll on a student’s wellbeing; there are a lot of deadlines, revision, and exams …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Run for a liberation position!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-run-for-a-liberation-position/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ariana Sadr-Hashemi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-run-for-a-liberation-position/</guid>
        <description>This year, liberation has really taken off as a priority for Imperial College Union. Campus has seen awareness-raising events and celebrations including Black History Month, Disability History Month, Interfaith week, and the ongoing LGBT History Month (as shown by the currently-rainbow-hued Queen’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Here’s what I’m up to at the moment!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-here-s-what-i-m-up-to-at-the-moment/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ariana Sadr-Hashemi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-here-s-what-i-m-up-to-at-the-moment/</guid>
        <description>From Felix articles to Under Pressure week, my term so far has been full to the brim with mental health talks and discussions. I’m well aware that, as this is the first year my position has existed, most of the things I start are too big for me to be able to finish. That said, I’ve managed to get …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Making sure to look after your friends</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-making-sure-to-look-after-your-friends/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ariana Sadr-Hashemi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-making-sure-to-look-after-your-friends/</guid>
        <description>The Under Pressure campaign this week has highlighted the stress associated with studying and various ways to deal with it. However, many students at Imperial struggle with their mental health in silence due to the pervasive attitude that having difficulties with mental health is a weakness. This is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A call to arms! Why we need to change our mental health provision </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-a-call-to-arms-why-we-need-to-change-our-mental-health-provision/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ariana Sadr-Hashemi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-a-call-to-arms-why-we-need-to-change-our-mental-health-provision/</guid>
        <description>It’s a well-known fact that the majority of students at Imperial will experience some mental health difficulties during their studies. Typically, the first place they are sent is to the Imperial Counselling Service. However, to send students there by default operates under the assumption that the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Here’s what I’m up to at the moment!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-here-s-what-i-m-up-to-at-the-moment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ariana Sadr-Hashemi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-here-s-what-i-m-up-to-at-the-moment/</guid>
        <description>Stepping into the newly-created role of Mental Health Liberation Officer, I was acutely aware of the scale of the challenges faced. In the Mentality Survey, which was run two years ago, 70% of student at Imperial reported mental stresses or a mental health problem. It’s so important that we hit the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial survival guide</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-imperial-survival-guide/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Ariana Sadr-Hashemi,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-imperial-survival-guide/</guid>
        <description>Coming to university can be a difficult and stressful time. There are loads of new things to try, club mailing lists to sign up to, and people to ask “Which Oxbridge college rejected you?” But along the way, it’s important to make sure that you’re taking good care of youself, not only physically, …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
