<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sg3114/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/sg3114/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>IC Radio – Come and get involved!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-ic-radio-come-and-get-involved/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sebastian Gonzato,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-ic-radio-come-and-get-involved/</guid>
        <description>Are you in a band? Want to get more exposure? ICRadio has started streaming bands live from the Jazz and Rock room in the West Basement from 8pm to 9pm on Thursdays, and we’re looking for bands to come on and play! The IC sessions are a great opportunity for your band to get some exposure, as well …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Environmental Society – It&#39;s easy bee-ing green</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-environmental-society-it-s-easy-bee-ing-green/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sebastian Gonzato,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-environmental-society-it-s-easy-bee-ing-green/</guid>
        <description>Being Green should be something you strive to do all year round, but if you don’t know how then Imperial’s Green Week is a good place to start! The Environmental Society has an exciting calendar of activities planned from the 12th to the 18th of February aiming to inform and help you to lead a more …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The hidden side of psychedelics</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-the-hidden-side-of-psychedelics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sebastian Gonzato,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-the-hidden-side-of-psychedelics/</guid>
        <description>Professor David Nutt has been at Imperial since 2008, and has long been a well-known figure in the world of neuropsychopharmacoloy. He is the head of Imperial College’s own Neuro-psychopharmacology Unit, of which the Psychedelic Research Group is a part. Sebastian Gonzato caught up with him to find …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who needs kick drums when you have trance?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-who-needs-kick-drums-when-you-have-trance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sebastian Gonzato,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-who-needs-kick-drums-when-you-have-trance/</guid>
        <description>When you think of countries and good dance music, Italy definitely doesn’t come to mind. The age of Giorgio Moroder and Italo Disco (or as it later became known, disco) are long gone, and we have been left with the Crookers and Gigi D’Agostino. In short, Italian dance music is terrible.
Then came …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nights to get your heart racing: London’s DnB scene</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-nights-to-get-your-heart-racing-london-s-dnb-scene/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sebastian Gonzato,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-nights-to-get-your-heart-racing-london-s-dnb-scene/</guid>
        <description>Metalheadz XOYO 6th October
Goldie’s historic label is still going strong after 23 years with some solid recent releases from Detboi and Digital. If you’re into your dark and moody DnB then this won’t disappoint. And if you’re new to DnB, then be sure to check out Doc Scott and Source Direct playing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nuclear power is not part of the problem, it’s part of the solution
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-28-nuclear-power-is-not-part-of-the-problem-its-part-of-the-solution/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 15:13:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sebastian Gonzato,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-28-nuclear-power-is-not-part-of-the-problem-its-part-of-the-solution/</guid>
        <description>I’m currently in Switzerland, which is about to have its twelfth referendum this year (and you thought Brexit was bad). Having rejected a minimum living wage, the Swiss will be asked to vote on an initiative proposed by the Greens on whether to speed up the closing of nuclear power plants. Unlike …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The EU is good for Europe
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-the-eu-is-good-for-europe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 08:47:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sebastian Gonzato,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-the-eu-is-good-for-europe/</guid>
        <description>Let me start by saying that, generally, I am pro EU. Before university, I went to a European school, where I was taught extensively about the European Union in my history and geography classes. I’m not blind to the faults of the EU, namely that it is a prohibitively beaurocratic institution run by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Terrorism is a marginal and exaggerated threat
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-27-terrorism-is-a-marginal-and-exaggerated-threat/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 14:27:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sebastian Gonzato,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-27-terrorism-is-a-marginal-and-exaggerated-threat/</guid>
        <description>In 1853, the architect Georges-Eugène Haussmann was tasked with the renovation of Paris, a city crippled by overcrowding and disease. Part of his work involved creating large, straight boulevards that critics at the time said were to allow the army to manoeuvre more easily and to suppress armed …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
