<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/css11/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/css11/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Slendy is always, always watching
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-9-slendy-is-always-always-watching/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 19:35:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Skene,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-9-slendy-is-always-always-watching/</guid>
        <description>Slender: The Eight Pages was the first horror game I played. I remember seeing many videos of the game before I played it and thinking this doesn’t look that scary, so ignorantly I downloaded the free indie game and began to play.
The game sees your character alone in a dark forest searching for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Baboon: it&#39;s not just monkeying around
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-9-baboon-its-not-just-monkeying-around/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 15:12:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Skene,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-9-baboon-its-not-just-monkeying-around/</guid>
        <description>The games section here at Felix periodically get free games in to review. In the past, these have included such greats as Euro Bus Simulator 2 (see my past review). While these simulator games are fun to review I was very pleased when the opportunity arose to play upcoming PSVita game Baboon, as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Trialling the Fusion
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-11-trialling-the-fusion/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 21:46:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Skene,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-11-trialling-the-fusion/</guid>
        <description>I first got into trials way back when it first came to Xbox live arcade. It was gathering some hype and after downloading the demo I saw why. On the surface Trials is a very simple motorbike 2D racing game. You race on non-standard terrain courses using the few controls the game has to offer; …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grand Theft Goat
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-6-grand-theft-goat/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 02:53:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Skene,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-6-grand-theft-goat/</guid>
        <description>Wondering what games to play this summer? Here’s two great and perhaps unussual suggestions to get you started.
The first of the two games is Grand Theft Auto Four. Yes, four not five! Whilst five is the new better looking, bigger, better GTA there are reasons why four should not be forgotten. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mario Kart Gr8 - Best Mario Kart Ever?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-6-mario-kart-gr8-best-mario-kart-ever/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 02:52:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Skene,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-6-mario-kart-gr8-best-mario-kart-ever/</guid>
        <description>As a fan of the series ever since Mario Kart SNES I can truly say that, in my opinion, this is the best Mario Kart to date. Mario Kart, like many Nintendo games, has mostly retained the same formula for each game. You still race or battle whilst picking up items to aid yourself or knock out your …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Dino Killing Simulator: Calum&#39;s verdict
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-11-the-dino-killing-simulator-calums-verdict/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2014 18:13:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Skene,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-11-the-dino-killing-simulator-calums-verdict/</guid>
        <description>It was a Friday evening. My friend John, fellow games editor Max and me had been working on our coursework all day, and had just handed it in. 11am till 7pm is a long time to work and most students would probably want to follow this up by going to the pub to celebrate, but not us. When we finished …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Playing Elder Scrolls online beta!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-11-playing-elder-scrolls-online-beta/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2014 17:45:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Skene,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-11-playing-elder-scrolls-online-beta/</guid>
        <description>Ever since I first got my Xbox 360 with The Elder Scrolls 4: Oblivion, I have been a massive fan of the series, with Oblivion actually topping my favourite games of all time list. I’ve racked up 100’s of hours in Oblivion exploring, trying out different races &amp;amp; abilities and playing through the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>More than just a Terraria Clone
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-more-than-just-a-terraria-clone/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 06:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Skene,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-more-than-just-a-terraria-clone/</guid>
        <description>Starbound is a platform adventure game currently in beta and being developed by Chucklefish Games, a UK indie games studio. I love this game! I am eight hours in and I’ve barely even scratched the surface of all that is available in this game. Indeed I’ve only just completed the tutorial, a fun yet …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>GTA Online Adventure 1
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-12-gta-online-adventure-1/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 11:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Skene,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-12-gta-online-adventure-1/</guid>
        <description>Grand Theft Auto online finally enables you to play Grand Theft Auto how you want. Enabling you to create your character and setting you free on Los Santos to progress as you see fit. Here is one account of what goes down online.
First of all I made my character, a sweet Vince Neil surfer looking …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Medic Training Simulator
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-5-medic-training-simulator/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 10:29:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Skene,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-5-medic-training-simulator/</guid>
        <description>There are a ton of simulator games out there. For people who want to try their hand at Farming, driving a bus, or mining a stone quarry there are simulator games out there for you! These games portray all the elements you need to master to be successful in these games, often sacrificing fun in their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Time to pack out Braid
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-29-time-to-pack-out-braid/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 16:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Skene,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-29-time-to-pack-out-braid/</guid>
        <description>Indie Game the Movie is a great film for games fans. It follows the creation and reception of 3 Indie Games; Super Meat Boy, Fez and Braid. I already had played a lot of Super Meat Boy, and soon after the movie I caught Fez in a humble bundle. These were some of the best games I’ve ever played and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Confessions of GTA: Gamer Style
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-22-confessions-of-gta-gamer-style/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 14:29:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Skene,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-22-confessions-of-gta-gamer-style/</guid>
        <description>As a massive player of Grand Theft Auto 4, suprisingly I was not that excited for the new Grand Theft game. I felt that 4 would forever be my Grand Theft Auto game of choice and that 5 would just be more of the same in a disappointing way. The adverts showcasing the three new characters for this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wishing upon a Gaming Star
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-wishing-upon-a-gaming-star/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 16:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Skene,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-15-wishing-upon-a-gaming-star/</guid>
        <description> Super Mario 3D World As a massive fan of Super Mario 3D land for the 3DS and of all other 3D Mario games I have been super excited about Super Mario 3D world. A game which combines all the fun of 3D Mario but in stunning HD and, for the first time, multiplayer. Super Mario 3D world for the Wii U …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A bright outlook for Zeldaʼs future
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-13-a-bright-outlook-for-zeldas-future/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 12:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Skene,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-13-a-bright-outlook-for-zeldas-future/</guid>
        <description>The 3DS has sometimes suﬀ ered from its line-up, but it’s always had great Zelda games. Starting with Ocarina of Time 3D which was a great remastering of the original with a Master Quest. It’s a seriously good game which was enough for meto buy a3DS. Since then there have been a great many good …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Indied, Games that you will surely love!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-indied-games-that-you-will-surely-love/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 16:37:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Skene,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-indied-games-that-you-will-surely-love/</guid>
        <description>Recently I have picked up a few games through steam sales which I have loved for their originality. These were cheap games in which I have already racked up an impressive (or unimpressive depending on your viewpoint) number of hours in. So if you’re looking for a great game to add to your steam …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wii U No consider Nintendo?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-wii-u-no-consider-nintendo/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 16:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Skene,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-wii-u-no-consider-nintendo/</guid>
        <description>Last week my fellow games Editor Maximilian Eggl pointed out some of the main differences between the upcoming PS4 and Xbox One. Although I see many good things in both of these consoles I feel that even though it has already been out for a year, the Wii U deserves a mention. I am, as some may have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In Limbo? Here is your Bastion of F(ez)un#yolo
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-13-in-limbo-here-is-your-bastion-of-fezunyolo/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2013 23:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Skene,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-13-in-limbo-here-is-your-bastion-of-fezunyolo/</guid>
        <description>If you haven’t heard of Humble Bundle you should really check it out! They are an organisation that will regularly provide a bundle of games for any price you want to pay, and if you pay above the average (normally around £5) you will get some more “premium” games. Once you have selected how much …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Create and run your own Prison
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-13-create-and-run-your-own-prison/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2013 23:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Skene,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-13-create-and-run-your-own-prison/</guid>
        <description>The Felix games team were kindly given a copy of Prison Architect by Introversion. In this game you act as an architect and overseer of a Prison. You get to hire staff, build the prison, and then watch over as you gain more prisoners make money and expand. Many, many hours and just as many failed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Windwaker turns over a new Deku Leaf
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-16-windwaker-turns-over-a-new-deku-leaf/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 14:11:47 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Skene,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-16-windwaker-turns-over-a-new-deku-leaf/</guid>
        <description>There are few new games that hold my attention for very long anymore. I’m bored of games like Assassins Creed and Halo with their endless sequels that seem to offer nothing new except better graphics (even though I still buy them). However there is something about Nintendo that makes me forgive them …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>European Bus S(t)imulator 2012
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-european-bus-stimulator-2012/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 23:47:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Skene,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-european-bus-stimulator-2012/</guid>
        <description>Being games editor is a new job for me. Part of my expectations before agreeing to this role was that I would get games given to me to review. I didn’t mind which games, but thought it would be nice to not have to pay for every game I review. I accepted the role and on my first trip to the Felix …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I’ve forgotten why I like Amensia...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-ive-forgotten-why-i-like-amensia/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 23:46:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Skene,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-ive-forgotten-why-i-like-amensia/</guid>
        <description>A low drone sounds. “Dadddy, daddy, please don’t kill me.” Children begin to sing and a great machine starts up. “Daddy! Daddy!”… You awake in your bed, and go off in search of your children. Thus begins the 5-6 hour horror experience that is Amnesia: A Machine for Pigs, an indirect sequel to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Awesomenauts! Awesomesauce!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-awesomenauts-awesomesauce/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 13:47:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Skene,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-awesomenauts-awesomesauce/</guid>
        <description> For a long time Awesomenauts had a lonely existence in my Steam library. I picked it up in a sale and then there it sat unplayed. One day prompted by fellow editor Max I finally played it and realised the mistake I had made! Straight from the opening titles I knew I would love this game so sit …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
