<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/lawrencegood/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/lawrencegood/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>You Were Never Really Here – A thriller crossed with a horror crossed with an intense character study</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-you-were-never-really-here-a-thriller-crossed-with-a-horror-crossed-with-an-intense-character-study/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lawrence Good,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-you-were-never-really-here-a-thriller-crossed-with-a-horror-crossed-with-an-intense-character-study/</guid>
        <description>Tilda Swinton once called Lynne Ramsey “the Real McCoy”: a director whose films could not have been made by anybody else. Best known for her quiet and introspective work, Ramsay has garnered much critical acclaim – even having an “Every Frame a Painting” episode dedicated to her work. At first …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sally Potter’s dinner party from hell</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-sally-potter-s-dinner-party-from-hell/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lawrence Good,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-sally-potter-s-dinner-party-from-hell/</guid>
        <description>If you’d just been promoted to Shadow Minister for Health, wouldn’t you feel that a small party might be in order? Just a small get together with your nearest and dearest surely couldn’t hurt. Well, after watching The Party, it turns out you may want to reconsider.
A sharp and deeply funny chamber …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Handmaiden
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-the-handmaiden/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 17:23:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lawrence Good,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-the-handmaiden/</guid>
        <description>A young Korean woman arrives at a vast mansion, taking up position as handmaiden to the niece of a wealthy aristocrat. So begins this erotic, psychological thriller, a taut and captivating exploration of deceit, power, and sexuality in Japanese-ruled Korea. The latest film from director Park …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lady Macbeth
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-lady-macbeth/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 17:22:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lawrence Good,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-lady-macbeth/</guid>
        <description>How far would you be willing to go to assert your freedom? Who and what would you risk to pursue your own desires? Facing these questions is Katherine, the protagonist of Lady Macbeth, who, having been ‘bought’ to be the wife of a wealthy old man, finds passion through an affair with a stable boy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Salesman | Exploring the impact of violent acts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-the-salesman-exploring-the-impact-of-violent-acts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 17:07:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lawrence Good,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-the-salesman-exploring-the-impact-of-violent-acts/</guid>
        <description>Think of the worst thing you’ve seen a cowboy builder do. Is it bodging a driveway? Building the wrong wall? How about undermining the foundations of an entire apartment block, causing a mass exodus of tenants and starting a chain of events that drives sharp rifts between families and friends? So …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Through the Wall
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-through-the-wall/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 14:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lawrence Good,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-through-the-wall/</guid>
        <description>I’m tired of being alone – I just want to love, and to be loved” laments Michal (Noa Kooler), voicing a complaint that many Imperial students share. Yet instead of just drowning her sorrows like the rest of us, Michal resolves to marry in 22 days’ time, trusting in God to find her a husband. From …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
