<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mrangry/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mrangry/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Angry Geek returns... one last time?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-angry-geek-returns-one-last-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 19:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-angry-geek-returns-one-last-time/</guid>
        <description>Hello, readers. It’s been quite a while. I’m still a part of Imperial, just hanging onto the edges here, but it’s been years since I last graced these pages. New writers have to come in, and old ones have to shrivel up and quietly die in the corner under a pile of back issues – it’s the way it’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sexism and science
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-sexism-and-science/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 23:57:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-sexism-and-science/</guid>
        <description>I am a white male, born in the UK, and therefore I know as much about being oppressed, excluded or prejudiced against as David Cameron knows about struggling to make rent. There are, though, some things I feel I can say about sexism at Imperial, particularly in light of some recent Felix Comment …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Remembrance and regret
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-remembrance-and-regret/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 11:50:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-remembrance-and-regret/</guid>
        <description>You’d think that ‘anti-war’ would be a pretty easy position to present, wouldn’t you? When you think of things that we name Horsemen of the Apocalypse after, it’s not exactly a list of things that split opinion. There is no pro-Pestilence lobby. There is no Society for the Advancement of Famine. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Angry Geek is back
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-angry-geek-is-back/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 22:52:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-angry-geek-is-back/</guid>
        <description>Hello? Is this thing on? It’s been a while, you see. In fact, by my count less than half of the undergraduates were around the last time I wrote for Felix. I’d do a formal introduction and all, but the concept boils down to a pretty simple “I vehemently hate more things before breakfast than you’ve …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This week’s potential scandal
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-this-weeks-potential-scandal/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 22:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-this-weeks-potential-scandal/</guid>
        <description>Deep breaths everyone. Let’s open with the statement that no-one finds rape funny. So let’s do that: it’s not funny. No-one likes to see or hear about anyone being abused in such a way. I’m not particularly interested if you think male rape is under-represented, or if rape law only protects women, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rejection isn&#39;t the end of the world
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-rejection-isnt-the-end-of-the-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 23:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-rejection-isnt-the-end-of-the-world/</guid>
        <description>I’ve been helping out at interview days this year. Normally this is a task I avoid in the same way I avoid slapping my own balls with a wooden paddle – that is, by not agreeing to do it when I’m asked by my superiors (it happens more than you’d think). However, this year I am short on money and, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Occupying the middle ground
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-occupying-the-middle-ground/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 23:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-occupying-the-middle-ground/</guid>
        <description>George Howard wrote ever such an interesting piece on the Occupy protests the other week. You remember? It was the one that kept using the word socialist to describe a bunch of people expressing an opinion. You don’t remember. That’s alright, it’s not really necessary for what I’m going to say …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Religious tolerance is oatso simple
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-religious-tolerance-is-oatso-simple/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 21:27:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-religious-tolerance-is-oatso-simple/</guid>
        <description>I’ve started eating porridge. I waited and waited for the weather to get colder, but at some point it becomes obvious that I’m going to lose the staring contest with BBC Weather and I just break out the oats and jam. All year, I’m just waiting for winter to come around. So now I’m eating porridge …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Low Class versus No Class - Jeremy Kyle and Felix TV
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-low-class-versus-no-class-jeremy-kyle-and-felix-tv/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 22:42:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-low-class-versus-no-class-jeremy-kyle-and-felix-tv/</guid>
        <description>You know, it amazes me sometimes, the levels of objectionable shit I see every day without feeling the need to write about it here. The Christian Union’s latest poster, for instance, which advertised with glee a speaker who is said to “put the fear of God up atheists”, using the same reassuring …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The unhelpfulness of self-help
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-14-the-unhelpfulness-of-self-help/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 00:22:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-14-the-unhelpfulness-of-self-help/</guid>
        <description>A guy got on the tube and sat down next to me last week, which is a momentous enough event for me to open the column with because being that close to another human is a sure-fire way to ruin my week in spectacular style. Fortunately for me, the chap in question pulled out an iPhone and opened the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Another year of undue praise!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-another-year-of-undue-praise/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 01:48:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-another-year-of-undue-praise/</guid>
        <description>To those of you starting a new chapter of your lives at Imperial this month, welcome. This is the only paragraph you’re getting dedicated to you for the rest of the year if I can help it. Breathe it in. I’m here for you. I care. Listen to these words of encouragement and sympathy. Your life is hard, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who wants to get militant with me?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-11-who-wants-to-get-militant-with-me/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2011 17:31:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-11-who-wants-to-get-militant-with-me/</guid>
        <description>Surprise! A funding gap has emerged in universities. If you were in charge of estimating how many universities would ask for as much money as humanly possible and you predicted less than 100%, I feel like you have only yourself to blame.
So many universities are charging the full £9000 that the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Should we abolish super injunctions?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-should-we-abolish-super-injunctions/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 23:43:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-should-we-abolish-super-injunctions/</guid>
        <description>Yes – Gareth Rosser
The simple answer? Yes. Freedom of speech is one of the hallmarks of a civilised society, and injunctions curtail that freedom in a very real way. I mean, let’s be honest I’m a reasonable-ish person and in extreme and rare situations, I could be persuaded that injunctions might …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Education: not a luxury item
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-education-not-a-luxury-item/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 05:55:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-education-not-a-luxury-item/</guid>
        <description>The old adage about not discussing religion or politics with people is not to avoid arguments, it is because doing so makes one far too aware of how completely objectionable every other human being on the planet is. I found this out last week while responding to various opinions on the education …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Money matters
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-money-matters/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 19:17:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-money-matters/</guid>
        <description>I try not to get too interested in politics. It leads to disappointment and raised blood pressure, and I get enough of that during exam season as it is. I raised an eyebrow at the NHS reform debate, but even that managed to cool down after a week of whining from pressure groups, and my eyebrow …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I don&#39;t hate the royals, I just don&#39;t care
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-4-24-i-dont-hate-the-royals-i-just-dont-care/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 11:14:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-4-24-i-dont-hate-the-royals-i-just-dont-care/</guid>
        <description>The BBC posted a strange story on their site last week, where it equated not being excited about the royal wedding to being a staunch republican. I’d never heard the word being used outside the States until then, and the whole thing kind of weirds me out. News stations seem to have a real problem …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Whats wrong with the new generation?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-whats-wrong-with-the-new-generation/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 20:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-whats-wrong-with-the-new-generation/</guid>
        <description>Games. They&amp;rsquo;re like gigantic, electric playgrounds. And like playgrounds, nowadays they&amp;rsquo;re all tarmac and cutesy wooden houses for the reception kids to play in, whereas we were lucky to have a bit of rusty old pipe to play catch with. At least that&amp;rsquo;s the impression I get from Alex …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cynical practice
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-cynical-practice/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 06:06:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-cynical-practice/</guid>
        <description>John Wayne once mumbled, in the five spare minutes he had between starring in every Western movie ever, that “You can get more with a kind word and gun, than you can with just a kind word.” I know he said that, because I read it in a videogame once. And we read that and we think, “Eh, sounds about …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I can’t stand intolerant people
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-i-cant-stand-intolerant-people/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 19:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-i-cant-stand-intolerant-people/</guid>
        <description>I was linked to a post on Political Scrapbook this week, a blog which seems to mostly cover UK politics from the sort of left–wing perspective that makes you want to pat in on the head and pinch its cheek. The post in question highlighted the genocide–worthy activities of the York University Young …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don’t pity singles, pity me!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-dont-pity-singles-pity-me/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-dont-pity-singles-pity-me/</guid>
        <description>It’s Valentine’s Day pretty soon, as you’ve no doubt realised from the world’s sudden desire to shape everything into hearts and paint itself red, and that can only mean one thing. It’s time to feel unnecessarily awkward about being in a relationship when other people aren’t. Valentine’s Day must be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gove’s in charge? Seriously?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-goves-in-charge-seriously/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 19:44:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-goves-in-charge-seriously/</guid>
        <description>I try not to listen to BBC Radio if I can help it, because I want old age to hold some surprises and given that I already eat mint imperials all day and complain about ‘the youth’ I’m feeling that it’s not holding much back.
Last week a friend linked me to a radio segment that involved Michael Gove, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>TV license to kill your patience
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-tv-license-to-kill-your-patience/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 21:06:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-tv-license-to-kill-your-patience/</guid>
        <description>The television licensing people and I are playing a game. The rules of the game are pretty simple. The first player – that’s me – abides by all known laws this side of the Mars–Jupiter asteroid belt. The second player – Grand Duke John Hales of the London South West Enforcement Division – simply has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Angry New Year
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-angry-new-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 20:52:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-angry-new-year/</guid>
        <description>Happy New Year folks. Contractual obligations mean I must make at least one joke about not fulfilling resolutions in the first issue of the year, so here it is right now: I like my resolutions like I like my awkward man-hugs. Well-meaning initially and…not drawn out?
I’m not sure where I’m going …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Our leaders are idiots... no shit
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-our-leaders-are-idiots-no-shit/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 20:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-our-leaders-are-idiots-no-shit/</guid>
        <description>The praise for Julian Assange certainly is interesting to me. Not that I don’t admire the man; it’s very impressive what he’s done, and many of the papers released are genuinely hilarious to read. Mainly because they paint a picture that confirms the best and most accurate conspiracy of all - that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Geekiness goes beyond gaming
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-geekiness-goes-beyond-gaming/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2010 21:27:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-geekiness-goes-beyond-gaming/</guid>
        <description>This week I played some videogames. You might think that this isn’t particularly announcement–worthy in an age of Farmville and Bejewelled. On the face of it, videogames are part of our culture now. But read a gaming fansite or web forum and you’d be forgiven for thinking we were in the middle of a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Antisocial Network
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-antisocial-network/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 22:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-antisocial-network/</guid>
        <description>I’m beginning to like Facebook. Fact-fans out there will know that the first A Geek was actually about Facebook and how terrible it was. But even then I noted that at least it would offer a convenient way of sorting you all into groups that could be easily avoided. To be honest, my feelings about …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How the Geek stole Christmas
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-how-the-geek-stole-christmas/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 21:46:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-how-the-geek-stole-christmas/</guid>
        <description>I collapsed this week, caved in and put Fairytale Of New York by The Pogues on my iPod. It’s like funding an insurgency campaign in my mp3 player; it’s not offensively Christmassy, but it’s beginning to make the other albums on there consider rising up in protest and installing a festive …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We&#39;re all f***ed. So what?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-were-all-fed-so-what/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 18:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-were-all-fed-so-what/</guid>
        <description>Last week’s Black Sheep certainly got the column started with a bang. At least I thought it had, for the first hundred words. Then I realised the noise was coming from me smashing my head through the paper onto the desk underneath it.
The column, headed with the whorish grandmother of all rhetorical …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Event went off with a ‘pfft’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-the-event-went-off-with-a-pfft/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 19:49:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-the-event-went-off-with-a-pfft/</guid>
        <description>I decided I’d sit down and watch Channel 4’s latest purchase, “The Event”, last week. Partly because the advertising campaign had caught my eye, but mostly because it didn’t look anything like Lost. This turned out to be wrong on a level so fundamentally obvious it was only matched by the crushing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My body is a temple... to laziness
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-my-body-is-a-temple-to-laziness/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 18:55:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-my-body-is-a-temple-to-laziness/</guid>
        <description>A body like this doesn’t just happen by accident, you know. I’m gesturing at my midriff here, you can’t see from where you’re sitting, obviously. No, I work hard to maintain my physique, a bristling thirteen stone of organic matter. Here’s my routine for you – seven a.m., wake up. Eight a.m., wake …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You’re a bunch of greedy t***ts!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-youre-a-bunch-of-greedy-tts/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 20:00:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-youre-a-bunch-of-greedy-tts/</guid>
        <description>Oh, I’m sorry. I must’ve been emailing my imaginary Felix editor with an entirely imagined column about the need for you to shut your traps and adjust to life a bit better. My mistake. That would explain the reams of whiny toss on Facebook, Twitter, newspapers and my latest Moaning Gitfaces Weekly. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Beard optional...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-7-beard-optional/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 22:55:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-7-beard-optional/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to Imperial, home of the [insert obvious geek joke]. You’re either returning, or starting for the first time, as a scientist, engineer, or failed-medic-in-training, and congratulations to you. If you want to, you can shape the future of the world by improving our understanding and refining …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Change is overrated
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-1-change-is-overrated/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 22:34:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-1-change-is-overrated/</guid>
        <description>You’re on the brink of it. You’ve spent the last few months being told that your exams were too easy, your future is jobless, your university fees higher than ever, your hair too long and your generation’s romantic comedies too full of Gerard Butler. Most of these things are not true. Gerard Butler …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Angry Geek thinks you shouldn&#39;t suffer
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-27-angry-geek-thinks-you-shouldnt-suffer/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2010 17:07:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mr Angry,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-27-angry-geek-thinks-you-shouldnt-suffer/</guid>
        <description>In my Monday morning lectures there’s a ten-minute break in the three hours of unending pain, and during this time one of the students likes to go and get a coffee. Without fail, he comes back ten minutes late each week. As I am more anal than a particularly uptight haemorrhoid this irritates me …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
