<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rhidianthomas/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rhidianthomas/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Half a century of Hot Buttered Soul</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-half-a-century-of-hot-buttered-soul/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhidian Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-half-a-century-of-hot-buttered-soul/</guid>
        <description>The 1960s were the decade of soul. While the huge commercial success of Motown opened up white audiences previously inaccessible to black recording artists, soul extended far beyond Detroit. The distinctive Southern soul sound found its voice through Memphis’s Stax Records. In an era of segregation, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Imperial Bursary Scheme: a retrospective</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-the-imperial-bursary-scheme-a-retrospective/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhidian Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-the-imperial-bursary-scheme-a-retrospective/</guid>
        <description>Oh no, it’s another article about bursaries in Imperial! Though I can’t promise to be brief, I do promise that this is the last you’ll hear about it, from me, at least.
I’ll begin with the same preface given to every discussion of the bursary: genuine praise for the Imperial bursary scheme as a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Biff’s Jack Shack: turning jackfruit into fast food is not just for the vegans</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-biff-s-jack-shack-turning-jackfruit-into-fast-food-is-not-just-for-the-vegans/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhidian Thomas,Simran Kukran,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-biff-s-jack-shack-turning-jackfruit-into-fast-food-is-not-just-for-the-vegans/</guid>
        <description>The past 12 months have been more vegan inspired than ever; in fact, 2018 was the year of the vegan. Last year saw sales of meat-free food increase by a staggering 987%, with everyone from Beyonce to Benedict Cumberbatch getting in on the action. Like it or not, plant based (read: vegan) food is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Here’s what I’m up to at the moment!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-here-s-what-i-m-up-to-at-the-moment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhidian Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-here-s-what-i-m-up-to-at-the-moment/</guid>
        <description>As Ethics and Environment Officer, my job is to support and facilitate campaigns to make our university fairer, greener, and more sustainable. Below are some things I’ve been up to so far this term; if you think that there’s something I’ve missed, or that I could help you with, email me at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s time for us to make a stand on climate change</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-it-s-time-for-us-to-make-a-stand-on-climate-change/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhidian Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-it-s-time-for-us-to-make-a-stand-on-climate-change/</guid>
        <description>Unless you’ve been living under a rock, you’ve likely found it impossible to avoid Blue Planet II. Nowhere else is the beauty of the natural world as apparent as in our oceans, and the theatrics 1000 feet below the surface often uncannily mirror the dramas of our own day-to-day lives. We pick sides, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is so bad about fossil fuel companies, anyway?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-what-is-so-bad-about-fossil-fuel-companies-anyway/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 15:55:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhidian Thomas,Max Moynan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-what-is-so-bad-about-fossil-fuel-companies-anyway/</guid>
        <description>Divest Imperial are calling on College to remove its investments from fossil fuel companies, but what exactly is so bad about fossil fuel companies, anyway? Most attention is given to their impact on the climate through their carbon emissions, but fossil fuel companies often make headlines (or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial divestment campaign revived
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-imperial-divestment-campaign-revived/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 12:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhidian Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-imperial-divestment-campaign-revived/</guid>
        <description>This Monday will see the relaunch of the fossil fuel divestment campaign at Imperial. The new campaign will be called Divest Imperial, and at the official Launch Party on Monday evening campaigners are hoping to convince students that the recent successes of divestment groups such as the one based …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Climate change is a political problem
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-climate-change-is-a-political-problem/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 14:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Rhidian Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-climate-change-is-a-political-problem/</guid>
        <description>As political descriptors go, the humble watermelon is perhaps predictably an unconventional one: it is not wheeled out too often as a way of making a point. It’s a charge often levelled at politicians like Caroline Lucas, who are accused of being green on the outside but red (that is, socialist) on …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
