<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/andrew_melville/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/andrew_melville/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The Prem de la Prem</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-prem-de-la-prem/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrew Melville,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-prem-de-la-prem/</guid>
        <description>As the wheels of top flight English football groan into action again after an arduous fortnight of international bullshit, let’s have a look at what we’ve actually missed. £35+ match prices, hours of advertisements, and the weekends games spread over 20 different streaming services. Us football fans …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Joker</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-joker/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrew Melville,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-joker/</guid>
        <description>3 stars
Joker opens incredibly well. Lawrence Sher’s cinematography only adds to an already stunning performance from Joaquin Phoenix, while both are elevated by the original score. Robert De Niro’s inclusion as a late night talk show host adds even more credulity to the whole endeavour. But …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Paypal CEO replaced by 66,000 Guardian Readers</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-paypal-ceo-replaced-by-66-000-guardian-readers/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrew Melville,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-paypal-ceo-replaced-by-66-000-guardian-readers/</guid>
        <description>We work hard to achieve the right balance and to ensure that our decisions are values-driven and not political.” That was the press release churned out by Paypal’s PR team last Thursday, when they announced their decision to remove founder and former EDL leader Tommy Robinson’s (real name Stephen …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s time for students at Imperial to have real opinions</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-it-s-time-for-students-at-imperial-to-have-real-opinions/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrew Melville,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-it-s-time-for-students-at-imperial-to-have-real-opinions/</guid>
        <description>Last week, Loughborough University announced they would be launching an investigation into two of its students, resulting in the immediate suspension of one. This was the University’s response to what it referred to as a “racist and misogynistic” post on the “Loughborough Towersposting” Facebook …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Killer robots, memory scanners, and self-driving pizza – welcome to the Black Mirror future</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-killer-robots-memory-scanners-and-self-driving-pizza-welcome-to-the-black-mirror-future/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Andrew Melville,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-killer-robots-memory-scanners-and-self-driving-pizza-welcome-to-the-black-mirror-future/</guid>
        <description> USS CALLISTER
 2 STARS
Black Mirror ’s fourth season kicks off with a turn away from the dark, nihilistic tones of earlier seasons, opting instead for a campy parody of a sci-fi classic. Many critics have hailed the opening episode as the best of the season and it’s easy to see why: the story is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Black Mirror – What is it good for?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-black-mirror-what-is-it-good-for/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrew Melville,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-black-mirror-what-is-it-good-for/</guid>
        <description>While no Imperial Student will be a stranger to technology, I imagine not all share Black Mirror’s pessimistic view of tech as an existential threat. Despite creator Charlie Brooker claiming that his show is more warning than fear-mongering, the show focuses on how technology exacerbates the flaws …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rick and Morty  – back where we started?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-rick-and-morty-back-where-we-started/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrew Melville,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-rick-and-morty-back-where-we-started/</guid>
        <description>While offering some great adventures, this season lands between the previous two, as more time is devoted to the resolution of existing plot lines than the creation of new ones. Some might argue that this is a natural development of overarching plot lines introduced in earlier episodes – which this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Freshers are coming</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-freshers-are-coming/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrew Melville,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-freshers-are-coming/</guid>
        <description>It’s the first issue of the year, and Felix are already desperate to stay relevant. What is it the kids are into these days: politics, sex, and dwarves? Best do a Game of Thrones ™ double page spread then! Spoilers ahead.
Wildlings - Medics
Medics are the wildings incarnate. They’re natural enemies …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
