<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mb506/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mb506/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Boat Club shore up 106 BUCS points in one weekend
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-boat-club-shore-up-106-bucs-points-in-one-weekend/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 19:04:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mustapher Botchway,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-boat-club-shore-up-106-bucs-points-in-one-weekend/</guid>
        <description>This year’s BUCS Championship and Beginner’s Head was a successful one for Imperial. There were three golds, two silvers and two bronzes, as well as several other top ten placings.
Most students doubled and even tripled up in crews, racing down the 5km head course against the stream on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC shooters on target
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-ic-shooters-on-target/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 19:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mustapher Botchway,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-ic-shooters-on-target/</guid>
        <description>After traveling on the M25 for approximately 4 hours the Imperial College Shooting team arrived at the prestigious BUCS Clay Shooting Championship in Hodnet, Shropshire.
Imperial College took 8 shooters to the competition who were split into two equal teams, the undergraduates and overgraduates. As …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Four year trophy wait for Judo
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-four-year-trophy-wait-for-judo/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 18:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mustapher Botchway,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-four-year-trophy-wait-for-judo/</guid>
        <description>Last weekend, three London teams entered the 18th edition of Sheffield USIST, the biggest international student judo tournament held in the UK.
This team event involves 4 guys and 2 girls fighting in weight order. This year, 4 students from Imperial made it into the London A team: Bronwyn Dawson …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Depleted 1st XI edge into Cup Final
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-depleted-1st-xi-edge-into-cup-final/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 18:52:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mustapher Botchway,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-depleted-1st-xi-edge-into-cup-final/</guid>
        <description>Saturday 20 February was meant to be a free day for Imperial’s 1st XI. Given the fact that just under half of the starting XI were abroad, captain Mustapher Botchway had informally agreed with the RUMS (UCL Medicals) captain to reschedule the ULU Challenge Cup Semi-Final to the week after (27 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Eagles&amp;8217; unbeaten run ended by Warwick
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-imperial-eagles8217-unbeaten-run-ended-by-warwick/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 18:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mustapher Botchway,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-imperial-eagles8217-unbeaten-run-ended-by-warwick/</guid>
        <description>While the international competitions don’t seem to be that close and interesting anymore, which I have to blame the French for, the lower leagues still seem to have an edge to them. Imperial’s first ever league game in the autumn was against Warwick and, despite a clear loss, gave the team hope for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>&#39;Clover Power&#39; can&#39;t help IC Snooker at Midlands Cup
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-clover-power-cant-help-ic-snooker-at-midlands-cup/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 18:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mustapher Botchway,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-clover-power-cant-help-ic-snooker-at-midlands-cup/</guid>
        <description>The first weekend of February saw the first snooker tournament of the year; the Midlands Universities Snooker Championship. The two ICU Snooker teams met a little after 7 am for the train to the gloriously dull town of Coventry. Saturday offered a mixed bag of results: In the Individual …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College Football and Kick 4 Life join forces
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-imperial-college-football-and-kick-4-life-join-forces/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 18:39:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mustapher Botchway,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-imperial-college-football-and-kick-4-life-join-forces/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Football Club last month held the inaugural Kick 4 Life 5 a-side tournament in Ethos. Elite footballers from across our university were invited to test themselves at the highest level of indoor football, all in the name of raising funds for Kick 4 Life.
The event attracted a diverse …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hockey&#39;s winning streak continues
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-hockeys-winning-streak-continues/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 18:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mustapher Botchway,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-25-hockeys-winning-streak-continues/</guid>
        <description>Having trekked from one end of London to what seemed like the Far East, IC ladies 2s arrived at Redbridge Sports Centre in Essex ready to take on St Bart’s, only to find out that the hockey astro had been taken over by some hockey players of the miniature variety, who were playing a nice little …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FelixSport enters 2010, at a quick jog...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-14-felixsport-enters-2010-at-a-quick-jog/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 22:33:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mustapher Botchway,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-14-felixsport-enters-2010-at-a-quick-jog/</guid>
        <description>Welcome back! A new year, and a new term, are upon us, and 2010 promises to be a massive one in terms of sport. For starters, the winter Olympics are set to kick off in Vancouver next month.
From skiing to figure skating (not forgetting everyone’s favourite sport, curling), it should be a month of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sailing Club venture onto Welsh waters
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-14-sailing-club-venture-onto-welsh-waters/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 22:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mustapher Botchway,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-14-sailing-club-venture-onto-welsh-waters/</guid>
        <description>In December Imperial Sailing Club ventured into the land of sheep and dragons for their first away event of the year- The Welsh Dragon. With two days of sailing and a sheep themed social the event hosted by Cardiff University was set to be a good one.
Day one saw a frankly abysmal performance from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Men&#39;s first team miss out on top spot at Oxford
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-14-mens-first-team-miss-out-on-top-spot-at-oxford/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 19:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mustapher Botchway,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-14-mens-first-team-miss-out-on-top-spot-at-oxford/</guid>
        <description>A week after the individual championships in Nottingham, the men’s first team drove up to Oxford for their initial round of Premiership matches. This was the first major test of the season, facing up to the Oxford, Cambridge UCL and Bristol teams.
The day began against a somewhat ragged (not to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fencing grab the gold(s)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-14-fencing-grab-the-golds/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 19:24:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mustapher Botchway,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-14-fencing-grab-the-golds/</guid>
        <description>It was a weekend of mixed fortunes for the IC fencing club at the BUCS individual championships in Nottingham. Held annually, the competition brings together the best university fencers from around the country. Last year Imperial had three podium finishes, with Hannah Bryars taking the gold in …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
