<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/fmusic/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/fmusic/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The Expert’s Guide to Europe’s Ultimate Competition
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-the-experts-guide-to-europes-ultimate-competition/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 01:34:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-the-experts-guide-to-europes-ultimate-competition/</guid>
        <description>Going back to 1956, with one to six hundred million viewers annually, the Eurovision Song Contest is one of the largest-scale and longest-running television events in the world. This year thirty-seven countries will battle it out in Copenhagen for victory and the opportunity to host the competition …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lou Reed’s Life
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-lou-reeds-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 09:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-lou-reeds-life/</guid>
        <description>In 1956 a boy named Lewis Allen Reed was marched into a New York county psychiatric hospital by his parents and given electric shock therapy to ‘cure’ his bisexual instincts. The effect this had on his future career is debatable, however speaking in 1996 Reed recalled:
“They put the thing down your …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Four of the Best
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-four-of-the-best/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 14:51:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-four-of-the-best/</guid>
        <description> Gig Venues Café Oto Café Oto is the jewel in the crown of London’s experimental scene. Time and again it has proved worth a 40 minute trip to Dalston. This is in no small part due to its civilized atmosphere, where good gig etiquette is the rule rather than the exception. More notable, though is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Competition: Win 2 Tickets to See the Wailers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-5-competition-win-2-tickets-to-see-the-wailers/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2013 09:50:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-5-competition-win-2-tickets-to-see-the-wailers/</guid>
        <description>COMPETITION ALERT!
To kick off your 2013 Fresher&amp;rsquo;s Week we have two tickets to give away to see the Wailers at the Indigo2 on 30th September. They&amp;rsquo;re currently touring all their greatest hits including the Bob Marley classics. It&amp;rsquo;s set to be a cracking night!
To win the tickets, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kentish Fire put fresh spin on music video with 360° camera
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-7-8-kentish-fire-put-fresh-spin-on-music-video-with-360-camera/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2013 11:39:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-7-8-kentish-fire-put-fresh-spin-on-music-video-with-360-camera/</guid>
        <description>Ever wondered what it&amp;rsquo;s like to have eyes in the back of your head? Indie band Kentish Fire reveal all with an innovative new music video filmed using a 360° panoramic camera – the same used to create Google Street View maps. With help from a Kickstarter campaign starting this week, the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chvrches @ Village Underground
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-chvrches-village-underground/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 15:46:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-chvrches-village-underground/</guid>
        <description>Fresh from playing the Alexandra Palace with Everything Everything and Two Door Cinema Club the trio Chvrches came to the Village Underground with the weight of expectation lying squarely on their shoulders. They recently won best new non-US band at SXSW and made it into the top 5 of the BBC’s sound …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College Band ‘James And The Rabbit Hole’ through to the finals of Uni Music league
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-1-imperial-college-band-james-and-the-rabbit-hole-through-to-the-finals-of-uni-music-league/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 14:27:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-1-imperial-college-band-james-and-the-rabbit-hole-through-to-the-finals-of-uni-music-league/</guid>
        <description>Uni Music League is a unique project that has hit the UK with a bang. Acting as a support system for up-and-coming student musicians and bridging the gap between the unsigned world and the professional music industry, Uni Music League is the UK’s biggest student-based music competition. The immense …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS Album of the Week 17
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-ams-album-of-the-week-17/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 02:53:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-ams-album-of-the-week-17/</guid>
        <description>The Flaming Lips have come a long way since their debut album. Hear It Is, released in 1986 (not even kidding), was a grungey, noisey garage punk affair that few will even recognise as the psychedelic pop band who would cause such a stir in later years. From 1995-2002 the Flaming Lips released the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS Albums of the Year
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-ams-albums-of-the-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 14:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-ams-albums-of-the-year/</guid>
        <description> Alt-J: An Awesome Wave  OK, I’m hardly thinking outside the box here. ∆ (or Alt-J to those of you who aren’t massive pricks) have already won the Mercury Prize for An Awesome Wave and the album’s seen massive critical acclaim from all over. As such, it seems a bit of a cop out for me to call it my …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC Radio Special
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-ic-radio-special/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 21:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-ic-radio-special/</guid>
        <description>IC Radio, one of the oldest and coolest student stations in the country, is the official sound of Imperial College London. Broadcasting and streaming in crystal quality from icradio.com, we are on air 24 hours a day, alternating between live shows and playlists from our huge music library.
Anything …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS Album of the Week 4
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-ams-album-of-the-week-4/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 14:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-ams-album-of-the-week-4/</guid>
        <description>You might be wondering why the AMS are talking about Neil Young. You might be thinking, Neil Young’s not cool, he’s not relevant, he’s just some shit old country singer that nobody cares about anymore. I used to be like you. I always had this preconception of him as bland and uninspiring. The Status …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cave Painting: Votive Life
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-cave-painting-votive-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 23:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-cave-painting-votive-life/</guid>
        <description>Cave Painting are a Brighton based band signed to Third Rock Recordings. Their debut album Votive Life released on 24th September this year certainly promised much, but did it really deliver? There was a lot of hype surrounding the album prior to its release because of the popularity of their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Obama and Hip-Hope
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-obama-and-hip-hope/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 23:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-obama-and-hip-hope/</guid>
        <description>Music and the President of the United States of America has always had an interesting relationship. Music being played in the White House is a long standing tradition, dating back to ever since the Marine Band were invited to perform in the Executive Suite for President John Adams on New Year’s Day …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS Album of the Week 3
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-ams-album-of-the-week-3/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 23:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-ams-album-of-the-week-3/</guid>
        <description>Titus Andronicus’ first twoalbums are both fantastic. An eclectic brand of lo-fi punk done with furious passion and intelligence. A key theme of Titus Andronicus’ lyrics is nihilism. You can look at the first two albums as the first two steps in accepting nihilism. First you get really pissed off, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS album of the week 2
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-ams-album-of-the-week-2/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 03:17:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-ams-album-of-the-week-2/</guid>
        <description>It’s been a long two years for Egyptian Hip Hop, and after jumping off the hype machine they were so reluctantly thrust upon, they have returned with a debut album full of new material that takes a different, perhaps more accomplished direction than their earlier releases.
The infectious pop hooks …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Antics: in retrospect
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-antics-in-retrospect/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 03:16:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-antics-in-retrospect/</guid>
        <description>There aren’t many rock albums in the past decade which have been as darkly unique and memorable as Antics, the second release from New York based foursome Interpol. When Interpol are discussed nowadays, it is more in the context of what could have been, as their third and fourth releases flattered …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS album of the week
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-ams-album-of-the-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:36:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-ams-album-of-the-week/</guid>
        <description>If there’s one band who can wear the post-rock tag without shame, it’s Godspeed You! Black Emperor, famous for being able to capture the view of a city skyline burning and turn it into song. And they’re back, after leaving us with the somewhat disappointing Yanqui U.X.O. in 2002. The eight person …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Van She do Koko
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-van-she-do-koko/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:33:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-van-she-do-koko/</guid>
        <description>Various London clubs have offered Fresher’s Week deals, yet none of them were quite as enticing as Koko’s in Camden; an old theatre, with the stalls replaced with a dance floor, the circle with a bar and a 21st century sound system squeezed onto the Victoria stage. It’s a beautiful venue which still …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tame Impala - Lonerism
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-tame-impala-lonerism/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 21:29:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-tame-impala-lonerism/</guid>
        <description>Tame Impala released their debut album, Innerspeaker, in 2010. A 60s throwback made of fuzzy guitar and big psychedelic hooks, it was filled with catchy pop songs and hum-along melodies. Their new album is a much more complicated affair. Lonerism is the classic sophomore album. It’s a band maturing, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bestival: It’s in the name
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-bestival-its-in-the-name/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 21:26:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-bestival-its-in-the-name/</guid>
        <description>Monday morning at Bestival provided one of those typically British end-of-summer moments. As 50,000 hung-over festival goers packed up, or, in many cases, abandoned, their tents and gazebos, a distinct air of conclusion could be felt in the rainy skies of Robin Hill Country Park on the Isle of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hot albums... Mercury special
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-hot-albums-mercury-special/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 11:37:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-hot-albums-mercury-special/</guid>
        <description>Alt-J (∆) An Awesome Wave
Latest odds: 5&amp;frasl;1
I will admit that I would have preferred to have talked about the Django Django album, but because we reviewed the Dalston boys only a few months ago, it is only fair to give a mention to the album which in my opinion runs a close second. ∆’s debut …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bloc: Bigger, Better and Free?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-bloc-bigger-better-and-free/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 18:05:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-bloc-bigger-better-and-free/</guid>
        <description>With a new location, bigger names, and a wider line-up than ever, Bloc. 2012 looks to be a must-see for any electronic music lover. Covering big dubstep drops (Kode9, Loefah), alternative hip-hop (DOOM) and pioneering minimal composers (Steve Reich), the range at this year’s London based event will …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A very print-unfriendly band
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-a-very-print-unfriendly-band/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 21:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-a-very-print-unfriendly-band/</guid>
        <description>I was exceptionally upset to hear about the death last June of Seth Putnam, lead singer of Anal Cunt (or AxCx). For some reason, his death wasn’t reported that widely in the mainstream media, and in my post-teenage years my involvement in the metal scene has been dramatically diminished, so his …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Funk’s not dead
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-funks-not-dead/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 21:13:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-funks-not-dead/</guid>
        <description>Most people probably wouldn’t point to San Pedro, California, as a birthplace of punk, but they might as well. Punk isn’t Green Day and Blink-182, punk isn’t green hair and safety pins. Punk is an attitude and it can take any form you like. For Minutemen, that form was 2-minute bursts of jazzy, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Punk Planet by Douglas Heaven
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-punk-planet-by-douglas-heaven/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 21:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Music,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-punk-planet-by-douglas-heaven/</guid>
        <description>Argentine punk had a troubled upbringing. Though inspired by the notoriety of the Sex Pistols, Argentina’s pioneers couldn’t afford to play the same kind of media-baiting games. The year that brought us punk rock brought Argentina a vicious military dictatorship, and all evidence suggests dictators …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
