<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mw4414/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mw4414/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Netball Club ExeTour
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-netball-club-exetour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 14:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Madeleine Webb,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-netball-club-exetour/</guid>
        <description>In the lead up to Varsity, most clubs double up on training, start running extra fitness classes and generally work even harder on their sport. Naturally, netball chose to spend the weekend partying in Exeter. Getting the first bus out of London, 15 girls from a mixture of all 6 teams headed into …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>So you went to the march. What&#39;s next?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-so-you-went-to-the-march-whats-next/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 16:25:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Madeleine Webb,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-so-you-went-to-the-march-whats-next/</guid>
        <description>Protesting was the easy bit. Sorry to break it to you, but the Women’s March was not the finale, it was the opening number, and the rest of the show is no fun at all. I hate to ruin the mood because I was there on Saturday so I understand how intoxicating it can be – screaming “I’m mad as hell and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Netball 1s secure first victories of the season
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-7-netball-1s-secure-first-victories-of-the-season/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 13:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Madeleine Webb,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-7-netball-1s-secure-first-victories-of-the-season/</guid>
        <description>The first team had to wait 3 games to taste victory, but it was definitely worth it. Pre-ACC matches always have an extra sense of excitement but the home game at Heston against St Mary’s was the 1s first cup game and had a great atmosphere before the match even started. In the first quarter the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wildlife photographer of the year 2016
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-wildlife-photographer-of-the-year-2016/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 12:45:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Madeleine Webb,George Brooks,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-wildlife-photographer-of-the-year-2016/</guid>
        <description>Tucked away in a quiet corner of the Natural History Museum, The Wildlife Photographer of the Year (WPY) exhibition provides a welcome respite from the maddening crowds that flood the museum during the holiday season. The atmosphere changes as soon as you walk into the darkened room filled with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Coffee makes the brain go round
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-coffee-makes-the-brain-go-round/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 11:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Madeleine Webb,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-coffee-makes-the-brain-go-round/</guid>
        <description>Even though I don’t drink coffee, which coming from an Imperial college student may sound like an oxymoron, I have managed to successfully get through all-nighters on tea instead. Yet new research suggests that drinking coffee may have other benefits besides waking your brain up for that 9am …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Back to the shire
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-back-to-the-shire/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 11:33:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Madeleine Webb,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-back-to-the-shire/</guid>
        <description>Scientists are sent back to the drawing board as researchers suggest “hobbit” skull probably doesn’t belong to an ancient human.
The perpetual mystery of human evolution has just lost a potential grandfather of modern humans. In 2003 the remains of a new primate species, Homo Floresiensis, was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Scientists who made bank
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-scientists-who-made-bank/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 11:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Madeleine Webb,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-scientists-who-made-bank/</guid>
        <description>RBS last week announced the results from a Facebook poll (welcome to the future folks) whereby the mathematician and astronomer, Mary Somerville, was chosen by the people of Scotland to be the face of the £10 note for the foreseeable future. And yes, since Scottish money is legal tender in England, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Forests as carbon source, not carbon sink
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-forests-as-carbon-source-not-carbon-sink/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 11:29:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Madeleine Webb,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-forests-as-carbon-source-not-carbon-sink/</guid>
        <description>A key component in the fight against climate change has been the idea of controlled and regulated reforestation in regions destroyed by human actions. However, a recent study suggests that forests regrowing in Europe after mass deforestation between the 18th and 19th century are actually …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is science for everyone?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-is-science-for-everyone/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 09:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Madeleine Webb,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-is-science-for-everyone/</guid>
        <description>Sexism in science; is there a real problem? How do we fix it? When is everyone, including myself, going to shut up about it? Probably not for a while. And yes, I do realise that I could begin sounding like a broken record, considering this is the third piece I’ve written for Felix discussing the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Go home comet, you’re drunk.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-go-home-comet-youre-drunk/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 14:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Madeleine Webb,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-go-home-comet-youre-drunk/</guid>
        <description>Space happy hour is now a thing, and astronomy just got a whole lot more student friendly. While all the Halloween based excitement was focused on the “skull comet” TB145’s flyby, scientists discovered another asteroid that’s leaving a trail of alcohol almost as large as the one left by the average …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Women are needed to increase productivity
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-women-are-needed-to-increase-productivity/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 11:35:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Madeleine Webb,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-10-23-women-are-needed-to-increase-productivity/</guid>
        <description>Last month the United Nations adopted a new manifesto to change the world. Sounds dramatic, but the Global Goals for Sustainable Development are the new benchmark to measure our progress as a species for the next 15 years; and it turns out the scientific community may be the key to unlocking such …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
