<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ap4913/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ap4913/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The great Catalan paradox – why drawing borders is not a solution</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-the-great-catalan-paradox-why-drawing-borders-is-not-a-solution/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alan Perfect Ruiz De Velasco,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-the-great-catalan-paradox-why-drawing-borders-is-not-a-solution/</guid>
        <description>While I understand you’re probably reading this as a creative form of procrastination from one of those endless sessions in the library, you probably still think that a professional commentator’s opinion on the issue of Catalonia’s independence is where you would like to go if you need a trustworthy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Politics, ideologies, and how to choose the right side</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-23-politics-ideologies-and-how-to-choose-the-right-side/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alan Perfect Ruiz De Velasco,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-23-politics-ideologies-and-how-to-choose-the-right-side/</guid>
        <description>Every time student elections come back to Imperial, I always remember the sheer confusion of my old flatmate when deciding whom to vote for: “Back home in Italy, there is always a left-wing and a right-wing candidate in student politics. Choosing who to vote for was much easier there”.
I won’t get …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial is now the most unequal university in the UK – it doesn’t have to be</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-imperial-is-now-the-most-unequal-university-in-the-uk-it-doesn-t-have-to-be/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alan Perfect Ruiz De Velasco,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-imperial-is-now-the-most-unequal-university-in-the-uk-it-doesn-t-have-to-be/</guid>
        <description>What a great time to be an Imperial student. We have finally beaten Oxbridge at some ranking! What is it? Student satisfaction? Employability? Innovation? It doesn’t matter! We beat them!
Except it does matter. Enormously. According to a UCAS report, we have overtaken Oxford and Cambridge to become …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the fourth day of Christmas, my true love gave to me... CUATRO ALFAJORES</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-fourth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-cuatro-alfajores/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alan Perfect Ruiz De Velasco,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-on-the-fourth-day-of-christmas-my-true-love-gave-to-me-cuatro-alfajores/</guid>
        <description>While you might have heard about the most typical Spanish Christmas foods, I want to focus on a relatively unknown Christmas sweet: the alfajor, consumed generally in the south of Spain, and definitely a high point in humanity’s culinary achievements.
An alfajor is a very special sweet, made mostly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial should expand the gym at Ethos – it’s not that hard</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-imperial-should-expand-the-gym-at-ethos-it-s-not-that-hard/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alan Perfect Ruiz De Velasco,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-imperial-should-expand-the-gym-at-ethos-it-s-not-that-hard/</guid>
        <description>Let’s start with an assumed fact, and imagine that we live in a perfect, ideal world in which things work as they should and we don’t have to worry about anything. Let’s assume Imperial College is committed to tackling mental health issues.
Let’s say they are. I mean, they opened a counselling …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tête á Tête: Fred’s dead baby, Fred’s dead</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-t-te-t-te-fred-s-dead-baby-fred-s-dead/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alan Perfect Ruiz De Velasco,Charles Titmuss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-t-te-t-te-fred-s-dead-baby-fred-s-dead/</guid>
        <description>The revolution has finally arrived at the Felix Comment section!
Charles Titmuss
People rejoice! The brutal dictator General Fyles is no more! His evil reign has finally come to an end, after a prolonged internal struggle, led by the brave Colonel Alan Perfect and ably supported by Major Charles …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dear Mr Trump: it&#39;s time to pick a fight with Zuckerberg
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-dear-mr-trump-its-time-to-pick-a-fight-with-zuckerberg/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 15:12:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alan Perfect Ruiz De Velasco,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-dear-mr-trump-its-time-to-pick-a-fight-with-zuckerberg/</guid>
        <description>Dear Mr Trump: It is well known that you’re a regular reader of felix, so I sincerely hope you get to read this.
We all know you don’t like Silicon Valley. You and Larry Page are not exactly BFFs. I get it. Google donated almost half a million dollars to the Clinton campaign. California is a sort of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London should leave the UK
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-london-should-leave-the-uk/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 08:56:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alan Perfect Ruiz De Velasco,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-london-should-leave-the-uk/</guid>
        <description>We have always been the greatest, most prosperous hub for trade in the whole of Western Europe. Countless enemies have dared to invade us, all with the most unsuccessful results. Since Roman times, we have always resisted, preferring death to yield –always united against tyranny and oppression. We …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Of hipsters, exams, and millenials
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-of-hipsters-exams-and-millenials/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 11:05:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alan Perfect Ruiz De Velasco,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-of-hipsters-exams-and-millenials/</guid>
        <description>If you’re somehow reading this, you’re probably taking that small break in the library café before coming back upstairs for your revision. Here we are! It’s the final term! You’re probably, like me, starting to feel the library is not your second, but your first home. It is where all your life, …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
