<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/va208/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/va208/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The tale of why I hate food shopping
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-24-the-tale-of-why-i-hate-food-shopping/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 23:16:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Veli Akiner,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-24-the-tale-of-why-i-hate-food-shopping/</guid>
        <description>Say you’re on your way home from college, and you need to pop into the supermarket for a cheeky bit of grocery shopping, even dropping by the reduced section to buy a whole cheesecake that not only you’re never going to finish before it goes off but you end up paying more per unit of cheesecake …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don’t vote… yet
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-dont-vote-yet/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 21:44:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Veli Akiner,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-dont-vote-yet/</guid>
        <description>You heard me. Despite being torn three or more ways between candidates telling you to vote for them, hold back until you’ve heard what I have to say (assuming you have a voice in your head when reading this), or even completely. This article is no more than twelve hours from being too late for this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A revision of dietary laws
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-13-a-revision-of-dietary-laws/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2012 14:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Veli Akiner,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-13-a-revision-of-dietary-laws/</guid>
        <description>One of the overarching themes displayed by the main religions of the world is a set of dietary restrictions. An example is Islam, and its recommendation/order that you abstain from alcohol and swine. Many of these dietary restrictions were possibly in response to practical issues in the society in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Memes: a post mortem
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-imperial-memes-a-post-mortem/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 20:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Veli Akiner,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-imperial-memes-a-post-mortem/</guid>
        <description>Late on a Tuesday night, a monster was born. One that would increase exponentially with size; prove that Imperial students, for all their academic brilliance, follow the same behavioural patterns in a crowd as anyone else; and leave many of us sleep-deprived during our 9 o’clock lectures the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Things to do in Saariselkä
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-things-to-do-in-saariselk/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 22:47:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Veli Akiner,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-things-to-do-in-saariselk/</guid>
        <description>Saariselkä is a small tourist village in mountainous northern Finland which offers a beautiful landscape, various snow-based activities to get involved in and, of course, an opportunity to see the Northern Lights.
 Freeze to death  This is the Arctic Circle, which means temperatures that will …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Time to meet your malevolent maker
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-time-to-meet-your-malevolent-maker/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 20:18:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Veli Akiner,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-time-to-meet-your-malevolent-maker/</guid>
        <description>I called shenanigans on the existence of God at the tender age of ten. Even before I knew pie was more than something you threw in 20s slapstick comedies it never made sense to me for an omnipotent being to be benevolent, given that we have such terrible things in this world as Justin Bieber, truly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>If tube lines had a Christmas party...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-if-tube-lines-had-a-christmas-party/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 21:45:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Veli Akiner,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-if-tube-lines-had-a-christmas-party/</guid>
        <description>You know that friend of yours who&amp;rsquo;s always busy on weekends when you ask her to come out? She recently left a relationship that was just going round and round. Welcome to the Circle Line.
It takes this guy ages to get anywhere, sometimes going nowhere at all and just standing idly at the queue …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
