<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/news/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>We&#39;ve moved to a new location: felixonlinesummer.uk</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2020-04-05-new-website/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2020-04-05-new-website/</guid>
        <description>Head to felixonlinesummer.uk for our Summer 2020 coverage!
</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ethical Investment Paper Passed by College Council</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-ethical-investment-paper-passed-college-council/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-ethical-investment-paper-passed-college-council/</guid>
        <description>The paper, written by the Union President, Deputy President (Finance and Services), and Ethics and Environment Officer, was originally submitted on the 22nd of November and was passed with minor amendments from the President’s Board.
It establishes a ‘working group’ that is mandated to investigate …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Interviews: Anne Barrett, College Archivist</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-felix-interviews-anne-barrett-college-archivist/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-felix-interviews-anne-barrett-college-archivist/</guid>
        <description>Felix: Most students probably aren’t really aware that the college has archives – do you interact with students a lot?
Some of them are – particularly the constituent college unions – and I do host evenings with different groups. When I had the City and Guilds Union members in, they were looking at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Space: The Final Frontier</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-space-final-frontier/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-space-final-frontier/</guid>
        <description>The College has, in recent years, struggled with the amount of space available on the South Kensington campus, and is separately making decisions like the sale of St. Mary’s and the construction of White City – but projects are still ongoing to optimise the space available. One such project is the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Ongoing Direction of the Union</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-ongoing-direction-of-union/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-ongoing-direction-of-union/</guid>
        <description>It has been confirmed that Jon Tucker, the Business School’s Faculty Operating Officer, will be providing interim support to the Union following the departure of the Managing Director.
The decision was made after a discussion with College by Jill Finney, the Chair of the Union’s Board of Trustees, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union Council Votes 36:1 to Reject Increase in Halls Rent Price</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-union-council-votes-reject-increase-halls-rent/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-union-council-votes-reject-increase-halls-rent/</guid>
        <description>The Union and College are currently in negotiations over the price of rent in first-year accommodation, which College is proposing to increase by 12.2% overall in order to match a break-even model as calculated by Campus Services. On Tuesday, December 3rd, the Union President and Deputy President …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Graduate CEO of Spyras Named UK’s Most Promising Entrepreneur </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-imperial-graduate-ceo-spyras-named-uk-most-promising-entrepreneur/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Powell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-imperial-graduate-ceo-spyras-named-uk-most-promising-entrepreneur/</guid>
        <description>J: How did the initial idea for Spyras come to you?
G: The initial aim was to get a good grade in my masters to go on to a job in finance or consulting! The technology had been concepted in the Guder Research group and it just needed someone to take it to the next step and commercialise it. My …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Plans to Increase Halls Rent Again; Union to Negotiate Prices</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-college-plans-increase-halls-rent-union-negotiate-prices/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-college-plans-increase-halls-rent-union-negotiate-prices/</guid>
        <description>The price of rent in College-owned halls is set to increase again this year, with the student union acting in a consultation role with students.
The College’s total necessary revenue from halls rent is increasing by 12.2% in just one year in order to match a break-even model, in which revenue …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Managing Director of the Union Steps Down</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-managing-director-union-steps-down/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-managing-director-union-steps-down/</guid>
        <description>The Managing Director of the Union, Jarlath O’Hara, announced on 18th November that he will be stepping down from his role at the end of December. The announcement was made via an email sent internally to ICU staff, and marks the end of Jarlath’s four-year tenure in the role.
In the email, the only …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Strike Action: Pensions and Pay</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-strike-action-pensions-and-pay/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-strike-action-pensions-and-pay/</guid>
        <description>At 60 universities across the UK, university staff who are members of the University and College Union (UCU) are currently staging an eight-day walkout and strike action in response to the ongoing disputes regarding pensions, pay, and working conditions.
The Imperial branch of the UCU, however, is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union Kitchen Receives 2/5 Food Hygiene Rating</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-union-kitchen-receives-two-five-food-hygiene-rating/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-union-kitchen-receives-two-five-food-hygiene-rating/</guid>
        <description>The Union kitchen has received a low 2-out-of-5 rating for their food hygiene, after an inspection by a local council Environmental Health Officer (EHO) took place on August 23rd.
The areas assessed were hygienic food handling, cleanliness and condition of facilities, and management of food safety. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Food in Union Stops Due to Electrical Fault; “No Timeline” on Return</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-food-union-stops-due-electrical-fault-no-timeline-on-return/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-food-union-stops-due-electrical-fault-no-timeline-on-return/</guid>
        <description>The Union has not been providing food service in 568, its flagship venue on the South Kensington campus, for two weeks. The cause of the disruption is an “electrical fault” – specifically, that the circuit board to which the various kitchen appliances are attached to was being overloaded.
As a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Survey Shows What Students Really Think of Brexit</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-survey-shows-what-students-really-think-brexit/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-survey-shows-what-students-really-think-brexit/</guid>
        <description>A survey conducted by Dig-In – of freshers’ week welcome package fame – has demonstrated that a strong majority of students in the UK oppose Brexit. Out of over 35000 students surveyed, 38% stated that they ‘hated’ that the UK is leaving the EU, while a further 24% ‘dislike’ it – totalling for a 62% …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Plans to Put Path across Queen&#39;s Lawn</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-college-plans-put-path-across-queens-lawn/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-college-plans-put-path-across-queens-lawn/</guid>
        <description>The College is planning to place a path across the Queen’s Lawn – a move which has raised controversy amongst some students. The path will run across the diagonal of the lawn, based on analysis of timelapse photography showing the most-used path by pedestrians crossing.
The aim of the initiative is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Reports: Second Union Council</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-felix-reports-second-union-council/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-felix-reports-second-union-council/</guid>
        <description>As a reminder of the purpose of Council: the Council is the highest democratic decision-making body in the Union, at which the full-time Officer Trustees (OTs) and key student volunteers put policies into place, address ongoing issues by submitting and discussing papers, and receive updates from the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Record Turnout at Autumn Elections</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-record-turnout-autumn-elections/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-record-turnout-autumn-elections/</guid>
        <description>The Autumn elections ended on Thursday 24th October, with 329 student reps elected. Felix breaks down the data with the help of the Union Elections Team, and spoke to them about what made turnout so excellent this year.
To break down the data: the total turnout emerged at 34.31%, corresponding to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chemical Kitchen: Leading the Charge on Innovation</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-Chemical-Kitchen-Leading-Charge-on-Innovation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-Chemical-Kitchen-Leading-Charge-on-Innovation/</guid>
        <description>Chemical Kitchen, a new course rolled out within the Department of Chemistry, aims to introduce students to laboratory skills and practical experience via a more approachable and unconventional method. In groups of fifteen at a time, students spend three hours a day for three days in a newly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chemistry Introduces Roxy the Therapy Dog</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-Chemistry-Introduces-Roxy-Therapy-Dog/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-Chemistry-Introduces-Roxy-Therapy-Dog/</guid>
        <description>The Chemistry department has introduced weekly sessions with a therapy dog this term, in conjunction with the charity Therapy Dogs Nationwide, as one of a set of new wellbeing initiatives.
Originally, the suggestion for a ‘dog day’ was requested by students and reps, but the department felt that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Reveals Academic Strategy 2020-2025</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-College-Reveals-Academic-Strategy-2020-2025/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-College-Reveals-Academic-Strategy-2020-2025/</guid>
        <description>The Academic Strategy (AS) for the next five years has recently been unveiled by the College after a long development cycle. The Strategy will be used to inform the direction the College will take with regards to investing in new spaces, curriculum review, research foci, and more.
It builds upon the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College NHS Trust Staff Strike</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-imperial-college-nhs-trust-staff-strike/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-imperial-college-nhs-trust-staff-strike/</guid>
        <description>The strikes, organised by the United Voices of the World (UVW) trade union, took place on Monday 28th, Tuesday 29th, and Thursday 31st October, with an estimated 200 staff joining at some point over the three days. There are plans for further strike action over the coming weeks, for a total of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Counselling Service Expansion: A First Step</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-college-counselling-service-expansion-first-step/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-college-counselling-service-expansion-first-step/</guid>
        <description>The College has expanded the space available to the Student Counselling and Mental Health Advice Service, by renovating space in the old unoccupied Bernard Sunley hall in Evelyn Gardens. The new space opened on 7th October.
The budget for the expansion was around £150,000, which was used to convert …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Renews Times Partnership</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-imperial-renews-times-partnership/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-imperial-renews-times-partnership/</guid>
        <description>Imperial has renewed a partnership with The Times that gives both students and staff a free 12-month digital subscription, tied to their college accounts. The College originally started the partnership last year, but it was unknown whether it would continue.
The offering has been expanded this year, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mumps Outbreak Amongst Medics</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-mumps-outbreak-amongst-medics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,Eyad Abuelgasim,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-mumps-outbreak-amongst-medics/</guid>
        <description>There has been an outbreak of mumps among medic students over the last week, rendering several students confined to their homes while they wait for the infection to pass.
The NHS recommendation for isolation is five days, by which time infectivity is largely reduced as mumps is a ‘self-limiting’ …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>POV: The 2019 CTWC - The Year of Upsetris</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-POV-2019-CTWTC-year-upsetris/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Freddie Ugo,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-POV-2019-CTWTC-year-upsetris/</guid>
        <description>Following on from last week’s article covering the Classic Tetris World Championship, it is time to share the results!
It took place from the 19th - 21st and I was following it the whole way. Friday started fairly low-key. A quick Dr. Mario tournament followed by a speedrun competition in Tetris: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Launches J-IDEA Institute</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-imperial-launches-j-idea-institute/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-imperial-launches-j-idea-institute/</guid>
        <description>Imperial has launched a new institute as part of the School of Public Health in White City this week, targeted at predicting and preventing global health crises.
The institute, dubbed J-IDEA for the Abdul Latif Jameel Institute for Disease and Emergency Analytics, will utilise advanced mathematical …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Prince Andrew&#39;s Visit: Student Responses</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-prince-andrews-visit-student-responses/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-prince-andrews-visit-student-responses/</guid>
        <description>Our reporters generally noted several things.
Firstly, there were a very high – even a vast majority – of students who seemed unaware of the allegations against the Prince and thus were initially confused by the questions asked. This could be interpreted as either apathy, or a lack of knowledge. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Fossil Fuel Dichotomy at Imperial</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-fossil-fuel-dichotomy-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-fossil-fuel-dichotomy-imperial/</guid>
        <description>On the 10th of October, the UK Committee on Climate Change (CCC) delivered a report to government on how the government can engage the public in sustainable practices in order to reduce carbon emissions. The report was led by Dr. Richard Carmichael, an Imperial academic working with the Centre for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Meeting of Union Council: A Roundup</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-first-meeting-union-council-roundup/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-first-meeting-union-council-roundup/</guid>
        <description>The first Union Council of the year took place on the 8th of October. The Council is the highest democratic decision-making body in the Union, at which the full-time Officer Trustees (OTs) and key student volunteers put policies into place, address ongoing issues by submitting and discussing papers, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Prince Andrew Planning to Visit College</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-prince-andrew-planning-visit-college/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-prince-andrew-planning-visit-college/</guid>
        <description>There have been reports that Prince Andrew, The Duke of York, will be visiting Imperial’s White City campus on the 14th of October. The visit is in tandem with the ‘Pitch@Palace&amp;rsquo; entrepreneurship scheme that the Duke began in 2014, the penultimate ‘Boot Camp’ stage of which is being hosted on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The &#39;Welcome Carnival&#39;: Trouble at the Bars</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-welcome-carnival-trouble-at-bars/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-welcome-carnival-trouble-at-bars/</guid>
        <description>The Union’s ‘Welcome Carnival’ event, formerly known as the Freshers’ Ball, took place on Friday the 4th of October. Although historically the Freshers’ Ball has been a highly successful event – for many the highlight of Freshers’ Fortnight – the rebranded event fell flat this year.
The Carnival was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Guardian University League Tables: Imperial Maintains Position</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-guardian-university-league-tables-imperial-maintains-position/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-guardian-university-league-tables-imperial-maintains-position/</guid>
        <description>The Guardian university league tables for 2020 were published on 7th June. The tables rank UK universities both overall and for individual subjects.
Imperial maintained its overall position from last year in 7th, an impressive feat given that many London universities have declined. LSE, King’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Staff excellence is celebrated at the Annual Imperial Garden Party</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-staff-excellence-is-celebrated-at-the-annual-imperial-garden-party/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-staff-excellence-is-celebrated-at-the-annual-imperial-garden-party/</guid>
        <description>On Tuesday 18th June, Felix was in attendance at the annual Imperial Garden Party, a ceremony to honour staff who have made outstanding contributions to research and academic excellence, public engagement and outreach, teaching and student support, and to Imperial’s culture and community.
Staff …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Strike threat as College rejects plea to protect pensions</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-strike-threat-as-college-rejects-plea-to-protect-pensions/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-strike-threat-as-college-rejects-plea-to-protect-pensions/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College has rejected a request from the University and College Union (UCU) to commit to effectively capping employees’ pension contributions at 8%, despite warnings that the move could trigger strikes later this year and in 2020.
Last month, the College – along with most other universities …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union to launch h-bar evening food service</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-union-to-launch-h-bar-evening-food-service/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-union-to-launch-h-bar-evening-food-service/</guid>
        <description>Imperial students will soon be able to enjoy evening bar food at h-bar again, following the Union’s announcement that it will be launching a new menu at h-bar on Wednesday 26th June.
This comes in response to student discontent at College’s decision to cut the evening bar food offering at h-bar in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial hosts Prime Minister Theresa May</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-imperial-hosts-prime-minister-theresa-may/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-imperial-hosts-prime-minister-theresa-may/</guid>
        <description>Prime Minister Theresa May paid a visit to Imperial College London on Wednesday 12th June. Senior Teaching Fellow Dr. Colin Hale played host as the Prime Minister toured the department’s Carbon Capture Pilot Plant.
The Prime Minister, who was accompanied by Energy and Clean Growth Minister Claire …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union Awards 2019: Celebrating the Union&#39;s best</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-union-awards-2019-celebrating-the-union-s-best/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Alman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-14-union-awards-2019-celebrating-the-union-s-best/</guid>
        <description>The ninth Union Awards ceremony was held in Metric on June 6th, and saw the Union recognise and commemorate its top contributors for the year.
Winners included students and societies who demonstrated outstanding effectiveness in their roles, and have laid down a legacy that will benefit students …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tuition cuts a “shallow gesture” claims Labour minister</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-tuition-cuts-a-shallow-gesture-claims-labour-minister/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-tuition-cuts-a-shallow-gesture-claims-labour-minister/</guid>
        <description>Tuition fees should be slashed and repaid with less interest over a longer period of time before being written off, according to an independent report published last week. The report also recommends the reintroduction of maintenance grants.
The Augar report, commissioned in February 2018 as part of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A comparison of mental health systems in the UK, US and Asia</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-a-comparison-of-mental-health-systems-in-the-uk-us-and-asia/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Daisy Jennings-Gray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-a-comparison-of-mental-health-systems-in-the-uk-us-and-asia/</guid>
        <description>On Friday 17th May, Mentality hosted a talk from Rosie Dutt (BSc, MSc, MRes) on Mental Health Systems in the UK and Abroad. Rosie came in to discuss her Mental Health placement that she will be undertaking over this summer in a psychiatric facility in Bali; as well as to talk about the differences …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Location, location, location</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-location-location-location/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-location-location-location/</guid>
        <description>The other week, when they had the big marquee on the lawn [for Postgraduate Graduation], one of my colleagues was up here quite late and two or three international students were up here. My colleague said, ‘there’s nobody here, everyone’s gone home’, and they said, ‘I just want to take a photograph …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Patchy Queen&#39;s Lawn causes complaints</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-patchy-queen-s-lawn-causes-complaints/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jason Murugesu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-patchy-queen-s-lawn-causes-complaints/</guid>
        <description>The grass on Queen’s Lawn has been suffering greatly due to an excess of events being held on the space, resulting in student complaints. In recent months, it has hosted the drinks reception for Imperial’s Postgraduate Graduation. Heavy rainfall has also caused the grass to be waterlogged. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College to publish results of latest staff consultation regarding pension schemes </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-imperial-college-to-publish-results-of-latest-staff-consultation-regarding-pension-schemes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-imperial-college-to-publish-results-of-latest-staff-consultation-regarding-pension-schemes/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College will next week publish the results of the latest staff consultation regarding changes to their pension schemes.
This latest phase in the long-running dispute that saw countrywide strikes last year adds a third option to the 2018 valuation of the Universities Superannuation Scheme. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial and The Times host event tackling air pollution</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-imperial-and-the-times-host-event-tackling-air-pollution/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-imperial-and-the-times-host-event-tackling-air-pollution/</guid>
        <description>Monday evening saw Imperial and The Times collaborate to host the latest joint event in their year-long partnership.
The event, titled &amp;ldquo;How can we fix London&amp;rsquo;s air pollution problem&amp;rdquo; and consisting of a presentation and panel discussion, explored the media&amp;rsquo;s role in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is the Summer Ball &#34;unsustainable&#34;?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-is-the-summer-ball-unsustainable/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-is-the-summer-ball-unsustainable/</guid>
        <description>Preparations for Imperial College Union&amp;rsquo;s annual Summer Ball, which is set to be held on Saturday 22nd June, recently hit a snag as many of the involved student societies threatened to pull out over changes to this year&amp;rsquo;s event.
Dance Imperial, A Capella and Big Band societies were …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why I am going to vote in Thursday’s European Elections (23rd May)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-20-why-i-am-going-to-vote-in-thursday-s-european-elections-23rd-may/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Hilary Guite,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-20-why-i-am-going-to-vote-in-thursday-s-european-elections-23rd-may/</guid>
        <description>Some people might think it is not worth voting in these European elections as the referendum vote means we are going to leave, so why bother? However, a lot of people see this as a proxy for a second referendum and a way of showing support for staying in Europe.
Why would people like us, who believe …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Business School exam blunder</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-business-school-exam-blunder/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-business-school-exam-blunder/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Business School students were left reeling when it was revealed to them that they would have to resit an exam due to an error.
The students, who originally sat the Corporate Finance exam in Spring, noticed a &amp;ldquo;huge mess up&amp;rdquo;. Speaking to Felix, an MSc Climate Change, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College Union holds 7th annual Student Academic Choice Awards</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-imperial-college-union-holds-7th-annual-student-academic-choice-awards/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-imperial-college-union-holds-7th-annual-student-academic-choice-awards/</guid>
        <description>Monday evening saw Metric transformed to host the 2019 Student Academic Choice Awards (SACAs).
The award ceremony, which was first launched in 2012 to provide students the opportunity to recognise, reward and celebrate excellence amongst College staff, received over 1500 nominations. In February, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Everything you need to know about The Great Exhibition Road Festival 2019</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-everything-you-need-to-know-about-the-great-exhibition-road-festival-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-everything-you-need-to-know-about-the-great-exhibition-road-festival-2019/</guid>
        <description>This year, staff and students at Imperial College will see big changes to the annual Imperial Festival. With the 200-year anniversary of the births of Queen Victoria and Prince Albert fast approaching, this year the festival will be a collaborative effort for the first time. 19 other cultural …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial community pens open letter calling for confirmed support for the trans community</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-imperial-community-pens-open-letter-calling-for-confirmed-support-for-the-trans-community/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-imperial-community-pens-open-letter-calling-for-confirmed-support-for-the-trans-community/</guid>
        <description>Members of the Imperial community have come together to write a letter calling for Imperial College&amp;rsquo;s Senior Management to confirm its full support of the transgender community and condemn transphobia. This comes after it came to light that Imperial&amp;rsquo;s Vice Provost (Education), Professor …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mental Health Awareness Week</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-mental-health-awareness-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Becky Neil,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-mental-health-awareness-week/</guid>
        <description>Mental Health Awareness Week is coming next week from 13th - 19th May and the official theme from the Mental Health Foundation is Body Image. Body image is an insecurity that can affect all of us at any age and can really impact how we feel about ourselves. Feeling uncomfortable with your body can …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Exclusive: Professor Simone Buitendijk on the future of education at Imperial</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-felix-exclusive-professor-simone-buitendijk-on-the-future-of-education-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-felix-exclusive-professor-simone-buitendijk-on-the-future-of-education-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been two years since Imperial began the overhaul of its curriculum through the Learning and Teaching Strategy and, with the launch of increased digital learning - online degrees, a studio space and the use of Vitual Reality in courses such as Chemical Engineering and Medicine - it&amp;rsquo;s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial calls Access and Participation Plan discussion</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-imperial-calls-access-and-participation-plan-discussion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-imperial-calls-access-and-participation-plan-discussion/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College and the Union jointly held an open forum discussion on its plans to improve access for students from widening participation (WP) backgrounds.
The meeting took place from 12:00 - 13:00 in Meeting Room 3 in the Union Building and was attended by many of the Liberation Officers, as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Move Out Day Concerns Addressed by College</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-move-out-day-concerns-addressed-by-college/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-move-out-day-concerns-addressed-by-college/</guid>
        <description>Concerns have been raised by students about the Move Out Day for first year hall residents. In previous years, Move Out Day has always fallen on the last Saturday of term (which would be 29th June), but this year it has been pushed up to Thursday 27th June.
This will not affect the schedules of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College Science Showcase</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-imperial-college-science-showcase/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-imperial-college-science-showcase/</guid>
        <description>Pint of Science is a science festival that aims to communicate contemporary scientific developments to the public in an interesting, engaging and approachable way by bringing scientists to the pub and other accessible places. A driving factor in the success of Pint of Science is its ability to draw …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In Memoriam: Muhammad Hafiz Bin Zainal</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-30-in-memoriam-muhammad-hafiz-bin-zainal/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-30-in-memoriam-muhammad-hafiz-bin-zainal/</guid>
        <description>It is with deep regret that Felix shares the sad news that Muhammad Hafiz Bin Zainal (known as Hafiz), who joined the Department of Chemistry as an undergraduate student in 2015, has died. During his time at Imperial, Hafiz was very much involved in student societies and the wider Imperial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Winners of 2019 Leadership Elections announced at Results Party</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-16-winners-of-2019-leadership-elections-announced-at-results-party/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-16-winners-of-2019-leadership-elections-announced-at-results-party/</guid>
        <description>The 2019 Leadership Elections drew to a close at last night’s Results Party in Metric.
Next year’s Officer Trustees will be Abhijay Sood, Tom Fernandez Debets, Fifi Henry, Shervin Sabeghi and Ashley Brooks - in the positions of Union President, Deputy President (Clubs &amp;amp; Societies), Deputy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Counselling Explained</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-counselling-explained/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Becky Neil,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-counselling-explained/</guid>
        <description>Under Pressure, the Union campaign that gives students strategies for coping with heightened periods of stress, is back from 18th March – 22nd March so look out for events and stalls across campus. It also marks a good time to address the counselling service.
Everyone has seen films where someone …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial celebrates women&#39;s entrepreneurship at WE Innovate final</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-imperial-celebrates-women-s-entrepreneurship-at-we-innovate-final/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-imperial-celebrates-women-s-entrepreneurship-at-we-innovate-final/</guid>
        <description>Thursday 7th March saw five entrepreneurs compete for a share of a £30,000 prize fund in the final of Imperial Enterprise Lab&amp;rsquo;s WE Innovate women&amp;rsquo;s entrepreneurship programme.
The evening began with brief addresses from Liz Choonara, Head of Programmes &amp;amp; Community at the Imperial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is #fakenews damaging your health?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-is-fakenews-damaging-your-health/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alex &#39;Chippy&#39; Compton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-is-fakenews-damaging-your-health/</guid>
        <description>Fake News has made a bold entrance into the social media sphere. The term, commonly used by Donald Trump, was named 2017’s (ultimate) ‘Word of the Year’ by Collins Dictionary. It’s almost impossible to ignore fake news across social media and the sensationalist headlines have percolated into …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>500 Women Scientists</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-500-women-scientists/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-500-women-scientists/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday, 27th February, Dr. Kelly Ramirez visited Imperial College London to give a talk on “Transforming scientific institutions through crowdsourcing and gritty determination”. The theme of the discussion was “empowering women scientists through public engagement and advocation”.
In late …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Staff consulted over pensions in bid to avoid &#34;undeniable threat to jobs&#34;</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-staff-consulted-over-pensions-in-bid-to-avoid-undeniable-threat-to-jobs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-staff-consulted-over-pensions-in-bid-to-avoid-undeniable-threat-to-jobs/</guid>
        <description>Lecturers are once again being consulted about the future of their pensions as universities prepare for a planned increase in employer and employee contributions that is set to come into force later this year.
With the 2017 valuation of the Universities Superannuation Scheme (USS) concluded, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>StudentShapers Project opportunities available across College </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-studentshapers-project-opportunities-available-across-college/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alejandro Luy,Mike Streule,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-studentshapers-project-opportunities-available-across-college/</guid>
        <description>Staff and students often assume hierarchical positions in their relationship with one another – that of expert and novice, teacher and student or instructor and apprentice. You’ve likely already experienced this during your time at Imperial. In some ways it is a necessary part of education, but it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lauren Dennis to be honoured at We Innovate Final</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-01-lauren-dennis-to-be-honoured-at-we-innovate-final/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-01-lauren-dennis-to-be-honoured-at-we-innovate-final/</guid>
        <description>The WE Innovate program, a part of the Imperial Enterprise Lab, will be hosting its Final Showcase next Thursday, March 7th, from 18.20 – 21.00 in the City &amp;amp; Guilds Building. WE Innovate is Imperial’s flagship female entrepreneurship education program and, since its inception, 253 women have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Meet the Candidates!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-01-meet-the-candidates/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-01-meet-the-candidates/</guid>
        <description>Whenever you have bought food or drinks on campus, attended any society or sports club, or just used any non-College facility in the last year, you have engaged with the Union.
Imperial College Union is the organisation that aims to represent the views and interests of all Imperial College students, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Times hosts &#34;Designer Babies&#34; debate at Imperial</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-01-the-times-hosts-designer-babies-debate-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-01-the-times-hosts-designer-babies-debate-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Imperial’s partnership with The Times and The Sunday Times continued this week with a discussion of ‘designer babies’. Tom Whipple, science editor of The Times and chair of the event was joined on the panel by IVF pioneer Lord (Robert) Winston, Dr Güneş Taylor from the Francis Crick Institute, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What changes are coming to College Catering Service?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-01-what-changes-are-coming-to-college-catering-service/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claudia Caravello,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-01-what-changes-are-coming-to-college-catering-service/</guid>
        <description>Why are things changing?
In the past couple of months, the Union and College have been working together to gather a lot of data on food services through surveys, such as the Student Experience Survey (SES), Meat Free Monday (MFM) survey, and Catering feedback form, as well as through informal …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College settles bursary saga</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-college-settles-bursary-saga/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-college-settles-bursary-saga/</guid>
        <description>The 2015-2016 cohort bursary scheme saga is coming to a patchy end, with affected students having been contacted on Monday 18th February about new available opportunities being funded.
The affected students were notified of the opportunities that they would be eligible for, funded by the £250,000 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mental Health: A New Perspective</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-mental-health-a-new-perspective/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>ICSM Psychiatry Society,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-mental-health-a-new-perspective/</guid>
        <description>ICSM Psychiatry Society announces its 2019 Spring Conference - Mental Health: A New Perspective. Taking place on Saturday 2nd March from 10.30am - 4.30pm in the Sir Alexander Fleming Building, this unique conference promises to explore the theme of Stigma and Mental Health, bringing together …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>So, you think you know me...?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-so-you-think-you-know-me/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>ICSM RAG Fashion Show Team &#39;19,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-so-you-think-you-know-me/</guid>
        <description>What we’re doing
The ICSM RAG ‘You Know My Name’ Fashion Show 2019, held at The Clapham Grand on 12th March, is the most exuberant fundraising event hosted by the Medical School. The evening entails a decadent display of unique fashion, donated by twelve up-and-coming designers, and modelled by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>h-bar hit by College cuts</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-h-bar-hit-by-college-cuts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-22-h-bar-hit-by-college-cuts/</guid>
        <description>Staff and postgraduate students have been left disgruntled following the announcement that the popular h-bar will be ceasing its evening bar food service.
The decision, which was taken by College, means that, from Friday 1st March, food will no longer be available in h-bar after 7pm. This change is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial hospitals face £650m repair bill</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-imperial-hospitals-face-650m-repair-bill/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-imperial-hospitals-face-650m-repair-bill/</guid>
        <description>Three west London hospitals run by the Imperial College Healthcare NHS Trust are the most urgently in need of repair in the country. Charing Cross (which is the hospital with the highest urgent repair bill of £312m) in Hammersmith, St. Mary’s in Paddington and Hammersmith Hospital are facing total …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial to launch arts fellowship</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-imperial-to-launch-arts-fellowship/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-imperial-to-launch-arts-fellowship/</guid>
        <description>Staff and students at Imperial College London will be offered the opportunity to have their artistic and creative talents nurtured through a new arts fellowship starting in October 2019.
The Blyth Art Fellowship, a new initiative run through Imperial’s Blyth Music and Arts Centre, will provide …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Luna Terra Sol</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-luna-terra-sol/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Helen Money-Kyrle,Marta Wolinska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-luna-terra-sol/</guid>
        <description>On the evening of Friday 8th February, the Union Concert Hall was filled with a lively audience for the greatly anticipated annual Imperial College Charity Fashion Show: Luna, Terra, Sol. Sponsored by Godiva and organised by the Fashion and Design Society in collaboration with ICU RAG, the event …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sir Michael Barber visits Imperial</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-sir-michael-barber-visits-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-sir-michael-barber-visits-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Sir Michael Barber. the Head of the Office for Students (OfS), visited Imperial College London on the morning of Wednesday 13th February.
The OfS Head was accompanied by Imperial President, Professor Alice Gast, and the Provost, Professor Ian Walmsley, as the visit began at the Carbon Capture Pilot …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union to scrap breakfast offering following huge losses</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-union-to-scrap-breakfast-offering-following-huge-losses/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-union-to-scrap-breakfast-offering-following-huge-losses/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Union announced its decision to cancel its breakfast offering following substantial financial losses.
From Monday 18th February, Union Breakfast will cease to be served and the opening hours in FiveSixEight will revert to 12pm. The decision was taken a week ago, with the breakfast …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Insān - presenting conscious fashion</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-ins-n-presenting-conscious-fashion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ahmed Elgharably,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-ins-n-presenting-conscious-fashion/</guid>
        <description>What is Insan? – our purpose and aims
Insān presents a new fashion perspective. We present fashion that is introspective and directed, that tackles important messages and challenges pre-conceived barriers. We are a conscious fashion label that questions and answers.
We are acutely aware of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Positive changes to Leadership Elections 2019 as nominations open</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-positive-changes-to-leadership-elections-2019-as-nominations-open/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-positive-changes-to-leadership-elections-2019-as-nominations-open/</guid>
        <description>Nominations for The Leadership Elections 2019 opened on Monday 4th February with hundreds of opportunities for students to lead Imperial at the highest level, and a slew of positive changes aimed at improving the experience for both candidates and voters.
This is the biggest democratic exercise at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students to be refunded following Sport Imperial screw-up</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-students-to-be-refunded-following-sport-imperial-screw-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-students-to-be-refunded-following-sport-imperial-screw-up/</guid>
        <description>Imperial students who paid for gym membership prior to the 1st September 2018 change in pricing structure have been offered a refund due to an error on Sport Imperial’s part.
Sport Imperial acknowledged and apologised for the mistake in an email sent out on 5th October inviting all students who were …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Will Mondays forever be meatless?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-will-mondays-forever-be-meatless/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claudia Caravello,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-will-mondays-forever-be-meatless/</guid>
        <description>January has come and gone, along with the trial of Meat Free Monday. So what’s next? Will Meat Free Monday become a permanent scheme on campus?
Meat Free Monday (MFM) was a student campaign created from a combination of ideas that came from different undergraduate societies, PhD students, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial welcomes Deputy Editor of The Times</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-imperial-welcomes-deputy-editor-of-the-times/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-imperial-welcomes-deputy-editor-of-the-times/</guid>
        <description>Imperial played host to Emma Tucker, the Deputy Editor of The Times on Monday 28th January. After viewing a Data Observatory showcase in the Data Science Institute, Emma sat down with Felix for a brief interview:
Felix: How do you think fake news has affected your job or the job of being a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Imperialites win the Global Case Competition at Cambridge</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-the-imperialites-win-the-global-case-competition-at-cambridge/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Benoit Dubief,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-the-imperialites-win-the-global-case-competition-at-cambridge/</guid>
        <description>While studying at Imperial College London, one of the top ten universities in the world, one would expect to be faced with many opportunities take advantage of, perhaps even more so as a Business School student. However, the Global Case Competition was not one I had expected upon arrival, back in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What the hell are the SACAs?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-what-the-hell-are-the-sacas/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alejandro Luy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-what-the-hell-are-the-sacas/</guid>
        <description>You’ve been spammed with too many emails, you’ve seen the green posters, flyers and triangular table things in the cafes. Maybe you’ve grabbed a free tea or green apple at one of the stalls or seen someone running around in a ridiculous green morph suit. All just to grab your attention and tell you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cancer Awareness in Young People Week (CAYP)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-cancer-awareness-in-young-people-week-cayp/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Filippa Furniss,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-cancer-awareness-in-young-people-week-cayp/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Netball Club (ICUNC) have teamed up with societies across Imperial to bring you a week jam packed with events, with everything from talks on cancer symptoms (delivered by our very own students) to an infamous ACC night (did someone say Snakebite?) with an ICUNC twist. The week is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Future Developments to the South Kensington Campus</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-future-developments-to-the-south-kensington-campus/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-future-developments-to-the-south-kensington-campus/</guid>
        <description>The South Kensington Campus has a rich history. The campus today, founded mid-19th Century, has buildings with diverse origins – the Queen’s Tower built during Victorian times; the Royal School of Mines built in the Edwardian era; constructions in the 1950s that nearly doubled the size of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial celebrates inaugural Liberation &amp; Community Week</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-imperial-celebrates-inaugural-liberation-community-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-imperial-celebrates-inaugural-liberation-community-week/</guid>
        <description>Monday 21st January saw the launch of Imperial College Union’s first Liberation &amp;amp; Community Week, with a panel discussion hosted by the Deputy President (Welfare), Becky Neil.
The launch event, which was titled, “Inclusivity Starts Here” and took place in the Union Concert Hall, featured a panel …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New development in ongoing bursary saga</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-new-development-in-ongoing-bursary-saga/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-new-development-in-ongoing-bursary-saga/</guid>
        <description>Tuesday’s Union Council saw the announcement of £250k funding secured for “unfairly underfunded” 2015 bursary cohort students.
This represents the latest update in an ongoing saga following the Union’s request for reimbursement for undergraduate students from the “squeezed middle” £35,000 - £60,000 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Heroic Hamzah helps deliver baby at tube station</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-heroic-hamzah-helps-deliver-baby-at-tube-station/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-heroic-hamzah-helps-deliver-baby-at-tube-station/</guid>
        <description>First year medical student, Hamzah Selim, has delivered his first baby - at a tube station.
Hamzah, who graduated from Imperial in 2018 with a BSc in Biomedical Science and now studies at University College London, was on his way home following an anatomy lecture on the afternoon of Tuesday 15th …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial College Chemistry students to be offered cooking classes next autumn</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-imperial-college-chemistry-students-to-be-offered-cooking-classes-next-autumn/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Isabelle Zhang,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-imperial-college-chemistry-students-to-be-offered-cooking-classes-next-autumn/</guid>
        <description>Whether or not you are a chemist, you definitely have some experience with reacting chemicals – in the kitchen. On a molecular level, cooking is simply chemistry. The Imperial College London Department of Chemistry agrees, and will be advancing this notion by introducing a new module: “Introduction …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Business School made my life hell!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-the-business-school-made-my-life-hell/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-the-business-school-made-my-life-hell/</guid>
        <description>An ex-Imperial student has reached out to Felix to share the experience she had last year with the Business School; an experience which she describes as “tantamount to discrimination against people with mental health problems and those who are gender non-conforming.”
Amy Freelander, who works full …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bright Network Society of the Year Awards 2018</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-bright-network-society-of-the-year-awards-2018/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kathryn Jaitly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-bright-network-society-of-the-year-awards-2018/</guid>
        <description>Imperial’s Energy Journal Team were amongst teams from universities across the country to be nominated for the Bright Network Society of the Year Awards.
The Energy Journal was shortlisted in the Innovation category due to their unique concept for a cross-university collaboration, their use of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pension deficit down but doubts remain</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-pension-deficit-down-but-doubts-remain/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-pension-deficit-down-but-doubts-remain/</guid>
        <description>The university pension deficit has more than halved since 2017, according to a report released last week. A phased increase in employee contributions is due to begin in April. The news coincides with the beginning of a consultation to determine how much financial risk universities are willing to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>President&#39;s pay protected as debts double</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-president-s-pay-protected-as-debts-double/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-president-s-pay-protected-as-debts-double/</guid>
        <description>Imperial President Alice Gast has been named as one of the highest paid university heads in the country. The disclosure came shortly before it was revealed that Imperial has more than doubled its borrowing, giving it the largest debt of any British university.
Professor Gast receives a salary of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>As Tuesday&#39;s Brexit vote looms, Imperial left in dark about future </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-as-tuesday-s-brexit-vote-looms-imperial-left-in-dark-about-future/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jason Murugesu,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-as-tuesday-s-brexit-vote-looms-imperial-left-in-dark-about-future/</guid>
        <description>All day the news rumbles on. Theresa May continues to push her Brexit deal, and MPs continue to push back. The truth becomes abundantly clear, that not one politician, nor pundit truly knows what Brexit looks like for the people of this country. In this climate, universities must reassure their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ethos gym expanding!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-ethos-gym-expanding/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-ethos-gym-expanding/</guid>
        <description>Ethos gym is to be expanded in the new year, following months of collaboration between the Deputy President (Clubs &amp;amp; Societies) [DPCS], Sport Imperial and the College.
This change comes following complaints of the gym being too small and overcrowded in feedback taken over the last two years. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s a Sabb, Sabb Situation</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-it-s-a-sabb-sabb-situation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-it-s-a-sabb-sabb-situation/</guid>
        <description>Felix: For the people that don&amp;rsquo;t know, can each of you explain what your role is.
James: I’m DPCS. My role is two-fold in looking after our 370-odd clubs and societies, their creation, their day-to-day running and, when things go wrong, basically helping them out of a pickle and supporting …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>January = Trial of Meat-Free Mondays!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-january-trial-of-meat-free-mondays/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claudia Caravello,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-january-trial-of-meat-free-mondays/</guid>
        <description>January. New Year, New Resolutions, so why not introduce some New Changes?
This January, College and the Union will be trialing their joint campaign, ‘Meat Free Mondays’. With student clubs (Enviro Soc, Veg Soc &amp;amp; APES), other interested students and Greening Imperial all wanting to start similar …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial joins forces with The Times to cultivate &#34;shared interests&#34;</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-imperial-joins-forces-with-the-times-to-cultivate-shared-interests/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-imperial-joins-forces-with-the-times-to-cultivate-shared-interests/</guid>
        <description>A partnership between Imperial and The Times and The Sunday Times was officially launched this week.
The “What the hell is going on?” event marked the start of a year-long collaboration, which will feature joint events to “advance shared interests in the future of science and culture”.
Tuesday …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Library to pilot Study Break Card scheme</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-library-to-pilot-study-break-card-scheme/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alejandro Luy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-library-to-pilot-study-break-card-scheme/</guid>
        <description>The Central Library is piloting a Study Break Card scheme for two weeks beginning Monday 3rd December.
The scheme is a direct response to the feedback from library users, via mediums such as the National Student Survey, Student Experience Survey and Library surveys, which prompted Library Services …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London university students help blood cancer charity, Anthony Nolan, celebrate 20 years of lifesaving</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-london-university-students-help-blood-cancer-charity-anthony-nolan-celebrate-20-years-of-lifesaving/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-london-university-students-help-blood-cancer-charity-anthony-nolan-celebrate-20-years-of-lifesaving/</guid>
        <description>Blood cancer charity, Anthony Nolan, celebrates 20 years of its student volunteer network, &amp;ldquo;Marrow&amp;rdquo;.
Imperial is amongst ten London universities with a Marrow society and, over the last 20 years, Imperial Marrow has joined other Marrow socieities in holding over 400 events to raise …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>White City Woes</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-white-city-woes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-white-city-woes/</guid>
        <description>Autumn 2018 saw the opening of the Molecular Sciences Research Hub (MSRH), which represents a new research home for the Department of Chemistry on Imperial’s new White City campus. With the first term in White City drawing to a close, Felix reached out to various staff and students across all levels …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Augar review: what does the future hold for tuition fees?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-augar-review-what-does-the-future-hold-for-tuition-fees/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-augar-review-what-does-the-future-hold-for-tuition-fees/</guid>
        <description>Tuition fees could be cut to £6,500 per year as part of the latest government review into higher education. The government is also urging shorter degrees to keep overall costs down.
The year-long Augar review will examine whether or not the current funding situation provides good value for money for …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
