<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/tna08/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/tna08/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Goodbye from me
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-21-goodbye-from-me/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2013 00:05:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-21-goodbye-from-me/</guid>
        <description>Well here we are. Nearly 30 issues later and we have come to the end. It’s pretty emotional really. I’ve invested an entire year of my life into this newspaper and I’m not sure what I can say that will do justice to how strange this feels. I will say that I hope you have enjoyed this year of Felix. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Holland Club Redevelopment
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-holland-club-redevelopment/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 23:47:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-holland-club-redevelopment/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday I had a tour of the area that used to be the Holland Club. The space is called Level 0. At the moment, extensive work is still going on, and there is much left to do. It is definitely, for all intents and purposes, a building site; you have to sign in and out and wear a high vis jacket …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Complaints on the rise
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-complaints-on-the-rise/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 23:39:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-complaints-on-the-rise/</guid>
        <description>Figures from the official watchdog, theOffice of the Independent Adjudicator (OIA), show that complaints by students at universities in England and Wales have reached an all time high. In 2012 there were 2012 complaints against universities, compared to 1605 the year before. Of the complaints, about …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rector’s Awards Announced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-rectors-awards-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 23:35:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-rectors-awards-announced/</guid>
        <description>President &amp;amp; Rector’s 2013 Awards and Medals for Excellence in Teaching, Pastoral Care, Research Student Supervision and Supporting the Student Experience. Apparently brevity wasn’t a concern for him.
Professor Jenny Higham (Medicine), Professor John Laycock (Medicine), Dr Alexander Whittaker …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Letting old cats out of their bags: Rupert Neate
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-letting-old-cats-out-of-their-bags-rupert-neate/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 16:57:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-letting-old-cats-out-of-their-bags-rupert-neate/</guid>
        <description>Rupert Neate was Editor in2005-06. I met him on a Friday at the Guardian headquarters. He currently writes for the economics section of the Guardian. He also tweets as @RupertNeate.
TA: How did you get involved in Felix and why?
RN: Started writing some news stories in my third year. That was really …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Letting old cats out of their bags: Pallab Ghosh
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-letting-old-cats-out-of-their-bags-pallab-ghosh/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 16:41:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-letting-old-cats-out-of-their-bags-pallab-ghosh/</guid>
        <description>Pallab Ghosh was Felix Editor from 1983&amp;frasl;84. He is currently a science correspondent at the BBC. I met him in the BBC offices. When he was Editor they printed in their in house print shop and the Editor was also the manager of the print shop, who printed club leaflets. He tweets as @BBCPallab. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Letting old cats out of their bags: Michael Llewellyn-Williams
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-letting-old-cats-out-of-their-bags-michael-llewellyn-williams/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 16:25:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-letting-old-cats-out-of-their-bags-michael-llewellyn-williams/</guid>
        <description>Michael Llewellyn-Williams was Editor of Felix in the year 1974&amp;frasl;75. He has had a fantastic life since being Felix Editor. He has travelled the world, “made a tonne of money” on the dot com wave, helped create Archie the Scotch Skeleton, worked with everyone from Carling Black Label to NatWest …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Opticians on Walkway shutting down
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-opticians-on-walkway-shutting-down/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 23:16:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-opticians-on-walkway-shutting-down/</guid>
        <description>The optician on the Sherfield Walkway is set to close. Just before Easter, the optician was called and told that the lease is being rescinded and that they have six months to leave – serving them notice is in the provisions of the lease. They will be gone by September and have been told that a new …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Difficulty in reaching out
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-difficulty-in-reaching-out/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 23:04:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-difficulty-in-reaching-out/</guid>
        <description>There I was thinking that I would have a nice, relaxing end of term. I thought that it was the summer term and so it would be chill, and, besides, I’ve done this weekly slog so many times that I should be used to it by now. I was very mistaken. This is a bigger mistake than that time Justin Bieber’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>RCC Awards announced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-7-rcc-awards-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 09:57:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-7-rcc-awards-announced/</guid>
        <description>The RCC has announced the winners of their awards. The RCC Club of the year was Caving. There was also a Fellowsip for Alistair Cott.
Four students got Distinguished Service Awards. They were: Matthew Lees (Mountaineering), Timothy Runcorn (Ice Hockey) Antoine Desmet (Wakeboarding) Dominic-Andradi …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oh Gee a Point Average
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-6-oh-gee-a-point-average/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 18:07:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-6-oh-gee-a-point-average/</guid>
        <description>A while ago some universities announced the possibility of using a UK GPA instead of the traditional grading system that we use. This is an interesting idea, and one that is worthy of debate. The College will at some point ultimately have to choose whether or not they switch. Imperial are a cautious …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Energia Fitness fun day next week
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-6-energia-fitness-fun-day-next-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 12:57:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-6-energia-fitness-fun-day-next-week/</guid>
        <description>Free fitness classes will be held on the Energia Fitness Fun Day, which is on Wednesday 19 June, in Ethos. The Active Lifestyle Team is bringing the day to students and you do not need to be a member of Ethos to take part.
There will be special guests, such as “a mystery, world renowned Les Mills …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Summer Election Results announced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-6-summer-election-results-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 10:53:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-6-summer-election-results-announced/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Union has announced the results for the Summer Elections. This election is for some of the part time positions but also included the sabbatical position of Deputy President (Education), as the former winner will be taking an interruption of studies and so is no longer able to take …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best position? On Albertopolis
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-5-best-position-on-albertopolis/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 17:56:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-5-best-position-on-albertopolis/</guid>
        <description> TEDxImperialCollege was a must see event. It had so much on offer (you even got your own lanyard) and must have hit home with the audience: it was trending on Twitter. Considering it contained absolutely zero Justin Bieber performances, that’s pretty special. Former Felix Editor/physics student …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Good, The Bad and The Elections
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-30-the-good-the-bad-and-the-elections/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2013 16:05:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-30-the-good-the-bad-and-the-elections/</guid>
        <description>This week, as always, there is a mixture of good news and bad news. I will start with the bad news. The tragic death of an Imperial alumnus is not the most pleasant thing to be reporting. It reminds me of another incident earlier this year, which was similarly upsetting to put into the paper. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial alumnus killed in Syria
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-30-imperial-alumnus-killed-in-syria/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2013 14:42:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-30-imperial-alumnus-killed-in-syria/</guid>
        <description>An Imperial alumnus has been killed in Syria after a bomb hit the field hospital where he was treating patients in challenging conditions. Isa Abdur Rahman (pictured), 26, was a medical student at Imperial and was killed while helping the British charity Hand In Hand for Syria (HIHS).
Dr Rahman was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>St Mary’s library gets revamp
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-30-st-marys-library-gets-revamp/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2013 12:11:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-30-st-marys-library-gets-revamp/</guid>
        <description>The medical library at St Mary’s has been reopened following six months of renovation works on the building and facilities.
The library is to be renamed the Fleming Library (after Sir Alexander Fleming).
The renovation, which was first planned in 1999, cost a total of £3 million. Half of this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Summer Elections underway
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-30-summer-elections-underway/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2013 12:05:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-30-summer-elections-underway/</guid>
        <description>Nominations have closed for Imperial College Union’s Summer Elections. Voting will be open from Monday 3 June to Friday 7 June.
This year, the position of Deputy President (Education) will be part of the election. This is after the original winner of the post had to give it up due to an interruption …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A stone’s throw away
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-30-a-stones-throw-away/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2013 09:16:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-30-a-stones-throw-away/</guid>
        <description>Museums are funny places. Not har-har funny, and not even someone tripping and then pretending they actually meant to stumble for a few steps funny. They’re funny in that many people wait until they are abroad to go to them. I do this quite a lot. Justin Bieber did that once in Amsterdam, but the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sex Survey’s back
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-sex-surveys-back/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 22:35:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-sex-surveys-back/</guid>
        <description>The Sex Survey has come back for another fucking year. Well that’s a couple of puns out of the way, so I guess we can get onto more serious(ish) stuff.
We have the pretty infographics for you to look at, as well as plenty of analysis. Hope you enjoy it! Just tap here and go testicles, sorry, nuts. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial students win trip to Rotterdam
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-imperial-students-win-trip-to-rotterdam/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 22:30:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-imperial-students-win-trip-to-rotterdam/</guid>
        <description>Two Imperial students, Aran Kankiwala and Shi Yunn Chua, have won a competition that gave them the prize of a three-day all expenses paid program of events in Rotterdam last week as Shell’s special VIP guests.
They were two of the 20 winning students. The winners were from the UK, Germany and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Not For Profit Careers Fair
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-not-for-profit-careers-fair/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 22:29:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-not-for-profit-careers-fair/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London is hosting a careers fair that is just for the Not For Profit sector on Thursday 13 June. It is a new event that has been added after feedback from Imperial students. Companies in attendance will range from the Civil Service Fast Stream to Teach First to Global Vision …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Student led teaching award winners announced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-student-led-teaching-award-winners-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 22:27:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-student-led-teaching-award-winners-announced/</guid>
        <description>The winners of Imperial College Union’s first Student Academic Choice Awards have been announced at a ceremony on Tuesday 21 May. Over 150 people attended the event.
The eight winners (see box at the end of the article) were picked from over 400 entries that the Union received. Best Teaching for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chinese university may open UK facility
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-chinese-university-may-open-uk-facility/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 22:25:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-chinese-university-may-open-uk-facility/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London has signed a memorandum of understanding with Zhejiang University (ZJU) that could see the creation of a UK facilty for the Chinese university at White City, where Imperial’s new Imperial West campus is to be built.
The memorandum was signed on the morning of 15 May 2013 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Horizing to the challenge
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-horizing-to-the-challenge/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 21:49:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-23-horizing-to-the-challenge/</guid>
        <description>It’s drawing to the end of another year at Imperial. Everyone has some kind of big deadline looming, except for the lucky few that finish early. It’s around this time that extra curricular activities suffer. If you go to level 4 of the Library and suggest to someone that they do work for something …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial are looking at your memes
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-imperial-are-looking-at-your-memes/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 20:53:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-imperial-are-looking-at-your-memes/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London posted on the Imperial Memes Facebook Page to warn students about the content of some of the Memes. College posted reminding people not to damage the reputation of Imperial of themselves. The post was deleted soon after being posted.
The message said that College have been …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Alleged animal abuse investigation scope announced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-alleged-animal-abuse-investigation-scope-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 20:47:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-alleged-animal-abuse-investigation-scope-announced/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London have announced the makeup of the committee and the areas of the allegations of animal cruelty that they will be investigating. The committee, lead by Professor Steve Brown, will investigate and assess the culture and approach to animal care and welfare at College. The Home …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PETA complains to the Rector over Queen’s Lawn petting zoo
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-peta-complains-to-the-rector-over-queens-lawn-petting-zoo/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 20:46:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-peta-complains-to-the-rector-over-queens-lawn-petting-zoo/</guid>
        <description>PETA have written to the President &amp;amp; Rector of Imperial College London urging him to stop the Union’s plans for a petting zoo on Queen’s Lawn on Thursday 23 May. The letter calls the petting zoo “ill-conceived” and asks for Imperial to “make a formal to avoiding future events that promote the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Behaving like animals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-behaving-like-animals/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 20:42:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-behaving-like-animals/</guid>
        <description>This week brings some news about the allegations of animal cruelty levelled against Imperial. They’re rushing to the rescue with a three month long investigation. In other words “let’s just kick this can into the distance, and then write a report that will be long and boring and hopefully nobody …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial finds partners
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-imperial-finds-partners/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 20:41:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-imperial-finds-partners/</guid>
        <description>Imperial has partnered with Oxford, Cambridge, UCL and Southampton to form a new consortium named Science and Engineering South Consortium (SES-5). The idea is to innovate and explore new ideas through collaboration. The SES-5 have a combined annual research spend of over £1.3 billion. Together they …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I’m going to make you an offer
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-im-going-to-make-you-an-offer/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 20:39:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-im-going-to-make-you-an-offer/</guid>
        <description>A student has won £300 at the Technology in Medicine and Surgery conference’s Dragon’s Den style competition. Tom Webb’s idea was to distribute 5000 postcards depicting the four deadliest snakes in India with information about each. He says that there is “a significant chance that this idea could …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Drugs Survey
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-felix-drugs-survey/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 19:08:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ross Gray,Philip Kent,Philippa M Skett,Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-felix-drugs-survey/</guid>
        <description> The full version is available online.
Out of the 762 responses that we received, 54% said that they had tried illegal drugs. Splitting this into male and female showed that 57% of men said that they had taken drugs, whereas 49% of women said that they had.
 57% of men and 49% of women said that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Examining hope
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-9-examining-hope/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 15:35:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-9-examining-hope/</guid>
        <description>It’s that time of year once again. The last term and the last stretch of College until exams are over (hopefully you won’t be returning in summer for resits). You can almost sense the high tension and stress in the air. It’s a familiar feeling and reminds you that the culmination of months (and in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A first isn’t all people look for...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-9-a-first-isnt-all-people-look-for/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 12:11:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-9-a-first-isnt-all-people-look-for/</guid>
        <description>It’s exam season. Everyone at Imperial is slaving away behind a desk, energy drink of choice in hand. It’s the time of year when finding a spare computer in the Library is enough to make you ecstatic, and noticing it’s not free and someone is using the classic penny in the arrow key trick will send …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Royal Society Fellowships for three Imperial scientists
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-9-royal-society-fellowships-for-three-imperial-scientists/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 12:07:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-9-royal-society-fellowships-for-three-imperial-scientists/</guid>
        <description>Three Imperial scientists have been granted Fellowship of the Royal Society. Professor the Lord Ara Darzi of Denham, Professor Joanna Haigh, and Professor Sir Steve Bloom were all recognised for their “contributions to science, both in fundamental research resulting in greater understanding, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Not shaken, not stirred
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-2-not-shaken-not-stirred/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2013 14:07:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-2-not-shaken-not-stirred/</guid>
        <description>Departmental Cocktail Parties being held on campus may have to change their format from now on. This emerges after the Chemistry Cocktail Party, which is due to be held near the end of this academic year, has been forced to have a format change due to licensing laws and incidents at previous parties …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Fourth in Complete University League Table
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-2-imperial-fourth-in-complete-university-league-table/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2013 13:51:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-2-imperial-fourth-in-complete-university-league-table/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London have come fourth in the 2014 Complete University Guide league table. This is the same spot that Imperial occupied last year. Cambridge (pictured) came top, with Oxford second and LSE third.
In the subject tables, Imperial was also near the top; every subject was at very least …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Postgraduate anger at Health Centre access being removed
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-2-postgraduate-anger-at-health-centre-access-being-removed/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2013 13:48:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-2-postgraduate-anger-at-health-centre-access-being-removed/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Health Centre will no longer be letting postgraduate students use their services if they live outside of the registration area. Imperial College Union informed the postgraduate students of the change via email, which prompted over 200 replies mostly stating anger and upset at the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Election results announced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-2-election-results-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2013 13:41:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-2-election-results-announced/</guid>
        <description>The results for the Big Elections 2013 were announced at the end of last term. The turnout was the second highest that Imperial College Union has ever received.
David Goldsmith, this year’s RAG Chair, will be Union President, after being elected with 2395 votes in the 4th Round. Yasmin Edwards will …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union awards open
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-2-union-awards-open/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2013 13:40:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-2-union-awards-open/</guid>
        <description>Union Award nominations for this year have opened. Any student can nominate another student for their contributions to the Union. This can be with their contributions to a club or society or other work. There are four levels of recognition, which from Fellowship with Distinction to Union Colours. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial given women in science award
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-2-imperial-given-women-in-science-award/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2013 13:39:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-2-imperial-given-women-in-science-award/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London has won an award recognising support for the careers of women in science, technology, engineering, maths and medicine. The Athena Swan silver status has only been granted to three universities, with Queen’s University Belfast and University of Nottingham being the other two. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial rises in student satisfaction table
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-2-imperial-rises-in-student-satisfaction-table/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2013 13:33:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-2-imperial-rises-in-student-satisfaction-table/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London have placed 41 in the Times Higher Education Student Experience Survey. This is up from a position of 71 last year. University of East Anglia came top of the table, with Oxford in second and Sheffield in third.
The area that Imperial seemed to stand out most in was the “Fair …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Education and Student strategy up for review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-2-education-and-student-strategy-up-for-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2013 13:30:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-2-education-and-student-strategy-up-for-review/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London have created a paper on the future Education and Student Experience strategy. Between now and Friday 10 May staff, students, and alumni are asked to give their views on the outcome. Views are being sought for actions proposed and on what to prioritise. To contribute online, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Empty computer room in Library kept locked for days
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-2-empty-computer-room-in-library-kept-locked-for-days/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2013 13:27:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-2-empty-computer-room-in-library-kept-locked-for-days/</guid>
        <description>Computer room 204 in the Library was recently locked as their was training scheduled. The door has a sign saying it is booked. This meant that students were unable to use the computers inside. However, there are days when nobody has been seen in the room. A student complained to the Library staff …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Love for business
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-a-love-for-business/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 02:37:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-a-love-for-business/</guid>
        <description>As I walk into the airy Business School on time for a meeting (for once), I wonder where any offices could be. Having snuck in by nefarious means, attempting to be clandestine as I tailgate an unsuspecting accomplice, I realise that the furthest I’ve ever been into the Business School is the café. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Halls woes continue
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-halls-woes-continue/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 00:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-halls-woes-continue/</guid>
        <description>The halls saga continues, with Garden Hall, and the halls in Evelyn Gardens’ futures still unclear. As well as this there is the possibility of new halls being built in North Acton. Jeff Magee, Principle of the Faculty of Engineering, discussed the halls in a meeting of student reps. Discussing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>273 staff members on over £100,000
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-273-staff-members-on-over-100000/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 00:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-273-staff-members-on-over-100000/</guid>
        <description>273 members of staff at Imperial College London during the period of 2011&amp;frasl;12 were paid over £100,000. This is according to the official reports released at the end of each academic year. Keith O’Nions, the President &amp;amp; Rector, was, in total, renumerated £354,000. This figure is actually a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Big Elections: voting shuts at midday on Friday
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-big-elections-voting-shuts-at-midday-on-friday/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-big-elections-voting-shuts-at-midday-on-friday/</guid>
        <description>Voting in this year’s Big Elections is going to close on midday at Friday. The elections are to determine who will be in various Union positions next year, including the Sabbatical positions, the RCSU, CGCU and ICSMSU Exec. Committees, and the Student Trustee positions. The Union will be hoping to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union Council cancelled due to lack of agenda items
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-union-council-cancelled-due-to-lack-of-agenda-items/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 00:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-union-council-cancelled-due-to-lack-of-agenda-items/</guid>
        <description>The latest meeting of Union Council was cancelled as no agenda items had been tabled. All of the Sabbatical’s reports are online and were delivered on time, like Ashanti is.
</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Aero students given funding to build RC plane
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-aero-students-given-funding-to-build-rc-plane/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 00:06:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-aero-students-given-funding-to-build-rc-plane/</guid>
        <description>A 35 strong group of students, led by Edward Kardouss, Areonautics Year 1 Rep, will build a remote control (RC) aircraft that will take off, water bomb a target, make a flying loop, fly for 10 minutes, and eject a parachutist and land. The Department of Aeronautics has agreed to fund the project as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Medics stage protest over BUCS decision
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-14-medics-stage-protest-over-bucs-decision/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 23:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-14-medics-stage-protest-over-bucs-decision/</guid>
        <description>The British Universities &amp;amp; Colleges Sport (BUCS) acts as the national governing body for higher education sport in the UK. They have decided that a single educational institution should not be able to compete as two separate teams. This means that the current system where Imperial College (IC) …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hall so hard, College can’t affordably locate me
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-14-hall-so-hard-college-cant-affordably-locate-me/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 23:57:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-14-hall-so-hard-college-cant-affordably-locate-me/</guid>
        <description>And we’re back to some more of the same. Yeah, I get it, I know, it’s been going on for a while. But, hey, if we all just forget this and say “this is boring now let’s talk about the email storm or something else” then we do a disservice to future students. It’s exactly what everyone at the top …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Big Elections 2013: the race is on
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-the-big-elections-2013-the-race-is-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 23:48:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-the-big-elections-2013-the-race-is-on/</guid>
        <description>On 3 March at 23:59 nominations for this year’s Big Elections closed. These are the elections for a large number of positions at Imperial College Union. All of the Sabbatical positions will be elected by the student body of Imperial, with the Union hoping to beat last year’s record turnout. All of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Queen’s first concert honoured in Metric!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-queens-first-concert-honoured-in-metric/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 23:37:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-queens-first-concert-honoured-in-metric/</guid>
        <description>Brian May and Roger Taylor from Queen were at Imperial in Metric on Tuesday 5 March to unveil a plaque commemorating their first public performance, which took place in the Union Concert Hall. The event was greeted with much enthusiasm by all present, with Paul Beaumont, Union President, giving in a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Poor Gardening
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-poor-gardening/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 23:33:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-poor-gardening/</guid>
        <description> Another week another issue. This week has been absolutely shattering. In fact, I am so tired that when I came into work today (Thursday) I put on my scarf, went to the door, then turned around and looked for my scarf as I thought I had lost it. It’s just been one of those weeks. Work, sleep, eat: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Protest over Garden closure
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-protest-over-garden-closure/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 23:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-protest-over-garden-closure/</guid>
        <description>Students are campaigning against the closure of Garden Hall, following reports that it may be turned into office space. The students who started the campaign to save the hall were living in it at the time as either hall seniors or freshers. They have created an online petition, which, following its …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pressure continues over Acton
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-pressure-continues-over-acton/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 01:10:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-pressure-continues-over-acton/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Union have continued the pressure on Imperial College London over the plans for halls in Acton. There has continued to be unease amongst the student body about the plans. The issue has been raised and discussed at numerous meetings, including the Student Welfare Committee, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Translation Unit decision delayed
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-translation-unit-decision-delayed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 01:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-translation-unit-decision-delayed/</guid>
        <description>The decision on thefate of the Translation Studies Unit (TSU) has been delayed until June leaving all involved uncertain about their future. The Management Board of Imperial College London met on Friday 22 February to review the feedback gathered from staff, students and external interested parties …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bird flu research restarts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-bird-flu-research-restarts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 01:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-bird-flu-research-restarts/</guid>
        <description>Research is into artificial strains of H5N1 (bird flu) is resuming following a voluntary halt from scientists in January 2012 amid safety concerns. Professor Wendy Barclay from Imperial College London is one of 40 authors of a letter recently published in Nature, which outlines the situation and why …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Soap opera Acton
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-soap-opera-acton/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 00:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-soap-opera-acton/</guid>
        <description> The new halls saga continues.
What’s interesting in all of this is that the finances of keeping Evelyn Gardens seem to be being used as a reason for retaining the halls. The lease is still going to last for another 30 odd years. In 30 years time I will be a very old Felix Editor. The amount of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Smokers told to stop lighting up by buildings
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-smokers-told-to-stop-lighting-up-by-buildings/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 00:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-smokers-told-to-stop-lighting-up-by-buildings/</guid>
        <description>Students at Imperial College London have been receiving emails about smoking on the South Kensington campus. The purpose has been to remind students that they are not allowed to smoke by the entrances to buildings. The emails have been sent by the Heads of Departments, seemingly on the request of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New scholarship fund for Indian postgraduate students at Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-new-scholarship-fund-for-indian-postgraduate-students-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 00:43:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-new-scholarship-fund-for-indian-postgraduate-students-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Indian alumni and Imperial College London are launching a programme of new PhD scholarships for Indian postgraduates. The scholarships will be available to those who have a degree from an Indian institute and are in financial need. The website states that “priority will be given to who have not …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Paragon: a case study of distance
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-paragon-a-case-study-of-distance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 00:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-paragon-a-case-study-of-distance/</guid>
        <description>Paragon halls are located in Brentford, about six and a half miles from the South Kensington campus of Imperial College London, which is where most students need to be every day. The use of the halls is a temporary stopgap measure; the problem was caused by the last minute renovation of Wilson …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Anger over new halls
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-21-anger-over-new-halls/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 23:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-21-anger-over-new-halls/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London is planning to build a large hall of residence in North Acton that will potentially replace halls that are cheaper and located far closer to the South Kensington Campus. The North Acton Halls could be used as a replacement for Garden Halls and the halls in Evelyn Gardens, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College are Acton up
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-21-college-are-acton-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 23:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-21-college-are-acton-up/</guid>
        <description>Halls in North Acton is a terrible idea and should be immediately reversed. It’s a terrible idea. Evelyn Gardens are the way forward for now until you find a better alternative to North Acton. In an ideal world Evelyn Gardens would be kept on as halls for the foreseeable future. If there needs some …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NSS flaw found
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-nss-flaw-found/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 21:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-nss-flaw-found/</guid>
        <description>A flaw in the NSS has been exposed once more. It is possible, and not too difficult, for students to fill out the survey on behalf of others, raising concerns over the security of the survey – particularly due to the importance place on its results in league tables.
Felix reported last year that it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Council rises up
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-council-rises-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 21:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-council-rises-up/</guid>
        <description> It was a good thing to see that Council decided to vote to have a clear opinion on something. Especially that people came to a decision and didn’t care what the sabbs thought and made up their own mind. This happened on not one but two occasions, which was refreshing. Perhaps it had something to do …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Education and Experience Survey to close on Tuesday 19 February
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-education-and-experience-survey-to-close-on-tuesday-19-february/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 13:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-education-and-experience-survey-to-close-on-tuesday-19-february/</guid>
        <description>The Education and Student Experience Survey will be closing on Tuesday 19 February.
The survey is an anonymous way to tell the College your view on their future educational strategy. It is online and takes the form of a questionnaire with open text responses for students and staff to fill out with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kisses record confirmed
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-kisses-record-confirmed/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 13:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-kisses-record-confirmed/</guid>
        <description>Sarah Greasley, an Imperial postgraduate student, has received her certificate for the new World Record. She managed a total of 127 kisses in the end.
The record wasbroken in Ethos by the Materials postgraduate student. She seems to be excited about the record.
Felix actually helped her by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Heads of department extend their tenure
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-heads-of-department-extend-their-tenure/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 13:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-heads-of-department-extend-their-tenure/</guid>
        <description>The Heads of the Department of Chemical Engineering and Electrical and Electronic Engineering have both accepted an extension of their roles.
Professor Andrew Livingston FREng has accepted an extension to his appointment as Head of the Department of Chemical Engineering to 30 September 2016. He has …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PhD students could get twelve month write up period
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-phd-students-could-get-twelve-month-write-up-period/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 13:13:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-phd-students-could-get-twelve-month-write-up-period/</guid>
        <description>It is likely that PhD students will be getting their writeup period extended to twelve months for all Departments, it emerged on Tuesday 12 February.
Imperial College Union Council passed a paper that resolved to discuss the idea with key stakeholders and to lobby College. It was mentioned in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Condomed to obscurity
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-condomed-to-obscurity/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 11:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-condomed-to-obscurity/</guid>
        <description>Condoms have been around for quite a while now, allowing men all around the world to awkwardly fumble and pretend they know what they’re doing. The design has actually been pretty similar for over 50 years. The reason being that latex condoms are cheap and pretty easy to make, use, discard …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change to give talk at Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-8-secretary-of-state-for-energy-and-climate-change-to-give-talk-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 01:06:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-8-secretary-of-state-for-energy-and-climate-change-to-give-talk-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Edward Davey, Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, will be giving a talk at Imperial College London on Wednesday 13 February. He will be giving the annual Newitt Lecture on the energy challenge faced by society.
The title of the talk will be“The Energy Challenge: Technology and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Money Week offers prizes
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-8-money-week-offers-prizes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 01:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-8-money-week-offers-prizes/</guid>
        <description>There will be an event in Level 2 of the Sherfield Building at 11:30am - 2:30pm on Tuesday 12 February in aid of Student Money Week. The aim of the Week is to raise awareness of student financial issues and offer help, advice and offer tips on how to save money and helping students budgeting …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Love your surveys
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-love-your-surveys/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 23:07:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-7-love-your-surveys/</guid>
        <description> Just in case you are wondering if your eyes are being weird or not: they aren’t. This week is the closest we get to a Valentine’s issue, so I changed the colour of the top bit and the drop cap to red. How romantic.
Education and Student Experience This was on last week’s front page and is still …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A very chunky review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-a-very-chunky-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 23:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Caroline Wood,Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-a-very-chunky-review/</guid>
        <description>It definitely sounds as if it’s going to be amazing. The fudge is actually pretty nice. The problem is when you compare it to just a normal Chunky: doesn’t add so much that you think it’s revolutionary. Okay, we know that it’s not exactly supposed to be pioneering new grounds, but, still, some …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial launches Education and Student Strategy Survey
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-imperial-launches-education-and-student-strategy-survey/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 22:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-imperial-launches-education-and-student-strategy-survey/</guid>
        <description>Imperial have launched an anonymous survey to help to develop an Education and Student Strategy. The website consists of a questionnaire with all open text responses for students and staff to fill out with their thoughts on the education and student experience. The survey is behind a log in wall, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Title from the Queen for Imperial professor
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-title-from-the-queen-for-imperial-professor/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 22:34:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-title-from-the-queen-for-imperial-professor/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London’s Faculty of Engineering has been awarded a rare honour from Her Majesty the Queen to mark the Diamond Jubilee. The title is Regius Professor, and only two have been awarded in the past 100 years.
This year, twelve entries were awarded this title. Originally six were planned, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Run for Felix Editor!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-run-for-felix-editor/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 22:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-run-for-felix-editor/</guid>
        <description>Elections are here once again. It seems like only yesterday I was putting my name down for Felix Editor and hoping someone seconds me.
I thought I would give some advice for those thinking of running for a sabbatical position in the Big Elections. It applies for all of the positions, but especially …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Increase in uptake of the NSS
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-increase-in-uptake-of-the-nss/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 22:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-increase-in-uptake-of-the-nss/</guid>
        <description>There has been a large increase in the percentage of students filling in the NSS when compared to the same time last year.
The figures show that all departments except for Civil Engineering have a higher percentage. This has been attributed to the Department waiting until exams to remind students. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Student makes racism complaint to College
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-student-makes-racism-complaint-to-college/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2013 01:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-student-makes-racism-complaint-to-college/</guid>
        <description>A black student has raised a complaint of racism after being asked to show identification by security officers following a call made to College by a member of staff who thought the student may not be a member of Imperial.
The complaint was raised near the end of last term, and to Felix’s knowledge …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The paradox of Paragon: Imperial students pay more for the same halls
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-the-paradox-of-paragon-imperial-students-pay-more-for-the-same-halls/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2013 01:14:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-the-paradox-of-paragon-imperial-students-pay-more-for-the-same-halls/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London students are paying more for the same room in the same halls than students from two other London universities. Freshers from Imperial pay £155 per week for a room in Paragon. Students from West Thames College London (West Thames) and University of West London (UWL) both pay …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lost in Translation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-lost-in-translation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2013 00:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-lost-in-translation/</guid>
        <description>The Translation Unit of Imperial is under threat. There is currently a “consultation period” going on. This will decide the fate of the Unit. The idea being that it doesn’t fit with College’s strategy. Maybe it doesn’t, but how is anyone supposed to know given that when you ask them they refuse to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A long term strategist
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-a-long-term-strategist/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 00:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-a-long-term-strategist/</guid>
        <description>Tim Arbabzadah: Does your background help you in your current role? Did you gain – I hate this word – transferrable skills?
Debra Humphris: It keeps me fairly grounded in what we’re trying to achieve. Universities are extraordinary institutions and Imperial is definitely one of the best. Not just in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where to work
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-17-where-to-work/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 23:44:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-17-where-to-work/</guid>
        <description>This week there is a feature on page 10 (it’s one of my picks) about internships. The basic idea is to interview a few people who have done city internships and some that have done third sector work. The plan is to see what similarities and differences there are. Obviously, this isn’t some survey …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union to hold referendum on NUS
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-union-to-hold-referendum-on-nus/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 22:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-union-to-hold-referendum-on-nus/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Union will hold an NUS referendum during this year’s sabbatical elections, which will take place from 8-15 March 2013.
The referendum will be to decide whether or not we re affiliate with the NUS (National Union of Students).
Comment by Union President Paul Beaumont is available …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial’s got no SOLE?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-imperials-got-no-sole/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 22:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-imperials-got-no-sole/</guid>
        <description>Participation in SOLE shows that Earth Sciences once again has 100% participation rate, with the lowest being Biomedical Science at 34%.
Life Sciences also showed adisappointingly low 48% turnout.
This year the Department of Earth Sciences and Engineering piloted a scheme where you could fill out …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Head of Library Sevices retires
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-head-of-library-sevices-retires/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 22:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-head-of-library-sevices-retires/</guid>
        <description>Debby Shorley, the Director of Library Services, has retired.
She arrived at Imperial in 2007 and told Reporter, the College magazine, that she “loved (almost!) every minute of it.” She went on to say that “Different universities have different cultures, and the College has a real indefinable buzz …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial hires first ever Provost
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-imperial-hires-first-ever-provost/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 22:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-imperial-hires-first-ever-provost/</guid>
        <description>Professor James Stirling CBE FRS has been named the first Provost of Imperial College London.
He will be in charge of all academic matters, and so will be in charge of both education and research. He will report to the President and Rector, who will, in future, be more front facing in the UK and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kestral Chaos
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-kestral-chaos/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 22:07:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-kestral-chaos/</guid>
        <description>An investigation was launched after astaff member thought a kestral may have been either shot (yes, shot, as in by a gun) or had died after colliding with Sherfield.
After the investigation, it turned out that nobody had been doing some hunting of kestrals on campus, and that the bird was actually a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Just be honest
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-just-be-honest/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 21:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-just-be-honest/</guid>
        <description>Let me level with you. Since becoming Editor I have very often worn glasses. I consider myself a contact wearer. However, I ran out of contacts and I just haven’t had the time to go to get more. Okay, I’ll be more honest, Ihave had the time to get more contacts; I just personally preferred to spend …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Merry Christmas
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-merry-christmas/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 01:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-merry-christmas/</guid>
        <description>The title says it all really! Merry Christmas and have a fantastic new year everybody. If you have exams, then, as I said before: relax, panic a bit, but try to take at very least Christmas Day and New Year’s Eve off. Saying that, I’m pretty sure that for my third and fourth year exams I didn’t take …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Massive building project underway
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-massive-building-project-underway/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 00:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-massive-building-project-underway/</guid>
        <description>Any keen eyed students who were at Imperial last year will definitely notice the differences around campus, specifically the Mechanical Engineering Building. This is not a simple recladding to revamp the building’s look. It is in fact part of a major redevelopment of building on the South Kensington …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s the return of the yard
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-its-the-return-of-the-yard/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 00:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-its-the-return-of-the-yard/</guid>
        <description>Paul Beaumont, Union President, has proposed a new “Retailing of Alcohol” policy to the Executive Committee (Exec.), which will change the bar opening hours and yards.
The bar will now have to remain open until the advertised closing time (which is section 5 of the policy). Yards, as mentioned …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Grantham says scientists should be more vocal
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-grantham-says-scientists-should-be-more-vocal/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 00:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-grantham-says-scientists-should-be-more-vocal/</guid>
        <description>Jeremy Grantham, who, through the Grantham Foundation for the Protection of the Environment, funds theGrantham Reasearch Institute on Climate Change (of which there is one in Imperial) has written for Nature saying that scientists should “Be persuasive. Be brave. Be arrested (if necessary)”. He …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Clubs with Wordpress sites need to upgrade or be hacked... intense
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-clubs-with-wordpress-sites-need-to-upgrade-or-be-hacked-intense/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 21:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-clubs-with-wordpress-sites-need-to-upgrade-or-be-hacked-intense/</guid>
        <description>Imperial clubs with old Wordpress sites are vulnerable toattack from hackers.
A number of the Clubs and Societies at Imperial College Union have been running outdated versions of Wordpress, which leaves them open to attack. The problem is easily fixed by simply keeping installations up to date when …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ageing slowly
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-ageing-slowly/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 21:42:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-ageing-slowly/</guid>
        <description>On the day of writing this I am turning 23, and now probably need to become a terribly serious individual, or something like that. I say this because that is what happens as you get older: you become all grown up and proper. You use words like “whom”, have food that has been “drizzled” with olive …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dutch Courage
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-23-dutch-courage/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2012 12:22:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-23-dutch-courage/</guid>
        <description>The Holland Club has closed. The space will be redeveloped by College and Commercial Services into something new. Apparently, everyone was crying out for more food outlets. Dinner and such. So what will become of the space, now called Level 0? Well, Eastside 2.0 is what I hope it doesn’t become. We …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Holland Club Closed
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-holland-club-closed/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 22:38:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-holland-club-closed/</guid>
        <description>The tender process has come to an end and the Holland Club will close the bar on 21 December 2012. Commercial Services will open a new, unnamed outlet in the space at the end of September 2013.
There has been an ongoing campaign to save the Holland Club amongst staff and students. The Facebook page …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science and relaxing
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-science-and-relaxing/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 20:59:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tim Arbabzadah,Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-science-and-relaxing/</guid>
        <description>This week, the front page contains a storyabout science spending cuts. It’s all a bit economics heavy, but the gist is that, in real terms, science spending was cut by a lot in the 2010-2011 year.
At a science university it is not exactly a contentious point to say that science, and research and …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
