<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rtf08/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rtf08/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>So long and thanks for all the Physics
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-so-long-and-thanks-for-all-the-physics/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 13:09:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-23-so-long-and-thanks-for-all-the-physics/</guid>
        <description>Six years is a long time to spend in this place. If my Imperial career were a child, it would be preparing for its first year of primary school by now: shiny new rucksack perched on its back, lunch money nestled in its pocket. Like a parent leaving his child at the school gates, it’s time I let …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Racism in Northern Ireland
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-6-racism-in-northern-ireland/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 02:40:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-6-racism-in-northern-ireland/</guid>
        <description>To say that Northern Ireland has come a long way since its sectarian civil war is a cliché but it’s worth saying: we’ve come a long way. The soldiers no longer patrol the streets. The curfews no longer empty the streets at night. The bombs no longer tear through shopping centres and flesh. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Professor Pendry Shares $1mill. Prize
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-2-professor-pendry-shares-1mill-prize/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 12:42:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-2-professor-pendry-shares-1mill-prize/</guid>
        <description>Imperial physicist Sir John Pendry was this week announced as joint winner of the $1 Million Kavli prize for his groundbreaking work in optics. Pendry is most famous as the inventor of the world’s first working invisibility cloak, a product of his work on meta materials.
Meta materials are unique in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tell me friends, what is your Secret?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-tell-me-friends-what-is-your-secret/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 02:01:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-9-tell-me-friends-what-is-your-secret/</guid>
        <description>It’s often said that in the Internet Age there is no more anonymity but this is only half true. Yes, thanks to Facebook I’ll know that the girl from my old English class in Year 12 has just broken up with her boyfriend and is playing Taylor Swift on a tear-filled triumphant loop on Spotify but the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hating headlines that tell you how to feel
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-7-hating-headlines-that-tell-you-how-to-feel/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 13:00:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-4-7-hating-headlines-that-tell-you-how-to-feel/</guid>
        <description>There’s something strange about the way we treat emotions; they have become products to be bought and sold. It was crazy American Pentecostal Christianity that first got me thinking about this. I went to a Pentecostal service in Philadelphia with a family with whom I was staying. The differences …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reconciling science with poetry
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-reconciling-science-with-poetry/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 03:28:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-reconciling-science-with-poetry/</guid>
        <description>I am sat at a pew in Westminster Abbey, filled with a sense of awe and reverence. Unlike the elderly lady to my right, her hands clasped in silent petition, I am not here for prayer. I am, however, here on a pilgrimage of sorts in an attempt to understand the power and limits of science.
Five steps …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The New Year in Northern Ireland
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-the-new-year-in-northern-ireland/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 09:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-the-new-year-in-northern-ireland/</guid>
        <description>Those who complain that British politicians lack principles should look to Northern Ireland. There is surely no other part of the UK where so many political leaders have such stupid, boring and ultimately harmful principles. Take Edwin Poots, Northern Ireland’s Health Minister, who has spent £37,000 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial hosts new cybersecurity institute
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-imperial-hosts-new-cybersecurity-institute/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 03:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-imperial-hosts-new-cybersecurity-institute/</guid>
        <description>Imperial is to host a new centre focussed on preventing cyber attacks against UK industry and infrastructure. The new centre will be artfully named the Research Institute into Trustworthy Industrial Control Systems and will focus on preventing cyber attacks on large infrastructure such as nuclear …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>World Shocked By Mandela Death
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-world-shocked-by-mandela-death/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 03:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-world-shocked-by-mandela-death/</guid>
        <description>Nelson Mandela, the last great national liberator of the past century, died yesterday at his home in Johannesburg following a 12 year battle with prostate cancer. Loved around the world as a freedom fighter and peace maker, Mandela’s death was announced by South African President Jacob Zuma as the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Exhibition Ode: Fenton Reflects
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-exhibition-ode-fenton-reflects/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 17:09:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-exhibition-ode-fenton-reflects/</guid>
        <description>This being my last of an excessive six years at Imperial, I can’t help but wonder, with more than a little panic, just how different life will be outside of the academic bubble. Excactly how I’ll gel with a world of 9-5s, responsibility, mortgages and early nights is uncertain. One thing I do know …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to analyse aid: using statistical analysis to improve effectiveness
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-how-to-analyse-aid-using-statistical-analysis-to-improve-effectiveness/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 13:11:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-how-to-analyse-aid-using-statistical-analysis-to-improve-effectiveness/</guid>
        <description>There is probably no other question in economics that evokes such strong emotions and creates such a clear divide between left and right. To the left, the world’s poor are caught in a poverty trap; without the minimum resources to help them help themselves, they will never break out of this cycle. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why you should make way for cyclists
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-why-you-should-make-way-for-cyclists/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 02:24:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-why-you-should-make-way-for-cyclists/</guid>
        <description>This time last year I bought a bike. It had taken four years of living in the city but I was finally living my stereotyped London dream of flying around on two wheels, fluorescent jacket fluorescing and carbon emissions zeroing; king of the road. The bike was freedom. Unlike the tube, I could get …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Head to Head: Rory Fenton on Integrated Education
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-11-head-to-head-rory-fenton-on-integrated-education/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 23:37:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-11-head-to-head-rory-fenton-on-integrated-education/</guid>
        <description>Public services should be open to all people, regardless of their beliefs. That so simple a statement should need to be shouted is madness and yet this is exactly what is needed in the UK. The truth is that for all our advances in other areas of human rights, when it comes to religious and belief …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Men: How To Talk About Gender
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-imperial-men-how-to-talk-about-gender/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 01:03:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-imperial-men-how-to-talk-about-gender/</guid>
        <description>Most students at Imperial are men. I don’t imagine this comes as much of a surprise to most Felix readers. While this gender imbalance is obvious from the first day of Freshers Week, what it means and how to talk about it can be more challenging. Whispered remarks about “The Ratio” can be heard on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Uncle Rory’s Freshers Week Tips
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-27-uncle-rorys-freshers-week-tips/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2013 23:17:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-27-uncle-rorys-freshers-week-tips/</guid>
        <description>You’ll be hearing this a lot this week but things were quite different back in my day. My day was 2008- Metric was a box called DB’s, Southside and Eastside were building sites, Facebook was a new thing and Justin Bieber was still an embryo. It was amazing. But as you prepare for the modern …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Losing My Religion
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-losing-my-religion/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 00:51:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-losing-my-religion/</guid>
        <description>There is nothing more liberating than simply being yourself. There is probably also nothing harder. For many across the UK struggling to leave their family’s religion, this is exactly the challenge they face everyday. I know – I was one of them.
Raised Catholic in Northern Ireland, religion was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to look good dead
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-how-to-look-good-dead/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 23:42:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-how-to-look-good-dead/</guid>
        <description>I was told once that the best way to know a city is to get lost in it. I can’t say if this is a universal truth but with my truly terrible sense of direction I’ve had plenty of chances to put it to the test. It was just this Monday that Imade my favourite finding to date. Bumbling around the mean …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Faitheism: the importance of dialogue
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-faitheism-the-importance-of-dialogue/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 00:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-18-faitheism-the-importance-of-dialogue/</guid>
        <description>Every Christmas for the past several years I sit down and I cry. It’s not that I’m sad; it’s an important tradition. Every Christmas I sit down and watch It’s A Wonderful Life and like a predictable fool each time I’m blinking back salty water. And it’s not just with this film – name a tear jerker …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Religion for Atheists
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-religion-for-atheists/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 22:54:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-religion-for-atheists/</guid>
        <description>&amp;ldquo;An atheist church”
I repeated the sentence a few times to myself while making my way along Islington’s St Paul’s road on Sunday morning. St Paul’s famous road to Damascus led him to found Christian communities but this St Paul’s road was taking me to a whole new concept of human community: an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Like Geldof mixed with Bush”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-like-geldof-mixed-with-bush/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 19:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-like-geldof-mixed-with-bush/</guid>
        <description>If you’ve been online at all in the past week, chances are you’ll have seen Kony 2012, a 30-minute video about the Lord’s Resistance Army (LRA) in central Africa made by the charity Invisible Children, officially the most viral video in the history of the internet. But along with the inevitable …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We need a new kind of giving
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-we-need-a-new-kind-of-giving/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 21:35:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-we-need-a-new-kind-of-giving/</guid>
        <description>If you are a science student at Imperial there’s very little you can do to get involved in international aid. The medics can use their skills to deliver life-saving vaccinations in Mozambique. The engineers can use their skills to build drought-fighting dams in El Salvador. And us scientists? We get …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Bottom Billion
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-the-bottom-billion/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 19:39:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-the-bottom-billion/</guid>
        <description>The world of international development is more often than not more complex than the image the rock concerts and heart-strings-tugging TV ads might project. Often riddled with scandalous corruption and heated debate, a heavy dose of evidence is clearly needed. Oxford Professor Paul Collier aims to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Poverty should occupy your mind
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-poverty-should-occupy-your-mind/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 23:36:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-poverty-should-occupy-your-mind/</guid>
        <description>When a friend came from home to visit me this weekend, the Occupy protest at St Paul’s Cathedral was an obvious stop on the tourist trail. Whether you agree with the protestors or not, the creation of a functioning tent civilisation with its own library, media centre and even a ‘university’ is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>From the United States with Love
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-from-the-united-states-with-love/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 21:28:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-from-the-united-states-with-love/</guid>
        <description>The Twentieth Century has been marked and shaped by many international alliances. From NATO to the Warsaw pact, these alliances have changed our world, for better or worse. But even as NATO warplanes fly over Libya and the Arab League rails against Syria, the strongest and most enduring of these …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Just how conservative are we?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-just-how-conservative-are-we/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 21:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-just-how-conservative-are-we/</guid>
        <description>The week before I started my first year here I went to the Fresher’s Fair at Queen’s University Belfast, my local. Going to Imperial’s the week after was a more or less similar affair – the same hobbies and sports, the same international societies and charities. But one thing stood out as missing – …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Through the language glass
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-28-through-the-language-glass/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 00:09:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-28-through-the-language-glass/</guid>
        <description>Could the language you speak affect how you think? The idea has long been shunned by academics as a relic of an imperialist, racist past when non- Europeans were deemed damned to low level thought by their “unsophisticated” languages. But not all who have held this view have been racist — haven’t we …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>7 Billion? That&#39;s Numberwang!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-7-billion-thats-numberwang/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 22:52:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-7-billion-thats-numberwang/</guid>
        <description>This Tuesday, the UN is expected to name a child, somewhere in the world, as the planet’s seven billionth living resident. The news has been greeted with alacrity by much of the same planet’s media, most notably The Guardian, which ran articles such as “Why current population growth is costing the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The economics of occupation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-the-economics-of-occupation/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 21:43:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,Kadhim Shubber,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-the-economics-of-occupation/</guid>
        <description>As we picked our way through the tents outside St Paul’s Cathedral this Monday one thing was clear: anarchists are not an easy bunch to organise. Not a surprise, perhaps, but add to this a passionate belief in not telling others what to do, and suddenly you find yourself voting about whether to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>One little piggy went to market
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-14-one-little-piggy-went-to-market/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 10:19:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-14-one-little-piggy-went-to-market/</guid>
        <description>I have a confession to make. Over the last year or so, I’ve been really quite evil. I really never meant to be, but there it is. Evil as a doorknob. Like many of my ilk, I can pin point the exact day the evil started, it was in November 2009 and I was in the Felix office, chatting to the Business …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>When conflict begets wisdom
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-when-conflict-begets-wisdom/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 19:33:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-when-conflict-begets-wisdom/</guid>
        <description>Two years ago, on a January afternoon, an Israeli shell hit Dr. Izzeldin Abuelaish’s home in Gaza, killing three of his daughters and his niece. Nothing can replace the hole left in his life by that shell. Yet the Harvard educated gynaecologist stood in front of the Imperial College Israeli Society …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Massacre in Kenya
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-massacre-in-kenya/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 19:31:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-massacre-in-kenya/</guid>
        <description>She didn’t stand a chance. Carrying underarm the small goat she was hoping to trade, Akiru could only join the other traders as they were rounded up in a small village along Ethiopia’s border with Kenya. The following morning she was one of twenty Kenyans carried away in bin bags by Catholic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is this the end of nuclear power?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-is-this-the-end-of-nuclear-power/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 21:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Joseph A L Letts,Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-is-this-the-end-of-nuclear-power/</guid>
        <description>On Friday 11th March 2011, an earthquake of magnitude 9.0 struck 230 miles off the coast of northern Japan. As well as triggering a devastating tsunami, the earthquake has also caused problems with a nuclear plant in Fukushima, with developments keeping the global community sitting on the edge of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>“Bullets were coming across us from both sides”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-bullets-were-coming-across-us-from-both-sides/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 20:19:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-bullets-were-coming-across-us-from-both-sides/</guid>
        <description>We finished dinner around ten o’clock and the shooting started perhaps ten minutes later. It may be a cliché but the air really did feel electrified as I hugged the ground to myself in the pitch black night. Bullets were soon coming across us from both sides of our camp but two minutes later, twelve …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is the future nuclear?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-is-the-future-nuclear/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 20:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-is-the-future-nuclear/</guid>
        <description>On Thursday 17th February, three of the UK’s leading experts on nuclear power came to Imperial to discuss their pet subjects in a debate organised by A Global Village; Imperial’s global affairs journal. Joining the debate were Professor Jim Skea OBE, Director of the UK Energy Research Centre, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Female empowerment to save the world
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-female-empowerment-to-save-the-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 20:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-female-empowerment-to-save-the-world/</guid>
        <description>The role that women play in the alleviation of poverty is becoming increasingly apparent in development research. In a sad irony, it is also increasingly clear that they bear the majority of the burden of this same poverty. The figures are alarming – women work two thirds of the world’s working …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>South Sudan: democracy amidst chaos
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-south-sudan-democracy-amidst-chaos/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 19:57:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-south-sudan-democracy-amidst-chaos/</guid>
        <description>On Sunday, the Southern region of Africa’s largest country started voting in a week-long referendum on whether or not to become the world’s newest country.
You only have to look at a map of Sudan to see how unlikely it was that the country should have ever been unified. British and Egyptian …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Peace in Korea
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-peace-in-korea/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 18:43:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rajat Jain,Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-peace-in-korea/</guid>
        <description>It is clear that North Korea is in a dire state in humanitarian and political terms. On the 60th anniversary of the start of the Korean War and 10th anniversary of opening diplomatic relations with the United Kingdom, from the outside it seems things have only gotten worse and this trend can only …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welfare cuts could pay for science!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-welfare-cuts-could-pay-for-science/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 19:14:24 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-welfare-cuts-could-pay-for-science/</guid>
        <description>Wednesday’s Spending Review brought with it the news, much speculated and feared in this paper, that science spending would itself face cuts. The research budget will be frozen, which means a real terms cut of 10%; about £500 million. This may not sound like too much but it comes at a time when …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lib Dems in trouble over higher fees
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-lib-dems-in-trouble-over-higher-fees/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 19:20:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rajat Jain,Rory Fenton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-lib-dems-in-trouble-over-higher-fees/</guid>
        <description>The last few months have not been good for the Liberal Democrats. With poll ratings plummeting from 23 to 14% since joining the coalition, the reality of power for the first time in over a century is quickly turning into a nightmare. Low party morale and a new (but not, he stresses, New) Labour …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lord Browne points to higher fees
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-lord-browne-points-to-higher-fees/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 19:07:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,Alexander Karapetian,Anna Perman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-lord-browne-points-to-higher-fees/</guid>
        <description>Universities should be unlimited in charging fees to students, the Browne review of university funding has recommended. The influential review, released early this week, outlined various proposals and potential changes in higher education funding to the government, including lifting the current cap …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
