<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/htb08/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/htb08/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Are we living under the tyranny of science?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-are-we-living-under-the-tyranny-of-science/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Bennie,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-are-we-living-under-the-tyranny-of-science/</guid>
        <description>I’ve noticed posters around college, and have been leafleted with a manifesto. At first, I was a little taken aback by their stance: ‘We believe the scientific method is dogmatic and prescriptive, and it restricts creativity of thought in science.’ The group, calling themselves the ‘Against Method …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lecturers are striking: where can we claim our tuition fee refund?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-12-lecturers-are-striking-where-can-we-claim-our-tuition-fee-refund/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Bennie,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-12-lecturers-are-striking-where-can-we-claim-our-tuition-fee-refund/</guid>
        <description>Universities are becoming businesses, treating students as customers. If so, they need to offer refunds when they can’t provide the services they are expected to provide.
After discussions with Universities UK (UUK) over pensions ended without an agreement, members of the University and College …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ewe look familiar</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-ewe-look-familiar/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Bennie,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-ewe-look-familiar/</guid>
        <description>Researchers at the University of Cambridge have demonstrated that sheep have face-recognition abilities, comparable to those of humans and non-human primates.
Eight sheep were trained to recognise the faces of actors Jake Gyllenhaal and Emma Watson, former US President Barack Obama, and BBC …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can graphic design save your life? </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-can-graphic-design-save-your-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Meesha Patel,Henry Bennie,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-can-graphic-design-save-your-life/</guid>
        <description>Wellcome Collection is one of the best museums in London: they hold large blockbuster exhibitions that dip into a small section of Henry Wellcome’s collection, easily one of the largest private collections that has ever existed.
Wellcome was interested in human health and medicine with his ultimate …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fetishisation of the Nobel Prize continues</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-fetishisation-of-the-nobel-prize-continues/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Bennie,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-fetishisation-of-the-nobel-prize-continues/</guid>
        <description>Rainer Weiss, Kip Thorne, and Barry Barish received the Nobel Prize for Physics for their discovery of gravitational wave: distortions in the fabric of space and time.
They led the Laser Interferometer Gravitational-Wave Observatory (LIGO) project and helped to make and keep it a reality. However, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Saunders explores the limbo between life and death in debut novel</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-saunders-explores-the-limbo-between-life-and-death-in-debut-novel/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Bennie,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-saunders-explores-the-limbo-between-life-and-death-in-debut-novel/</guid>
        <description>I was fearful when I heard about Lincoln in the Bardo almost a decade ago. I’m not a fan of historical novels and was aware of the difficulties that come with moving from short stories to novels. My fears were unfounded, George Saunders’ first novel is a triumph. To even call it a historical novel …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why do science when it doesn’t make any money?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-why-do-science-when-it-doesn-t-make-any-money/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Bennie,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-why-do-science-when-it-doesn-t-make-any-money/</guid>
        <description>One of our shortcomings as a country has been that whilst we’re brilliant at primary research and at scientific discovery, we’re less successful at making the most of those discoveries for commercial purposes – at getting businesses to actually get in there and exploit the discoveries which our …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Always be a zebra</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-always-be-a-zebra/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Bennie,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-always-be-a-zebra/</guid>
        <description>orming groups is a basic human drive. You are probably already a member of many groups: your family, your country, and probably multiple WhatsApp groups. But how did we humans become so social?
Researchers have long studied the evolution of social groups in bees and birds. It seems their complex …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are we happier when the weather is good?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-are-we-happier-when-the-weather-is-good/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Bennie,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-are-we-happier-when-the-weather-is-good/</guid>
        <description>t would be pretty easy to assume from anecdotal evidence that humans prefer warm sunny days rather than cold wet ones. But what empirical evidence is there for this? Patrick Baylis and his colleagues at Stanford University have carried out the largest investigation into the relationship between …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Neutrino experiment strikes gold</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-neutrino-experiment-strikes-gold/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Bennie,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-neutrino-experiment-strikes-gold/</guid>
        <description>he UK government has agreed to invest £65 million in a US particle physics project, as part of its first high-level science and research treaty with the US.
DUNE, the Deep Underground Neutrino Experiment and the LBNF, Long-Baseline Neutrino Facility have secured investment following the signing of a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cherry Popping | Drugs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-14-cherry-popping-drugs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 10:02:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Henry Bennie,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-14-cherry-popping-drugs/</guid>
        <description>You arrive at university as a member of one of two tribes.
The first tribe is composed of members that are somewhat knowledgeable about drugs, have taken them, know friends that take them and are generally aware that recreational drug use is a thing and for the most part are comfortable with it.
I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>But for all you are is but a King
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-but-for-all-you-are-is-but-a-king/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 20:55:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Bennie,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-but-for-all-you-are-is-but-a-king/</guid>
        <description>But for all you are is but a King, Lost out upon the sea.
His hands were crabs, his feet were fish, his soul the sea. He wept for days that could not be, he wept for years to be. He had but only two sons, both were to be of sea but one gave land his hand.
But I am your King! Are you not my brother? …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Barbican
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-barbican/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 18:22:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Henry Bennie,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-barbican/</guid>
        <description>His sister is always busy got to keep to time time is the law tick tock. His sister has no plants inorganic sleek smooth, straight, safe she used to carry the stream things like he did zip zap they are flies, filthy flies zap zip every night, waiting on every street corner.
Architects made them …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
