<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Film on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/film/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Film on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/categories/film/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>2019 in Review: The Best Films I’ve Seen this Year</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-2019-in-review-best-films-this-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Zuzanna Janusz,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-2019-in-review-best-films-this-year/</guid>
        <description>It was not a difficult task to name my favourite films I watched this year – the ones listed below were truly memorable and entertaining. So here is my selection, a bit eclectic I would say, and since there is no way to rank these gems, I present them in alphabetical order – enjoy.
BROKEN FLOWERS …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Festive Favourites</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-festive-favourites/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charlotte Arrand,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-festive-favourites/</guid>
        <description>Since it is the season, I thought I would make a list of my go-to Christmas films for the December period. They aren’t going to be ground breaking - I’m sure you will have watched them before - nor will they be films I consider impressive, however they give me that warm festive feeling and get me …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Knives Out (2019)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-knives-out/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dominic Ede,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-knives-out/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
It’s not often that a film starts getting almost unanimous praise from critics, so when this murder mystery from Rian Johnson started to garner attention from almost every direction, it left me wondering: what makes this film so good?
It centres around the family of Harlan Thrombey, a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mind the Gap: Movies to Look Out for this Break</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-mind-gap-movies-look-out-for-break/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jasmin Daley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-mind-gap-movies-look-out-for-break/</guid>
        <description>It’s cold, you’re bored, and your friends from home are looking for something to do. Look no further than our list of new releases to keep you entertained while we’re away.
BLACK CHRISTMAS: 12th December
A loose remake of the 1974 fan favourite Christmas movie. As the nights grow colder and darker, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Most Important Films of the Decade</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-most-important-films-of-decade/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charlotte Arrand,Zuzanna Janusz,Dominic Ede,Jasmin Daley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-most-important-films-of-decade/</guid>
        <description>Now that this decade is coming to a close, for the last paper of the year we thought we’d do a roundup of what we think are the most important films of the 2010’s, featuring one from each film writer. These films don’t necessarily line up with the ones we have loved the most, however, they are what …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Third Man (1949): A Look at the Film Turning 70</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-the-third-man-1949-look-at-film-turning-70/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dominic Ede,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-the-third-man-1949-look-at-film-turning-70/</guid>
        <description>Looking back at this aged and distant film allows you to visualise the significant amount of time that has passed since Felix was established in 1949, and also gives some relevant perspective in the advances cinema has made. Written by Graham Greene, the film centres around Holly Martins (Joseph …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The All-Nighter Film List for December</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-all-nighter-film-list-for-december/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jameel Sardharwalla,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-all-nighter-film-list-for-december/</guid>
        <description>With the end of term looming I’m sure many of you are feeling a mix of fatigue, anxiety, and excitement; so what better to re-energise you for these last few weeks than an all-nighter of films?
ZOMBIELAND: DOUBLE TAP (19:00)
It’s been an incredible 10 years since the first film graced the screens …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Big Fish (2003)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-big-fish-2003/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Zuzanna Janusz,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-big-fish-2003/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
Searching for a heart-warming film to watch on a November evening in an attempt to combat mid-term blues, I came across Big Fish, a childhood classic. I did remember it was entertaining and uplifting, but having seen it such a while ago, I had forgotten some twists and details of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hell, only with more feathers: The Birds (1963)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-hell-with-more-feathers-the-birds-1963/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jasmin Daley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-hell-with-more-feathers-the-birds-1963/</guid>
        <description>Although unlikely antagonists, director Alfred Hitchcock solidifies his mastery of the horror genre by making everyday birds as menacing as any Freddie Kruger or Mike Myers. On a roll after the success of Psycho just three years earlier, Hitchcock brings to life Daphne du Maurier’s short story of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The King (2019)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-the-king-2019/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Charlotte Arrand,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-22-the-king-2019/</guid>
        <description>3 stars
I would like to preface this by saying that under usual circumstances, this is probably not a film I would be inclined to watch, however, as a result of my undying love for Robert Pattinson, I have been somewhat anticipating the release of The King since watching its trailer. And whilst my …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>La Chinoise (1967)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-la-chinoise-1967/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dominic Ede,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-la-chinoise-1967/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
As an afterthought to this review, earlier this year I read an Ali Smith book called ‘Public Library and Other Stories’. While (slightly) irrelevant to the book, the cover featured a shot of two people reading on a balcony with strong red, white, and blue colours dominating the frame. On the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Souvenir: A Film about Film</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-souvenir-film-about-film/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Zuzanna Janusz,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-souvenir-film-about-film/</guid>
        <description>A film about film – Joanna Hogg takes us on a sentimental trip back to the 80s, telling a partly autobiographical story of Julie, an inexperienced filmmaker searching for a theme for her first picture and falling in love with a mysterious man.
What sounds like a coming of age story that many could …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your Father’s Murderer: A Letter to Zachary</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-your-fathers-murderer-a-letter-to-zachary/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dominic Ede,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-08-your-fathers-murderer-a-letter-to-zachary/</guid>
        <description>Sometimes it’s nice to just have a good cry at a movie, cathartic even; so with a quick Google for some of the saddest films ever made, followed by a little scrolling on Reddit, I came across this recommendation from Ubertraquer with the bold words “without a doubt the most tragic and heart …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Zombi Child</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-zombi-child/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jasmin Daley,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-zombi-child/</guid>
        <description>3 stars
Despite opening with bloodshed (thanks to a slice-and-dice scene with a giant fish) Zombi Child is not the slasher the name may suggest. Rather, it is an uncovering of the Haitian history behind the term ‘Zombi’. The story follows Haitian earthquake survivor Melissa as she becomes acquainted …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Marriage Story: BFI Film Festival</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-marriage-story-BFI-film-festival/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dominic Ede,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-marriage-story-BFI-film-festival/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
What I love about Marriage Story. It’s a great film, moving. The writing is provoking and rexal. It’s a film that’s honest, really honest. It makes you cry. It makes you laugh. It’s very clear about what it wants to portray. It is excellent.
If this introduction seems a little strange to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tammy and the T-Rex</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-tammy-t-rex/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Miles Gulliford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-tammy-t-rex/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
Two years ago, a friend of mine first introduced me to Tammy and the T-Rex: “Dinosaurs? Romance? On YouTube?” I thought to myself. “This is too good to be true”.It was not.
We spent the next hour and a half watching Stewart Raffill’s incredible brainchild, a memory I recall with great …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Meet the Film Editors</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-meet-film-editors/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dominic Ede,Charlotte Arrand,Matthew Leontsinis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-18-meet-film-editors/</guid>
        <description> Dominic Ede:
With first term already swiftly underway, I’m sure many of you will be unsure what to do with all this free time you have. To ease your concern we’ve created our lists of top 5 films with a little bit of something for everyone.
First, cutting our favourite films down to a list of five …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Joker</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-joker/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrew Melville,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-joker/</guid>
        <description>3 stars
Joker opens incredibly well. Lawrence Sher’s cinematography only adds to an already stunning performance from Joaquin Phoenix, while both are elevated by the original score. Robert De Niro’s inclusion as a late night talk show host adds even more credulity to the whole endeavour. But …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Farewell</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-the-farewell/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Dominic Ede,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-the-farewell/</guid>
        <description>4.5 stars
You’d be forgiven for not having heard the name Lulu Wang before Sundance 2019, but after making a big splash this year with The Farewell, her name should be at the top of directors we can be sure to expect more of in the future.
Based on Wang’s own experience, The Farewell follows Billi …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Vita &amp; Virginia Review</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-vita-virginia-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-24-vita-virginia-review/</guid>
        <description>Sometimes called the longest love-letter in history, Virginia Woolf wrote Orlando, the fictional biography of a gender-bending, time travelling Elizabethan nobleman, as a tribute to her friend, and sometimes-lover, Vita Sackville-West. Based to a great extent on the letters that the two acclaimed …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Avengers: Endgame</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-avengers-endgame/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aidan Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-avengers-endgame/</guid>
        <description>Once again directed by Joe &amp;amp; Anthony Russo, starring Robert Downey Jr., Chris Evans, Chris Hemsworth, Mark Ruffalo, Scarlett Johansson and Jeremy Renner as the original Avengers, Paul Rudd as Ant-Man and Josh Brolin as Thanos, mega-blockbuster Avengers: Endgame is the direct sequel of Avengers: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Us</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-us/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-us/</guid>
        <description>Two years have passed by since Jordan Peele’s directorial debut, Get Out. It was a critical and commercial success and earned Peele an Oscar for Best Screenplay. I love Get Out. The thrill of riding this rollercoaster of a movie in a packed screening was overwhelming. Peele impressively toyed with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Being John Malkovich</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-being-john-malkovich/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-being-john-malkovich/</guid>
        <description>I recently turned twenty. After battling through the bittersweet feelings of aging, a newfound existential angst and a sudden realisation of one’s mortality, I found it in myself to truly cherish this milestone and discover this treasure of a film from the year I was born.
Being John Malkovich is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Captain Marvel:Review</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-captain-marvel-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aidan Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-captain-marvel-review/</guid>
        <description>Directed by Anna Boden and Ryan Fleck, starring Brie Larson, Samuel L. Jackson and Jude Law, Captain Marvel is the first female-led superhero film produced by Marvel Studios. Politics and social agenda aside, Captain Marvel is an entertaining, though not fully satisfying, chapter of the Marvel …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Clockwork Orange: 50 years on.</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-a-clockwork-orange-50-years-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rowan Dixon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-a-clockwork-orange-50-years-on/</guid>
        <description>Nearly 50 years since its initial release in 1971, A Clockwork Orange is being released again for the big screen. For 27 years it was next to impossible to watch it here in the UK after it was banned from being shown in cinemas in 1973, with several court hearings blaming the actions of some …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oscars 2019: Felix Film’s take on the Winners, the Losers, and yearly scheduled general disappointment</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-oscars-2019-felix-film-s-take-on-the-winners-the-losers-and-yearly-scheduled-general-disappointment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mikhail Demtchenko,Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-oscars-2019-felix-film-s-take-on-the-winners-the-losers-and-yearly-scheduled-general-disappointment/</guid>
        <description>Best Picture
Academy Prediction:
Probably Green Book or The Favourite
What we want to win: I’d want to see Roma win, personally; maybe it might? BlacKkKlansman probably would win if this were ten years ago. Anything except A Star is Born.
The nominees for Best Picture are arguably the most diverse …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Memory Loss, Chopping off fingers, and Erotic musical numbers: A Perfect Valentine Trio</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-memory-loss-chopping-off-fingers-and-erotic-musical-numbers-a-perfect-valentine-trio/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aidan Chan,Sung Soo Moon,Mikhail Demtchenko,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-memory-loss-chopping-off-fingers-and-erotic-musical-numbers-a-perfect-valentine-trio/</guid>
        <description>Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind
Tis the season of romance! Whether you’re looking for a film for your next night in with your significant other, or to drown the bitter feeling of rejection, Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind is surely the answer. It’s a film that’s suitable for all couples, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse, yet another Sony  Spider-Man reboot, but it’s actually good?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-spider-man-into-the-spider-verse-yet-another-sony-spider-man-reboot-but-it-s-actually-good/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sam Welton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-spider-man-into-the-spider-verse-yet-another-sony-spider-man-reboot-but-it-s-actually-good/</guid>
        <description>Sony pictures is very hit-or-miss when it comes to super hero films. Sam Ramey’s Spider-Man trilogy can probably be credited with kick-starting the modern superhero boom, in which Spider-Man 2 is still widely considered an exemplar. However, it’s been a bumpy ride. Fantastic 4 has had three films …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The (Oscars’) Favourite</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-the-oscars-favourite/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rowan Dixon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-the-oscars-favourite/</guid>
        <description>The Favourite is a miss-match of fish eye videography, royal lesbian sex, aristocratic duck racing and some kickass wheelchairs. This film is quite simply all about who Queen Anne’s best friend is, battled out between Sarah Churchill, the queen’s longest and closest friend, and Abigail Masham, a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Roma: a triumph of cinema or the pinnacle of home viewing?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-roma-a-triumph-of-cinema-or-the-pinnacle-of-home-viewing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-roma-a-triumph-of-cinema-or-the-pinnacle-of-home-viewing/</guid>
        <description>I have been anticipating Alfonso Cuaron’s new film, Roma, since its warm reception around the festival circuit last year. It’s been six years since Gravity, a film that swept the board with its accolades, both technical and artistic. After making several high-profile, comfortably budgeted, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s a Wonderful Felix Film Christmas: The Lowdown of Must Watch Christmas Films this Holiday Season </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-it-s-a-wonderful-felix-film-christmas-the-lowdown-of-must-watch-christmas-films-this-holiday-season/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mikhail Demtchenko,Aidan Chan,Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-it-s-a-wonderful-felix-film-christmas-the-lowdown-of-must-watch-christmas-films-this-holiday-season/</guid>
        <description>The Nightmare Before Christmas
Less of a nightmare, more of a dream for a Christmas movie choice
Sick of the Jingle Bells and the Christmas lights? Tired of fake white beards and elven tights? Well you are in luck my mates, for The Nightmare Before Christmas awaits. From the inexplicable mind of Tim …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LISFF: A Celebration of the Possibilities of Short Film</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-lisff-a-celebration-of-the-possibilities-of-short-film/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mikhail Demtchenko,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-lisff-a-celebration-of-the-possibilities-of-short-film/</guid>
        <description>After two years of sold-out screenings, premieres, and dozens of excellent short films, LISFF is delighted to return to Kino Bermondsey for a third year.
LISFF 2018 will run December 9th – 12th, showcasing new talent, and filmmakers of independent spirit making creative and innovative use of low …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fantastic Beasts: The Crimes of Bad Storytelling</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-fantastic-beasts-the-crimes-of-bad-storytelling/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aidan Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-fantastic-beasts-the-crimes-of-bad-storytelling/</guid>
        <description>I walked into the cinema with mild apprehension. I knew that the critical reception was particularly unfavorable, yet I had hoped that this would be a Pirates of the Caribbean: Dead Man’s Chest scenario, where the film would still be immensely fun to watch. After two hours of sitting and hoping for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Man: Review</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-first-man-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aidan Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-first-man-review/</guid>
        <description>Directed by Damien Chazelle and starring Ryan Gosling and Claire Foy (as Neil and Janet Armstrong respectively), First Man is an impressive depiction of the moon landing. Damien Chazelle opted for a very realistic and grounded approach when tackling this groundbreaking event. Using nearly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Johnny English’s Third Strike</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-johnny-english-s-third-strike/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sam Welton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-johnny-english-s-third-strike/</guid>
        <description>Johnny English Strikes Again is an unfortunate movie. It feels like it ran out of something; maybe it was time, maybe it was interest, but it was probably money. What could have been another classic Rowan Atkinson vehicle has ended up a hollow and corporate mess, and yet the occasional scene had the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Russian Film Week returns to London in November!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-20-russian-film-week-returns-to-london-in-november/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mikhail Demtchenko,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-20-russian-film-week-returns-to-london-in-november/</guid>
        <description>The third Annual Russian Film Week will be held on November 25 to December 2, 2018 in landmark venues across London: BFI Southbank, Regent Street Cinema, Curzon Mayfair, Empire IMAX Leicester Square as well as in Edinburgh, Cambridge and Oxford.
The eight-day festival celebrates the best of new …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don’t Burn Your Bridges Before You Get To Them!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-don-t-burn-your-bridges-before-you-get-to-them/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-don-t-burn-your-bridges-before-you-get-to-them/</guid>
        <description>The BFI London Film Festival last week drew to a close, showcasing films from newbie filmmakers and seasoned veterans from around the globe. I was lucky enough to catch Burning, a South Korean noir directed by Lee Chang-dong. Lee offers a three-handed hypnotic and tense drama with impressive …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Venom: The Worst Kind of Bad Film</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-venom-the-worst-kind-of-bad-film/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sam Welton,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-venom-the-worst-kind-of-bad-film/</guid>
        <description>Venom is a bloated mess. The spectre of studio compromise looms over it in a big way. It has some glaring flaws but I can’t entirely hate it, since there were elements and sequences I found really engaging.
It’s the worst kind of bad film: passion and talent are on display and at some point this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Go Watch The Wife, If Only for Glenn Close</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-go-watch-the-wife-if-only-for-glenn-close/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aidan Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-go-watch-the-wife-if-only-for-glenn-close/</guid>
        <description>The Wife, directed by Björn Runge and starring Glenn Close and Jonathan Pryce, is a story about Joan Archer, the wife of Nobel Prize in Literature recipient Joseph Castleman (Jonathan Pryce). Glenn Close, as the eponymous “Wife” proves to be the most stunning and transcendent feature of the film.
As …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Masters of the Melancholic Movie Music</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-masters-of-the-melancholic-movie-music/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Guthrie Ruby,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-masters-of-the-melancholic-movie-music/</guid>
        <description>A month ago, in the throes of feeling ill and in the dumps, I turned not to Netflix but my old DVD collection. After wiping away the dust and sifting through the selection, I found, tightly tucked at the back of the drawer, a bunch of DVDs all created by the most celebrated Japanese animation …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BlacKkKlansman: A Klever koncious Komedy</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-blackkklansman-a-klever-koncious-komedy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-blackkklansman-a-klever-koncious-komedy/</guid>
        <description>Ah, the seventies — a vibrant era of yesteryear, whose key highlights include the heinous hairdos, sleaze-core fashion, disco music, and of course, the racial tension between white and black peoples of America. However, BlacKkKlansman is far from a period piece, as director Spike Lee embellishes …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>American Animals and the Hazards of Adaptation</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-american-animals-and-the-hazards-of-adaptation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aidan Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-american-animals-and-the-hazards-of-adaptation/</guid>
        <description>American Animals, directed by Bart Layton, is about the real-life story of 4 young adults, Spencer (Barry Keoghan), Warren (Evan Peters), Eric (Jared Abrahamson) and Chas (Blake Jenner) who decided to steal several books of extremly high value, including The Birds of America and On the Origin of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Film’s Student Essentials</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-felix-film-s-student-essentials/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sung Soo Moon,Aidan Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-felix-film-s-student-essentials/</guid>
        <description>Y TU MAMA TAMBIEN
DIR: Alfonso Cuaron
SCRIPT: Alfonso Cuaron, Carlos Cuaron
Literally translating to “And Your Mother Too”, Y Tu Mama Tambien is a coming-of-age film set in Mexico about two young men and an older woman searching for an invented beach called “la Boca del Cielo”, or “Heaven’s Mouth”. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The cinema of Japanese master Hirokazu Kore-eda</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-the-cinema-of-japanese-master-hirokazu-kore-eda/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-the-cinema-of-japanese-master-hirokazu-kore-eda/</guid>
        <description>This year’s Cannes Film Festival, which closed last month, saw a timely focus on the issues of sexual harassment that have dominated the film industry press over the last year. The discussion reached a shocking conclusion when actor Asia Argento made a speech during the closing ceremony, accusing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>François Ozon’s sexual thriller fails to ignite</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-fran-ois-ozon-s-sexual-thriller-fails-to-ignite/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-fran-ois-ozon-s-sexual-thriller-fails-to-ignite/</guid>
        <description>With Amant Double, there is the sense that French director François Ozon is returning to where he is most comfortable: sexual psychodrama. While Ozon’s filmography has some notable exceptions – the high-camp comedy Potiche among them – he seems to be most at home when straddling the line between …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>That Summer: The revenge of Grey Gardens</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-that-summer-the-revenge-of-grey-gardens/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-that-summer-the-revenge-of-grey-gardens/</guid>
        <description>In terms of Great American Mysteries, the story of the Beales ranks up there with Lindbergh’s baby or the Black Dahlia. Why and how, exactly, did ‘Big Edie’ and ‘Little Edie’ Beale, the mother-daughter duo, lock themselves inside their decrepit mansion in the East Hamptons for decades, slowly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Breadwinner fails to win our heart</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-the-breadwinner-fails-to-win-our-heart/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-31-the-breadwinner-fails-to-win-our-heart/</guid>
        <description>The Breadwinner, Nora Twomey’s follow-up to her breakout film The Secret of Kells, opens with a scene we are to take as paradigmatic of life in Afghanistan at the turn of the 21st century: a one-legged man, who fought in the Soviet-Afghan war, hawks a red dress his daughter has never had the chance …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On Chesil Beach: A strained drama that loses it in the last act</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-on-chesil-beach-a-strained-drama-that-loses-it-in-the-last-act/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-on-chesil-beach-a-strained-drama-that-loses-it-in-the-last-act/</guid>
        <description>On Chesil Beach has perhaps the longest sex scene I’ve ever seen in my history of cinema-going. We encounter newly-weds Florence (Saoirse Ronan) and Edward (Billy Howle) right at the beginning of Dominic Cooke’s film, and – shortly after sitting through the post-wedding dinner from hotel hell – they …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lean on Pete: Transmissions from the Interior West</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-lean-on-pete-transmissions-from-the-interior-west/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-11-lean-on-pete-transmissions-from-the-interior-west/</guid>
        <description>What is a Western? While everybody might know a film is a Western when they watch it, the actual definition is – as with any attempt to define cultural movements – difficult to pin down, squirming and wriggling away like a slippery eel. The American Film Institute has defined the Western as films …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A tale of two women</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-a-tale-of-two-women/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-a-tale-of-two-women/</guid>
        <description>Filmgoers looking for stories of complex women struggling to succeed in a man’s world, which simultaneously serve as an exploration and critique of a particular cultural moment are this week, surprisingly, spoiled for choice. Funny Cow (Dir: Adrian Shergold) and Let the Sunshine In (Dir: Claire …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Isle of Dogs: A cute tail that lacks some bite</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-isle-of-dogs-a-cute-tail-that-lacks-some-bite/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sung Soo Moon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-isle-of-dogs-a-cute-tail-that-lacks-some-bite/</guid>
        <description>It’s been four years since the release of The Grand Budapest Hotel, a commercial and critical success for director Wes Anderson. It’s a tough act to follow, but Isle of Dogs is a delightful addition to Anderson’s body of work – his offbeat filmmaking style translates impressively to animation, which …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can we break the glass chair, and bring more women directors into the film industry?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-can-we-break-the-glass-chair-and-bring-more-women-directors-into-the-film-industry/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-can-we-break-the-glass-chair-and-bring-more-women-directors-into-the-film-industry/</guid>
        <description>Hollywood is narcissistic. A community that reflects the vanity and self-obsession of its constituents, when Tinseltown reflects back on 2017 they will not remember it for the Fall of Mosul, the Rohingya Crisis, or the ousting of Robert Mugabe, but for the wave of allegations of sexual misconduct …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You Were Never Really Here – A thriller crossed with a horror crossed with an intense character study</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-you-were-never-really-here-a-thriller-crossed-with-a-horror-crossed-with-an-intense-character-study/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lawrence Good,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-you-were-never-really-here-a-thriller-crossed-with-a-horror-crossed-with-an-intense-character-study/</guid>
        <description>Tilda Swinton once called Lynne Ramsey “the Real McCoy”: a director whose films could not have been made by anybody else. Best known for her quiet and introspective work, Ramsay has garnered much critical acclaim – even having an “Every Frame a Painting” episode dedicated to her work. At first …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Oscars 2018: predictable results, predictable protests, predictable jokes, predictable disappointment</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-the-oscars-2018-predictable-results-predictable-protests-predictable-jokes-predictable-disappointment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-the-oscars-2018-predictable-results-predictable-protests-predictable-jokes-predictable-disappointment/</guid>
        <description>In the early hours of the morning, UK time, another year in the film industry came to a close, as Jimmy Kimmel closed out the 90th Academy Awards. The winners headed off to the after party, cleaners began sweeping the theatre floor of discarded acceptance speeches and candy wrappers, and film …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Film’s guide to the Oscars – who will win, who should win, and who’ve been left out in the cold</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-felix-film-s-guide-to-the-oscars-who-will-win-who-should-win-and-who-ve-been-left-out-in-the-cold/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Ashley Luckyram,Mark Aduol,Mikhail Demtchenko,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-felix-film-s-guide-to-the-oscars-who-will-win-who-should-win-and-who-ve-been-left-out-in-the-cold/</guid>
        <description>Oscars season is upon as! And, as is traditional, Felix are here to give you a rundown of what will win on the night, as well as what should win, and who didn&amp;rsquo;t even get a nomination:
 Best Picture
 It’s been a complicated awards season. Call Me by Your Name started out in the lead when it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Baftas 2018: A predictable awards ceremony that leaves the road to the Oscars clear</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-baftas-2018-a-predictable-awards-ceremony-that-leaves-the-road-to-the-oscars-clear/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-baftas-2018-a-predictable-awards-ceremony-that-leaves-the-road-to-the-oscars-clear/</guid>
        <description>Even for those at Imperial who aren’t particularly interested in film, the presence of the 2018 Baftas was difficult to miss. For one thing, the evening was hosted at the Royal Albert Hall, allowing some students and staff the chance to engage in some star-spotting (insert pun about Blackett astro …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Black Panther: Ryan Coogler breaks the mould of a superhero film</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-black-panther-ryan-coogler-breaks-the-mould-of-a-superhero-film/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chimdi E Igwe,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-black-panther-ryan-coogler-breaks-the-mould-of-a-superhero-film/</guid>
        <description>Arguably the most anticipated film of 2018 arrived last week. Black Panther, the latest addition to the Marvel Cinematic Universe canon, and directed by Ryan Coogler, was released in cinemas worldwide this February.
Black Panther is set in the fictional country of Wakanda, a technologically advanced …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Guillermo del Toro shows us the shape of his dreams in this fantasy romance</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-guillermo-del-toro-shows-us-the-shape-of-his-dreams-in-this-fantasy-romance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-guillermo-del-toro-shows-us-the-shape-of-his-dreams-in-this-fantasy-romance/</guid>
        <description>&amp;ldquo;Disobedience is one of the strongest signals of your conscience of what is right and what is wrong” said Guillermo del Toro when promoting his masterpiece Pan’s Labyrinth, “when you disobey in an intelligent way, you disobey in a natural way, it turns out to be more beneficial than blind …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lady Bird: Love and cinema in Sacramento</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-lady-bird-love-and-cinema-in-sacramento/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-lady-bird-love-and-cinema-in-sacramento/</guid>
        <description>Don’t you think maybe they are the same thing? Love and attention?”
Christine “Lady Bird” McPherson (Saoirse Ronan) is in her last year of high school, at a catholic institution in the city of Sacramento, California. Her dream, like innumerable other teens across the states of America, is to get as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Loveless: Andrey Zvyagintsev gets under the skin of modern Russia</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-loveless-andrey-zvyagintsev-gets-under-the-skin-of-modern-russia/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-loveless-andrey-zvyagintsev-gets-under-the-skin-of-modern-russia/</guid>
        <description>Andrey Zvyagintsev’s Loveless, his follow up to his 2014 Leviathan, features one of the most haunting images I’ve encountered in cinema: Shenya (Maryana Spivak) and Boris (Aleksey Rozin), a middle-class couple in the throes of an ugly divorce, argue about what they should do with their son Alexey …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Diversity at the Oscars – how far have we come?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-diversity-at-the-oscars-how-far-have-we-come/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark Aduol,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-diversity-at-the-oscars-how-far-have-we-come/</guid>
        <description>Before 1962, Hollywood didn’t make many films about race. This made some moviegoers unhappy. So, they put down their popcorn, picked up their picket signs and marched over to Hollywood Boulevard demanding that film studio executives increase the racial diversity of characters in their films. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Phantom Thread: A haunting masterpiece</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-phantom-thread-a-haunting-masterpiece/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-phantom-thread-a-haunting-masterpiece/</guid>
        <description>Though he excelled as a young actor in the National Youth Theatre, in 1975 Daniel Day-Lewis made a decision that almost deprived us of some of the very greatest performances ever seen on screen. Then an unruly 18 year old, Day-Lewis elected not to pursue the arts, instead applying for a five year …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Last Flag Flying: Linklater’s latest </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-last-flag-flying-linklater-s-latest/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-last-flag-flying-linklater-s-latest/</guid>
        <description>If looking back teaches us one thing, it is that the past is a strange and foreign land. If we are to ascribe to the films of Richard Linklater a mission statement, however, it would be to make that land familiar. Or rather, familiar enough.
Linklater is a director who trades in nostalgia, an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On Directing Film</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-on-directing-film/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-on-directing-film/</guid>
        <description>The announcement of the Academy Award nominations last week saw the usual surprises and snubs roll in. One particular category has continued to be the source of much debate throughout awards season, with commentators and voters alike unable to come to agreement. Across the Golden Globes, BAFTAs, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Greg Barker’s Obama doc The Final Year is an exercise in hagiography</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-greg-barker-s-obama-doc-the-final-year-is-an-exercise-in-hagiography/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-greg-barker-s-obama-doc-the-final-year-is-an-exercise-in-hagiography/</guid>
        <description>There are many terrible things about Trump’s ascension to the presidency, which – despite the cries of those who say it was an ‘inevitable’ side effect of the rise in identity politics – still comes as a shock, a full year on from his inauguration. But one aspect of his rise to power which, while …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Post – confessions of a news editor</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-the-post-confessions-of-a-news-editor/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-the-post-confessions-of-a-news-editor/</guid>
        <description>Not content with getting his grubby hands all over the American presidency, Donald Trump has now invaded the world of cinema, albeit indirectly. Just was we have now entered the ‘post-Weinstein’ era, we have also entered into the ‘Trumpian’ age of cinema: now all films that come out need to be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Shape of Oscars</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-the-shape-of-oscars/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-the-shape-of-oscars/</guid>
        <description>While not as glamorous as an affair as the big ceremony at the Dolby Theatre in the Spring, the announcement of the Academy Award nominees is nonetheless an anticipated event. Streamed live from the Samuel Goldwyn Theatre in Beverley Hills, announcers Tiffany Haddish and Andy Serkis had some …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A messy, ham-fisted take on race and violence</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-18-a-messy-ham-fisted-take-on-race-and-violence/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-18-a-messy-ham-fisted-take-on-race-and-violence/</guid>
        <description>Three Billboards Outside Ebbing, Missouri, shows what writer and director Martin McDonagh does best: write sharp, expletive-filled dialogue that snaps across the screen like it was created by Aaron Sorkin’s angry kid brother. Over the course of two previous features, and numerous stage works, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gary Oldman showing us how it’s done-kirk</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-18-gary-oldman-showing-us-how-it-s-done-kirk/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-18-gary-oldman-showing-us-how-it-s-done-kirk/</guid>
        <description>Darkest Hour begins and ends with a cacophony of yelling. And in the 120 minutes between these two shots, there is plenty more shouting, although none do so louder or more verbosely than Gary Oldman, who transforms himself into Winston Churchill for this film about the early days of his premiership. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is time up for Woody Allen?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-18-is-time-up-for-woody-allen/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-18-is-time-up-for-woody-allen/</guid>
        <description>Little over three months have passed since allegations of sexual misconduct against movie industry czar Harvey Weinstein emerged, and since then the flood of reports of Hollywood abuse shows no sign of abating. Not only have more victims of Weinstein come out of the shadows – more than 80 as things …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sundance Film Festival: Start as you mean to go on</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-18-sundance-film-festival-start-as-you-mean-to-go-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-18-sundance-film-festival-start-as-you-mean-to-go-on/</guid>
        <description>In 1978 the very first Sundance Film Festival took place, with the goal of showcasing the potential of American independent cinema. On offer were films from the likes of Martin Scorsese and Elia Kazan. It is fair to say that since then Sundance has been an integral part of the independent film …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Money can’t buy you everything…</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-money-can-t-buy-you-everything/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-money-can-t-buy-you-everything/</guid>
        <description>Any opinion of Ridley Scott’s latest film, All the Money in the World, is going to be indelibly coloured by the situation surrounding its production. Scheduled to be released in the States at the end of last year, with Kevin Spacey in the lead, the film seemed doomed following the numerous sexual …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Coming to a screen near you soon…</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-coming-to-a-screen-near-you-soon/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-coming-to-a-screen-near-you-soon/</guid>
        <description>For some people, January may bring thoughts of new year’s resolutions, gym sessions, and anxiously awaiting the sun to return. For cinephiles, however, it marks the true beginning of awards season: the Oscar nominations will be announced at the end of this month, and before those are given out we …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fahrenheit 11/9 Review</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-fahrenheit-11-9-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rowan Dixon,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-fahrenheit-11-9-review/</guid>
        <description>As with all Michael Moore’s films Fahrenheit 11&amp;frasl;9 (not 9&amp;frasl;11 , that’s his other one) is one of the most eye-opening films of the year, and one I think more of us should see. The film opens with celebrities and news hosts from the run-up to the 2016 election joking about how Trump would …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Awards season contenders: our top picks</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-21-awards-season-contenders-our-top-picks/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-21-awards-season-contenders-our-top-picks/</guid>
        <description>Were this article a film, I’d like to think that it would be in contention for recognition from the Academy. It had a clear and bold start, compelling second act, and now, hopefully, a memorable ending. But seriously, let’s talk about who will end up winning the big prizes next spring. There are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>For your consideration: the first annual Felix Film Awards for 2017</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-21-for-your-consideration-the-first-annual-felix-film-awards-for-2017/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-21-for-your-consideration-the-first-annual-felix-film-awards-for-2017/</guid>
        <description>As the year winds to a close, in lieu of compiling a list of the best films, directorial work and acting performances, we have decided to hand out prizes to those who merit them for their outstanding creative efforts. We imagine that the finest talents in world cinema are sat at the edge of their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Justice League fails to save the (cinematic) day</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-justice-league-fails-to-save-the-cinematic-day/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-justice-league-fails-to-save-the-cinematic-day/</guid>
        <description>Justice League had a lot to prove from the get go. With three critically panned films and only one moderate successfully movie in Wonder Woman, Warner Brothers and DC Comics had a lot to make up for and improve upon. While Justice League is ultimately a step in the right direction, it doesn’t quite …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mudbound – A sweeping epic that plays out like an intricate character study </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-mudbound-a-sweeping-epic-that-plays-out-like-an-intricate-character-study/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark Aduol,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-mudbound-a-sweeping-epic-that-plays-out-like-an-intricate-character-study/</guid>
        <description>Look out at the world and you’ll notice all the things that set you apart from everyone else; the characteristics that make you – and everyone else – unique and different. Mudbound however, is a reminder of what we all share – the human struggle to take control of our lives and make something out of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Our guide to the 2018 awards season contenders II: the Film Editors strike back: Judgement Day: Reloaded</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-our-guide-to-the-2018-awards-season-contenders-ii-the-film-editors-strike-back-judgement-day-reloaded/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-01-our-guide-to-the-2018-awards-season-contenders-ii-the-film-editors-strike-back-judgement-day-reloaded/</guid>
        <description>As the year winds down I always find myself reflecting back on the best films to emerge over the past twelve months, and this inevitably leads to speculation on which ones might end up with Academy Award nominations and wins. These two categories do not always align, and last week I ran through some …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Our guide to the 2018 awards season contenders (Part 1)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-our-guide-to-the-2018-awards-season-contenders-part-1/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-our-guide-to-the-2018-awards-season-contenders-part-1/</guid>
        <description>Fall festival season is over, trailers for the final films of the year have dropped, and prestige pictures are beginning to roll out their wide releases left, right, and centre. You guessed it: it’s awards season. While there are strong arguments to made that artworks shouldn’t really be compared in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Barry Lyndon: Stanley Kubrick’s greatest masterpiece</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-barry-lyndon-stanley-kubrick-s-greatest-masterpiece/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Purdy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-barry-lyndon-stanley-kubrick-s-greatest-masterpiece/</guid>
        <description>Upon release, Barry Lyndon was met with intense scorn from some critics: Pauline Kael described it as a “coffee-table movie” and others called it dry, boring, and empty. They were wrong. Barry Lyndon is a visual and philosophical masterpiece that, in my eyes, is Stanley Kubrick’s greatest work. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First They Killed My Father: Angelina Jolie’s first directorial triumph</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-first-they-killed-my-father-angelina-jolie-s-first-directorial-triumph/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark Aduol,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-first-they-killed-my-father-angelina-jolie-s-first-directorial-triumph/</guid>
        <description>First They Killed My Father, subtitled A Daughter of Cambodia Remembers, tells the story of Cambodian author Loung Ung and her battle to stay alive under the brutal regime of the Khmer Rouge. Most films that deal with war often tend to hover around a particular incident during the conflict. Whether …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wonder Women: who rules the silver screen? Part Deux</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-wonder-women-who-rules-the-silver-screen-part-deux/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-wonder-women-who-rules-the-silver-screen-part-deux/</guid>
        <description>5 Marion Cotillard
Best Performances: La Vie en Rose, Two Days One Night, The Immigrant, Rust and Bone
Hailing from Paris, Marion Cotillard has always mixed English and French roles, particularly from 2003 onwards. She announced herself on the global stage in 2007 by winning the Oscar for best …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An exercise in unremitting tension and horror</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-an-exercise-in-unremitting-tension-and-horror/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-an-exercise-in-unremitting-tension-and-horror/</guid>
        <description>It seems that for Greek director Yorgos Lanthimos, who directed Dogtooth and The Alps before making his move into English-language cinema with 2015’s The Lobster, the term ‘clinical’ may be a compliment. Since his breakout feature back in 2009, Lanthimos has ploughed the same furrow, excelling in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Luca Guadagnino serves us up a shimmering slice of young desire</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-luca-guadagnino-serves-us-up-a-shimmering-slice-of-young-desire/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-luca-guadagnino-serves-us-up-a-shimmering-slice-of-young-desire/</guid>
        <description>From Maggie Cheung slipping out onto the Hong Kong streets in her cheongsam, looking for some noodles to eat in In the Mood for Love, to the sparks illuminating the faces of the Danish ascetics in Babette’s Feast as they are served the meal of a lifetime, cinema and food have always been a powerful …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wonder Women: who rules the silver screen?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-wonder-women-who-rules-the-silver-screen/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-wonder-women-who-rules-the-silver-screen/</guid>
        <description>Following the release of the trailer for Sir Daniel Day-Lewis’ final film, Phantom Thread, last week, I looked at who may attempt to fill his enormous boots as the finest actor in the world. There were a number of excellent candidates, and in the end Day-Lewis’ fellow Paul Thomas Anderson …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Like a Heartbeat Drives You Mad – short films on the dark side of love</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-like-a-heartbeat-drives-you-mad-short-films-on-the-dark-side-of-love/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Purdy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-like-a-heartbeat-drives-you-mad-short-films-on-the-dark-side-of-love/</guid>
        <description>Love can be troublesome, complex, and macabre, and Like a Heartbeat Drives You Mad offers extensive insight into this dark side of human intimacy. The series consists of ten short films shot from around the world, from Glasgow to Delhi, through which we witness an eclectic range of traumatic love …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Moving on from Daniel: where do we go now?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-moving-on-from-daniel-where-do-we-go-now/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-moving-on-from-daniel-where-do-we-go-now/</guid>
        <description>As he named The Master the best film of 2012, Peter Bradshaw of The Guardian labelled the anticipation around the release of a Paul Thomas Anderson film as “event cinema”, only comparable to the legend surrounding the great Stanley Kubrick. America’s newest master’s latest, esoterically titled …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sally Potter’s dinner party from hell</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-sally-potter-s-dinner-party-from-hell/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lawrence Good,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-sally-potter-s-dinner-party-from-hell/</guid>
        <description>If you’d just been promoted to Shadow Minister for Health, wouldn’t you feel that a small party might be in order? Just a small get together with your nearest and dearest surely couldn’t hurt. Well, after watching The Party, it turns out you may want to reconsider.
A sharp and deeply funny chamber …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An operatic nightmare of psychological trauma</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-an-operatic-nightmare-of-psychological-trauma/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-an-operatic-nightmare-of-psychological-trauma/</guid>
        <description>You Were Never Really Here
Dir: Lynne Ramsay. Script: Lynne Ramsay. Starring: Joaquin Phoenix, Ekaterina Samsonov, Judith Roberts, John Doman. 85 minutes
4.5 Stars
An unprecedented level of discussion was prompted when the line-up was announced for the Cannes Film Festival in the spring. The new …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Film’s Summer 2017 cinema round-up</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-felix-film-s-summer-2017-cinema-round-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mark Aduol,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-felix-film-s-summer-2017-cinema-round-up/</guid>
        <description>Depending on who you are, the summer movie season was either a blessing or a disaster. For film studio executives, it was unquestionably dismal. There was little comfort in watching each new release miss its box office targets. On Labour Day Weekend – the long summer weekend in the United States …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Death of Stalin: Armando Iannucci returns</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-the-death-of-stalin-armando-iannucci-returns/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Ashley Luckyram,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-the-death-of-stalin-armando-iannucci-returns/</guid>
        <description>Scotsman Armando Iannucci is the finest political satirist of the 21st century. Through his television shows The Thick of It and it’s American adaptation Veep, he has shown a propensity for mocking politicians who ostensibly claim to have the interests of the people at heart, while actually only …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stretching your student loan: cinema on a budget</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-stretching-your-student-loan-cinema-on-a-budget/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Mikhail Demtchenko,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-stretching-your-student-loan-cinema-on-a-budget/</guid>
        <description>5. Picturehouse Cinema – £5 Matinee; £7 Weekdays
When you think of cinema chains, you think of overpriced popcorn at Odeon, or £15 tickets at Vue, but Picturehouses breaks the mold. Located in some of the most archi-tecturally unique buildings in London, Picturehouses spreads from the Ritzy Theatre …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your Name: Freaky Friday by way of Kierkegaard
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-20-your-name-freaky-friday-by-way-of-kierkegaard/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 18:26:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-20-your-name-freaky-friday-by-way-of-kierkegaard/</guid>
        <description>In his latest amine film Your Name, which has broken box-office records in Japan and beyond, director Makoto Shinkai chooses a plot-line which has a long pedigree: body swapping. Shuffling characters’ consciousnesses around is a trope that stretches back to the 19th Century and beyond. In Your Name, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LFF: Manchester by the Sea
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-5-lff-manchester-by-the-sea/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 20:37:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Stephens,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-5-lff-manchester-by-the-sea/</guid>
        <description>If you were to rely on the list of previous winners of the Best Actor Oscar as a definitive list of cinema history’s greatest performances, you would probably have one clear go-to when thinking of acting techniques for a sure-fire win (apart from being white): shouting. It has seemed throughout the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LFF: La La Land
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-5-lff-la-la-land/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 20:30:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Stephens,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-5-lff-la-la-land/</guid>
        <description>It turns out Ryan Gosling is as roguishly charming and wonderful in person as we all hoped he would be. I was lucky enough to see La La Land for the first time at a London Film Festival screening, after which he appeared to a hurricane of cheers and thrown roses/knickers for a Q&amp;amp;A. When asked …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LFF: A Monster Calls
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-5-lff-a-monster-calls/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 20:27:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Meryl Chittethazhathu Anil,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-5-lff-a-monster-calls/</guid>
        <description>Storytellers are a threat,” wrote Chinua Achebe, “they threaten all champions of control, usurpers of the right-to-freedom of the human spirit”. It is this power, that of a simple story well-told, that director J. A. Bayona is trying to tap with his latest feature A Monster Calls, an adaptation of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LFF: Certain Women | Postcards from the edge of solitude
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-5-lff-certain-women-postcards-from-the-edge-of-solitude/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 20:22:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Meryl Chittethazhathu Anil,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-5-lff-certain-women-postcards-from-the-edge-of-solitude/</guid>
        <description>Certain Women, American director Kelly Reichardt’s sixth film, begins with a shot that serves as a statement of intent: a rusting old train slowly drags itself across the Montana landscape, framed by snowy mountain peaks; stoic in its solitude, it chuffs and puffs along the track, determined to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Modern Classics of Cinema | Super 8
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-modern-classics-of-cinema-super-8/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 17:24:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Hafiz Zainal,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-modern-classics-of-cinema-super-8/</guid>
        <description>J. J. Abrams’ sci-fi adventure Super 8 is a poetic tribute to early Spielberg films, taking us down the avenue of their childhood memories: shooting action films with neighbourhood friends on an 8mm format camera – known as the Super 8, it was first marketed in the 60’s as a user-friendly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Handmaiden
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-the-handmaiden/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 17:23:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lawrence Good,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-the-handmaiden/</guid>
        <description>A young Korean woman arrives at a vast mansion, taking up position as handmaiden to the niece of a wealthy aristocrat. So begins this erotic, psychological thriller, a taut and captivating exploration of deceit, power, and sexuality in Japanese-ruled Korea. The latest film from director Park …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
