<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/monami_miyamoto/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/monami_miyamoto/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Witnessing Life on the Frontline of Climate Change</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-witnessing-life-on-the-frontline-of-climate-change/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Monami Miyamoto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-witnessing-life-on-the-frontline-of-climate-change/</guid>
        <description>On April 18th, BBC One broadcasted the highly anticipated documentary “Climate Change: The facts”. Needless to say, it was one of the most devastating hours of my entire easter holiday (really putting revision into perspective). Hosted by the trusted veteran, sir David Attenborough, this documentary …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Land of Hope and Glory</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-land-of-hope-and-glory/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Monami Miyamoto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-08-land-of-hope-and-glory/</guid>
        <description>On Tuesday, VegSocs from Imperial, LSE, Kings and Middlesex University collaborated to host a film screening of “Land of Hope and Glory”, followed by a talk by the producer, Ed Winters. Ed Winters, also known as “Earthling Ed” is one of the most well-known faces of UK vegan activism, and has been …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tap Here to Stop Food Waste</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-tap-here-to-stop-food-waste/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Monami Miyamoto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-tap-here-to-stop-food-waste/</guid>
        <description>On 11th February the Social Innovation Academy at LSE (London School of Economics) hosted a talk titled ‘The War on Food Waste’, with 3 entrepreneurs from start-ups tackle food waste. These companies included ODDBOX, DayOld and OLIO, each represented by their founders or board members.
Food waste is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Book Review: Green Giants</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-book-review-green-giants/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Monami Miyamoto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-book-review-green-giants/</guid>
        <description>Although ‘sustainability’ is a constant buzzword in our society and people seem to understand that its somewhat important, I feel that many of us don’t know what it really means to be sustainable. Should we stop using plastic all together? Should we abandon eating all meat and dairy? Should we never …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2018: A big year for the vegan movement</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-2018-a-big-year-for-the-vegan-movement/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Monami Miyamoto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-2018-a-big-year-for-the-vegan-movement/</guid>
        <description>Last Tuesday (15th of January), Environmental Society, VegSoc and APES collaborated to host a movie screening event for the film VEGAN 2018. Out of curiosity I attended. I came out of it feeling a mixture of emotions - partly overwhelmed by the density of the information, partly empowered to know …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Oddly inspiring</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-oddly-inspiring/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Monami Miyamoto,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-oddly-inspiring/</guid>
        <description>I’d like to believe that every one of us, at least in part, can do something better for the environment. But I also know that for some, this can seem dauting, difficult, or just too time consuming - which is why, I thought I’d share my experience with ODDBOX, a UK based company committed to tackling …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
