<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/tn509/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/tn509/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The right to offend
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-the-right-to-offend/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 23:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tagore Nakornchai,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-the-right-to-offend/</guid>
        <description>In case you haven’t been following the news, here’s a quick summary: the UCL Atheist, Secular and Humanist Society’s president stepped down this week after massive pressure from the UCL Union. The Society had used a picture from the “Jesus and Mo” web comic to advertise an event, and were promptly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Retribution is a dish best served cold... with friends
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-retribution-is-a-dish-best-served-cold-with-friends/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 04:35:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tagore Nakornchai,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-retribution-is-a-dish-best-served-cold-with-friends/</guid>
        <description>The Warhammer 40,000 universe is a violent place. There are literally a hundred ways to die: you can be chopped up by a chainsaw sword, gnawed to death by a giant bug, have your mind blown up by a psychic space-elf, or shot in the back by your own side to hide some obscure secret._ Dawn of War II: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Breaking a two-party system
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-breaking-a-two-party-system/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 19:24:55 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tagore Nakornchai,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-breaking-a-two-party-system/</guid>
        <description>I’m looking at the Canadian election results and can’t help but feel slightly jealous. This time last year, after the debates, the Lib Dems were looking at a surge similar to the New Democratic Party’s (NDP) surge, and Labour looked like it was heading towards electoral oblivion. The NDP has pulled …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lansley’s plans will stitch up the NHS
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-lansleys-plans-will-stitch-up-the-nhs/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 21:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tagore Nakornchai,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-lansleys-plans-will-stitch-up-the-nhs/</guid>
        <description>The NHS is one of Britain’s most cherished institutions – pretty much the only thing Labour and the Conservatives agreed on during the general election was the need to safeguard the NHS from budget cuts. It has gone through one of the biggest spending increases in it’s history.
Yet, despite …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is immigration a problem?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-is-immigration-a-problem/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 20:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tagore Nakornchai,Haralambos Dayantis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-is-immigration-a-problem/</guid>
        <description>Yes – Haralambos Dayantis
“It often leads to ghettoisation”
Immigration to the UK is increasingly being recognised as a problem, and not just within the Daily Mail’s typical demographic. Research by Ipsos MORI has shown that 71% of people aged 16-24 are concerned about immigration. This should come …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is it time we elected the House of Lords?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-is-it-time-we-elected-the-house-of-lords/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 20:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tagore Nakornchai,Matthew Parker,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-is-it-time-we-elected-the-house-of-lords/</guid>
        <description>Yes – Tagore Nakornchai
The idea that there would be an unelected legislative chamber completely and utterly unaccountable to scrutiny and democratic processes seems completely foreign in a modern, liberal democracy. Yet that is exactly what the House of Lords is – a body made up of MPs who lost …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why I still agree with Nick
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-why-i-still-agree-with-nick/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 20:06:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tagore Nakornchai,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-why-i-still-agree-with-nick/</guid>
        <description>The Lib Dems have been criticized by everyone and their dog since they joined the coalition last May – the turnaround on tuition fees, their complicity in the public sector cuts, allowing the Tories in to Number 10. We’ve all heard it before: the Lib Dems are doomed, we’ll never vote for them again, …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
