<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/fsport/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/fsport/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial reach next round in Cup
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-imperial-reach-next-round-in-cup/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 11:53:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-imperial-reach-next-round-in-cup/</guid>
        <description>It’s safe to say that the ICUAFC 6th XI hasn’t had the best of starts to the season. However, when it comes to the cup, league form is thrown out of the window and we made the epic journey to North London with confidence to play RUMS (UCL Medics) 3s. Despite the biblical deluge in West London, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Sail Past Brighton
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-imperial-sail-past-brighton/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 10:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-imperial-sail-past-brighton/</guid>
        <description>On a windy Wednesday in west London, Imperial 1st XV hosted Brighton at Harlington for their third match of the season. Off the back of a 24-0 win against their inferior university colleagues, IC were brimming with confidence going into this game with a very strong team on paper, only missing centre …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Thump RUMS in Shenley
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-imperial-thump-rums-in-shenley/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 09:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-imperial-thump-rums-in-shenley/</guid>
        <description>ICUAFC 5’s set off on the long trip to North London on Saturday for a matchup against London rivals RUMS 3’s. The team’s arrival at Shenley was excitedly received by veteran footballer and long-time IC 5’s fan Gianfranco Zola. Unfortunately captain Clarke couldn’t fit him into the team in place of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial has good showing at Spooky Duathlon
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-imperial-has-good-showing-at-spooky-duathlon/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 09:53:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-imperial-has-good-showing-at-spooky-duathlon/</guid>
        <description>On Sunday 27th, six fellow triathletes (plus old boy Sam O’Neil) took to Hyde Park to take part in the Jekyll and Hyde Park Halloween Duathlon. With the clocks going back alarms were tentatively set, not really knowing whether we’d unknowingly cause ourselves to turn up to the race an hour early or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Brush Aside the Medics
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-imperial-brush-aside-the-medics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 01:17:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-imperial-brush-aside-the-medics/</guid>
        <description>After a poor first performance against UCL last week, IC Rugby’s 1st XV desperately needed to turn up with their heads switched on. Playing in the league against varsity rivals, Imperial Medics, IC were looking to give them a repeat performance of last year’s victory at The Stoop. The atmosphere in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Triathlon Club make a splash at Aquathlon
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-triathlon-club-make-a-splash-at-aquathlon/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 20:20:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-triathlon-club-make-a-splash-at-aquathlon/</guid>
        <description>The first event of the tri club racing calendar brought nine athletes to London Fields, competing in the swim-run combo known as an aquathlon. This early season competition was an opportunity to blow away some of the summer cobwebs for returning members, whilst for a couple of others it was an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICUCC beaten by UCL
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-icucc-beaten-by-ucl/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 22:22:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-icucc-beaten-by-ucl/</guid>
        <description>With his 100% winning record as skipper on the line, Vignesh Venkateswaran once again took up the reins of captaincy as he led the ICUCC 1st XI to face off against arch-rivals UCL, in a nail-biting London derby.
Conditions could not have been more perfect; it was warmer outside the scorebox than …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sun, sea, sand: Fellwanderers hike Pembrokeshire
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-5-sun-sea-sand-fellwanderers-hike-pembrokeshire/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 16:56:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-5-sun-sea-sand-fellwanderers-hike-pembrokeshire/</guid>
        <description>Friday, 24th of May: a rainy day in London, what else would you expect? But 12 brave, hiking loving students were ready to leave for Pembrokeshire, Wales on a Fellwanderers weekend trip. Since it was a bank holiday weekend, it took us quite a while to get to Wales. But by the time we arrived, it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tenpin get bowled over
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-tenpin-get-bowled-over/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 17:50:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-tenpin-get-bowled-over/</guid>
        <description>The British University Tenpin Bowling Association (BUTBA) Cup final against Loughborough, Sheffield, and Portsmouth took place in Rugby last bank holiday Sunday.
In the semi-final, we were matched against our Northern dominant rival, Sheffield. Facing six strong Sheffield bowlers who all had 180-pin …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Checkmate at Chess Congress
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-checkmate-at-chess-congress/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 02:09:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-checkmate-at-chess-congress/</guid>
        <description>On a cool Friday February afternoon a rag-tag team of students (and alumni that can’t seem to get away) gathered in the shadow of the Royal Albert Hall to take a van-load of trestle tables into Imperial College’s Union Dining Hall in preparation for an event that has been a long time coming – the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BUCS points galore for ICBC in Boston
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-bucs-points-galore-for-icbc-in-boston/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 19:28:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-bucs-points-galore-for-icbc-in-boston/</guid>
        <description>ICBC’s high performance contingent made the ever dreary trip to Boston on Saturday 9th February and came out with some good results, hopefully putting them in the mixer for international selection this year. BUCS small boats head was also incorporated into the GB trials, so Imperial athletes were …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Women&#39;s Water Polo can also handle balls pretty well
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-8-womens-water-polo-can-also-handle-balls-pretty-well/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 00:27:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-8-womens-water-polo-can-also-handle-balls-pretty-well/</guid>
        <description>On the morning of January 26th, three Waterpolo girls teams arrived at Imperial from Nottingham, Norwich and Birmingham for a competitive weekend of games against three London-based teams. Our own captain Lil had organized for all the matches of our BUCS league to take place on January 26th and 27th …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Men’s Water Polo handle their balls right
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-8-mens-water-polo-handle-their-balls-right/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 00:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-8-mens-water-polo-handle-their-balls-right/</guid>
        <description>The men’s water polo team are midway through what has already been our most successful season to date. This year we found ourselves in the top division after being promoted last year, along with Warwick, Oxford and Cambridge in what some would call the most intellectual sporting league in the UK. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>High hopes for Handball at Champs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-8-high-hopes-for-handball-at-champs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 00:23:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-8-high-hopes-for-handball-at-champs/</guid>
        <description>Last weekend saw the eagerly anticipated UK universities Handball tournament of the year – the Association of British University Handball Clubs (ABUHC) University Championships 2013. After winning 3rd place in the 2012 tournament and a dedicated start to year for the Imperial Eagles handball club, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICSM Badminton still unbeaten
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-icsm-badminton-still-unbeaten/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 20:57:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-24-icsm-badminton-still-unbeaten/</guid>
        <description>With the highest number of members in the history of the club, it has been one of the most successful years for ICSM Badminton in both team performance and social events. All of our teams have put on their best performance yet with the women’s and mixed doubles’ team currently taking the top spot in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICU Dance salsa to success
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-icu-dance-salsa-to-success/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 03:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-icu-dance-salsa-to-success/</guid>
        <description>As the Imperial Dance team celebrate another success at Nottingham’s Varsity 2012, there’s no better time to learn
This is a little daunting for most people. It was most apparent to me when I attended a wedding recently in which the groomwas unable to lead his wife in a slow waltz. We seem to be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fencers Continue Winning Streak
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-fencers-continue-winning-streak/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 23:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-fencers-continue-winning-streak/</guid>
        <description>Cardiff, Sunday lunch time. Imperial Fencing Women’s 1st park the minibus and make their way through the labyrinth-like venue to find the fencing piste. On the schedule for the day are Oxford and Cardiff University, ranked last and middle of the league respectively. Are the Imperial girls going to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Storming Success for Equestrian Team
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-storming-success-for-equestrian-team/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 23:17:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-storming-success-for-equestrian-team/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Equestrian 1st team had a great start to the season at Royal Holloway’s home competition at Wayside stables near Windsor. Despite the torrential rain and howling winds the team prevailed and won, with individuals placed 1st (Captain Rachel Gregory), 2nd (Liane Marshallsay), 5th …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Runners dominate Luton relays again
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-runners-dominate-luton-relays-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 23:12:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-runners-dominate-luton-relays-again/</guid>
        <description>Last Sunday morning, our four Imperial teams arrived in a sunny but cold Luton, ready to once again dominate the Luton Marathon Relays. Simply put, each relay team consists of three people, each running a third of a marathon.
Accompanying us also were three ‘Old Boys (and girls)’ teams made up of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Shorinji Kempo
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-23-shorinji-kempo/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2012 00:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-23-shorinji-kempo/</guid>
        <description>It is a Sunday morning in Finsbury Park. Unusually for London in November, the sun’s rays play across the city, giving relief from the slight chill in the air. The lack of any discernible tension in the air conceals the fact that the area will soon see the commencing of the 2012 British Shorinji …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fencing avoid the fake tan
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-fencing-avoid-the-fake-tan/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 22:23:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-fencing-avoid-the-fake-tan/</guid>
        <description>Rolling into Essex campus the slightly understrength 3rd team were prepared for a bashing, things started well with Jamie ‘destroyer’ Simpson damaging Essex in the warm-up. Then first up was our foil team of Andy Simpson, Niall Corry and Thoe Suter. Getting us off to a great start was old timers …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Just keep running, running...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-just-keep-running-running/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 23:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-just-keep-running-running/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday 17th October saw 42 runners from Imperial College make the journey to north London to take on the “mountains” of Hampstead Heath. This marked the start of the annual London Colleges Cross Country League, with six races taking place around London over two terms.
A race rich in tradition …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICSM Netball’s storming start to the season
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-icsm-netballs-storming-start-to-the-season/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 23:13:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-icsm-netballs-storming-start-to-the-season/</guid>
        <description>ICSM 5s started their new BUCS season last Wednesday with a convincing win against Roehampton 5s 33-19. It started off as a perfect day for netball, blue skies and with the team showing up perfectly on time, calming their captain’s pre-match jitters. ICSM turned over Roehampton’s first centre-pass …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Knights in shining armour win again!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-knights-in-shining-armour-win-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 23:09:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-knights-in-shining-armour-win-again/</guid>
        <description>It’s a cold Saturday morning as IC Fencing Women’s 1st‘ makes their way over to Oxford. It’s the first weekend out of two, and they’re going to fence Cardiff University, University of Oxford, University of Cambridge and UCL, the other 4 strongest teams in the South of UK. The epee team, first up on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gaelic Football girls score at double header
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-gaelic-football-girls-score-at-double-header/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 23:07:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-gaelic-football-girls-score-at-double-header/</guid>
        <description>How does a division 3 sport’s team respond to the challenge of playing two division 1 standard teams back to back within the one day?
Surely they wouldn’t possibly dream of accepting and should redundantly assume their inevitable defeat? This is not how ICGAC Ladies operate. So on Sunday the 21st …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Mints pot black in Nottingham
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-imperial-mints-pot-black-in-nottingham/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 23:04:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-imperial-mints-pot-black-in-nottingham/</guid>
        <description>Over the weekend of the 27th-28th October the Imperial College English 8 ball pool team began their preparations for BUCS success in February 2013 by participating in the third English Universities Pool Championships in Nottingham. Team Imperial (the so-called ‘Mints’) were confident of success and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Netball 2s continue winning streak
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-netball-2s-continue-winning-streak/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 03:04:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-netball-2s-continue-winning-streak/</guid>
        <description>This week saw a busy week for ICUNC with 8 scheduled games and the first LUSL games of the season.
On Monday evening the 1sts took on QM 1sts away, the game started quite closely but QM started to pull away. Lack of familiarity within the 1sts and small mistakes give plenty to work on in training, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LAX women crush opposition
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-lax-women-crush-opposition/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 03:02:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-lax-women-crush-opposition/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday the 17th, the Imperial Womens’ first team played their first match of the season against Reading. Despite being their first match as a team, Imperial dominated from the first whistle with Ellie Hill scoring the first goal and setting us off to an awesome start.
Defence was on form, with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC Rowers get more golds
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-ic-rowers-get-more-golds/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 02:58:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-ic-rowers-get-more-golds/</guid>
        <description>The Diamond Jubilee Regatta was held over the weekend of the 20-21st October at the scene of the summer’s Olympic rowing frivolities, Dorney Lake. The prospect of a major 2 kilometre sprint event just three weeks into the autumn term struck fear into even the hardiest IC rower. However, despite the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Only Way Is IC Netball
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-the-only-way-is-ic-netball/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:08:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-the-only-way-is-ic-netball/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday the netball first team played Essex 1’s at home in Ethos to kick off their BUCS season. With only 3 returning members no one was quite sure how the team would perform under match pressure and there were a lot of nerves before the first whistle.
The match got off to a shaky start for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC Rowers take on World U23s in Trakai
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-ic-rowers-take-on-world-u23s-in-trakai/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 21:28:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-ic-rowers-take-on-world-u23s-in-trakai/</guid>
        <description>The Under-23 World Championships were held in Trakai, Lithuania between 11th- 15th July. This year medic Tim Richards and biochemist Wilf Kimberley donned the triple hooped vests to represent their country and defend Imperial’s honour which they did in style.
The road to Trakai was by no means easy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Wolverines dodge victory
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-imperial-wolverines-dodge-victory/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 21:19:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-imperial-wolverines-dodge-victory/</guid>
        <description>The Imperial Wolverines had a fantastic start to their season with both teams taking home medals after a suspense-riddled day in Hatfield.
The morning started off in standard fashion, with the Wolverines discovering the endless delays away from Hyde Park due to the Royal Parks half marathon, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mud in Manchester
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-mud-in-manchester/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 20:39:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-mud-in-manchester/</guid>
        <description>After a successful Fresher’s Fair and first run (with a record turnout of 80) Cross Country and Athletics club travelled up to Manchester for our first race of the year. Expecting cold temperatures, mist and rain we were surprised to find ourselves faced with a lovely sunny day!
Birthday boy Sam …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Testing Triathlon waters
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-testing-triathlon-waters/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 20:30:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-testing-triathlon-waters/</guid>
        <description>I joined Imperial’s triathlon club in October 2011, with no real intention of ever competing in any triathlon; all I wanted was to come to the swimming sessions so that I could keep eating pies while a stress fracture healed. But even as Christmas rolled round and my foot went back to working order, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A lemon fresh look at fresher trials
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-a-lemon-fresh-look-at-fresher-trials/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 13:34:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-a-lemon-fresh-look-at-fresher-trials/</guid>
        <description>Women’s Rugby After hiring their new coach Danny last Christmas, Women’s rugby has gone from strength to strength. With 15 freshers turning up to trials Charlotte, The current President, is looking to build on their success last year and get promoted from their current league, BUCS South 2A. Also …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Harvard take a hammering
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-harvard-take-a-hammering/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 13:27:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-harvard-take-a-hammering/</guid>
        <description>As the ICURFC 1st XV arrived for their first match of tour against Harvard it was clear that things in America were going to be a bit different. We were first informed that we would be playing on an artificial rubber crumb pitch rather than grass, and then that the Harvard team were only willing to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First ever Imperial all-ladies bowling team
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-first-ever-imperial-all-ladies-bowling-team/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 22:19:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-first-ever-imperial-all-ladies-bowling-team/</guid>
        <description>Last November, bowlers from Imperial College London competed at the regional BUTBA (British University Tenpin Bowling Association) competition and blazed the lanes, emerging as 1st runners up. Congratulations to Christopher Chan who bowled an average of 211, ranked 2nd overall and to all the other …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Riding 1st team grab league top spot
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-riding-1st-team-grab-league-top-spot/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 23:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Sport,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-riding-1st-team-grab-league-top-spot/</guid>
        <description>The first riding team have moved into first place in their league after an impressive win in Buckinghamshire on Wednesday. Picking up individual 1st 3rd and 7th places, Rachel Gregory, Ilse daly, Sinead Conneely and Mikaela Bryant-Meisner are now in a favourable position with two competitions left, …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
