<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/fbusines/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/fbusines/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>What happens at uni...stays at Unii.com
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-what-happens-at-unistays-at-uniicom/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 15:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Business,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-what-happens-at-unistays-at-uniicom/</guid>
        <description>In 2011, Marco Nardone graduated with a degree in Physics from Imperial College. In just two years, the 25-year-old has become CEO &amp;amp; founder of the UK’s biggest student-only social networking platform, Unii.com.
The journey to becoming a social networking entrepreneur has been exciting, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Facebook celebrity? Looking for a job?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-facebook-celebrity-looking-for-a-job/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 00:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Business,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-facebook-celebrity-looking-for-a-job/</guid>
        <description>The eternal procrastinating tool… Facebook. Or is it? Adzuna, a social job search engine, has developed a way to help you get hired with a little help from your friends. Launched out of a central London pub in July 2011, this small London startup, with over 1.5 million monthly visitors, classifies …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Next Adventure: The Start-up Life
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-the-next-adventure-the-start-up-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 21:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Business,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-the-next-adventure-the-start-up-life/</guid>
        <description>The Next Adventure: Why The Start-Up Life Might Be For You.
It’s a strange thing, the transition from university to the world beyond. For people used to setting their own schedules, to blazing a bit of a trail, to grabbing the talented people around them to embark on a creative project, it can feel …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Gate to an Imperial success story
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-21-the-gate-to-an-imperial-success-story/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 13:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Business,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-21-the-gate-to-an-imperial-success-story/</guid>
        <description>Exams… Library, presentations… Library, coursework&amp;hellip; Library. Being an Imperial College student is usually associated with the “nerdiness” stigma. If you weren’t already one when you got in, the general idea is that by the time you leave, you will have become a super studying sleepless monkey. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Finding your way around the Valley
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-finding-your-way-around-the-valley/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 23:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Business,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-finding-your-way-around-the-valley/</guid>
        <description>When it comes to the crunch explaining what ‘Silicon Valley’ actually represents – ask yourself – do you really have a clear understanding? For most of us, I suppose the influence from popular social media tools and cool high tech gadgets will probably relate us to multinational corporations like …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Entrepreneurs ‘hail’ new app
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-entrepreneurs-hail-new-app/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 02:13:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Business,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-entrepreneurs-hail-new-app/</guid>
        <description>Last Monday, Imperial Entrepreneurs invited the people behind Hailo –The Black Cab App, to its weekly event, Startup Mondays. Russell Hall, one of the co-founders of Hailo spoke to us about their success story and what makes Hailo so popular, to a point that even celebrities and serial entrepreneurs …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Productivity solutions
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-productivity-solutions/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2012 20:38:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Business,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-11-productivity-solutions/</guid>
        <description>Personally, I do not think that procrastination is entirely bad. While we delay the work, we may find out a shortcut or a better way to finish the work in short time. As Aaron Burr wisely said, “Never do today what you can do tomorrow. Something may occur to make you regret your premature action.” …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The UK should adopt the Euro
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-the-uk-should-adopt-the-euro/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 20:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Business,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-the-uk-should-adopt-the-euro/</guid>
        <description>In last Wednesday’s Autumn Statement, George Osborne confirmed that the UK economy’s health was far worse than his office had expected. He blamed the ongoing Eurozone crisis of negatively affecting the UK’s economic growth, by pointing out the negative impact the former had had in our country’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why is the UK economy sinking, too?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-why-is-the-uk-economy-sinking-too/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 20:47:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Business,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-why-is-the-uk-economy-sinking-too/</guid>
        <description>The Eurozone crisis has all the traits of a perfect story: a choral drama with a fuzzy and mistrusted antihero, pompous and obscure villains, few and powerless heroes, and many victims; the plot is so twisted that its outcome remains as mysterious as exciting, and its consequences so open to chance …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Western tragedy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-a-western-tragedy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 19:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Business,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-a-western-tragedy/</guid>
        <description>As a result of the so-called “Euro debt crisis” – whose solution seems to be too distant still to be clear – several of the euro club countries have been bailed out. Starting with Greece (2009), Ireland (2010) and Portugal (2010) have also been rescued, and in all the cases, the process followed a …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
