<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/hjw13/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/hjw13/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>This week on Game of Thrones
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-this-week-on-game-of-thrones/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 09:33:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Harry J A Wilkinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-this-week-on-game-of-thrones/</guid>
        <description>We’re coming up to the final episodes of the second to last season of this show and they apparently still have the time to meander around for an episode with nothing particularly interesting happening. Ah well, here’s a recap anyway.
We open with Lady Crane giving her monologue as Cersei at Joff’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This week on Games of Thrones
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-this-week-on-games-of-thrones/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 08:35:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Harry J A Wilkinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-this-week-on-games-of-thrones/</guid>
        <description>A big reveal this episode, hope you’re ready to board the hype train.
We’re dropped into an unfamiliar, oddly idyllic sequence of some happy villagers building some kind of chapel. This being Game of Thrones, I was half-expecting a dragon to come and burn everyone to a crisp just for being too happy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This week on Games of Thrones
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-this-week-on-games-of-thrones/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 09:24:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Harry J A Wilkinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-this-week-on-games-of-thrones/</guid>
        <description>This week’s episode came with a lot of throwbacks to characters of previous seasons. Hope you’ve got a good memory.
We open with a return to Meera dragging Bran away from the White Walkers (moment of silence for Hodor) while Bran has frantic visions, contrasting the Ice of the White Walkers with the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This week on Game of Thrones
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-this-week-on-game-of-thrones/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 09:24:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Harry J A Wilkinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-this-week-on-game-of-thrones/</guid>
        <description>A third of the way through the season and it’s really starting to get going. We pick up at the Wall where Jon apparently had to pop back into Castle Black after storming off last episode (“Jon you’ll need a coat! You of all people should know winter is coming!”). We then get the first of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This week on Game of Thrones
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-this-week-on-game-of-thrones/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 09:23:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Harry J A Wilkinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-this-week-on-game-of-thrones/</guid>
        <description>Another week, another load of dead characters. We start off where we left last time with Jon Snow wondering what the hell just happened after being stabbed in the heart, Melisandre wondering how on Earth she just did that and Davos trying to remember how he got involved in this storyline in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Weekly Game of Thrones – S6 Episode 1
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-weekly-game-of-thrones-s6-episode-1/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:58:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Harry J A Wilkinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-weekly-game-of-thrones-s6-episode-1/</guid>
        <description>After slapping viewers in the face last season with another huge character death, Game of Thrones returned this week with a relatively uneventful episode, filled with set up for the rest of the season. Spoilers ahead (obviously).
This being the first season to completely overtake the books in nearly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The future of Netflix
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-the-future-of-netflix/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 12:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Harry J A Wilkinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-the-future-of-netflix/</guid>
        <description>Netflix recently has rolled out measures to ban people from using proxies to access their service. What this means for the service’s customers is that you are effectively confined to watching what is available in your own country. This is an issue for subscribers basically anywhere except the US …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cartoon Corner: Bojack Horseman
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-cartoon-corner-bojack-horseman/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2016 12:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Harry J A Wilkinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-5-cartoon-corner-bojack-horseman/</guid>
        <description>Bojack Horseman is a show about an alcoholic horse who was the star of a Cosby-esque family sitcom in the 90s, now dealing with a life of loneliness and depression. Also, it is fantastic.
The Netflix original animated series stars Arrested Development’s Will Arnett, Breaking Bad’s Aaron Paul and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Making a Murderer
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-making-a-murderer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 10:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Harry J A Wilkinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-making-a-murderer/</guid>
        <description>Making a Murderer, released to stream on Netflix in December 2015, is Netflix’s second foray into documentary filmmaking after the mostly ignored Chef’s Table. It has already been described by many as the service’s most addictive program yet.
The series follows the story of Steven Avery, a resident …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
