<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jl4310/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jl4310/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The game best played on the move
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-the-game-best-played-on-the-move/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 21:42:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jacob Lea-Wilson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-the-game-best-played-on-the-move/</guid>
        <description>Launched in London last month was a new online game called Chromaroma. The game is played on the London transport network and utilises your Oyster travel card to gain information regarding your commuting. Players can get points by many different actions but each swipe of your card contributes to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can we simply ‘Ctrl&#43;S’ our past?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-can-we-simply-ctrls-our-past/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 05:58:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jacob Lea-Wilson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-can-we-simply-ctrls-our-past/</guid>
        <description>In 1986 the BBC launched an ambitious campaign to repeat the Domesday Book collection of data in the 11th Century. The information was thought lost, a victim to digital obsolescence which is when a form of data storage becomes unreadable due to outdated technology. Through the perseverance and hard …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Sci-Fi-Brom-Com
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-a-sci-fi-brom-com/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 19:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jacob Lea-Wilson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-a-sci-fi-brom-com/</guid>
        <description>They always said they wanted to do a trilogy of genres. First there was Shaun of the Dead (Rom-Zom-Com) then came Hot Fuzz (Thrill-Com) and now we have Paul (Sci-Fi-Brom-Com). All three have the emphasis placed firmly on the comedy aspect but all have different appealing values. This latest venture …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>EU ends charger nightmare
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-eu-ends-charger-nightmare/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 20:19:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jacob Lea-Wilson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-eu-ends-charger-nightmare/</guid>
        <description>Plans for a universal phone charger for all mobile handsets sold in the EU have gone ahead this week. Manufacturing has already begun by many of the 14 firms that have subscribed to the initiative, which will see a special charging port added to all devices manufactured from now on.
This will help …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Fighter
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-the-fighter/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 20:48:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jacob Lea-Wilson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-the-fighter/</guid>
        <description>Do we really need another boxing film? Can anyone make a film that will better the much loved Rocky? Or a film that is as aesthetically pleasing as Raging Bull, which has the reputation of being so beautiful that each frame could be hung on a wall as a piece of art? Will we ever see a true story …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Make your own iPhone app
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-make-your-own-iphone-app/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 19:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jacob Lea-Wilson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-make-your-own-iphone-app/</guid>
        <description>Chances are you’ve read about the 14-year-old that recently designed a mobile application for the iPhone, which proved to be incredibly popular. So popular in fact it knocked your friend and mine, ‘Angry Birds’, off the top spot to earn the American teenager the position of number 1 free app in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Happy New Year?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-happy-new-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 19:42:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jacob Lea-Wilson,Aditya Narayanan,Guo Heng Chin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-happy-new-year/</guid>
        <description>As another year begins again and starts us off right at the beginning of Oscar season, the Felix Film writers take a look back at the best of cinema in 2010 – in case you were in some kind of year-long coma – and discuss some of our most anticipated films of 2011.
There are three clear frontrunners …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A festive comedy-horror from Finland
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-a-festive-comedy-horror-from-finland/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 20:21:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jacob Lea-Wilson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-a-festive-comedy-horror-from-finland/</guid>
        <description>Bored of the festive season? Bored of mince pies and cold weather? If you’re looking for something different this season, you need not look any further than this Finnish film about an ancient child-eating devil Santa, Rare Exports: A Christmas Tale, which has been slated as this year’s premier …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cannibals and modern family dysfunction
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-cannibals-and-modern-family-dysfunction/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 20:53:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jacob Lea-Wilson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-cannibals-and-modern-family-dysfunction/</guid>
        <description>In 2004 I was travelling in Australia when someone dared me to go to the cinema. The idea was to go to see Super Size Me, the Morgan Spurlock documentary, whilst eating two super-sized McDonald’s Big Mac meals. I succeeded in the challenge although it put me off McDonald’s for the duration of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LTE to the Party. UK lags behind on 4G
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-lte-to-the-party-uk-lags-behind-on-4g/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 20:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jacob Lea-Wilson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-lte-to-the-party-uk-lags-behind-on-4g/</guid>
        <description>We’ve been stuck with 3G (Third Generation) networks in the UK since March 2003. Technology has moved on significantly in the last seven years, but unfortunately we have not. The USA, Japan and most of Europe have already signed deals and are set to have the next generation of mobile networks …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
