<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/calvin_nesbitt/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/calvin_nesbitt/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>ONE: Rough Edged Insights to the State We’re In</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-ONE-rough-edged-insights-state-were-in/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calvin Nesbitt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-ONE-rough-edged-insights-state-were-in/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
Reconciliation, compromise &amp;amp; understanding. These are words one would be hard pushed to find mentioned in modern British political discourse. So evident is their absence that the more hopeless among us may feel they have been forever barred from the British psyche. Here in One, a show …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Death of a Salesman</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-death-of-a-salesman/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calvin Nesbitt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-17-death-of-a-salesman/</guid>
        <description>Arthur Miller’s Death of a Salesman holds a place in the western theatrical collective consciousness that is only occupied by a few other plays. It’s eternally performed, eternally taught, eternally lauded. A play one has probably lied about seeing at some point, not out of some desire to impress, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Folk tales of an anti-facist working-class hero</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-folk-tales-of-an-anti-facist-working-class-hero/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calvin Nesbitt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-15-folk-tales-of-an-anti-facist-working-class-hero/</guid>
        <description>Whilst living in Scotland I learnt that there are few better ways to spend a cold Tuesday night than in one of the many folk bars dotted throughout the country. Here, in the warm atmosphere of ale and brown wood, musicians walk in and out, playing freely, sipping from their pints, waxing lyrics and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Good Dog: Tales of Dignity in the Cauldron of Poverty</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-good-dog-tales-of-dignity-in-the-cauldron-of-poverty/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calvin Nesbitt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-good-dog-tales-of-dignity-in-the-cauldron-of-poverty/</guid>
        <description>Poverty has a drowning effect. Those who are economically oppressed will often find themselves berated for paddling in an overly ferocious manner as they struggle for breath. Whilst the media and large swathes of politicians have failed to give voice to these suffocating communities, many artists …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Tragedy of King Richard the Second</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-the-tragedy-of-king-richard-the-second/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calvin Nesbitt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-11-the-tragedy-of-king-richard-the-second/</guid>
        <description>There has not been a more appropriate time to perform The Tragedy of King Richard the Second. When else in modern British political history have questions of leadership, the right to rule and the role of governance been drawn more into question than now?
When the excellent Simon Russell Beale, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Misty – A rousing one man show taking aim at simplified views of individuals and their lived experiences</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-misty-a-rousing-one-man-show-taking-aim-at-simplified-views-of-individuals-and-their-lived-experiences/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calvin Nesbitt,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-misty-a-rousing-one-man-show-taking-aim-at-simplified-views-of-individuals-and-their-lived-experiences/</guid>
        <description>Never before have the politics of identity demanded a spotlight in the media as they do today. Whilst this is an undoubtedly revelatory and welcome change to western society at large, room for the grey and blurred aspects of our inner selves must be made. Arinze Kené’s searing one man show makes an …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
