<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/wbe15/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/wbe15/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Translations – Mythical Ireland speaks the Common Tongue</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-translations-mythical-ireland-speaks-common-tongue/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Waleed A El-Geresy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-translations-mythical-ireland-speaks-common-tongue/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
Director Ian Rickson’s new production of Brian Fiel’s play Translations is staging at The National Theatre. Set in an 1833 hedge school in Baile Beag (English: Ballybeg), an Irish speaking community in County Donegal, the play explores the lingual boundaries that divide us and define us.
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>La Belle Sauvage: Dust after Darkness</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-la-belle-sauvage-dust-after-darkness/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Waleed A El-Geresy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-la-belle-sauvage-dust-after-darkness/</guid>
        <description>Another year, another Philip Pullman series! Well, not really. The last world-renowned series that Pullman released was His Dark Materials, and what a series it was. But that was all too long ago. Those familiar with His Dark Materials might think of it as the atheist’s take on Narnia. Those who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brexit, greed, and the making of modern Britain</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-brexit-greed-and-the-making-of-modern-britain/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Waleed A El-Geresy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-brexit-greed-and-the-making-of-modern-britain/</guid>
        <description>There is more death in that kind of life and more life in that kind of death. That is the message of Saint George in reference to a life lived under the rule of the despotic dragon. On the face of things these two characters should be at the heart of an epic tale of heroism versus evil, but Rory …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Twelfth Night | A contrast between subtlety and aplomb
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-twelfth-night-a-contrast-between-subtlety-and-aplomb/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 15:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Waleed A El-Geresy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-twelfth-night-a-contrast-between-subtlety-and-aplomb/</guid>
        <description>Going into the National Theatre’s production of Shakespeare’s Twelfth Night, I was expecting a slightly less-conventional production. I was not wrong. Director Simon Godwin is certainly not afraid to show us that this is a modern play from the off, with a flashy display of a shiny car cruising onto …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Macbeth | Breathing new life into Shakespeare
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-macbeth-breathing-new-life-into-shakespeare/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 14:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Waleed A El-Geresy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-macbeth-breathing-new-life-into-shakespeare/</guid>
        <description>Shakespeare for schools is an attempt by director Justin Audibert to bring Shakespeare closer to a ‘younger audience’: school children, especially those who may have been disillusioned by endless GCSE English lessons analysing iambic pentameter, may not have had the chance to step back and simply …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wish List | A harrowing portrait of zero-hours contracts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-wish-list-a-harrowing-portrait-of-zero-hours-contracts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 17:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Waleed A El-Geresy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-wish-list-a-harrowing-portrait-of-zero-hours-contracts/</guid>
        <description>If someone were to wander into the snug stage-room on the top floor of the Royal Court Theatre on Friday evening, if they were lucky enough to enter at the right moment, they might chance upon what appears to be an impromptu, karaoke rendition of Meat Loaf’s I Would Do Anything For Love. A bemusing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Deep Blue Sea at The National
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-the-deep-blue-sea-at-the-national/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 09:30:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Waleed El Geresy,Waleed A El-Geresy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-the-deep-blue-sea-at-the-national/</guid>
        <description>This is the frustrating, and tragic tale of a woman called Hester Collyer. She is, as the title of the play suggests, stuck between a newfound lover and her husband. The play is a strange but intriguing one which explores the difficult relationship the trio shares, centred of course around Hester. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An encounter you won&#39;t forget
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-21-an-encounter-you-wont-forget/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2016 13:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,Waleed El Geresy,Waleed A El-Geresy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-21-an-encounter-you-wont-forget/</guid>
        <description>McBurney’s performance recounts the story of Loren McIntyre– an American photographer who travels into the Amazon rainforest to attempt to capture on film an elusive, indigenous people called the Mayoruna. It quickly becomes apparent however that this story did not happen in the past alone, but is …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
