<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/felixteam/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/felixteam/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial students react to the ECJ&#39;s motion on the banning of religious symbols
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-imperial-students-react-to-the-ecjs-motion-on-the-banning-of-religious-symbols/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 16:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-17-imperial-students-react-to-the-ecjs-motion-on-the-banning-of-religious-symbols/</guid>
        <description> Banning religious symbols is discrimination Hafiza Irshad discusses the recent ruling by the European Court of Justice The triple penalty that Muslim women face – for being a woman, for being a Muslim and often for being of an ethnic minority group – has never been more prominent. Muslim women are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>And the Best Picture Award goes to...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-and-the-best-picture-award-goes-to/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 14:19:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-and-the-best-picture-award-goes-to/</guid>
        <description> Arrival | Cale Tilford&amp;rsquo;s pick With Arrival, Denis Villeneuve has turned a tedious and uninteresting topic – the translation of an alien language – into science-fiction spectacle. From its meticulous sound design to its subdued lighting, the whole film looks and sounds otherworldly. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Drug Bible | Modafinil 101
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-drug-bible-modafinil-101/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 16:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-drug-bible-modafinil-101/</guid>
        <description> What it does Modafinil is used to increase the alertness of the user. Whilst it is normally used to treat narcolepsy and other sleep disorders, it is also commonly used as a study drug. Once taken, expect to feel more awake and typically less prone to frustration, allowing you to become more …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is porn hurting your brain?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-is-porn-hurting-your-brain/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:54:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-is-porn-hurting-your-brain/</guid>
        <description>Last night I masturbated. That’s not particularly exciting in itself – a pretty standard Thursday night – but when I found myself alone in bed looking for some me-time, I automatically reached for my phone for some inspiration. Realising that I didn’t know when I got in this habit, so I decided to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s a queer gal to do/see/watch/listen to? Our guide to your gal-pal culture fix
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-whats-a-queer-gal-to-doseewatchlisten-to-our-guide-to-your-gal-pal-culture-fix/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 15:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-whats-a-queer-gal-to-doseewatchlisten-to-our-guide-to-your-gal-pal-culture-fix/</guid>
        <description> Film Appropriate Behaviour
Desiree Akhavan directs and stars in this comedy about an American-Iranian bisexual going through a breakup. It’ll make you feel worse about your recent breakup but then, strangely, better. It’s pretty funny and feels quite real. The protagonist also struggles with coming …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>That moment you’re rushing on sugar
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-that-moment-youre-rushing-on-sugar/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 18:13:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-that-moment-youre-rushing-on-sugar/</guid>
        <description>The dictionary definition of a drug is either “A medicine or other substance which has a physiological effect when ingested or otherwise introduced to the body” or “A substance taken for its narcotic or stimulant effects”. Each of these definitions are perfectly valid, and classify drugs as having …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Thoughts on the #MuslimBan protests
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-thoughts-on-the-muslimban-protests/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 15:54:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-thoughts-on-the-muslimban-protests/</guid>
        <description> Nora Abdoun (ISoc publicity officer) condemns Theresa May but finds hope in the British people As a Muslim, I was inevitably outraged by Trump’s #MuslimBan. As a British national, I was equally outraged by our government’s complicity with it. For a Prime Minister who claims to lead a country that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Protesting Trump | The Women’s March through the eyes of Imperial students
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-protesting-trump-the-womens-march-through-the-eyes-of-imperial-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 14:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-protesting-trump-the-womens-march-through-the-eyes-of-imperial-students/</guid>
        <description>    Indira Mallik   Ana Villanueva | felix reader I asked myself a question the first time I heard about the Women’s March: Is it necessary? The answer is yes. I joined tens of thousands of people because I needed to share a message too. It was not a complaint. We advocated tolerance and respect for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Aubergines and their many uses
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-aubergines-and-their-many-uses/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:44:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-aubergines-and-their-many-uses/</guid>
        <description>Yes, the aubergine – delicious in dips, smokey and rich, and yet equally at home in a spicy, lip-smacking curry, the aubergine is a vehicle for flavour without compare. I think my love affair began when I would take home small scoops of baba ghanouj, a levantine dip of smoked, roasted aubergine, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Spring term picks | felix’s film editors let you know their top films to look out for
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-spring-term-picks-felixs-film-editors-let-you-know-their-top-films-to-look-out-for/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:37:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-spring-term-picks-felixs-film-editors-let-you-know-their-top-films-to-look-out-for/</guid>
        <description> Christine | Released 27th January Christine tells the harrowing story of Christine Chubbuck, a Florida news anchor who killed herself live on air in 1974. Rebecca Hall takes on the titular character in a powerhouse performance that mines the depths of Chubbuck’s self-destructive tendencies; due to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tossing fruit salad
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-tossing-fruit-salad/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 16:21:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-tossing-fruit-salad/</guid>
        <description> I know that times are tough when you go back home for the holidays. You’ve got used to having your freedom and privacy during term time, and maybe even got used to having a bae that keeps the sexual frustration at bay. Maybe you’ve got used to being able to use that corn-on-the-cob shaped vibrator …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The fight to use LSD for research purposes
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-the-fight-to-use-lsd-for-research-purposes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 16:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-the-fight-to-use-lsd-for-research-purposes/</guid>
        <description>There is evidence that certain psychedelic drugs can ‘reset’ irregular functioning of the brain if administered in a safe and controlled method, thus leading to ground-breaking revelations in medicine. This is perhaps contrary to what you may believe if you have been reading this column for the past …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What makes you more likely to take drugs?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-what-makes-you-more-likely-to-take-drugs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 16:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-what-makes-you-more-likely-to-take-drugs/</guid>
        <description>All people are the same. Or are they? When it comes to drug use it appears they are not, especially according to the catchily-named Home Office document Drug Misuse: Findings from the 2014&amp;frasl;15 Crime Survey for England and Wales. Second edition.
Some of the key findings of the report are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to have a one night stand (in Metric)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-how-to-have-a-one-night-stand-in-metric/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 16:14:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-how-to-have-a-one-night-stand-in-metric/</guid>
        <description> 1 | Preparation If you’re planning on pulling, you need to prepare yourself and your environment. This means making sure that your personal grooming is on point and your fridge is stocked. Sex is 90% preparation, 10% copulation. Good things to have - A clean bathroom - Spare towels (clean spare …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Disabled people are not sexless
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-disabled-people-are-not-sexless/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 15:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-disabled-people-are-not-sexless/</guid>
        <description>Life is hard, and finding our way through the labyrinth of dating, relationships, and sex is one of the hardest and most formidable tasks we face as millennials. One thing that’s usually a given is that we all like sex (unless you’re asexual, which is totally okay, or you make the choice not to have …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Drug Bible | Cocaine
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-drug-bible-cocaine/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 15:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-drug-bible-cocaine/</guid>
        <description> What it does Cocaine is a powerful energising stimulant. Once taken, expect to feel stereotypical effects such as an increased heart rate, sweating, and dilated pupils (that’s right, you will feel your pupils dilate). Cocaine acts by increasing the concentration of serotonin and dopamine in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Masturbation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-masturbation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 14:46:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-masturbation/</guid>
        <description>  Yes, masturbation. We all do it, and those who say they don’t are probably lying. Right? Well, actually, maybe not. The felix Sex Survey reveals that year on year, about 10% of us never indulge in a little self-pleasure, with that number skewed by around a quarter of the women who never polish the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The changing face of drug dealing
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-the-changing-face-of-drug-dealing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 14:42:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-the-changing-face-of-drug-dealing/</guid>
        <description>Traditionally, drugs have been bought by ringing up your friendly neighbourhood dealer. You would agree a time and place to meet, either some shady alley or perhaps one of your houses if you were actually friends. Drugs would then be transacted, for a probably pre-determined price, with the purchase …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Steroids
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-steroids/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 15:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-steroids/</guid>
        <description> Taking advantage of a November Tuesday evening free for coursework deadlines, you head down to Ethos to the gym. You’re in decent shape, feeling good about yourself, and you’re satisfyingly still just about able to hit the same maxes that you could in the summer when you were working out every day. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The politics of pubes
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-the-politics-of-pubes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 15:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-the-politics-of-pubes/</guid>
        <description> Have you ever felt like someone was judging your pubes? Most of us have felt under some pressure to neaten up, groom, or man-scape our bits, but is this a social expectation that we place on ourselves, or do other people actually care about how well maintained we are down there?
When it comes to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Weed | The politics of legalisation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-weed-the-politics-of-legalisation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 15:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Agnese Abrusci,Christopher Haig,Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-weed-the-politics-of-legalisation/</guid>
        <description> USA | Hilary vs. Trump, but does it really make a difference? In the final leg of the presidential debate a few days ago, supporters of Republican nominee Donald Trump started spreading fake memes under the hashtag #StopThePot in an attempt to mislead voters about Democratic presidential nominee …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We asked for your sex stories. This is what we got.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-we-asked-for-your-sex-stories-this-is-what-we-got/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 15:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-we-asked-for-your-sex-stories-this-is-what-we-got/</guid>
        <description> Call me James It’s the day after the 2015 General Election. I, a Labour voter, am heartbroken, and have just spent four hours on a coach to visit my tory-voting then-boyfriend. I’m pleasantly surprised by the lack of gloating and the sex has temporarily taken my mind off of my woes – that is until …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Interviews Felix Editor Candidate: Grace Rahman
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-felix-interviews-felix-editor-candidate-grace-rahman/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 17:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-felix-interviews-felix-editor-candidate-grace-rahman/</guid>
        <description>Voting is now open! Click here to take part now.
Already voted? Take part in our exit poll to tell us who you voted for!
What made you run for this position?
I just love Felix, man.
What is the main change you would like to implement if elected?
Our online presence would be my main priority. At the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Interviews Deputy President (F&amp;S) Candidate: Chris Kaye
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-felix-interviews-deputy-president-fs-candidate-chris-kaye/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 17:29:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-felix-interviews-deputy-president-fs-candidate-chris-kaye/</guid>
        <description>Voting is now open! Click here to take part now.
Already voted? Take part in our exit poll to tell us who you voted for!
What made you run for this position?
I&amp;rsquo;m very keen to use my experience (as both a user and as a trustee) to improve services for all our members. For club &amp;amp; society …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Interviews Deputy President (Welfare) Candidate: Jennifer Watson
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-felix-interviews-deputy-president-welfare-candidate-jennifer-watson/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-felix-interviews-deputy-president-welfare-candidate-jennifer-watson/</guid>
        <description>Voting is now open! Click here to take part now.
Already voted? Take part in our exit poll to tell us who you voted for!
What made you run for this position?
I love being ICSMSU Welfare. Although occasionally emotionally challenging, it’s been incredibly rewarding. I am good at this job. I care for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Interviews Deputy President (Education) Candidate: Chun-yin San
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-5-felix-interviews-deputy-president-education-candidate-chun-yin-san/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 21:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-5-felix-interviews-deputy-president-education-candidate-chun-yin-san/</guid>
        <description>Voting is now open! Click here to take part now.
Already voted? Take part in our exit poll to tell us who you voted for!
What made you run for this position?
I have been a Rep since my first year in College, and I have immensely enjoyed it. It’s one thing just sitting there and complaining about …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Interviews Felix Candidate: Grace Rahman
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-5-felix-interviews-felix-candidate-grace-rahman/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 21:48:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-5-felix-interviews-felix-candidate-grace-rahman/</guid>
        <description>What made you run for this position?
I just love Felix, man.
What is the main change you would like to implement if elected?
Our online presence would be my main priority. At the moment our website isn’t as good as it could be, but we’ve got the content that could make it great. I’m also going to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Interviews Deputy President (Welfare) Candidate: Jennifer Watson
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-5-felix-interviews-deputy-president-welfare-candidate-jennifer-watson/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 21:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-5-felix-interviews-deputy-president-welfare-candidate-jennifer-watson/</guid>
        <description>What made you run for this position?
I love being ICSMSU Welfare. Although occasionally emotionally challenging, it’s been incredibly rewarding. I am good at this job. I care for students and some trust me with their deepest feelings and worries, a privilege and duty I take very seriously. I have a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Interviews Deputy President (F&amp;S) Candidate: Christopher Kaye
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-5-felix-interviews-deputy-president-fs-candidate-christopher-kaye/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 21:39:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-5-felix-interviews-deputy-president-fs-candidate-christopher-kaye/</guid>
        <description>What made you run for this position?
I’m very keen to use my experience (as both a user and as a trustee) to improve services for all our members. For club &amp;amp; society finances and approvals, I want to approach everything with a “how can we get this done” attitude.
What is the main change you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Interviews Deputy President (F&amp;S) Candidate: Elizabeth Campbell
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-5-felix-interviews-deputy-president-fs-candidate-elizabeth-campbell/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 21:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-5-felix-interviews-deputy-president-fs-candidate-elizabeth-campbell/</guid>
        <description>Voting is now open! Click here to take part now.
Already voted? Take part in our exit poll to tell us who you voted for!
What made you run for this position?
In talking to friends on committees I realise that monetary issues and perceived fairness of allocated funds are a major point of contention …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Interviews Deputy President (F&amp;S) Candidate: Ali Lown
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-5-felix-interviews-deputy-president-fs-candidate-ali-lown/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 21:36:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-5-felix-interviews-deputy-president-fs-candidate-ali-lown/</guid>
        <description>Voting is now open! Click here to take part now.
Already voted? Take part in our exit poll to tell us who you voted for!
What made you run for this position?
I’ve been heavily involved in societies all my time at Imperial, and in that time, I’ve been driven crazy by lots of things that could be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Interviews Deputy President (C&amp;S) Candidate: Tom Rivlin
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-5-felix-interviews-deputy-president-cs-candidate-tom-rivlin/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 21:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-5-felix-interviews-deputy-president-cs-candidate-tom-rivlin/</guid>
        <description>Voting is now open! Click here to take part now.
Already voted? Take part in our exit poll to tell us who you voted for!
What made you run for this position?
I’m sure everyone says this, and I’m sure it’s true for them too, but I genuinely love the Union, Imperial College, and the clubs and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Interviews Deputy President (C&amp;S) Candidate: Isabelle Barrett
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-5-felix-interviews-deputy-president-cs-candidate-isabelle-barrett/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 21:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-5-felix-interviews-deputy-president-cs-candidate-isabelle-barrett/</guid>
        <description>What made you run for this position?
There’s a lot more to Imperial than academia. Clubs and societies are an integral part of university life; they give a feeling of achievement, belonging and ultimately happiness, which is crucial for welfare.
I know how the union works with experience from the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Interviews Deputy President (C&amp;S) Candidate: Benjamin Howitt
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-5-felix-interviews-deputy-president-cs-candidate-benjamin-howitt/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 21:29:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-5-felix-interviews-deputy-president-cs-candidate-benjamin-howitt/</guid>
        <description>Voting is now open! Click here to take part now.
Already voted? Take part in our exit poll to tell us who you voted for!
What made you run for this position?
Other than, “I’m a massive Union hack”? I wasn’t in halls for my first year, and that meant almost of my closest friends came from the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Interviews President Candidate: Lucinda Sandon-Allum
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-5-felix-interviews-president-candidate-lucinda-sandon-allum/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 21:27:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-5-felix-interviews-president-candidate-lucinda-sandon-allum/</guid>
        <description>Voting is now open! Click here to take part now.
Already voted? Take part in our exit poll to tell us who you voted for!
What made you run for this position?
Working within the RCSU, as a Constituent Union, has been one of the highlights of my time at Imperial. I also feel the Union has made my time …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix Interviews President Candidate: Luke Armitage
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-5-felix-interviews-president-candidate-luke-armitage/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 21:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-5-felix-interviews-president-candidate-luke-armitage/</guid>
        <description>What made you run for this position?
I knew that I would undeniably win the election, so there seemed to be no other option really. Also, I thought that I would get to meet Kris Kaye.
Also, through concentration, I can raise and lower my cholesterol at will.
What is the main change you would like to …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
