<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/varshit_dusad/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/varshit_dusad/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The dawning of the age of synthetic biology</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-the-dawning-of-the-age-of-synthetic-biology/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Varshit Dusad,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-the-dawning-of-the-age-of-synthetic-biology/</guid>
        <description>Would you like to have a vegan hamburger? Are you concerned with the deteriorating environment? Are you a biology geek eager to explain why biology is cool? The answer to such wide-ranging questions is synthetic biology.
What is synthetic biology? Formally, it is the interdisciplinary science of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bringing in a new era of healthcare data</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-bringing-in-a-new-era-of-healthcare-data/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Varshit Dusad,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-07-bringing-in-a-new-era-of-healthcare-data/</guid>
        <description>GDPR is in full effect, and technology companies are sweating to work out the appropriate strategy to comply with new regulations governing digital data. However, amidst this data frenzy around our web footprint, a new conversation around a different kind of data is taking place: healthcare data! …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Getting down with the kids</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-getting-down-with-the-kids/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Varshit Dusad,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-24-getting-down-with-the-kids/</guid>
        <description>Who doesn’t love chocolate? While you and I might enjoy its taste freely, there are 80,000 children each year who are unable to do so. The reason: they suffer from type 1 diabetes, which manifests itself at an early age. Unlike type 2 diabetes, which comes into effect at an old age, due to the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ready player one – how games are fuelling ‘citizen science’</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-ready-player-one-how-games-are-fuelling-citizen-science/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Varshit Dusad,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-ready-player-one-how-games-are-fuelling-citizen-science/</guid>
        <description>If you were told that the next solution to one of our endearing medical and scientific challenges may be coming from a bunch of computer gamers around the world, your immediate reaction will be one of disbelief. Though it sounds surprising, a computer game called FoldIt has been a beneficial tool in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Understanding apoptosis: the human suicide squad</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-05-understanding-apoptosis-the-human-suicide-squad/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Varshit Dusad,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-05-understanding-apoptosis-the-human-suicide-squad/</guid>
        <description>Are you aware that human cells also have their own version of a suicide squad? This squad comes into action in times of extreme distress, when cells have extinguished all other means to combat their stress. Their call to action means only one thing – destruction of the cells themselves, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Crossing the blood-brain barrier: the final frontier</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-crossing-the-blood-brain-barrier-the-final-frontier/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Varshit Dusad,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-15-crossing-the-blood-brain-barrier-the-final-frontier/</guid>
        <description>Gene therapy serves as a means to introduce artificial DNA into cells, which can then be transcribed and translated into proteins in order to treat various medical conditions. However, there remain many limitations for treating medical conditions associated with the central nervous system. Gene …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How do you solve a problem like planetary mass?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-how-do-you-solve-a-problem-like-planetary-mass/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Varshit Dusad,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-02-how-do-you-solve-a-problem-like-planetary-mass/</guid>
        <description>When Pluto was downgraded from being called a planet, it made you ponder over the criteria for the classification of a planetary object. In reality, the proper definition of a planet is more important than just the semantics. It can provide astronomers finding new celestial objects with a basis of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Say it with DNA – how our genetic code could hold the key to our data storage problems</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-say-it-with-dna-how-our-genetic-code-could-hold-the-key-to-our-data-storage-problems/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Varshit Dusad,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-19-say-it-with-dna-how-our-genetic-code-could-hold-the-key-to-our-data-storage-problems/</guid>
        <description>Data has been hailed as the oil of this century. Just like oil, entire industries rely on data analytics to develop consumer-centric products, which are nowadays in constant demand. Google Search, Facebook Recommendations, and pretty much everything else on the Internet has become part of new ‘Data …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Does the future of organ transplant lie in bioprinting?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-12-does-the-future-of-organ-transplant-lie-in-bioprinting/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Varshit Dusad,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-12-does-the-future-of-organ-transplant-lie-in-bioprinting/</guid>
        <description>Nothing could be more painful for patients and their families than waiting for an organ to save their life. According to latest NHS figures, the average wait time for a kidney transplant is 944 days – despite a significant decrease from 1,153 days previously, two and a half years is a long time to …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
