<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Longread on Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/highlights/longread/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Longread on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/highlights/longread/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Getting to the truth of Jasper Johns
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-22-getting-to-the-truth-of-jasper-johns/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 18:56:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-9-22-getting-to-the-truth-of-jasper-johns/</guid>
        <description>On the way out of the press viewing of the Royal Academy&amp;rsquo;s latest exhibition, Jasper Johns: ‘Something Resembling Truth’, an immense monograph of the titan of 20th century American art, I overhear a fragment of a conversation: “and when did he die?”
Johns is still going strong, but it is an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cooked breakfast removed from SCR menu amid wide-ranging changes to campus services
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-26-cooked-breakfast-removed-from-scr-menu-amid-wide-ranging-changes-to-campus-services/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2017 14:02:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-26-cooked-breakfast-removed-from-scr-menu-amid-wide-ranging-changes-to-campus-services/</guid>
        <description> On the 31st July, the Senior Common Room (SCR) served its last cooked breakfast to Imperial College London staff and students. From the 1st August, the SCR has removed cooked breakfasts from its menu as part of a wide-ranging series of changes to campus services, affecting a number of areas.
As …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>National Student Survey results reveal wide ranges in student satisfaction
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-25-national-student-survey-results-reveal-wide-ranges-in-student-satisfaction/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 10:26:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-25-national-student-survey-results-reveal-wide-ranges-in-student-satisfaction/</guid>
        <description> The results from the National Student Survey (NSS), which saw a number of universities omitted following a boycott, show a divide among Imperial students, with a wide range in satisfaction rates between undergraduate courses.
The survey, which is given to all final-year undergraduates, showed that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial student halls fail fire safety tests on cladding
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-9-imperial-student-halls-fail-fire-safety-tests-on-cladding/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 09:48:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-9-imperial-student-halls-fail-fire-safety-tests-on-cladding/</guid>
        <description>The cladding system used in Woodward Buildings, one of Imperial College London’s newly-built student halls, has failed governmental fire safety testing. Sources from inside the hall also report multiple failures to adhere to fire safety policy, Felix can reveal.
The results of the tests were …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Eurovision Song Contest: The pop and the politics*
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-7-eurovision-song-contest-the-pop-and-the-politics/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 08:55:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-8-7-eurovision-song-contest-the-pop-and-the-politics/</guid>
        <description> I once had the misfortune of watching Eurovision with only an Argentinian, a Mexican, and a Lebanese for company. If you’re not European (or Australian, apparently), Eurovision seems to be very confusing and completely un-understandable. For us Europeans, either on the mainland or stuck on little …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>E3 2017 | Follow up
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-e3-2017-follow-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 17:06:02 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Qasim Mahmood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-e3-2017-follow-up/</guid>
        <description>Microsoft had a few more reveals, including PlayerUnknown’s Battlegrounds, State of Decay 2, Minecraft in 4K and DragonBall FighterZ. They then proceeded to an extended look at Sea of Thieves, Rare’s open-world pirate game, which featured treasure hunting, riddle solving and a large-scale naval …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Swet Shop Boys | Rap heroes of our time
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-swet-shop-boys-rap-heroes-of-our-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 17:01:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-swet-shop-boys-rap-heroes-of-our-time/</guid>
        <description>On the first of June, midway through his set, Riz Ahmed signalled for the sold-out crowd at Scala to quiet down. Leaning in close, unaccompanied by music, he rapped his 2011 single Sour Times; “Please allow me to vouch for mine…/ losing my religion to tomorrow’s headlines”. It had been exactly a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Three years after my roommate’s death I’m ready to move on
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-three-years-after-my-roommates-death-im-ready-to-move-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:56:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jonathan Masters,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-three-years-after-my-roommates-death-im-ready-to-move-on/</guid>
        <description>A few weeks ago I finally came to the end of my three year course at Imperial, and although it is a cliché, the time has simply flown by. As I handed in the final final final draft of my undergraduate dissertation into turnitin, I suddenly burst into tears. Now it could have been a combination of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Abuse is not a valid comment
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-abuse-is-not-a-valid-comment/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:45:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-abuse-is-not-a-valid-comment/</guid>
        <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been writing and editing Comment for felix for years, and it’s my strongly held opinion that a student newspaper without opinion is not a student newspaper worth having. University is a time when we’re all growing up, finding ourselves and forming our beliefs, and a huge part of this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Soul of a Nation | A searing portrait of the Civil Rights Era
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-23-soul-of-a-nation-a-searing-portrait-of-the-civil-rights-era/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 12:13:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-23-soul-of-a-nation-a-searing-portrait-of-the-civil-rights-era/</guid>
        <description>“Is there a black aesthetic, and if there is, what form does it take?” is the question that concerns the artists assembled for Soul of a Nation. For some, like the Spiral collective, the answer lay in monochrome paintings with a strong political message. In Norman Lewis’ America the Beautiful, a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Swet Shop Boys | Rap heroes for our time
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-15-swet-shop-boys-rap-heroes-for-our-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 17:13:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-15-swet-shop-boys-rap-heroes-for-our-time/</guid>
        <description>On the first of June, midway through his set, Riz Ahmed signalled for the sold-out crowd at Scala to quieten down. Leaning in close, unaccompanied by music, he rapped his 2011 single Sour Times; “Please allow me to vouch for mine…/ losing my religion to tomorrow’s headlines”. It had been exactly a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Queer British Art (1861-1967) | Ostracised, criminalised, but never conquered
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-15-queer-british-art-1861-1967-ostracised-criminalised-but-never-conquered/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 15:59:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-15-queer-british-art-1861-1967-ostracised-criminalised-but-never-conquered/</guid>
        <description>Little rainbows have been popping up everywhere lately - on Facebook, in Skittles adverts, soon they’ll arriving on London’s streets. In fact, the rainbow flag has been flying over Tate Britain for some months now. The gallery will be kicking off the London Pride celebrations next Saturday with a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Summer Exhibition at the Royal Academy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-15-the-summer-exhibition-at-the-royal-academy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 15:17:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-15-the-summer-exhibition-at-the-royal-academy/</guid>
        <description>There aren’t many galleries in which you might expect to see a multimillion pound creation by a Turner prize winning artist exhibited on equal footing with an oil by Joe Bloggs from Surrey, but that is exactly what the Royal Academy’s Summer Exhibition offers. Each year, tens of thousands of works …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to dump someone (you met in Metric and subsequently fell in love with)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-how-to-dump-someone-you-met-in-metric-and-subsequently-fell-in-love-with/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 16:16:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Theresa Davey,Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-how-to-dump-someone-you-met-in-metric-and-subsequently-fell-in-love-with/</guid>
        <description> You were weak. Despite our foolproof guides on how to have a one night stand (in Metric), ‘How to have a one night stand (in Metric)’, and how not to fall in love with someone (from Metric), ‘How not to fall in love with someone (from Metric)’, you went ahead and fell in love with someone (from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The great age of the 3DS
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-the-great-age-of-the-3ds/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 15:25:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Saad Ahmed,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-the-great-age-of-the-3ds/</guid>
        <description> The 3DS has been the go-to portable games machine of its time, testified by the sales of over 65 million units, and is a shining example of how to make a perfect handheld console. Its only other portable rival, the Playstation Vita is as good as dead these days, and mobile games don’t even come …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial academics on Trump and climate
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-imperial-academics-on-trump-and-climate/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 14:48:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-imperial-academics-on-trump-and-climate/</guid>
        <description>Last week Trump declared to the world that he’d be pulling the US out of the Paris Agreement. Within hours, Elon Musk resigned from the President’s Board of Advisors, American states such as California went rogue and protested the move, vouching to uphold their commitment anyway, and world leaders …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why I’m voting Labour
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-why-im-voting-labour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 14:16:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Abhijay Sood,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-why-im-voting-labour/</guid>
        <description>Soft on security, denying the deficit, and incapable of addressing concerns over immigration. These sound like the sort of accusations the Conservatives levelled at the last Labour government not too long ago, and yet after seven years in government, these are all areas in which the Conservative …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Manifesto breakdowns
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-manifesto-breakdowns/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:59:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,Cale E Tilford,Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-manifesto-breakdowns/</guid>
        <description> This piece aims to break down the main party manifestos and summarise a few key policies. This is by no means a full and in-depth analysis of each party. Mainly because the manifestos are long and complex, and it’s exam season. [Insert tinfoil hat theory that the timing of the election coincides …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An idiot’s guide to the UK general election
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-an-idiots-guide-to-the-uk-general-election/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:57:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-an-idiots-guide-to-the-uk-general-election/</guid>
        <description>Ding ding ding, it’s election time again. No, you haven’t woken up from that nap in 2020, they’ve called an early election. Do you have no idea who you’re voting for? Well, you’re in luck my friend, because we’ve got a whole pull-out complete with manifesto breakdowns, and personal views on who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Party candidates come to Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-party-candidates-come-to-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:50:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Joanna Wormald,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-party-candidates-come-to-imperial/</guid>
        <description>A hustings of local parliamentary candidates was held yesterday in Blackett which saw Victoria Borwick (Conservatives), Cllr Alan De’Ath (Labour), Bridget Fox (LibDems), Richard Braine (UKIP), and finally Bill Cashmore (Green), engaging in a debate on Education, Public Health and Brexit.
Borwick, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Afterhours sessions in the Central Library
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-afterhours-sessions-in-the-central-library/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:29:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-afterhours-sessions-in-the-central-library/</guid>
        <description>How does one end up in the Library past midnight? Maybe you had a paper to submit tomorrow. You thought you had everything under control. You were halfway there but you made the mistake of taking a break and committing to an episode of the Great British Bake Off. Six hours later you get a text from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All shall love me in despair
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-all-shall-love-me-in-despair/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 12:51:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Shaul Rosten,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-all-shall-love-me-in-despair/</guid>
        <description>As we move, it seems inevitably, towards a Theresa May-led government, let&amp;rsquo;s take a moment to think about the fallout for the political landscape of the future. Leaving aside the speculations as to the potential success of Mrs. May as future PM, consider what will be left wilting on the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Twelfth Night at the Globe | Emma Rice remixes Shakespeare with disco anthems and glittery fun
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-31-twelfth-night-at-the-globe-emma-rice-remixes-shakespeare-with-disco-anthems-and-glittery-fun/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 23:02:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-31-twelfth-night-at-the-globe-emma-rice-remixes-shakespeare-with-disco-anthems-and-glittery-fun/</guid>
        <description>When last season, Emma Rice was appointed artistic director, the Globe seemed to set a new course. Her tenure would mean the company would no longer be focused simply on conservation of Shakespeare but on mutation and adaptation of the classic texts for a modern audience. Yet, this, only her second …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Xavier Dolan | In praise of popular art
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-xavier-dolan-in-praise-of-popular-art/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 17:21:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Leo Diaz,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-xavier-dolan-in-praise-of-popular-art/</guid>
        <description>Xavier Dolan is not your average director. What first sets him apart is that he is extremely young: 28 at the time of writing, he’s already released six full-length features. He directed his first, I Killed My Mother, when he was just 20, and his 2014 Mommy received the Jury Prize at Cannes, along …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>More Life by Drake
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-more-life-by-drake/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 16:24:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-more-life-by-drake/</guid>
        <description>After countless delays (something which is seemingly becoming an unfortunate feature of all Drake releases these days), More Life was finally released on 18th March. My excitement was palpable to say the least. In my opinion, Drake’s work often falls victim to his own procrastination and hype, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Divestment has worked before, and will work again
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-divestment-has-worked-before-and-will-work-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 15:57:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Conor O&#39;Riordan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-divestment-has-worked-before-and-will-work-again/</guid>
        <description>As the threat of climate change continues to loom large over society, activists are turning to more creative methods to encourage the large-scale change that we urgently need. Where traditional political methods have failed, divestment is now making serious progress on university campuses, in city …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Roman Tragedies: A medieval masterpiece for a Facebook Live world
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-20-roman-tragedies-a-medieval-masterpiece-for-a-facebook-live-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 21:36:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adam Gellatly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-20-roman-tragedies-a-medieval-masterpiece-for-a-facebook-live-world/</guid>
        <description>Enobarbus is a dying man. So overcome with grief at having betrayed his closest friend, Mark Antony, to Octavius Caesar, he can no longer bear to live. His cries and pleas for forgiveness are translated from Dutch to English courtesy of surtitles. A cameraman follows him as he stumbles across the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let’s talk about Drugs #realtalk
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-lets-talk-about-drugs-realtalk/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 14:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,David Charchoglyan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-10-lets-talk-about-drugs-realtalk/</guid>
        <description>Do you know why some drugs are called ‘Drugs’ with a capital D? Or why your school was so eager to drill into you that some things are bad no-questions-asked-because-I-said-so during those insufferable PSHE lessons? Why some substances are kept completely out of our reach and have a seven year …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gang Signs and Prayer
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-gang-signs-and-prayer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 15:24:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-gang-signs-and-prayer/</guid>
        <description>Over recent years, the UK grime and urban scene has had a renaissance and one man has been at the forefront of this wave – the WickedSkengMan live in the flesh, Stormzy (Michael Omari Jr.) In addition to his raw musical talent, Stormzy’s omnipresence on social media: uploading daily Snapchat …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Twelfth Night | A contrast between subtlety and aplomb
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-twelfth-night-a-contrast-between-subtlety-and-aplomb/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 15:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Waleed A El-Geresy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-3-3-twelfth-night-a-contrast-between-subtlety-and-aplomb/</guid>
        <description>Going into the National Theatre’s production of Shakespeare’s Twelfth Night, I was expecting a slightly less-conventional production. I was not wrong. Director Simon Godwin is certainly not afraid to show us that this is a modern play from the off, with a flashy display of a shiny car cruising onto …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NeighbourHOOD Grammys 2016
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-neighbourhood-grammys-2016/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 14:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-neighbourhood-grammys-2016/</guid>
        <description> Album of the year The Life of Pablo, Kanye West [aka Yeezus] “We on an Ultralight Beam… This is a God dream… This is everything.”
Despite the unprecedented commercial success of Views, the committee came to the decision that Drizzy simply has to come harder than he did on this album to be deserving …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>And the Best Picture Award goes to...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-and-the-best-picture-award-goes-to/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 14:19:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-and-the-best-picture-award-goes-to/</guid>
        <description> Arrival | Cale Tilford&amp;rsquo;s pick With Arrival, Denis Villeneuve has turned a tedious and uninteresting topic – the translation of an alien language – into science-fiction spectacle. From its meticulous sound design to its subdued lighting, the whole film looks and sounds otherworldly. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Moonlight | A miraculous masterpiece
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-moonlight-a-miraculous-masterpiece/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 14:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-moonlight-a-miraculous-masterpiece/</guid>
        <description>In Barry Jenkins’ masterful film Moonlight, the coming of age of a gay, black man is compressed down into a mere 111 minutes, distilled for your viewing pleasure.
Nearly split into three sections – revealing the structure of the play upon which it is based, Tarell McCrary’s In Moonlight Black Boys …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Postgraduate study is wrought with classist undertones
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-postgraduate-study-is-wrought-with-classist-undertones/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 14:37:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-postgraduate-study-is-wrought-with-classist-undertones/</guid>
        <description>The UK has a vast historic class divide – only those from the upper-middle classes who are in severe denial about our country would go so far as to say that class does not remain a huge cultural barrier today. Education has traditionally been something for the rich, and our modern higher education …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Patriots leave it late to secure historic win
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-patriots-leave-it-late-to-secure-historic-win/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 16:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Imraj Singh,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-patriots-leave-it-late-to-secure-historic-win/</guid>
        <description>Super bowl came about due to a merger agreement between two of the rival American football leagues the AFL (American Football league) and the NFL (National football league). This became official in 1970 when the NFL we all know and love was created. At that time there were only 26 teams, the rest …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s a queer gal to do/see/watch/listen to? Our guide to your gal-pal culture fix
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-whats-a-queer-gal-to-doseewatchlisten-to-our-guide-to-your-gal-pal-culture-fix/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 15:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-whats-a-queer-gal-to-doseewatchlisten-to-our-guide-to-your-gal-pal-culture-fix/</guid>
        <description> Film Appropriate Behaviour
Desiree Akhavan directs and stars in this comedy about an American-Iranian bisexual going through a breakup. It’ll make you feel worse about your recent breakup but then, strangely, better. It’s pretty funny and feels quite real. The protagonist also struggles with coming …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Being non-binary at Imperial is not fun
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-being-non-binary-at-imperial-is-not-fun/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 14:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-being-non-binary-at-imperial-is-not-fun/</guid>
        <description>There is a misconception held by many queer secondary school students that universities are very progressive and tolerant places. The It gets better project is all but built on this idea promoted by society that it’s okay if times are tough now, because one day you will escape your small town. You …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All hail the sublime starch, the chieftan of cuisine, the triumphant tuber | the potato
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-all-hail-the-sublime-starch-the-chieftan-of-cuisine-the-triumphant-tuber-the-potato/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 17:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanjay Bhattacharya,Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-all-hail-the-sublime-starch-the-chieftan-of-cuisine-the-triumphant-tuber-the-potato/</guid>
        <description> The humble spud. Where to start? How many foodstuffs can compare to the tuber that brought a whole nation to its knees – and I’m not talking about the Irish potato famine, but rather the introduction of potatoes to haute cuisine. People had been searching for a starch that was affordable yet …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>La Traviata
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-la-traviata/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 17:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-la-traviata/</guid>
        <description>An exhibition of harlotry upon the public stage!” denounced The Times when La Traviata was first staged in London in 1856. Although it is now the most frequently staged opera worldwide, La Traviata’s beginnings were plagued by stern censorship and moral outrage. That a common prostitute should be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Christine | On the outside looking in
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-christine-on-the-outside-looking-in/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 16:48:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-christine-on-the-outside-looking-in/</guid>
        <description>The television, with its ability to repeatedly display the images of those who have long since departed, can act as an electronic graveyard, conjuring up spirits from the past. It is fitting, therefore, that Christine – the latest film by Antonio Campos, which deals with the on-air suicide of news …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Thoughts on the #MuslimBan protests
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-thoughts-on-the-muslimban-protests/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 15:54:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-thoughts-on-the-muslimban-protests/</guid>
        <description> Nora Abdoun (ISoc publicity officer) condemns Theresa May but finds hope in the British people As a Muslim, I was inevitably outraged by Trump’s #MuslimBan. As a British national, I was equally outraged by our government’s complicity with it. For a Prime Minister who claims to lead a country that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Students take to the streets to protest Trump | Are the days of political apathy over?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-students-take-to-the-streets-to-protest-trump-are-the-days-of-political-apathy-over/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 15:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-students-take-to-the-streets-to-protest-trump-are-the-days-of-political-apathy-over/</guid>
        <description>Donald Trump has consistently been on the collective consciousness for a while. Though Trump’s presidency could globally affect climate change and human rights, to name only a few areas of concern, amongst some journalistic circles, there’s the additional concern that the international focus on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Israeli ambassador’s secret visit to Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-israeli-ambassadors-secret-visit-to-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 14:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-israeli-ambassadors-secret-visit-to-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Last week the Israeli Ambassador to Britain, Mark Regev visited Imperial College, giving a talk in the Clore Lecture Theatre in Huxley Building. The talk, for which publicity was incredibly limited, was attended by around 200 students and was shrouded in secrecy right up until the very last moment. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Most anticipated hip-hop albums of 2017
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-most-anticipated-hip-hop-albums-of-2017/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 16:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-most-anticipated-hip-hop-albums-of-2017/</guid>
        <description> 10. Lil Wayne | Tha Carter V Cast your mind back to June 2008. Lil Wayne and Birdman were still best mates and Wayne had just dropped his critically acclaimed sixth studio album, including four top 20 singles, and went on to be Wayne’s most successful to date, selling 3.6 million copies and winning …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Our Academy Award #hottake
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-our-academy-award-hottake/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 16:46:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-27-our-academy-award-hottake/</guid>
        <description>The announcement of the nominees for the 89th Academy Awards this week marked the beginning of the end of the year-long awards process, which begins with the Cannes Film Festival in May, and ends with the Oscars, 8 months later. As usual, the list of nominees contains few surprises, with the Academy …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How not to fall in love with someone (from Metric)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-how-not-to-fall-in-love-with-someone-from-metric/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Theresa Davey,Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-how-not-to-fall-in-love-with-someone-from-metric/</guid>
        <description> This is a follow up to our piece ‘How to have a one night stand (in Metric)’. For those of you who somehow missed it, we provided a tried-and-tested plan of action designed to get you laid after a night in Metric. This plan was meant to get you in and out without leaving any trace. But expectedly, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A series of final problems | Sherlock
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-a-series-of-final-problems-sherlock/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-a-series-of-final-problems-sherlock/</guid>
        <description>In 2010 when Sherlock was first introduced to the world as Arthur Conan Doyle’s great detective being brought into the 21st century, co-creator Steven Moffat explained his motivations in making the series to Premium Hollywood thus: “This wasn’t a case of, ‘Let’s grab that off the shelf and update …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Basic food for basic students (you’re basic)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-basic-food-for-basic-students-youre-basic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 14:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-13-basic-food-for-basic-students-youre-basic/</guid>
        <description>For many of us, it’s revision week time! Yay!! Can you feel the enthusiasm? I can feel it all around campus – especially in the library late at night or when I see some girl crying in the bathroom; I’m not saying that men do not cry in the bathroom, but I for one cannot see them – the perks of using …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tossing fruit salad
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-tossing-fruit-salad/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 16:21:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Team,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-tossing-fruit-salad/</guid>
        <description> I know that times are tough when you go back home for the holidays. You’ve got used to having your freedom and privacy during term time, and maybe even got used to having a bae that keeps the sexual frustration at bay. Maybe you’ve got used to being able to use that corn-on-the-cob shaped vibrator …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to build Hogwarts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-how-to-build-hogwarts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 16:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-how-to-build-hogwarts/</guid>
        <description> 2009 | The first gingerbread We weren’t ambitious. We built a cute little gingerbread house. It only took one batch of gingerbread and a few sweets for decoration, and it disappeared remarkably quickly. How things were to change!
2010 | The castle This took two whole batches of gingerbread. We …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A seat at the (culture) roundtable
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-a-seat-at-the-culture-roundtable/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 15:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-a-seat-at-the-culture-roundtable/</guid>
        <description>During the American election cycle on his comedy show Last Week Tonight, John Oliver had a running gag – “look up,” he’d say “that faint glimmer in the distance? That’s rock bottom.” So it has seemed for most of 2016; in almost every sphere, particularly in politics, bad news has been followed by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Andy’s Top 10 hip-hop albums of 2016
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-andys-top-10-hip-hop-albums-of-2016/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 14:57:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andy Djaba,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-andys-top-10-hip-hop-albums-of-2016/</guid>
        <description> 10. Kendrick Lamar | “Untitled Unmastered” In March Kendrick surprised fans with a compilation of unused demos recorded during the making of 2015’s To Pimp a Butterfly, his 3rd studio album. Kendrick previewed three of the tracks on late night talk shows throughout 2015 and during his performance …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your favourite films of 2016
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-your-favourite-films-of-2016/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 14:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Film,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-your-favourite-films-of-2016/</guid>
        <description> Alex Heib, Max Lewis-Clarke and Meryl Anil 1. Arrival Intelligent sci-fi films are rare, with ones involving aliens rarer still. Arrival uses these foreign beings to examine how language shapes our view of the world, how it can be the source of conflict but also how it can be the solution. This …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An idiot’s guide to 2016
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-an-idiots-guide-to-2016/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 14:28:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-an-idiots-guide-to-2016/</guid>
        <description> It’s been a rollercoaster ride. Except a rollercoaster ride where you threw up on yourself at the start. But, let’s take a trip down memory lane; there are a few nuggets of joy to be found amongst the pile of crap that was 2016. Promise.
January So it didn’t really get off to the best of starts did …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The disquieting strangeness of Blue Velvet
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-the-disquieting-strangeness-of-blue-velvet/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 15:51:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-the-disquieting-strangeness-of-blue-velvet/</guid>
        <description>Degraded, slapped around, humiliated and undressed in front of the camera” wrote Roger Ebert, esteemed American film reviewer, of Isabella Rossellini’s performance in David Lynch’s 1986 film Blue Velvet. “When you ask an actress to endure those experiences, you should keep your side of the bargain …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>felix talks NSS and Imperial’s teaching strategy plans with VP for Education
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-felix-talks-nss-and-imperials-teaching-strategy-plans-with-vp-for-education/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 15:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-felix-talks-nss-and-imperials-teaching-strategy-plans-with-vp-for-education/</guid>
        <description>So I guess we should probably start by welcoming you to Imperial. How are you finding it so far?
It’s amazing, I’m having a great time. It’s the best job I’ve had ever I think, at least that’s what it feels like right now, it’s only been four months. There’s a lot that needs to be done, which of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chocolate, Christmas and Cheese
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-chocolate-christmas-and-cheese/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 11:47:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-9-chocolate-christmas-and-cheese/</guid>
        <description>If rolling in cash and taking baths in champagne in a mansion in Saint-Jean-Cap-Ferrat is your lifetime goal, may I suggest a better alternative: earning an OBE for “services to chocolate”.
Why did I suddenly draw light to this matter? All after an inspiring evening of chocolate with Chantal Coady …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Paralympians achieve legendary status but who was there to witness history in the making ?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-paralympians-achieve-legendary-status-but-who-was-there-to-witness-history-in-the-making-/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 16:48:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Beng Tan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-paralympians-achieve-legendary-status-but-who-was-there-to-witness-history-in-the-making-/</guid>
        <description>The partying and fireworks on a wet, rainy night in and around the Maracanã Stadium marked the grand finale of the biggest sporting showpiece of the year and brought a happy ending to two weeks full of sweat, grit, determination, tension, sportsmanship, joy, tears, more sportsmanship and the very …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Interview | David Henson MBE
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-interview-david-henson-mbe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 16:40:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sam Smith,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-interview-david-henson-mbe/</guid>
        <description>I struggle to get out of bed some mornings. OK, most mornings. OK, OK, I’m still in bed watching Jeremy Kyle yell at someone for having 3 wives and 1 kid whom they all swear is theirs, but we’ve gone off topic. Seeing as this is ‘disability week’ I figured I should talk to someone who knows enough …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Return to Stars Hollow | Gilmore Girls
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-a-return-to-stars-hollow-gilmore-girls/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 15:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-2-a-return-to-stars-hollow-gilmore-girls/</guid>
        <description>Reviving beloved TV shows can be a tricky business. Shows that are missed tend to build up a mythology around them; with time and absence, every fault and inconsistency is forgiven. To bring them back, however, is to burst the rose tinted bubble of fond nostalgia and push them into the harsh lens of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Four hours of tapas-style dining later
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-four-hours-of-tapas-style-dining-later/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 14:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-four-hours-of-tapas-style-dining-later/</guid>
        <description>Sometimes I wish I could duplicate myself. One to go to those dreaded 9am lectures, one to do the laundry and one to tend to the exploding experiments in the lab. And at the end of the day, we can all gather and dine at one of the many restaurants on my to-visit list. There’s nothing wrong with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>VP Education kicks off teaching consultations
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-vp-education-kicks-off-teaching-consultations/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 13:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-25-vp-education-kicks-off-teaching-consultations/</guid>
        <description>Imperial launched its College-wide consultation on the Learning and Teaching Strategy this Wednesday with a Town Hall meeting which saw Vice-Provost of Education, Simone Buitendijk, address the issues raised by Imperial’s disappointing NSS scores. “All of us know that student experience isn’t …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ante Up | a new age of hip hop
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-ante-up-a-new-age-of-hip-hop/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 15:42:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Mazen Almaskati,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-ante-up-a-new-age-of-hip-hop/</guid>
        <description>For a form of music so deeply rooted in a culture of self-certainty and dazzling bravado, you might not expect artists of the genre to be tackling sensitive issues relating to isolation, depression, violence and substance abuse. This however, is exactly what we’ve seen take place with fresh new …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cohen’s light has gone dark, but the night will not have him
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-cohens-light-has-gone-dark-but-the-night-will-not-have-him/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 15:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Adam Gellatly,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-cohens-light-has-gone-dark-but-the-night-will-not-have-him/</guid>
        <description>This is not strictly a review. Given the circumstances it can’t be. Instead, it is a look at how an album takes on a new life when its creator passes away so shortly after its release – or, more appropriately, how an album allows for the continuation of a life that is no more. If you read …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Four Horsemen of the Trumpocalypse
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-the-four-horsemen-of-the-trumpocalypse/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 14:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-18-the-four-horsemen-of-the-trumpocalypse/</guid>
        <description>Last Wednesday the world woke to darkness – a fascist, misogynistic, anti-semitic, Islamophobic, racist, sexual assaulter who has called Mexicans rapists, made fun of a reporter’s disability, praised every dictator under the sun from Putin to Kim Jong-Un, ridiculed the heroism of prisoners of war, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Overpopulation | Is it a myth? Is it inevitable? Should we be worried?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-overpopulation-is-it-a-myth-is-it-inevitable-should-we-be-worried/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 16:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jawaad Farooq,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-overpopulation-is-it-a-myth-is-it-inevitable-should-we-be-worried/</guid>
        <description>On watching Dan Brown’s Inferno this weekend, the question of how we would survive overpopulation struck a chord with me. It may have been a slightly dull film at times but the theme nevertheless was a relevant and intriguing one. Essentially, a billionaire concerned with overpopulation creates a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Women in sci-fi | A space oddity?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-women-in-sci-fi-a-space-oddity/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 13:44:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-women-in-sci-fi-a-space-oddity/</guid>
        <description>Around the halfway point of Denis Villeneuve’s latest sci-fi thriller Arrival, which touches down this week, I found myself questioning the circular nature of time. But while the film itself – with its focus on language, neurology, and chronology – does try and upset our conventionally-held notions …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Girls Can do without Sport Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-imperial-girls-can-do-without-sport-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 14:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-imperial-girls-can-do-without-sport-imperial/</guid>
        <description>There are a lot of things that Imperial girls can do, including studying science and engineering, leading clubs and societies, and, presumably, going through adolescence, meaning that by the time we’re at Imperial, we’re probably women, not girls. But one area where we seem to be lacking, according …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In defence of ‘nasty women’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-in-defence-of-nasty-women/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 14:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Andrada Balmez,Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-in-defence-of-nasty-women/</guid>
        <description>On the evening of the 19th October, at the University of Nevada’s Las Vegas campus, the phrase ‘nasty woman’ entered the internet’s lexicon. These words were uttered by Donald Trump towards the end of the third and final election debate, in a contest that has been defined by mud-slinging, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A beginner’s guide to Denis Villeneuve
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-a-beginners-guide-to-denis-villeneuve/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 14:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Tom Stephens,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-a-beginners-guide-to-denis-villeneuve/</guid>
        <description>Hugh Jackman –was it as scary to work with him in Prisoners as it looked? What the were all the spiders about in Enemy? And how the hell do you pronounce that last name?! There are many questions we’d love to ask Denis Villeneuve, the man who’s gone from abduction drama to existential horror to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wildlife photographer of the year 2016
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-wildlife-photographer-of-the-year-2016/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 12:45:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Madeleine Webb,George Brooks,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-4-wildlife-photographer-of-the-year-2016/</guid>
        <description>Tucked away in a quiet corner of the Natural History Museum, The Wildlife Photographer of the Year (WPY) exhibition provides a welcome respite from the maddening crowds that flood the museum during the holiday season. The atmosphere changes as soon as you walk into the darkened room filled with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An idiot’s guide to the US Election
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-3-an-idiots-guide-to-the-us-election/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 23:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-3-an-idiots-guide-to-the-us-election/</guid>
        <description> Remember 2012? The London Olympics, (almost) the end of the world and the last US presidential election? Well fast forward four years and we’ve had another set of Olympics, another election cycle is coming to a climax and, if you believe everything people are saying on Twitter, the world is coming …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Drunk consent is not consent. My rape story
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-drunk-consent-is-not-consent-my-rape-story/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 22:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-drunk-consent-is-not-consent-my-rape-story/</guid>
        <description>This week the coat I lost on the night I was raped found its way back to me.
Having languished, dirty and unloved, at the back of a cupboard in a house I occasionally visited for parties, it was unearthed in a start-of-year clean and returned to me. I had been there a year and a half ago for a club …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>International dance championships
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-international-dance-championships/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 22:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Claire Chan,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-international-dance-championships/</guid>
        <description>What is it about ballroom dancing that so enthrals us? The public’s fascination with ballroom dancing began years ago in Hollywood, with Fred Astaire and Ginger Rogers lighting up the silver screen. And as the wild success of TV programs like Strictly Come Dancing and Dancing With The Stars shows, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Casting women in male roles is not a gimmick
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-casting-women-in-male-roles-is-not-a-gimmick/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 16:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Steadman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-casting-women-in-male-roles-is-not-a-gimmick/</guid>
        <description>Shakespeare. “Who owns Shakespeare? “. This is the idea Phyllida Lloyd and company set out to challenge with her all-female production of Julius Caesar at the Donmar Warehouse in 2012.
It’s easy to dismiss that move as a gimmick, a knock-off copy of the all-male Shakespeare productions that pop up …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lagos to London | My transition
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-21-lagos-to-london-my-transition/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 10:25:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Selin Olenik,Daniel Ogbonna,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-21-lagos-to-london-my-transition/</guid>
        <description>I was born and raised in Lagos, the most populated city in Nigeria and in Africa as a whole. On September 30th 2014, less than 3 weeks after my 17th birthday, probably the most defining event in my life so far occurred. I moved to London to attend Imperial College.
Before leaving, my parents gave me …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Half a century of boldly going...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-14-half-a-century-of-boldly-going/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 10:30:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Selin Olenik,Anurag Deshpande,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-14-half-a-century-of-boldly-going/</guid>
        <description> Fifty years ago, as the spectre of the Cold War loomed over the world and the first battles of the civil rights movement were being fought, a corny, slightly overacted show with bold utopian and egalitarian aspirations made its way onto the prime-time lineup. Trek wore its heart on its sleeve, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ten things I hate about you
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-7-ten-things-i-hate-about-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 17:32:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Theresa Davey,Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-7-ten-things-i-hate-about-you/</guid>
        <description> We’ve come to the end of Freshers’ Week, and maybe you’ve had a bit too much fun. We’ve all been there, made mistakes, and done things that we live to regret with the bad-boy (or girl) hall senior who seems so mature and experienced. Regardless of how, when, or why, many people all over Imperial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Nobel vs Ig Nobel prizes
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-7-the-nobel-vs-ig-nobel-prizes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 17:09:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lizzie E Riach,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-7-the-nobel-vs-ig-nobel-prizes/</guid>
        <description> Whereas the Nobel Prizes embody the recognition and respect all scientists strive for, the Ig Nobel Prizes are given out annually for some of the weirdest and most unlikely research materials in each category. Both are significant events in the science calendar, but for very different reasons. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A field guide to the culture tribes of London
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-a-field-guide-to-the-culture-tribes-of-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 19:56:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Fred S Fyles,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-a-field-guide-to-the-culture-tribes-of-london/</guid>
        <description> For the uninitiated, London can be a strange and scary place. However, for the ornithologically-inclined, it can be a place of wonder. Let felix be your guide, taking you on a tour of the different culture tribes you can spot in the capital. Bonus points if you manage to see them all!
The Techno …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>So I heard you like science?!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-so-i-heard-you-like-science/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 19:16:05 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Lef Apostolakis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-so-i-heard-you-like-science/</guid>
        <description> Ok! You made it, you’re in nerd centrali.e. Imperial College, 8th best university in the world (apparently). So you probably really, really, really like science. I get you, so do I. Don’t ask me why, it’s just one of those things, those guilty pleasures you don’t publicly admit to. In case your …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An idiot’s guide to... Summer 2016
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-an-idiots-guide-to-summer-2016/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 16:53:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-3-an-idiots-guide-to-summer-2016/</guid>
        <description> Ah, summer. That brief and fleeting moment of respite between the end of one exam period and the start of the next? Well here’s a recap for those of you who either forgot what went down or were on one of those holidays where you’re in a cave for a month because it cleanses your soul.
Brexit So, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Idiot’s Guide To A Post Brexit World
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-7-4-an-idiots-guide-to-a-post-brexit-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 09:55:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-7-4-an-idiots-guide-to-a-post-brexit-world/</guid>
        <description>So, we’re out. What now, eh? What came to pass last Thursday and early Friday morning was, whichever way you cut it, historic. No full country, this deep in the EU, has left it before and now we’ve got to deal with the fallout for better or for worse.
Chaos was the undoubtedly the adjective of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Editors’ picks of the past year...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-the-editors-picks-of-the-past-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 09:29:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-the-editors-picks-of-the-past-year/</guid>
        <description> Picks for summer The Serpentine Pavilion
The Serpentine Gallery’s Pavilion, a mere stone’s throw from the South Ken campus, is perhaps one the best places to amp up the culture factor on a sunny summer’s day. It’s free, it’s outside (bang in the middle of Hyde Park), and it houses a caf. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Royal Academy Summer Exhibition
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-royal-academy-summer-exhibition/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 09:26:12 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-royal-academy-summer-exhibition/</guid>
        <description>The Summer Exhibition at the Royal Academy is a bit like Glastonbury of the arts world, if the people who went were 97% white with a mean age of sixty. Along with fixtures like Wimbledon, it heralds in the summer, bringing together established artists from all the different disciplines: printmaking, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The FELIX Sex Survey 2016
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-the-felix-sex-survey-2016/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 09:01:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-the-felix-sex-survey-2016/</guid>
        <description>Here it is, for the sixth year running, the infamous FELIX Sex Survey results. Thank you so much to everyone who trusted us with your deepest, darkest, and occasionally unrealistic and obviously made-up secrets (we deleted those responses from our data). Six hundred or so of you took the time to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is David Hockney all he&#39;s cracked up to be?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-is-david-hockney-all-hes-cracked-up-to-be/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 08:34:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-is-david-hockney-all-hes-cracked-up-to-be/</guid>
        <description>Soon, London art galleries will be in the throes of a David Hockney takeover. Starting from July, the Royal Academy will showcase ‘82 portraits and one still life’, and beginning in February next year, the Tate will host a comprehensive retrospective spanning decades of the artist’s work. It should …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let me eat cake
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-let-me-eat-cake/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 09:32:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-let-me-eat-cake/</guid>
        <description>Marie Antoinette once said, “Let them eat cake.” If I were a peasant back in the days of the French Revolution, I’d happily take her words as a genuine attempt to offer me cake, ditch my hunger for the stale baguettes and munch on the amazing French creations for the rest of my life, maybe a vanilla …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The EU contribution to the Arts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-the-eu-contribution-to-the-arts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 09:01:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Max F Falkenberg McGillivray,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-the-eu-contribution-to-the-arts/</guid>
        <description>According to the Leave campaign, it is to the tune of £350m a week that the patriarchal dictators in the EU extort our poor impoverished island. As the great cultural icons Boris and Nigel might like to believe, if it were not for the bloodsucking greed of the EU, each and every British family up …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Escaping the uncanny valley
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-escaping-the-uncanny-valley/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 08:59:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Cale E Tilford,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-27-escaping-the-uncanny-valley/</guid>
        <description>A major criticism of the Uncharted trilogy has always been that it is more style than substance, that is focuses too heavily on glorious set-pieces and stunning scenery to mask its flaws. That is not to say that these games don’t have substantial playable elements – they do – but the gameplay that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Go-nuts for doughnuts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-go-nuts-for-doughnuts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 09:22:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Christy Lam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-go-nuts-for-doughnuts/</guid>
        <description>Throwback to the seven years spent in an all-girls boarding school in the countryside. A weekend trip to the nearest town with an actual supermarket was a sacred privilege only to those of Year 9 and above, while you have to be at least in Year 12 to be allowed to step on the train on the opposite …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FELIX investigates study drugs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-felix-investigates-study-drugs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 09:02:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Grace G Rahman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-felix-investigates-study-drugs/</guid>
        <description>Like all good things in life, this article starts with a disclaimer: FELIX is by no means advocating the use of these so-called study drugs. I don’t know about you, but shitting every hour doesn’t scream productive work mode to me, – each to their own. We’re just giving you some facts and student …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Centrefold complaints and halls drama
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-centrefold-complaints-and-halls-drama/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 08:52:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-20-centrefold-complaints-and-halls-drama/</guid>
        <description>In response to Issue 1633 Centrefold (netball) Dear Felix
I attended the Imperial College Festival last weekend. I was inspired and captivated by the enormous range of research and innovation that I was able to discuss in detail with students, researchers and professors who were all passionate about …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An idiot’s guide to the EU referendum
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-an-idiots-guide-to-the-eu-referendum/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 08:57:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Matthew Johnston,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-an-idiots-guide-to-the-eu-referendum/</guid>
        <description>Over the course of the last UK election period and for the bulk of 2016 so far, the media and news in general has been focussed on the UK’s membership within the European Union, but what’s actually going on?
Where did the EU come from?
In essence the European Union (EU) is a group of 28 countries …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Trials and Tribulations at BUCS Sprint ‘16
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-trials-and-tribulations-at-bucs-sprint-16/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 10:24:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Madeleine L Whybrow,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-trials-and-tribulations-at-bucs-sprint-16/</guid>
        <description>On Sunday 1st May, seventeen of Imperial’s bravest triathletes descended upon the sleepy town of Calne, Wiltshire to compete in the 2016 BUCS Sprint Triathlon. Gathered outside SAF at the ungodly hour of 5:45am, some quick Imperial brains spotted that there were actually only sixteen recruits …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Seeding the Veggie Power
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-seeding-the-veggie-power/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 10:20:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sarah Kakadellis,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-seeding-the-veggie-power/</guid>
        <description> The foodies, meat lovers or simply punctilious readers amongst you may remember last week’s article raising arguments for meat consumption, or rather, for not feeling guilty about it as long as you accepted the responsibilities. And I thought there would be nothing better than hunting my friend’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A guide to Eurovision 2016
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-a-guide-to-eurovision-2016/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 10:09:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jamie M Thomas,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-a-guide-to-eurovision-2016/</guid>
        <description> After Måns Zelmerlöw’s victory for Sweden in Vienna last year, this year sees “Europe’s favourite TV show” head to Stockholm for the third time in the competition’s history, and it’s set to be a big one! We’ll also see a massive change to the voting system, with each country awarding two sets of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Live and let live, as long as you’re not tasty
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-live-and-let-live-as-long-as-youre-not-tasty/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:59:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Sanjay Bhattacharya,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-live-and-let-live-as-long-as-youre-not-tasty/</guid>
        <description> Morals are tricky things to have. I try, like I’m sure most of you do, but there are grey areas for me. Food can contain many of them. Like all transcendental ideas, it is sometimes easiest to simply pick and choose them as you like, but when they tie in to the very substance we consume every day …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your guide to what’s hot in art this term
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-your-guide-to-whats-hot-in-art-this-term/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:54:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-your-guide-to-whats-hot-in-art-this-term/</guid>
        <description>Les Blancs at the National Theatre now until 2nd June
Lorraine Hansberry’s final drama, written eleven years after her most acclaimed work A Raisin in the Sun, is an oft-neglected masterpiece of the American stage, and a ‘highly theatrical search for the soul of post-colonial Africa.’ In it, an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Iconic sex toys that changed the world
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-iconic-sex-toys-that-changed-the-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:43:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-iconic-sex-toys-that-changed-the-world/</guid>
        <description> This article was published as part of FELIX&amp;rsquo;s Sex Survey launch. Do the survey here.
If there’s one thing that I’ve learnt over the course of my adult life, it’s how to get myself off, and I don’t think there’s any shame in admitting that. In recent years, more and more women have begun …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
