<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jc7413/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jc7413/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Don McCullin</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-don-mccullin/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-don-mccullin/</guid>
        <description>Don McCullin is best known as a ‘war photographer’, a title that does not sit easy with him. To him, photography is about empathy, but he has never felt that the impact of his pictures have done enough to end the suffering of the people he depicts. ‘If you can’t feel what you’re looking at,’ he …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ovid’s Metamorphoses</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-ovid-s-metamorphoses/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-ovid-s-metamorphoses/</guid>
        <description>How many ways can one make age-old tales fresh and exciting? In 80 minutes, international theatre company Pants on Fire tells a selection of stories from Ovid’s epic Metamorphoses: Jupiter transforms his mortal lover Io into a sad cow in a gas mask, Theseus is tended to by a gaggle of giggling …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tacenda</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-tacenda/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-tacenda/</guid>
        <description>Would you watch the same day played out again and again? Lizzie and Joy are best friends, but as Joy is crashing at Lizzie’s flat, they are getting on each other’s nerves. Joy is trying to get bored businessmen interested in her free sanitary pads campaign, while Lizzie’s music classroom is about to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>La Traviata continues to delight</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-la-traviata-continues-to-delight/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-la-traviata-continues-to-delight/</guid>
        <description>Verdi’s La Traviata is undoubtedly one of the most well-loved and familiar operas of all time. First performed in London at Her Majesty’s Theatre in 1856, it is now the most-performed opera in the world. This particular production of the Royal Opera House, directed by Richard Eyre, celebrates its …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mary Oliver: a poet that speaks to all</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-mary-oliver-a-poet-that-speaks-to-all/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-01-mary-oliver-a-poet-that-speaks-to-all/</guid>
        <description>When Krista Tippett interviewed the late poet Mary Oliver on her radio show ‘On Being’ back in 2015, she referred to Oliver’s poem ‘Wild Geese’ as “a poem that has saved lives”. This might seem an exaggerated claim, but for me at least, it holds some truth.
For a teenager in the last year of school, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Joy to your bookshelf</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-joy-to-your-bookshelf/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jia Qi Tan,Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-joy-to-your-bookshelf/</guid>
        <description>Eleanor Oliphant is Completely Fine by Gail Honeyman
Winner of the British Book Awards, this stunning debut novel by Gail Honeyman delves deep into loneliness, connections and the power of kindness. The theme of isolation is one that is rarely explored in contemporary culture; as Honeyman puts it, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>TS Eliot Prize 2018: an ‘intensely political’ shortlist</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-ts-eliot-prize-2018-an-intensely-political-shortlist/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-19-ts-eliot-prize-2018-an-intensely-political-shortlist/</guid>
        <description>The TS Eliot Prize in poetry is one of the most prestigious poetry prizes for the English language. Last year, to celebrate the 25th year of the prize, the winner’s prize money was increased to £25,000 - making it the most valuable prize in British poetry. It is no surprise then that the prize is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>White Teeth</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-white-teeth/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-white-teeth/</guid>
        <description>When White Teeth was published back in 2000, by a hitherto-unknown, fresh-out-of-Cambridge Zadie Smith, it added a fresh perspective to the gathering conversation about Britain’s cultural diversity. Smith was different because she actually grew up in the melting pot of race, religion and culture in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I’m Not Running runs out of steam</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-i-m-not-running-runs-out-of-steam/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-i-m-not-running-runs-out-of-steam/</guid>
        <description>Pauline Gibson is a young doctor, having served in a small provincial hospital for most of her career. When the authorities threaten to close down the hospital in order to concentrate resources and services, she finds herself campaigning against its closure, becoming something of a national …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Man Booker Prize 2018: a rundown of the shortlist</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-the-man-booker-prize-2018-a-rundown-of-the-shortlist/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-the-man-booker-prize-2018-a-rundown-of-the-shortlist/</guid>
        <description>Milkman, by Anna Burns
Anna Burns is the first Northern Irish writer to win the coveted prize – previous Irish writers have all been from the Republic. She is also the first female writer to win since 2013, when Eleanor Catton won for The Luminaries. The Booker’s chair of judges, philosopher Kwame …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Funny, the Painful and Everything in Between</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-the-funny-the-painful-and-everything-in-between/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-the-funny-the-painful-and-everything-in-between/</guid>
        <description>This is what my mother and I like to talk about,” says Karla defensively, as Don shouts at her from across the flimsy hospital curtains to shut up. “Yes, but this is a hospital!” Don retorts. Karla, an aspiring stand-up comedian, had been practicing permutations of lines like “I have been single for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix recommends autumn reading</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-felix-recommends-autumn-reading/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-felix-recommends-autumn-reading/</guid>
        <description>Normal People by Sally Rooney
Longlisted for the Man Booker Prize this year, Rooney’s second novel follows less than a year after her celebrated debut Conversations with Friends. The praise heaped on Conversations applies to her new novel – witty and elegant, both novels are testament to Rooney’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix recommends – reading for summer days</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-15-felix-recommends-reading-for-summer-days/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-15-felix-recommends-reading-for-summer-days/</guid>
        <description>Mrs Dalloway by Virginia Woolf
Virginia Woolf’s most well-known work crackles with a vibrant energy and zest. Set on a ‘Wednesday in mid-June’, it remains one of the best portrayals of London in the early summer, full of the vibrant optimism that characterises long days in the city. Taking place …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Picasso 1932: the man’s pivotal year in paintings</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-picasso-1932-the-man-s-pivotal-year-in-paintings/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-picasso-1932-the-man-s-pivotal-year-in-paintings/</guid>
        <description>How do you measure a year? In paintings, of course – at least for Picasso. 1932 was a pivotal year for Picasso in more ways than one. By this point in time he was a celebrated artist, but critics were beginning to speak of him in the past tense, rather than as a visionary of the future. Feeling …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Summer and Smoke sizzles with spectacular sentiment in stunning revival</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-summer-and-smoke-sizzles-with-spectacular-sentiment-in-stunning-revival/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-16-summer-and-smoke-sizzles-with-spectacular-sentiment-in-stunning-revival/</guid>
        <description>It is a time-tested dichotomy – the body versus the soul, the mind, with its emotions and intellect, versus the body’s sensual physical pleasures. The battle between the two is the focus of one of Tennessee Williams’ earliest and rarely-performed plays, Summer and Smoke. In a stunning new revival by …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Deterred by Beckett’s infamous motormouth? Not I.</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-deterred-by-beckett-s-infamous-motormouth-not-i/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-deterred-by-beckett-s-infamous-motormouth-not-i/</guid>
        <description>Samuel Beckett’s Not I is notoriously difficult to perform. It is a short, continuous stream of words from the character Mouth that loops in and out of coherence, jumping between sentences, interspersed with repetition and interjections.
In 1972, American actress Jessica Tandy performed it in a New …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dispatches from the VAULT Festival</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-dispatches-from-the-vault-festival/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-dispatches-from-the-vault-festival/</guid>
        <description>Dean joined the army, and ‘Danny’ joined the Islamic State. Dean has been captured by ISIS, and is currently tied to a pole with Danny as his guard. Both men had grown up in the UK. Bismillah! An ISIS Tragicomedy is an hour-long conversation between the two, exploring issues in British society, from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flamenco absent in this Flamenco Festival show</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-flamenco-absent-in-this-flamenco-festival-show/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-flamenco-absent-in-this-flamenco-festival-show/</guid>
        <description>I like flamenco dance and music, and was thus particularly excited about this show; however, perhaps because I chose the wrong show out of the various nights on offer, or because the festival’s theme was not as I had anticipated - Isabel Bayón and Israel Galván’s show, Dju-Dju was spectacularly bad …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Raising the portcullis: uncovering queer literature</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-raising-the-portcullis-uncovering-queer-literature/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-22-raising-the-portcullis-uncovering-queer-literature/</guid>
        <description>The book that first led me to the wonderful world of queer literature was Oranges are Not the Only Fruit by Jeanette Winterson. As one of our A level texts, Oranges provided me with a first hand account of what it was like to grow up as a lesbian girl, especially within a conservative, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix recommends Valentine&#39;s reads… or the books to help you to forget about romance</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-felix-recommends-valentine-s-reads-or-the-books-to-help-you-to-forget-about-romance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,Alice Peberdy,Indira Mallik,Pavan Inguva,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-09-felix-recommends-valentine-s-reads-or-the-books-to-help-you-to-forget-about-romance/</guid>
        <description> Written on the Body by Jeanette Winterson
 The first question is, who is the narrator? She or he is never named, and their gender never revealed. &amp;ldquo;Why is the measure of love loss?&amp;rdquo; asks the opening sentence, and throughout the book we are taken through the narrator’s clandestine …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>If you could live a beautiful dream, why would you wake up to reality?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-if-you-could-live-a-beautiful-dream-why-would-you-wake-up-to-reality/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-01-if-you-could-live-a-beautiful-dream-why-would-you-wake-up-to-reality/</guid>
        <description>I have never enjoyed Chinese opera. Chinese opera to Chinese youth nowadays is a bit like what Shakespeare is to English-speaking youth – something confined to the realm of literary studies. And if they are popularly enjoyed, often it is only in some form of modern adaptation.
For just three nights …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Strong contenders for 2017 T. S. Eliot Prize for poetry</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-strong-contenders-for-2017-t-s-eliot-prize-for-poetry/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-11-strong-contenders-for-2017-t-s-eliot-prize-for-poetry/</guid>
        <description>The T. S. Eliot Prize, awarded by the Poetry Book Society, is arguably one of the most prestigious poetry prizes in the world. Awarded every year to a poetry collection in English first published in the UK or Ireland, it has seen many household names winning in the past, including Ted Hughes, Carol …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2017 in review: the Arts editors take you through the best exhibitions and shows in London this year</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-2017-in-review-the-arts-editors-take-you-through-the-best-exhibitions-and-shows-in-london-this-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,Adam Gellatly,Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-2017-in-review-the-arts-editors-take-you-through-the-best-exhibitions-and-shows-in-london-this-year/</guid>
        <description>It’s a strange feeling, when you feel like you know an artist, that you have a reasonable understanding of his work, to then discover him afresh. But exactly what I experienced at Tate Britain in February, when the gallery put on the largest ever arrangement of Hockney’s work.
David Hockney, The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Clash of Cultures: Phoenix Editors special</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-clash-of-cultures-phoenix-editors-special/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,Adam Gellatly,Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-clash-of-cultures-phoenix-editors-special/</guid>
        <description>Phoenix, Felix ’s sister arts publication, returns this week with a teaser 8-page pullout. Arts Editors Indira Malik and Adam Gellatly and Felix Editor-in-Chief Fred Fyles talk to Phoenix Editors Liliane Laborde-Edozien, Catherine Webb, and Joy Aston about their plans for the magazine and their love …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kazuo Ishiguro, winner of 2017 Nobel Prize in Literature, is master of words and the heart</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-kazuo-ishiguro-winner-of-2017-nobel-prize-in-literature-is-master-of-words-and-the-heart/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-kazuo-ishiguro-winner-of-2017-nobel-prize-in-literature-is-master-of-words-and-the-heart/</guid>
        <description>I first encountered Kazuo Ishiguro’s writing back in high school, in the form of his short story collection Nocturnes. I had won some book vouchers, and was browsing the local bookstore for something worth buying when I came across this slim volume. Five Stories of Music and Nightfall, it read, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Literature should not just be about ‘dead white men’</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-literature-should-not-just-be-about-dead-white-men/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08-literature-should-not-just-be-about-dead-white-men/</guid>
        <description>Much has been written so far about ‘decolonising’ the English Literature curriculum, after Cambridge University’s English undergraduate Lola Olufemi wrote an open letter imploring her faculty to broaden their curriculum to include non-white writers. The letter, signed by around 150 students, called …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Tis the season to be reading</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08--tis-the-season-to-be-reading/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,Alice Peberdy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-08--tis-the-season-to-be-reading/</guid>
        <description>Got a family member you need to get a last-minute gift for? Why not get them a book – at least it&amp;rsquo;s easy to wrap!
This is Going To Hurt, by Adam Kay
Have a healthcare professional among your family and friends? Even if you don’t, they are sure to enjoy this hilarious journal by ex-doctor, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Decolonising the canon: Felix recommends</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-decolonising-the-canon-felix-recommends/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Fred S Fyles,Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-decolonising-the-canon-felix-recommends/</guid>
        <description>Trumpet, by Jackie Kay
Kay’s only novel Trumpet is in a class of its own, and one of the most unconventional books I’ve ever read. Joss Moody is a renowned jazz musician whose death sparks a frantic seeking of truth by his son and the public about his ‘true’ identity and gender. It explores the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Felix guide to life drawing classes in London</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-the-felix-guide-to-life-drawing-classes-in-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-the-felix-guide-to-life-drawing-classes-in-london/</guid>
        <description>London Life Drawing (Clerkenwell)
Where? B&amp;amp;H Buildings, Clerkenwell When? Mondays, 7-9.30pm How much? £6 concession per class
This session is part of Adrian Dutton’s London Life Drawing classes, which happen at various locations around London, including in Hoxton and Bethnal Green. This …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In the words of a young poet finding her feet</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-in-the-words-of-a-young-poet-finding-her-feet/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-10-in-the-words-of-a-young-poet-finding-her-feet/</guid>
        <description>What do we know of someone else’s life, besides what they choose to reveal to us? What more of a life that was tragically cut short, and has remained an enigma since?
In a newly-published tome of never-before-seen letters by 20th-century poet Sylvia Plath, we steal glimpses of a young, gifted poet …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Words of migratory flight</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-words-of-migratory-flight/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-words-of-migratory-flight/</guid>
        <description>The world is a fleeting glory”, reads Asha Lul Mohamud Yusuf’s poem, The Scab. To the more than 110,000 Somali-born immigrants living in the UK, many of whom fled the Somali Civil War as refugees, this cannot be more true. Stability is an illusion when one has to witness one’s own country torn apart …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An evening discussion with the Booker Prize nominees</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-an-evening-discussion-with-the-booker-prize-nominees/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-20-an-evening-discussion-with-the-booker-prize-nominees/</guid>
        <description>It was the night before the announcement of the 2017 Man Booker Prize winner, and it was the first time the shortlisted writers had all come together in the same space. In the Royal Festival Hall, where all six shortlisted writers sat next to each other on stage, the anticipation was palpable amid …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Edinburgh Fringe: celebrating diversity and genius</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-edinburgh-fringe-celebrating-diversity-and-genius/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-edinburgh-fringe-celebrating-diversity-and-genius/</guid>
        <description>While studying in Edinburgh, I got the impression that this usually mild-mannered, quietly beautiful city takes on a completely different personality every August. Students who had been around in August spoke of the Royal Mile being flooded with tourists, the impossibility of getting anywhere, the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Arts editors completely destroy box office incomes!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-arts-editors-completely-destroy-box-office-incomes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,Adam Gellatly,Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-arts-editors-completely-destroy-box-office-incomes/</guid>
        <description>National Theatre: Entry Pass
The NT offers an Entry Pass to those aged 16 - 25. After registering and providing proof of age, you’ll be entitled to a whole range of NT delights including access to exclusive workshops and events, and discounts in the NT bookshops, cafes, backstage tours and prop …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gaiman’s London is never where you think it is</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-gaiman-s-london-is-never-where-you-think-it-is/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-12-gaiman-s-london-is-never-where-you-think-it-is/</guid>
        <description>Neil Gaiman has an uncanny knack for picking out the essence of a place.
In American Gods, Gaiman weaved the battle between ancient gods and modern greed into an epic tale of contemporary America. Neverwhere, in my opinion, should be read by everyone who lives in London. Richard, the protagonist, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get to know your friendly neighbourhood Arts team!</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-get-to-know-your-friendly-neighbourhood-arts-team/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,Adam Gellatly,Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-get-to-know-your-friendly-neighbourhood-arts-team/</guid>
        <description>INDIRA
Painting, making up stories, and endlessly ambitious crafts projects have been part of my life since early childhood. My writing in particular however never really found a focus until I came to Imperial. Maybe it was watching too much Gilmore Girls during my formative years, but the one thing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where’s the culture at?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-where-s-the-culture-at/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,Adam Gellatly,Indira Mallik,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-17-where-s-the-culture-at/</guid>
        <description>GREEN PARK
Royal Academy: Best known for its annual extravaganza - the Summer Exhibition - the RA hosts a whole range of exhibitions. Upcoming shows not to be missed are Jasper Johns; ‘Something Re-sembling Truth’, and Dali/Duchamp, an exhibition that will explore how their outlook on art and life …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Every man’s read for the new year
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-every-mans-read-for-the-new-year/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 15:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-12-16-every-mans-read-for-the-new-year/</guid>
        <description>I have always found myself inexplicably drawn to books about regret, lost opportunities, death, and dying. Perhaps there is something cathartic about reading of other people’s regrets, regrets that are disturbingly close to home yet safely ensconced in the realm of fiction. Perhaps it is the ritual …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>When pills aren’t enough
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-when-pills-arent-enough/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 08:33:24 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-when-pills-arent-enough/</guid>
        <description>Cathy Rentzenbrink begins her story with a night out. On a summer’s day twenty-six years ago, she had decided to head home first, bored, while her brother remained behind in the bar hoping to “get lucky”.
“Matty never, in any sense of the word, ‘got lucky’ again,” she continued, as she recounted how …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>People, Places and Things
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-people-places-and-things/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 10:15:20 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-6-people-places-and-things/</guid>
        <description>As I sat placidly in my seat waiting for the play to start, the announcement to turn off our mobile phones was played. That was all expected. But then the announcement repeated itself, and it seemed that a thousand voices were echoing it at the same time, louder and louder and reaching a mad climax …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your guide to what’s hot in art this term
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-your-guide-to-whats-hot-in-art-this-term/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:54:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-your-guide-to-whats-hot-in-art-this-term/</guid>
        <description>Les Blancs at the National Theatre now until 2nd June
Lorraine Hansberry’s final drama, written eleven years after her most acclaimed work A Raisin in the Sun, is an oft-neglected masterpiece of the American stage, and a ‘highly theatrical search for the soul of post-colonial Africa.’ In it, an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Great Britain, strange yet familiar
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-great-britain-strange-yet-familiar/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:50:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-great-britain-strange-yet-familiar/</guid>
        <description>It is often said that familiarity breeds contempt. While that may not be true in life all the time, in photography at least, introducing a new observer to a tired scene can definitely produce some fresh perspectives. It is with this notion that British photographer Martin Parr curates Strange and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Psychedelia and existentialism, hand-in-hand
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-30-psychedelia-and-existentialism-hand-in-hand/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 18:43:15 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-30-psychedelia-and-existentialism-hand-in-hand/</guid>
        <description>As I sat placidly in my seat waiting for the play to start, the announcement to turn off our mobile phones was played. That was all expected. But then the announcement repeated itself, and it seemed that a thousand voices were echoing it at the same time, louder and louder and reaching a mad climax …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Great Britain, strange yet familiar
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-30-great-britain-strange-yet-familiar/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 15:50:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-30-great-britain-strange-yet-familiar/</guid>
        <description>It is often said that familiarity breeds contempt. While that may not be true in life all the time, in photography at least, introducing a new observer to a tired scene can definitely produce some fresh perspectives. It is with this notion that British photographer Martin Parr curates Strange and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Earnestly unpredictable and stylistically important
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-30-earnestly-unpredictable-and-stylistically-important/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 01:25:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-30-earnestly-unpredictable-and-stylistically-important/</guid>
        <description>Flying cakes, crashing plates, a cacophonous score and a healthy dose of Wilde witticisms – Gerald Barry&amp;rsquo;s operatic adaptation of The Importance of Being Earnest has it all. Being an enormous fan of Wilde, this production brought the Wilde-ness of one of the most recognisably …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>From Bizarre to Sublime at the Barbican
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-23-from-bizarre-to-sublime-at-the-barbican/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2016 14:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,Jake A Mossom,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-23-from-bizarre-to-sublime-at-the-barbican/</guid>
        <description>Tuesday saw the first of three performances by the Los Angeles Philharmonic Orchestra in residency at the Barbican. Dudamel led the players in five pieces (four programmed and then surprisingly an encore, which we don’t see that often with British orchestras) that ranged from novel to bizarre and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The boys wanna be her
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-the-boys-wanna-be-her/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 12:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Indira Mallik,Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-11-the-boys-wanna-be-her/</guid>
        <description>Judith Leyster
Leyster, born in 1606 was the only woman to be appointed one of the Dutch Masters. It’s easy to see why, ‘Self-Portrait’ (pictured left) brilliantly shows what a virtuoso and throughly modern painter she was. The composition is a break from the rigidity and formality of portraiture of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On the shoulders of literary giants
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-on-the-shoulders-of-literary-giants/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 12:01:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-on-the-shoulders-of-literary-giants/</guid>
        <description>It was an odd set-up – the 2500-seater Royal Festival Hall packed to the brim, eagerly watching just two individuals on stage. Sat slightly angled towards each other and separated by an unassuming coffee table were two of the greatest literary figures of our time. I was seated right at the back …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An encounter you won&#39;t forget
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-21-an-encounter-you-wont-forget/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2016 13:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,Waleed El Geresy,Waleed A El-Geresy,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-21-an-encounter-you-wont-forget/</guid>
        <description>McBurney’s performance recounts the story of Loren McIntyre– an American photographer who travels into the Amazon rainforest to attempt to capture on film an elusive, indigenous people called the Mayoruna. It quickly becomes apparent however that this story did not happen in the past alone, but is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London Students’ Neuroscience Network
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-london-students-neuroscience-network/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 11:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-12-london-students-neuroscience-network/</guid>
        <description>Last weekend, Imperial played host to the largest ever student-led Neuroscience conference, organised under the banner of the London Students’ Neuroscience Network (LSNeuroN). For the first time, neuroscience societies of the five London medical schools – Imperial, UCL, King’s College London, Bart’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Subterranean arts festival promises to surprise
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-subterranean-arts-festival-promises-to-surprise/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 09:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-1-29-subterranean-arts-festival-promises-to-surprise/</guid>
        <description>Have you ever wondered what goes on underneath London’s famous “graffiti tunnel” that is Leake Street, near Waterloo station?
Halfway down the tunnel is the entrance to The Vaults, a subterranean labyrinth of creative space and entertainment. For the third year running, the venue will be home to the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Beckett in the City: A Potent Reminder of Inequality
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-15-beckett-in-the-city-a-potent-reminder-of-inequality/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2015 11:37:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-15-beckett-in-the-city-a-potent-reminder-of-inequality/</guid>
        <description>Sometimes, a creative piece comes along that leaves you thinking about its issues for a long time, surfacing now and then as a question, emerging here and there as an idea. These works leave an imprint of the artist’s thoughts on you, and you are left with a view of the world through another’s eyes. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ninagawa’s Hamlet shows a new Bard
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-27-ninagawas-hamlet-shows-a-new-bard/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 18:03:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-27-ninagawas-hamlet-shows-a-new-bard/</guid>
        <description>Right from the outset, Ninagawa Company’s Hamlet looked like it had been plucked out of an ancient Japanese film. Blue fog shrouded the stage as Hamlet, Horatio, and the guards dart across the stage, confronted by the ghost of Hamlet’s father. Spine-chilling Eastern music beats steadily in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Celebrating the Queen of Modernism
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-celebrating-the-queen-of-modernism/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 12:58:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-15-celebrating-the-queen-of-modernism/</guid>
        <description>From the very opening moments of Woolf Works, the audience realises that what they are about to experience will not be anything one would expect from a conventional ballet, but a bold, mixed-media theatrical experiment with dance as its main act.
We are greeted by a recording of Virginia Woolf’s own …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Ode to Medicine, Mortality, and Art
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-an-ode-to-medicine-mortality-and-art/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 12:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-an-ode-to-medicine-mortality-and-art/</guid>
        <description>In his poem Larynx, Pablo Neruda implored of Death:
Why are you following me?
What do you want with my skeleton?&amp;hellip;
Why do you have to take me?
What business have I with Heaven?
Hell doesn’t suit me –
I feel fine on the earth.”
The anxiety of the speaker upon learning of a possible laryngeal …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A journey into the sea’s depths
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-3-a-journey-into-the-seas-depths/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 14:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-3-a-journey-into-the-seas-depths/</guid>
        <description>A strip of water runs across the stage, which itself slopes upstage, with vague impressions of a ship’s windows in the distance. Daland’s crew shuffles around, clearing up after a storm as Daland announces that they will be heading home soon, and Senta, his daughter, will be waiting for him. This …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Beauty and Betrayal at the ENO
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-22-beauty-and-betrayal-at-the-eno/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 17:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-22-beauty-and-betrayal-at-the-eno/</guid>
        <description>When it was first performed in 1853, the Venetian opera house La Fenice insisted that Verdi’s La Traviata be staged in the past, around 1700, despite his original intention of a contemporary staging. Perhaps the initial resistance was due to the opera’s controversial nature painting the main …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Seeing photography in a new light
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-17-seeing-photography-in-a-new-light/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2015 16:37:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-17-seeing-photography-in-a-new-light/</guid>
        <description>Photography exhibitions are often about particular movements, themes, or individual photographers. Rarely do you find an exhibition as all-encompassing as this show of the best of the Royal Photographic Society’s (RPS) collection. Besides including instantly recognizable photos, such as Steve …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Some Metatheatre Most Remarkable
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-11-some-metatheatre-most-remarkable/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 22:23:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-11-some-metatheatre-most-remarkable/</guid>
        <description>Despite reading the synopsis beforehand, I was entirely unprepared for Six Characters in Search of a Story, an intense piece of metatheatre that turns all convention on its head. Written in 1921 by Luigi Pirandello and first performed in the same year to mixed reviews, I can only imagine how …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mapping the City – Cartography Reimagined
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-31-mapping-the-city-cartography-reimagined/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2015 18:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-31-mapping-the-city-cartography-reimagined/</guid>
        <description>If self is a location, so is love:
Bearings taken, markings, cardinal points,
Options, obstinacies, dug heels and distance,
Here and there and now and then, a stance.
These words of well-loved poet Seamus Heaney resonated in my head as I explored this new exhibition of street art and graffiti at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial’s Hidden Artistic Treasures
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-31-imperials-hidden-artistic-treasures/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2015 18:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-31-imperials-hidden-artistic-treasures/</guid>
        <description>Every morning, students stream into Imperial College from Queen’s Gate, turning in at Imperial College Road and passing by a red brick house on their left without as much as a second glance. Few students realise that the Victorian townhouse is both Grade II Listed, and the residence of the President …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>&#39;Tis Pity She&#39;s a Whore - Shakespeare&#39;s moral dilemma
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-18-tis-pity-shes-a-whore-shakespeares-moral-dilemma/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 15:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-18-tis-pity-shes-a-whore-shakespeares-moral-dilemma/</guid>
        <description>Despite being written almost 400 years ago in a society vastly different from our own, this Renaissance classic still evokes visceral responses. There is something deeply attractive about a story of passionate love between brother and sister, vengeful adulteresses and corrupt cardinals which all end …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Tis Pity She’s a Whore – Shakespeare’s moral dilemma
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-tis-pity-shes-a-whore-shakespeares-moral-dilemma/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 21:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-tis-pity-shes-a-whore-shakespeares-moral-dilemma/</guid>
        <description>Despite being written almost 400 years ago in a society vastly different from our own, this Renaissance classic still evokes visceral responses. There is something deeply attractive about a story of passionate love between brother and sister, vengeful adulteresses and corrupt cardinals which all end …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Witty, irreverent, political collages
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-witty-irreverent-political-collages/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 05:42:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-witty-irreverent-political-collages/</guid>
        <description>What: Hannah Hoch Where: Whitechapel Gallery, E1 When: Until 23rd March Price: £9,95, £7.95 concessions
In Heads of State (1920), two portly figures are pictured in their bathing suits before a feminine backdrop of butterflies, flowers and a woman with a parasol. One figure is the first president of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Critic Laughs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-the-critic-laughs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jingjie Cheng,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-the-critic-laughs/</guid>
        <description>What: Richard Hamilton
Where: Tate Modern, SE1
When: 13th February - 26th May
Price: £14.50, concessions £12.50
Richard Hamilton. Father of pop art, experimenter of consumer design, right? If that is all you associate with this icon of twentieth century British art, this massive retrospective at the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
