<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/calum_drysdale/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/calum_drysdale/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>It is Not Corbyn that we Should be Blaming but Labour Centrists</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-not-corbyn-blame-labour-centrists/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-12-09-not-corbyn-blame-labour-centrists/</guid>
        <description>The Red Wall
The so-called ‘Red Wall’ includes many of the old Labour strongholds like Great Gimsby, Workington, that is famously being challenged by the Tories, and Don Valley. Many of these seats have non-local MPs who have been given a safe seat as a reward. Don Valley in Yorkshire, for example, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Shook: Becoming a Father Behind Bars</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-shook-becoming-father-behind-bars/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-shook-becoming-father-behind-bars/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
Shook is as close to a perfect play that I think I have ever seen. Set in a prison classroom, three convicts, all with pregnant girlfriends, are receiving lessons on how to be fathers. Opening with rapid wit and banter the play first comes across as an entertaining but fundamentally shallow …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Tiger Will See You Now</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-tiger-will-see-you-now/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-tiger-will-see-you-now/</guid>
        <description>4 stars
I live with medics, and from the way they go on, one could be forgiven for thinking that the last thing that any of them want is to be a doctor. Which is why it is so funny that the ICSM medics chose to put on Tiger Country last week as their autumn play. This is a play based on the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>DramSoc Presents: Macbeth</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-dramsoc-presents-macbeth/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-dramsoc-presents-macbeth/</guid>
        <description>Shakespeare is the eternal snake. Just when you think you have him pinned down, he writhes away, changes shape or just turns to smoke in your hands. His texts, so well trod, in the hands of successive centuries of directors retain the ability to shock generation after generation.
Dramatists and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NATO Needs Replacing</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-nato-needs-replacing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-15-nato-needs-replacing/</guid>
        <description>NATO was already creaking. Everyone could see it, from congressmen in the US tearing their hair out at Trump’s tweets to autocrats licking their lips. But no one wanted to say anything, because the emperor’s clothes are lovely until a child points out that he is naked. Macron is the allegorical …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pretty Fly for a Sci-fi</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-pretty-fly-for-sci-fi/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-pretty-fly-for-sci-fi/</guid>
        <description>5 stars
Based on the 1961 book of the same name by Polish author Stanisław Lem, Solaris recounts the events that occur on a research station hovering in orbit above the titular ocean planet. Orbiting between two stars, Solaris defies scientific explanation, behaving not as a planet but more like a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stranger Things Called, they want their ’80s Gimmick Back</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-stranger-things-called-want-80s-gimmick-back/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-25-stranger-things-called-want-80s-gimmick-back/</guid>
        <description>3 stars
Three thieves all with different motivations try to break into a gallery to steal a famous painting. As they work their way through the gallery, they unknowingly affect each other’s progress before finally meeting. Of course only one of them can actually end up with the painting&amp;hellip;
The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BP Should Pay RSC More</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-bp-should-pay-rsc-more/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-10-11-bp-should-pay-rsc-more/</guid>
        <description>While activists might feel flushed with victory, they have damaged the funding sources of the RSC without offering a credible alternative.
I can only imagine that a sound like an airplane loo flushing went around the auditorium, there was so much indrawing of breath, after Richard Dawkins admitted …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The UK’s hidden opioid crisis</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-the-uk-s-hidden-opioid-crisis/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-07-the-uk-s-hidden-opioid-crisis/</guid>
        <description>The phrase ‘opioid crisis’ has in the past had a Teflon-like quality about it, like ‘civil war’ or ‘theocracy’. These are terms used to describe distant news items. Fentanyl and oxycodone were intangible problems. However, studies by the Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development (OECD) …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This week, we remember the dead</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-this-week-we-remember-the-dead/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-31-this-week-we-remember-the-dead/</guid>
        <description>Early Western explorers to China returned telling stories about a land of silk, jade and dragons. A whole artistic movement was birthed, Orientalism, that imagined the East – in particular China – as a semi-real land more out of story books than realism. The ruling Communist Party seems determined …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Labelling The Independent Group MPs “traitors” is exactly why they left</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-labelling-the-independent-group-mps-traitors-is-exactly-why-they-left/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-04-labelling-the-independent-group-mps-traitors-is-exactly-why-they-left/</guid>
        <description>When The Independent Group MPs left, they were in disgust at the state of their own parties. Let us consider the personal toll this must have taken. Many MPs grew up knowing that they wanted to be in politics, and what party they wanted to be a part of. They will have spent years working in small …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is Universal Basic Income the real solution to poverty?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-is-universal-basic-income-the-real-solution-to-poverty/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-is-universal-basic-income-the-real-solution-to-poverty/</guid>
        <description>Before I begin I should clarify some terms. The Finland experiment cannot truly be called an experiment in Universal Base Income. UBI is the idea that the government should give each of its citizens a ‘basic’ form of income. It has been picked up by both the left and the right with both the Green …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Labour defections - a Tory perspective</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-the-labour-defections-a-tory-perspective/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-the-labour-defections-a-tory-perspective/</guid>
        <description>On Monday seven Labour MPs announced that they were leaving the Labour party in protest at Jeremy Corbyn’s leadership and his refusal to act on anti-Semitism present within the party. This has drawn inevitable comparisons with the Social Democrat Party, a group of four former ministers who resigned …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Marvel Comics Presents: Corbyn and Sidekick McDonnell</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-marvel-comics-presents-corbyn-and-sidekick-mcdonnell/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-25-marvel-comics-presents-corbyn-and-sidekick-mcdonnell/</guid>
        <description>There is nothing fundamentally objectionable about a beret. It is a piece of headgear that prevents heat loss from the scalp. This is in the same way as there is nothing wrong with a single influenza virus. It is unlikely to do any harm by itself. What is scary, however, is when there are lots of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>And then what?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-and-then-what/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-and-then-what/</guid>
        <description>At some point, this Brexit nonsense must end. Reason, though seemingly in short supply nowadays, demands it. Any transition period will come to an end. Any backstop will be withdrawn from and a new norm for the country will arrive, however uneasily. The question is whether this new norm will arrive …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nick Makoha: poetry on the boards</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-nick-makoha-poetry-on-the-boards/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-nick-makoha-poetry-on-the-boards/</guid>
        <description>At the beginning of The Dark , Michael Balogun, one of the show’s two actors, introduces himself. “Hi,. I’m Nick”. We are then asked to close our eyes and remember that “You are me”. In this disarming way begins a play that subtly whisks the audience into the complicated and human world of Idi …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello Ian. There are some things that I would like to talk to you about regarding your exhibition…</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-hello-ian-there-are-some-things-that-i-would-like-to-talk-to-you-about-regarding-your-exhibition/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-30-hello-ian-there-are-some-things-that-i-would-like-to-talk-to-you-about-regarding-your-exhibition/</guid>
        <description>Alone again. I had two tickets. VIP ruddy tickets and no one bit. Although having been to the exhibit, let it not be said that the students of Imperial had bad taste. I jest. Some.
Hislop occupies an odd place in our national consciousness. He enjoys acting like an outsider, happily jeering at the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>And Then There Were None like it</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-and-then-there-were-none-like-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-23-and-then-there-were-none-like-it/</guid>
        <description>What if I asked you what the most popular book ever written was? Off the top of your head. Think fast. Now you can feel smug if you thought the Bible, and even smugger if you got Shakespeare in second but what about third? Now we can quibble about figures but why don’t you take my word for it or, if …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Two is Company, Three’s a crowd, and nine is frankly ridiculous</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-20-two-is-company-three-s-a-crowd-and-nine-is-frankly-ridiculous/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-20-two-is-company-three-s-a-crowd-and-nine-is-frankly-ridiculous/</guid>
        <description>We find ourselves at Piccadilly Circus on a wet Thursday night. I am going out with the parents and two of three smaller mes and tensions are already high. We are going to see Company, the old Sondheim ‘Musical Comedy’ that you have likely seen staring at you from buses and Tube station walls. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You couldn’t make it up if you tried</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-you-couldn-t-make-it-up-if-you-tried/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-you-couldn-t-make-it-up-if-you-tried/</guid>
        <description>Lands isn’t really about anything. On the face of it, it consists of watching a tragicomedic farce about a woman who can’t stop bouncing on a trampoline and her friend who tries in vain to get her off. But what could have been a somewhat insensitive piece about addiction becomes both darker and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reflecting poorly on me: Space Shifters at the Hayward Gallery</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-reflecting-poorly-on-me-space-shifters-at-the-hayward-gallery/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-reflecting-poorly-on-me-space-shifters-at-the-hayward-gallery/</guid>
        <description>Another week, another date and another gallery. I got invited to go and see the newish Space Shifters exhibition by an old friend last Sunday. I was running late and was rushing due to a highly improbable coincidence involving a Sunday lunch and planned engineering works. I had radioed ahead from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Find love, be happy: The Distance You Have Come</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-find-love-be-happy-the-distance-you-have-come/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-find-love-be-happy-the-distance-you-have-come/</guid>
        <description>When the reviewer writes, he must remember that many, if not all, of the people that read his words will not actually get to see it themselves. He has incredible power to influence how a play is perceived and received. He must remember that his own perspective is subjective and that his prejudices …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We are all individuals: The Turner Prize 2018</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-we-are-all-individuals-the-turner-prize-2018/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Calum Drysdale,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-we-are-all-individuals-the-turner-prize-2018/</guid>
        <description>A friend and I had a conversation recently about whether there was something fundamental to non-conforming (he is into that sort of thing). “By going outside of what is socially acceptable one defies. That act of independence and definition of oneself not by others’ standards but by one’s own is the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
