<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/kw911/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/kw911/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>“The mayor is unable to grasp the simple idea of appropriateness in context”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-20-the-mayor-is-unable-to-grasp-the-simple-idea-of-appropriateness-in-context/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 21:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-20-the-mayor-is-unable-to-grasp-the-simple-idea-of-appropriateness-in-context/</guid>
        <description>Those following ‘Shirtgate’ may have seen this image being shared on Reddit and Twitter. The Mayor of London certainly has, as this week he incorporated its idiotic message into a piece for the Telegraph, joining the keyboard warriors who have defeated feminism, showing it to be a mess of double …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bouncing back: new research supports rebound sex
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-17-bouncing-back-new-research-supports-rebound-sex/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 17:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-17-bouncing-back-new-research-supports-rebound-sex/</guid>
        <description>It’s official: the popular belief that people who have been dumped are more likely to have “rebound” sex is true, at least among students.
Lynne Cooper and Lindsey Barber at the University of Missouri followed the lives of 170 undergraduates who had recently been through a break-up, asking them to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On trains and privatisation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-on-trains-and-privatisation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 17:52:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-on-trains-and-privatisation/</guid>
        <description>The British railway system is the biggest example of the failures of privatisation. I’m not old enough to remember the change, but I’m sure the arguments were the same as those touted today for the privatisation of other well-functioning institutions: “private companies will run an efficient …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The epigenetic revolution
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-the-epigenetic-revolution/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 09:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-the-epigenetic-revolution/</guid>
        <description>The completion of the Human Genome Project in April 2003 was a milestone in science. Ten years on, however, Bill Clinton’s prediction that it would “revolutionise the diagnosis, prevention and treatment of most, if not all, human diseases” is far from the truth. For all the project’s contributions …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why solar cells prefer Adele over Beethoven
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-why-solar-cells-prefer-adele-over-beethoven/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 03:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-why-solar-cells-prefer-adele-over-beethoven/</guid>
        <description>Could Miley Cyrus help lower your energy bills?” asked the Daily Mail. The answer: probably not, but ambient noise could increase the efficiency of solar cells, researchers at Imperial College and Queen Mary University of London have found.
Professor James Durrant of Imperial’s Department of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Frozen rainbows and corkscrew lasers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-frozen-rainbows-and-corkscrew-lasers/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 21:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-frozen-rainbows-and-corkscrew-lasers/</guid>
        <description>Ortwin Hess is known for the ‘trapped rainbow’ principle, but this is just one step towards his exciting vision for metamaterials. “It stops light,” he says about it, “so the only thing it can do is ‘lase’ energy off its surface. Why is this different to a good old normal laser? It doesn’t have a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The magic of metamaterials
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-the-magic-of-metamaterials/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 21:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-the-magic-of-metamaterials/</guid>
        <description>Function through structure” is something of a mantra for researchers of metamaterials, a truly twenty-first century field which aims to create materials with bizarre and fascinating optical and magnetic properties, invented here at Imperial by Professor Sir John Pendry.
“It was serendipity, really,” …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Inside the Collider: a review of the new exhibition
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-inside-the-collider-a-review-of-the-new-exhibition/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 02:19:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-inside-the-collider-a-review-of-the-new-exhibition/</guid>
        <description>You’re very lucky to see this,” a professor with a bright orange waistcoat and bow tie tells us. “Usually, only scientists are allowed at internal meetings.” We were sat in a mock up of CERN’s lecture theatre; projected on the wall were the professor and other attendees. I don’t know if anyone at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>WTH is NaNoWriMo?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-wth-is-nanowrimo/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 00:12:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-25-wth-is-nanowrimo/</guid>
        <description>Whether it’s swimming 500 lengths or climbing 5,000 metres, we all know about the athletic challenges that some people rise to. Fewer know about the creative challenge that over a quarter of a million aspiring authors take up each year: writing a 50,000 word novel in thirty days.
National Novel …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Torrid State of the Onion
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-the-torrid-state-of-the-onion/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 19:32:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-the-torrid-state-of-the-onion/</guid>
        <description>It was something like a 90s cyberpunk’s dream: an anonymous, hidden marketplace on the “deep web” where everything from research psychedelics to stolen credit card details could be bought. The Silk Road, considered by some a bold experiment in libertarianism, by others the biggest online hotbed of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New form of matter created from photons
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-new-form-of-matter-created-from-photons/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 00:33:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-4-new-form-of-matter-created-from-photons/</guid>
        <description>The Harvard-MIT Center for Ultracold Atoms has created “photonic molecules” by binding photons together, as published in Nature last week. The team, led by Harvard’s Professor Mikhail Lukin and MIT’s Professor Vladan Vuletic, first cooled an extremely rarefied gas of rubidium atoms to a few degrees …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Keir&#39;s Summer Science
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-keirs-summer-science/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 14:48:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-9-29-keirs-summer-science/</guid>
        <description> Corkscrew molecules emit circularly polarized light Molecules than can emit and detect circularly-polarised light may be the next step forward in technologies such as computer displays, which currently waste over three quarters of light energy by passing it through filters for colour and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS album of the week 21
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-29-ams-album-of-the-week-21/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 12:40:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-29-ams-album-of-the-week-21/</guid>
        <description>With my short side-parted hair and corduroy jacket, I’m about as far away from metal as you can get. Always open to new experiences, however, Deafheaven’s upcoming sophomore album Sunbather caught my eye. Described as “shoegaze with black metal drumming and vocals,” and with a cover more reminiscant …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS Album of the Week 16
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-ams-album-of-the-week-16/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 22:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-7-ams-album-of-the-week-16/</guid>
        <description>Youth Lagoon consists of a single 23 year old man: Trevor Powers. His debut, The Year of Hibernation, was released back in 2011 and still stands as by far my favourite album to emerge from the stampede of lo-fi singer songwriters of recent years. Rarely going beyond a minimalist combination of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AMS Album of the Week 15
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-28-ams-album-of-the-week-15/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 23:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-28-ams-album-of-the-week-15/</guid>
        <description>The release of Wonderful, Glorious, the 10th album from long-tenured indie rock band Eels presents a worrying fact about music: sometimes, artists are overshadowed by their own success. Almost wholly the project of frontman Mark Oliver Everett, Eels’ music has been intensely personal: their debut …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Graphite supercapacitors are taking charge
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-28-graphite-supercapacitors-are-taking-charge/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 18:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-28-graphite-supercapacitors-are-taking-charge/</guid>
        <description>In a viral video released last week from the website www.upworthy.com, Richard Kaner and Maher El-Kady of the University of California, Los Angeles revealed that they have discovered a cheap and efficient new way of manufacturing graphene, in a way which could lead to the development of affordable …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A treatment for women vulnerable to miscarriages?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-a-treatment-for-women-vulnerable-to-miscarriages/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2013 01:52:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-a-treatment-for-women-vulnerable-to-miscarriages/</guid>
        <description>Researchers at Imperial College and the University of Warwick have identified molecular signals produced by cells in the womb saying whether an embryo can implant there or not, and suggest that drugs affecting these signals could be used to treat women vulnerable to miscarriages.
A fertilised embryo …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>But are you are scientist doe?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-but-are-you-are-scientist-doe/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2013 01:38:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-but-are-you-are-scientist-doe/</guid>
        <description>It’s happened: geek is chic, nerds are sexy, and everyone and their dog is ready to debate with creationists. Like Brian Cox’s smiling, wistful face, science itself is increasingly entering the public consciousness. Every haunt of internet culture – Reddit, 4chan, your Facebook friends, etc. – …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Moar elections!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-23-moar-elections/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2012 00:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-23-moar-elections/</guid>
        <description>Much like a promise to lower taxes, a call for more democracy is a cheap tactic for winning votes, yet one that, in what seems to be a continuing trend, the Conservative party have managed to completely cock up.
For those of youwho don’t know, last Thursday saw England and Wales’ first election for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Extremophiles found in Atacama
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-extremophiles-found-in-atacama/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 20:13:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-extremophiles-found-in-atacama/</guid>
        <description>New microbial lifeforms have been discovered on the slopes of high-altitude volcanoes in the Atacama desert, South America, an area previously thought inhospitable. Temperatures range from -10°C to 56°C, and incident ultraviolet radiation is twice that at sea level in the extremely arid areas where …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Just a joke?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-just-a-joke/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 21:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-just-a-joke/</guid>
        <description>Let me ask: what have you personally done to prevent rape recently? If you’re a man, the answer is hopefully “not raped anyone.” If you’re a woman, the answers will be many: avoiding dark places at night, avoiding walking alone, taking a taxi rather than public transport, not making eye contact with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sexism forum held at Union
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-sexism-forum-held-at-union/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 21:36:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-sexism-forum-held-at-union/</guid>
        <description>A forum on sexism at Imperial College was held on Tuesday, with the intention of investigating the extent of sexism within the college as well as brainstorming plans on how best to address it.
Earlier this term, a proposal to create a feminist society was submitted to the New Clubs Committee, who …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lubricated wood grinds better
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-lubricated-wood-grinds-better/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 19:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-lubricated-wood-grinds-better/</guid>
        <description>Scientists at Imperial College have discovered that efficiency savings of up to 80% in the production of biofuel can be made by lubricating the wood biomass.
Biofuels are used widely in Brazil, where all light vehicles run on ethanol or a 25% ethanol in gasoline blend, and the USA where gasoline …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The impact of immaturity
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-the-impact-of-immaturity/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 22:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-the-impact-of-immaturity/</guid>
        <description>Gaming has boomed recently: its popularity, company profits and presence in popular culture are at a level unimaginable twenty years ago. No one bats an eyelid if you say you play videogames, and the stereotype of a game player being a ‘nerd’ (and all that comes with it) is thankfully being broken …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Student mayoral manifesto launched
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-2-student-mayoral-manifesto-launched/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 01:06:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-2-student-mayoral-manifesto-launched/</guid>
        <description>A student manifesto has been released in light of the London mayoral and assembly elections in May. The document, produced by Student Vision for London in collaboration with many London universities’ student unions, outlines nine key issues for students with demands for the mayoral candidates to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First ever TEDx conference comes to Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-first-ever-tedx-conference-comes-to-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 00:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-first-ever-tedx-conference-comes-to-imperial/</guid>
        <description>The first ever TEDx conference to be held at Imperial is coming this March. Organised by a team of Imperial students, TEDxImperialCollege will feature live lectures and online videos in the TED format. The event on March 24 is titled The Great Exhibition and will “explore the connection between …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Quantum information rate measured
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-quantum-information-rate-measured/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 19:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-quantum-information-rate-measured/</guid>
        <description>Scientists have measured the rate at which quantum information travels through real systems. Changes, such as those in electronic spin or energy, propagate through materials at a limited speed; similar to the speed of light, this maximum theoretical limit known as the Lieb-Robinson bound has now …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fort Dwarfness. Wait, what?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-fort-dwarfness-wait-what/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 20:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-fort-dwarfness-wait-what/</guid>
        <description>Deep underground, a lonely dwarf miner breaks into an expansive cavern. As he stumbles out into the darkness, two trolls immediately set upon him. “Bugger,” I say, pausing the game to take a sip of tea, and plan best how to save him. I order my soldiers to go down and join the fight. Meanwhile, my …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A ode to the beauty of Minecraft
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-a-ode-to-the-beauty-of-minecraft/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 20:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-a-ode-to-the-beauty-of-minecraft/</guid>
        <description>Happy birthday, Minecraft, my sweetling. You’ve been like my own child all these years, but you’re all grown-up now, your features well formed and bug-free; yet you’re worth only a modest €20. It wasn’t always this way, you know. Oh yes - I remember before you were born.
Spring, 2009, what a fine …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why I hate entrepreneurs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-why-i-hate-entrepreneurs/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 20:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Keir Little,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-why-i-hate-entrepreneurs/</guid>
        <description>Don’t get me wrong – I take my hat off to anyone who can fashion a new idea, start a business, and successfully market it. But, despite this admiration (they’d be quick to call it envy), entrepreneurs are the most insufferable people that have ever talked at (rather than to) me.
Whether they’re …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
