<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/nf311/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/nf311/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Student’s death prompts riots at Ain Shams University, Cairo
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-students-death-prompts-riots-at-ain-shams-university-cairo/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 01:13:26 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nicholas Farmer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-29-students-death-prompts-riots-at-ain-shams-university-cairo/</guid>
        <description>Ain Shams University in Cairo has had to cancel exams after fears of protests by students following the controversial death of Engineering student Islam Salah Al-Din Atitu.
Atitu’s body was found on a desert road hours after he was called out of an exam by University staff at the request of an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can religion and science get on?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-14-can-religion-and-science-get-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 22:00:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nicholas Farmer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-14-can-religion-and-science-get-on/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Union Debating Society’s first public debate of the year saw students debate Lord Professor Robert Winston and Bioengineering Senior Lecturer Dr Jennifer Siggers on the motion “This house believes that religion is harmful to the progress of science” in front of a packed lecture …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Royal School of Mines wins the Bottle Match for the fifth year in a row
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-6-royal-school-of-mines-wins-the-bottle-match-for-the-fifth-year-in-a-row/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 14:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nicholas Farmer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-6-royal-school-of-mines-wins-the-bottle-match-for-the-fifth-year-in-a-row/</guid>
        <description>For the fifth year running Imperial’s Royal School of Mines were victorious in the Bottle Match against Camborne School of Mines, held at the Harlington Sports Ground on February 21st. Teams from the two mining schools went head to head in badminton, squash, netball, hockey, football and rugby in a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don’t get swept away by the Green Surge
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-9-dont-get-swept-away-by-the-green-surge/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 19:48:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nicholas Farmer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-9-dont-get-swept-away-by-the-green-surge/</guid>
        <description>The Greens have been all over the news recently, from David Cameron’s insistence that they appear in general election debates earlier this year, to the announcement that their membership has surpassed that of UKIP and is rapidly rising. The Green Party would have us believe that this is the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Crime Scene: Memory Lane
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-crime-scene-memory-lane/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 18:42:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nicholas Farmer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-crime-scene-memory-lane/</guid>
        <description>I recently took a stroll down the online memory lane that is the Felix archive, all the way back to the heady days of 1998. Times have changed.
Back then it was acceptable to write in to Felix to announce that the Union President was “utterly, utterly, utterly fucked” at the Summer Ball. It was also …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dri night&#39;s coverage does not whet the appetite
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-24-dri-nights-coverage-does-not-whet-the-appetite/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2014 13:43:03 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nicholas Farmer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-10-24-dri-nights-coverage-does-not-whet-the-appetite/</guid>
        <description>I suspect that I was not the only person disappointed to read the news article “Lesson Learnt: Never go in Dri” in last week’s issue (Felix 1584). This awful pun aside, I felt that the article unfortunately misrepresented and undermined Imperial College Union’s ‘Dri’ night, its first ever …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bergerac
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-6-bergerac/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 02:50:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nicholas Farmer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-6-bergerac/</guid>
        <description>Bergerac
This 80s gem comes to us from the scenic island of Jersey and stars good old Cornish boy John Nettles (now better known for top German TV hit, Midsummer Murders) as recovering alcoholic Jim Bergerac. Jersey native Bergerac rails against his island’s transformation from a tight knit pastoral …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tell Me it’s O-Kaye
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-24-tell-me-its-o-kaye/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 12:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nicholas Farmer,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-24-tell-me-its-o-kaye/</guid>
        <description>The most controversial of next year’s sabbatical officers is, no doubt, Chris Kaye. In an online media outlet that may never be named within these pages, we are told that the incoming Deputy President (Welfare) ran on a platform of a scaled back and cost-effective union, merging the positions of …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
