<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/lp707/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/lp707/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>“Shamazeballs?”
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-shamazeballs/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 23:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucia Podhorska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-shamazeballs/</guid>
        <description>With it being ‘Guilty Pleasures’ week on The X-Factor, I thought it oddly fitting to finally share my thoughts on the current season of one of the world’s most famous ‘talent’ shows.
The X-Factor was created by Simon Cowell and began its run on ITV back in 2004. The show has five stages: after …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where’s Buffy when you need her?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-wheres-buffy-when-you-need-her/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 18:21:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucia Podhorska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-wheres-buffy-when-you-need-her/</guid>
        <description>The Cabin in the Woods
Director Drew Goddard Screenwriters Joss Whedon, Drew Goddard Cast Kristen Connolly, Chris Hemsworth, Jesse William, Fran Kranz, Anna Hutchison
Usually, I am not a fan of horror movies, but knowing that this was written by Joss Whedon – the genius behind Buffy the Vampire …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Abrams vs. Alcatraz
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-abrams-vs-alcatraz/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 20:19:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucia Podhorska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-abrams-vs-alcatraz/</guid>
        <description>Created by J.J. Abrams, the mastermind behind Lost and Fringe, Alcatraz follows a special unit within the FBI dedicated to investigating the disappearance of the prisoners and guards from the infamous prison in 1963. The year is 2012 and the 63s, as they are commonly referred to, have started …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rooney dons her new tattoo
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-rooney-dons-her-new-tattoo/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 22:45:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucia Podhorska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-rooney-dons-her-new-tattoo/</guid>
        <description> The Girl with the Dragon Tattoo Director David Fincher Screenwriters Steven Zaillian, Stieg Larsson (novel) Cast Rooney Mara, Daniel Craig, Christopher Plummer, Robin Wright
Set in Sweden, the plot revolves around disgraced journalist Mikael Blomkvist (Craig) and 23-year-old hacker Lisbeth Salander …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Buffy – a cultural phenomenon
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-buffy-a-cultural-phenomenon/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 20:34:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucia Podhorska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-buffy-a-cultural-phenomenon/</guid>
        <description>There are shows you watch for mindless entertainment. There are shows you get hooked to, ones you simply need to watch every week. And then there are shows that come to define so many aspects of your life. For me, Buffy the Vampire Slayer is just that show.
In 1992, a man called Joss Whedon had a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sometimes answers just lead to more questions
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-sometimes-answers-just-lead-to-more-questions/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 23:06:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucia Podhorska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-sometimes-answers-just-lead-to-more-questions/</guid>
        <description>Writing reviews on shows I love is something I have found to be quite difficult. When I try to persuade someone to watch something I like, it generally ends with me saying, “Erm, yeah, you just need to watch it, cos it’s amazing.” And reviewing a show like LOST is even harder, because I never want …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Best in Class: Comedy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-best-in-class-comedy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 06:13:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucia Podhorska,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-best-in-class-comedy/</guid>
        <description>I am known in my group of friends as being somewhat obsessed with television and the film industry in general. I spend countless hours in front of my computer watching episode after episode of a favorite series and often find myself forgetting about the world outside and absorbing myself in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New HBO channel on Sky
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-new-hbo-channel-on-sky/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 20:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucia Podhorska,Matthew Allinson,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-new-hbo-channel-on-sky/</guid>
        <description>The Wire
When a series is chosen by Barack Obama as his favourite TV show, you know it’s going to be cool. Stand up comedian David O’Doherty made the joke that he knows people who love The Wire so much they can’t even describe it in words. “So what do you think of The Wire?” He asks, …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
