<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/nm708/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/nm708/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Centre for Doctoral Training Festival of Science next week
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-6-centre-for-doctoral-training-festival-of-science-next-week/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 02:39:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-6-centre-for-doctoral-training-festival-of-science-next-week/</guid>
        <description>The annual Centre for Doctoral Training (CDT) Festival of Science will be happening on Friday 13th June 2014 in the SAF lecture theatres. It is a chance for CDT students to come together to organise and present a showcase of current science and scientific issues to the Imperial College London …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>RCSU provides UROP Bursary for student from lower income background
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-6-rcsu-provides-urop-bursary-for-student-from-lower-income-background/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 02:38:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-6-rcsu-provides-urop-bursary-for-student-from-lower-income-background/</guid>
        <description>The RCSU UROP bursary has been awarded to an undergraduate student from the Department of Chemistry. This is a new initiative where the funding will be from the RCSU for students from lower income backgrounds.
Plabon Saha commented: “We also understand that one bursary might not make a huge …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Alumnus Michael Uren Donates £40 mill. for Biomedical Engineering Hub
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-2-alumnus-michael-uren-donates-40-mill-for-biomedical-engineering-hub/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 12:38:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-2-alumnus-michael-uren-donates-40-mill-for-biomedical-engineering-hub/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London has received a £40 million donation to build a state of the art biomedical engineering centre from a former student, Michael Uren and his Foundation.
The money will go towards paying for the Michael Uren Biomedical Engineering Hub. The centre will be built at the new Imperial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Students To Take Part in Summer of Student Innovation competition
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-23-imperial-students-to-take-part-in-summer-of-student-innovation-competition/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 14:23:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-23-imperial-students-to-take-part-in-summer-of-student-innovation-competition/</guid>
        <description>Two Imperial teams have entered the Summer of Student Innovation competition. This is a competition to fund ideas that use technology that can improve research and education.
There is currently an online voting process for the ideas that have been submitted. The ideas that reach over 250 votes will …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Face to Face with Abdulla Sheikh
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-24-face-to-face-with-abdulla-sheikh/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 03:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-24-face-to-face-with-abdulla-sheikh/</guid>
        <description>Can you tell us a bit about your current business in the sustainability sector?
Yes I can! Our name is Whotter; our team consists of myself, Carlo, a PHD from Physics and Arthur a Masters student from Paris. We are trying to harness green energy from waste as never done before. It’s an innovative …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chemical Engineering PhD receives award
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-24-chemical-engineering-phd-receives-award/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 03:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-24-chemical-engineering-phd-receives-award/</guid>
        <description>Dr Maria Fernanda Jimenez Solomon was awarded the prize; which is awarded to excellent PhD students who are doing research that helps solve industrial problems. Maria’s supervisor is the Head of the Department in Chemical Engineering, Professor Andrew Livingston. Maria’s research focuses on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Joseph Interfaith Foundation Discussion – Extremism: Its Root Causes And How To Address Them
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-an-joseph-interfaith-foundation-discussion-extremism-its-root-causes-and-how-to-address-them/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 04:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-3-7-an-joseph-interfaith-foundation-discussion-extremism-its-root-causes-and-how-to-address-them/</guid>
        <description>Comment: Bension Tilley (JSoc) Extremism is one of the most hotly-debated talks of our generation. The publicity it receives in the media reflects its profound importance in modern day political discourse. It would be true to say that the vast majority of extremism that we hear of is Islamic in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Amer Hasan on winning offers from 3 Dragons on Dragons’ Den for minicab price comparison startup
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-28-amer-hasan-on-winning-offers-from-3-dragons-on-dragons-den-for-minicab-price-comparison-startup/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 07:23:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-28-amer-hasan-on-winning-offers-from-3-dragons-on-dragons-den-for-minicab-price-comparison-startup/</guid>
        <description>This week Nida Mahmud caught up with Amer Hasan, an Imperial Alumnus and CEO of minicabit. He recently appeared on Dragons’ Den and recieved offers from three out of the five Dragons. Furthermore, minicabit is the first app to win an offer on the show. Minicabit is an app and website that enables …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union submits portfolio of evidence to College’s Residential Experience Review
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-union-submits-portfolio-of-evidence-to-colleges-residential-experience-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 03:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-union-submits-portfolio-of-evidence-to-colleges-residential-experience-review/</guid>
        <description>The Residential Experience review was announced by College at the start of the year. The aim of this review is to improve the residential experience students at Imperial have. The Union were asked to submit evidence for the review, which was bought to Union Council last week and approved for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College indirectly invests £785,000 in tobacco industry
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-college-indirectly-invests-785000-in-tobacco-industry/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 03:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-21-college-indirectly-invests-785000-in-tobacco-industry/</guid>
        <description>Earlier this week the London Student revealed that Imperial College has £785,000 indirectly invested in tobacco companies. This conflicts with the extensive cancer research done by Imperial academics.
The investment is split between investment firms, the College has a £505,000 share in British …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ereira’s Business Insight
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-19-ereiras-business-insight/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 17:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-19-ereiras-business-insight/</guid>
        <description>Tavistock Tutors was set up by Marcus Ereira and Luke Shelley when they were just 17 years old. A few years on, the business has grown tremendously and they have over 300 tutors on their books. They provide private tutors for GCSE and A-levels as well as extra-curricular activities. Tavistock Tutors …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial and Dyson to launch new Robotics Lab
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-14-imperial-and-dyson-to-launch-new-robotics-lab/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 04:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-14-imperial-and-dyson-to-launch-new-robotics-lab/</guid>
        <description>A new centre that collaborates with Dyson will be launching at Imperial in the Department of Computing, this will be the Dyson Robotics Laboratory.
This will be a £5 million collaboration between Imperial and Dyson, which aims to create computer vision programs that allows robots to move beyond …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Spin-off Seeks £175m in Stock Market IPO
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-imperial-spin-off-seeks-175m-in-stock-market-ipo/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 05:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-imperial-spin-off-seeks-175m-in-stock-market-ipo/</guid>
        <description>Circassia, a spinoff company from an Imperial lab discovery in 2006 has announced that it plans to float on the London Stock Exchange. It hopes to raise approximately £175 million in the initial public offering. Carissa is Imperial Innovation’s largest portfolio company, it is a biopharmaceutical …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial launches new Global MBA
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-imperial-launches-new-global-mba/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 04:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-2-7-imperial-launches-new-global-mba/</guid>
        <description>Imperial&amp;rsquo;s new global MBA course launched, which will make its teaching available to the world. Imperial Global MBA is a part-time online programme that teaches key business information via distance learning, so the student doesn’t need to be present in classes for most of the programme. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial and Huawei to cooperate on new data laboratory
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-imperial-and-huawei-to-cooperate-on-new-data-laboratory/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 17:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-31-imperial-and-huawei-to-cooperate-on-new-data-laboratory/</guid>
        <description>A top global ICT solutions company and Imperial will collaborate and invest on a data science lab. The research will be in areas such as energy, healthcare and smart cities. David Willetts, Universities and Science Minister said: ““Science and research are major contributors to the UK economy and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Teams reach BP competition semi-finals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-imperial-teams-reach-bp-competition-semi-finals/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 09:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-imperial-teams-reach-bp-competition-semi-finals/</guid>
        <description>Imperial students have made it through to the BP Ultimate Field Trip semi-finals. Four Imperial teams (X-tek, Team Griffon, Energineers &amp;amp; The Next Frontier) have reached the semi-finals stage, which will be held on the 3rd-4th February across the UK.
The Ultimate Field Trip is the UK’s flagship …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Victoria Line suffers from Civil Engineering mishap
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-victoria-line-suffers-from-civil-engineering-mishap/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 09:44:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-victoria-line-suffers-from-civil-engineering-mishap/</guid>
        <description>The Victoria line on Thursday 23 January was partly suspended with severe delays for several hours due to fast-setting concrete. Trains were not running between Warren Street and Brixton.
Nigel Holness, the director of London Underground said: &amp;ldquo;This afternoon our contractors were working on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Imperial College India Foundation Scholarship Programme
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-college-imperial-college-india-foundation-scholarship-programme/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 09:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-college-imperial-college-india-foundation-scholarship-programme/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College and Imperial College India Foundation will be increasing the size of their scholarship programme. The scholarship is for Indian postgraduate students who have an outstanding academic background and reside in India. The programme initially begun in September 2013, this year two full …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>YoYo mobile payments app rolled out on campus
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-yoyo-mobile-payments-app-rolled-out-on-campus/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 09:41:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-yoyo-mobile-payments-app-rolled-out-on-campus/</guid>
        <description>A new app, Yoyo, for mobile payment has recently launched at Imperial. JustYoyo is a business that was launched in August 2013, it is backed by Imperial Innovations. The new app enables food and drink to be bought from shops across the South Kensington campus.
Additionally, the Yoyo app can be used …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial opens new ICT centre at Imperial West
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-imperial-opens-new-ict-centre-at-imperial-west/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 09:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-24-imperial-opens-new-ict-centre-at-imperial-west/</guid>
        <description>Imperial has opened a new centre for ICT innovation at Imperial West.
This new centre is called London Node and it hopes to bridge the gap between the research that is taken and the delivery of the products commercially.
Paul Jenkins, the director of Node said: “This new Node will allow us to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>News Bites - The news in short (Issue 1564)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-news-bites-the-news-in-short-issue-1564/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 03:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-news-bites-the-news-in-short-issue-1564/</guid>
        <description>FINANCE
Last week, Huffington Post published an article ranking the most expensive universities to live and study at in the UK. The universities were ranked in terms of their total cost of living over three years.
The cost for Imperial came to £53,822. UCL was the second most expensive university …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lords Science Select Committee opens inquiry on International STEM Students
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-lords-science-select-committee-opens-inquiry-on-international-stem-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 02:58:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-lords-science-select-committee-opens-inquiry-on-international-stem-students/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Union has helped secure an inquiry by the House of Lords for the Science and Technology Committee.
The Union has been campaigning against the Immigration Bill since last November after a paper was passed at Council opposing the proposed changes that will negatively impact our …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ULU students protest in Senate House occupation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-ulu-students-protest-in-senate-house-occupation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 03:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-ulu-students-protest-in-senate-house-occupation/</guid>
        <description>Over 100 protesters occupied the University of London (UoL’s) headquarters on Wednesday 4 December. The protest took place to demonstrate against the UoL’s “undemocratic and unaccountable” running.
The protesters demanded 10 things, that included scraping plans to close the University of London …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UUK’s report on gender segregated seating
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-uuks-report-on-gender-segregated-seating/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2013 03:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-6-uuks-report-on-gender-segregated-seating/</guid>
        <description>Last week, Universities UUK, the UK’s universities representative organisation issued guidance on helping universities manage external speakers.
They concluded that universities can segregate students during speaker events when required, as long as there is fair access to both genders.
The report …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial to create new Centres for Doctoral Training for postgraduates
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-imperial-to-create-new-centres-for-doctoral-training-for-postgraduates/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 12:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-2-imperial-to-create-new-centres-for-doctoral-training-for-postgraduates/</guid>
        <description>Over 400 postgraduates will join seven Imperial doctoral training centres in the next five years. The research will be in areas ranging from fluid dynamics to chemical biology.
There will be a total of 70 Centres for Doctoral Training (CDTs) between 24 UK universities. The research will be in areas …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Born BBOXX Gets Silicon Valley Funding
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-imperial-born-bboxx-gets-silicon-valley-funding/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 15:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-imperial-born-bboxx-gets-silicon-valley-funding/</guid>
        <description>BBOXX, a spinout company from Imperial, brings solar energy products to developing countries has been given investment backing from a Silicon Valley venture capital company. BBOXX have received $1.5m backing from Vinod Khosla, who runs a billion dollar venture capitalist firm. Additionally, the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Joins NTU Renaissance Engineering Programme
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-college-joins-ntu-renaissance-engineering-programme/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 15:38:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-college-joins-ntu-renaissance-engineering-programme/</guid>
        <description>The Nanyang Technological University’s (NTU) Renaissance Engineering Programme (REP) picks the top 50 engineering students that are trained to be the “Engineering Leaders of Tomorrow”. Last week, Imperial signed a contract with NTU agreeing to partake in this scheme. The REP students study: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial’s New Twitter Tool
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-imperials-new-twitter-tool/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 03:38:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-8-imperials-new-twitter-tool/</guid>
        <description>A group of academics at Imperial have created a tool that is able to rank the most influential speakers on any topic. This is achieved by scoring the users of Twittter; it is known as the T-index and is dependent on many times they post and are retweeted. The T-index is defined separately for each …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Smoky not Smudgy is back!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-smoky-not-smudgy-is-back/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 09:47:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-5-smoky-not-smudgy-is-back/</guid>
        <description>As Charity Week draws to an end, this Sunday marks the return of Smoky Not Smudgy (SnS); this is a flagship ladies only pampering event. SnS is run by the ladies for the ladies. All proceeds go towards the Charity Week campaign, ultimately helping orphans and needy children in the poorest parts of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lord Darzi elected by Institute of Medicine
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-lord-darzi-elected-by-institute-of-medicine/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 09:11:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-lord-darzi-elected-by-institute-of-medicine/</guid>
        <description>Professor Lord Ara Darzi has been elected by the Institute of Medicine (IOM), which is the health sector of the US National Academy of Sciences.
Becoming a member of the IOM is a high honour in the health and medical field. Last week, 70 new members and 10 new foreign associates were elected for the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial ranked 5th in QS university rankings
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-24-imperial-ranked-5th-in-qs-university-rankings/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 23:32:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-24-imperial-ranked-5th-in-qs-university-rankings/</guid>
        <description>In September the annual QS university rankings were released, Imperial College London ranked 5th place.
Massachusetts Institute of Technology topped the table for the second year running, achieving a QS score of 100. Harvard took 2nd place, Cambridge was ranked 3rd, University College London was 4th …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial names first Regius Professor
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-24-imperial-names-first-regius-professor/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 23:29:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-24-imperial-names-first-regius-professor/</guid>
        <description>Imperial conferred its first Regius Professorship on Professor Chris Toumazou on Commemoration day for undergraduate students on 23 October.
Imperial received the title of Regius Professor of Engineering in January during the Queen’s Diamond Jubilee celebrations; which was received for the work …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union Elections now open
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-18-union-elections-now-open/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 20:43:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-18-union-elections-now-open/</guid>
        <description>Union elections are kicking off again on Friday 17 at 12pm, they will be open till Tuesday 22 at 12pm.
These elections are for Reps and Union Council. This year 464 students in total have stood for elections for 115 positions. This shows an increase to the number of total candidates that ran last …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>College Chemistry department wins Athena SWAN Gold award
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-11-college-chemistry-department-wins-athena-swan-gold-award/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 22:57:24 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-11-college-chemistry-department-wins-athena-swan-gold-award/</guid>
        <description>The Imperial Department of Chemistry has won an Athena SWAN Gold Award, making it one of the four departments in the UK to win one. This is the first gold level award for Imperial. The award acknowledges success in the increasing numbers of female students in science, which improves equality in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial’s TSU moves to UCL
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-3-imperials-tsu-moves-to-ucl/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2013 23:00:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-3-imperials-tsu-moves-to-ucl/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday 2 September, Imperial and University College London officially announced that the Translation Studies Unit (TSU) at Imperial will be moving to UCL. The TSU will be moving to UCL’s School of European Languages, Culture and Society, within the Faculty of Arts and Humanities. The school is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial slips to 113th in green league
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-imperial-slips-to-113th-in-green-league/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 23:34:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-20-imperial-slips-to-113th-in-green-league/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College London has been ranked 113th place in the People &amp;amp; Planet’s Annual Green League Table for 2013. This is a drop of 17 places since last year, where Imperial was ranked 96th place in the 2012 League Table.
The People &amp;amp; Planet are the UK’s largest student campaigning network; …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>$5000 essay prize for Imperial MBA student
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-6-5000-essay-prize-for-imperial-mba-student/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 15:26:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-6-5000-essay-prize-for-imperial-mba-student/</guid>
        <description>Mike Follett, a MBA student at the Business School has been awarded the first place award for an advertising competition, ADMAP prize 2013 for his essay. The essay was entitled “Thinking in 3D”. Mike will receive the Gold award and a cheque for $5,000 at the ADMAP Prize celebration event on June …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What religion truly means
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-30-what-religion-truly-means/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2013 14:44:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-30-what-religion-truly-means/</guid>
        <description>Isa’s name translates to “Jesus” in English; Jesus is an important prophet for Muslims, one who strived for the betterment of mankind. Isa tried to emulate the qualities of the prophet by devoting his youth, health, richness, time and, ultimately, life, for the sake of God through humanitarianism. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial alumnus killed in Syria
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-30-imperial-alumnus-killed-in-syria/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2013 14:42:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,Tim Arbabzadah,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-30-imperial-alumnus-killed-in-syria/</guid>
        <description>An Imperial alumnus has been killed in Syria after a bomb hit the field hospital where he was treating patients in challenging conditions. Isa Abdur Rahman (pictured), 26, was a medical student at Imperial and was killed while helping the British charity Hand In Hand for Syria (HIHS).
Dr Rahman was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Extra Sabbatical remits discussed
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-30-extra-sabbatical-remits-discussed/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2013 13:22:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-30-extra-sabbatical-remits-discussed/</guid>
        <description>Union Council has discussed giving extra remits and remaing the Sabbatical positions in the Union (except for Felix Editor and Medics President). Over the last ten years, the Union roles and remits for the President and four deputy Presidents have been kept relatively constant.
The paper was brought …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>London based Hedge Fund donates £20m to set up research centre
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-london-based-hedge-fund-donates-20m-to-set-up-research-centre/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 00:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-london-based-hedge-fund-donates-20m-to-set-up-research-centre/</guid>
        <description>A London-based Hedge Fund, Brevan Howard, have decided to donate £20.1 million ($30 million) to Imperial College in order to set up a finance research centre after them.
The money will be given to the Business School at Imperial; the founder of the hedge fund, Alan Howard, studied Chemical …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FinanceSoc named one of the top four societies at national awards
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-financesoc-named-one-of-the-top-four-societies-at-national-awards/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 00:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-1-financesoc-named-one-of-the-top-four-societies-at-national-awards/</guid>
        <description>Last week, Imperial College’s Finance Society (ICFS) was named one of the top four student societies in the country by Rate My Placement. This was the only Imperial society representing Imperial at the National Placement &amp;amp; Internship Awards 2013. ICFS was recognised for “outstanding commitment …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Think tank: £9000 fees cost more than save
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-think-tank-9000-fees-cost-more-than-save/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 00:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-think-tank-9000-fees-cost-more-than-save/</guid>
        <description>The Treasury has estimated that £1.7 bn will be saved by having higher tuition fees and putting an end to the teaching allowances.
However, the loss in potential earning by students notpursuing a degree will cause an increase of £3.6 bn, this figure was quoted by the university think-tank million+. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Successful week for RAG
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-21-successful-week-for-rag/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 23:57:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-21-successful-week-for-rag/</guid>
        <description>Raising and Giving (RAG), the charity arm of Imperial College Union had their annual RAG Week during 11-15 February. It was a week of fun filled events that raise money for RAG’s chosen charities. David Goldsmith, RAG Chair, said “RAG took over Imperial.”
   Credit: Benjamin Lester   The thousands …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union does not support closure of Translation Studies Unit
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-union-does-not-support-closure-of-translation-studies-unit/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 21:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-union-does-not-support-closure-of-translation-studies-unit/</guid>
        <description>The Union opposes theclosure of the Translation Studies Unit (TSU), following a vote at Union Council on Tuesday 12 February. The Union will also be seeking clarification on the reasons why the Unit will be closed and how the students will be supported in the completion of their studies; this is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>SOS Syria is underway
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-sos-syria-is-underway/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 21:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-14-sos-syria-is-underway/</guid>
        <description>There has been a fantastic response to the student lead initiative, Action Syria, raising awareness about the situation in Syria at Imperial College. The turmoil in Syria has become dramatically worse over the last two years. The situation in Syria is typically reported as political issue in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Action Syria
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-8-action-syria/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 01:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-8-action-syria/</guid>
        <description>Now the big question: how can you help? And how can you learn more about the situation in Syria? Everything can be answered by twosimple words: Action Syria.
Action Syria is a student lead initiative, backed by the Union at Imperial to raise awareness and humanise the civil unrest in Syria. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Syrian students face financial hardship
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-8-syrian-students-face-financial-hardship/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 01:19:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-8-syrian-students-face-financial-hardship/</guid>
        <description>Over the last few weeks most students at university have settled back into a routine of lectures, coursework and exams as they return to university ready to face the challenges ahead. However, the story is very different for the Syrian students at UK universities; the civil war in Syria means they …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Business School to mentor Indian school
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-8-business-school-to-mentor-indian-school/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 01:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-8-business-school-to-mentor-indian-school/</guid>
        <description>Improving management education is the focus of a new alliance between Imperial College Business School and the Hero Group in India. The Business school at Imperial will assist BML Munjal University (BMU) in India, to develop its School of Management. The Business School will act as a mentor …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial students in BP semi-finals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-imperial-students-in-bp-semi-finals/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 22:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-31-imperial-students-in-bp-semi-finals/</guid>
        <description>Imperial students have made it through to the BP Ultimate Field Trip semi-finals. Five Imperial teams, each with three engineering students have reached the semi-finals stage, which will be held on the 4th-5th February across the UK.
Emma Judge, BP Head of UK Graduate Resourcing commented: “We’re …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Academic uprising: 5% more professors
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-academic-uprising-5-more-professors/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2013 01:27:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-25-academic-uprising-5-more-professors/</guid>
        <description> On 17 January, the Higher Education Statistics Agency (HESA) released the first set of data from the 2011&amp;frasl;12 Staff record. This data provides information about staff employment at UK Higher Education Institutions (HEIs) on 1 December 2011. The results have been produced in partnership with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>€25m of funding won by IC
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-17-25m-of-funding-won-by-ic/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 23:45:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-17-25m-of-funding-won-by-ic/</guid>
        <description>The European Research Council (ERC) has awarded over €25m to Imperial College in the latest funding round. These grants are for 11 projects, and these include two prestigious synergy grants that promote partnerships in academic research.
The Synergy grant scheme was piloted this year, it allocates …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Podcasting arrives, well, sort of...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-podcasting-arrives-well-sort-of/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 00:53:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-podcasting-arrives-well-sort-of/</guid>
        <description> The implementationof video lecture recordings across the College has been a hot topic for discussion of late. Although video lectures have been piloted in Imperial for certain years in certain departments, the scheme is not yet available to all students.
The Panopto lecture recording suite is being …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Business school gets triple accreditation
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-business-school-gets-triple-accreditation/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 00:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-business-school-gets-triple-accreditation/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Business School has achieved triple accreditation. This comes after meeting the required standard from the Association to Advance Collegiate Schools of Business (AACSB). The Business school is now in the top 1% of business schools in the world to have triple accreditation from the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Research centre opens at Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-new-research-centre-opens-at-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 22:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-new-research-centre-opens-at-imperial/</guid>
        <description>Last week a new research centre opened at Imperial College London in St. Mary’s Hospital: The Imperial Clinical Phenome Centre. This is the second phenome centre to be launched this year in the UK, both centres are based at Imperial College. The centre is led by both Imperial College London and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union hiring new staff
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-union-hiring-new-staff/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 22:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-22-union-hiring-new-staff/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Union is hiring four new staff members whose combined salaries total over £100,000 per year, the budget for which was approved last year.
The salaries and job descriptions for these staff members used to be found online on the Union’s website. However, it has since been removed as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sciences are sliced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-sciences-are-sliced/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 20:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-sciences-are-sliced/</guid>
        <description>Overall government spending on Science, Engineering and Technology (SET) has fallen in real terms by £733m.
The drop from 2009-10 to 2010-11 (which is the most recent figures released) is the first fall since betwen the 2005-6 and 2006-7. The years between 2006-7 and 2009-10 have all seen an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Down to business?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-down-to-business/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 00:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nida Mahmud,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-down-to-business/</guid>
        <description> Imperial College London has consistently ranked within the World Top 10 in the QS rankings as well as in other respectable league tables. However, Imperial’s Business school rankings for the MBA programme are slipping, with Imperial’s MBA currently being ranked 46th place in the Financial Times. …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
