<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mb1111/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/mb1111/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>E3 Nintendo: Focus on the old
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-11-e3-nintendo-focus-on-the-old/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 21:43:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Barclay,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-11-e3-nintendo-focus-on-the-old/</guid>
        <description>Last up we have Nintendo and like last year they’re opting for a “Digital event” instead a press conference like the other big two. Essentially this means a series or pre-recorded announcements much like their regular Nintendo Direct events. Personally I see it as a cop out and as indicative of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>E3 Sony: Exclusives, Now
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-11-e3-sony-exclusives-now/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 21:41:59 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Barclay,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-11-e3-sony-exclusives-now/</guid>
        <description>Sony were the next of the big three to take the stage. Last year, Sony’s conference was a roaring success; a two hour “fuck you” to Microsoft. Rumour has it they initially planned to implement the same restrictive DRM with the PS4 but changed all this after the Xbox One backlash. Whether this change …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>E3 Microsoft: Focus on Gamers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-11-e3-microsoft-focus-on-gamers/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 21:40:19 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Barclay,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-6-11-e3-microsoft-focus-on-gamers/</guid>
        <description>It&amp;rsquo;s June, terms almost over and that can only mean one thing! Yes it’s E3 and it’s time for some of the worst, most awkward press conferences you’ll see all year. As always we begin with Microsoft. It’s fair to say that in the few short months since the Xbox One has been out sales have been …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Final Fantasy XIV: A Social MMORPG
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-final-fantasy-xiv-a-social-mmorpg/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 01:59:16 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Barclay,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-5-2-final-fantasy-xiv-a-social-mmorpg/</guid>
        <description>I can’t talk about Final Fantasy XIV without first talking about its predecessor: Final Fantasy XI, Square Enix’s first MMORPG. Released way back in 2002, FFXI was an amazing and beautifully flawed game. I have a bit of a love-hate relationship when it comes to MMOs. Of the several I’ve played they …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pondering Pandora
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-pondering-pandora/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2012 02:42:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Barclay,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-26-pondering-pandora/</guid>
        <description>Borderlands was, to be frank, a pretty weird concept. Combining a fully-fledged first person shooter with a Diablo-style loot-centric RPG? These ideas seem pretty hard to gel, when first thought about, but Borderlands worked because it just didn’t take itself seriously at all. The whole thing was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gamer girls get the shaft...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-gamer-girls-get-the-shaft/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:39:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Barclay,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-gamer-girls-get-the-shaft/</guid>
        <description>The fact that the majority of gamers are male is hardly a controversial statement. It’s almost tautological. Guys like games, girls don’t. Yet, fundamentally, I don’t see why one’s fondness of gaming should be so dominated by a person’s sex. Games are, at their most basic level, just interactive …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>OMG WTF FTL FTW
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-omg-wtf-ftl-ftw/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 21:38:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Michael Barclay,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-18-omg-wtf-ftl-ftw/</guid>
        <description>When I first met the new Games Editor we both agreed that Felix needed reviews of proper mainstream games. Indie games are great fun and it’s fantastic how the games industry is moving in this direction. However, those triple-A £40 games are the bread and butter of most people’s collections and what …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
