<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ak6309/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ak6309/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Courses suspended at Silwood
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-24-courses-suspended-at-silwood/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 22:36:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-24-courses-suspended-at-silwood/</guid>
        <description>Concerns regarding staff shortages have risen as entry to postgraduate courses in the Department of Life Sciences has been suspended. Courses such as the Entomology MRes and MSc and Integrated Pest Management MSc, held in Silwood Park, and Plant Science and Biotechnology MSc, held in South …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Break-in at Beit Hall
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-9-break-in-at-beit-hall/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 01:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,Aemun Reza,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-9-break-in-at-beit-hall/</guid>
        <description>Student residence Beit Hall was disrupted on Wednesday 29 February following a series of thefts that took place during a fire alarm. Following the alarm, which began at 1am and lasted for 45 minutes, students who left their doors open during the commotion returned to find items such as cash, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Interviewing the Faculty Union Presidents
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-2-interviewing-the-faculty-union-presidents/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 01:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-2-interviewing-the-faculty-union-presidents/</guid>
        <description>LUKE KANCZES – ROYAL COLLEGE OF SCIENCE UNION (RCSU) PRESIDENT
How have you improved the RCSU since last year? The biggest thing that’s improved this year has been The Science Challenge. Thanks to Paul Beaumont’s work as Science Challenge Chair we’ve managed to secure sponsorship and really revive …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Online petition to prevent mountain hut charges
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-2-online-petition-to-prevent-mountain-hut-charges/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 00:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-2-online-petition-to-prevent-mountain-hut-charges/</guid>
        <description>Having made the decision earlier this year, Sport Imperial began charging for a mountain hut used by various Clubs &amp;amp; Societies as a rest stop during outdoor trips. At first, the hut was free to use by societies and houses approximately twenty-five people. Prices of £50 for booking weekend use …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Life of Death
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-the-life-of-death/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 21:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-the-life-of-death/</guid>
        <description>I was lucky enough to buy a ticket to the Malaysian Society’s MNight long before the sales rush which rendered the Saturday showing sold out. It was a two-day production held in the Great Hall, and I attended the Sunday showing. It was the first time I’d been to such an event in my three years here, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nominations open for Union Big Elections
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-nominations-open-for-union-big-elections/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 22:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-nominations-open-for-union-big-elections/</guid>
        <description>Nominations for the Union’s ‘Big Elections’ opened on Monday 13 February with students able to put themselves forward as candidates for departmental and sabbatical positions. The site’s look and feel has been radically changed from previous elections, and the voting statistics have reportedly been …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flaws exposed in National Student Survey
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-flaws-exposed-in-national-student-survey/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 22:19:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-flaws-exposed-in-national-student-survey/</guid>
        <description>Students from the Department of Computing have teamed up with Felix to uncover methods which can be used to skew data being submitted to the National Student Survey (NSS) in favour of Imperial College.
The flaws rely on the availability of basic information required to pose as another student in the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>On rigging the NSS
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-on-rigging-the-nss/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 21:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-on-rigging-the-nss/</guid>
        <description>Our front page story this week uncovered a method students from the Department of Computing found to be able to mass impersonate final year students in the National Student Survey (NSS), effectively skewing the results in favour of Imperial. Of course, the aforementioned technique of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mind reading programs?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-mind-reading-programs/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 21:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-mind-reading-programs/</guid>
        <description>Scientists from the University of California, Berkley, have been able to successfully determine fragments of people’s thoughts by decoding brain activity caused by words they hear.
The study has given researchers further insight into how the brain processes language and paves the way for devices …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Vintage bar night for hockey club
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-vintage-bar-night-for-hockey-club/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 21:32:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-vintage-bar-night-for-hockey-club/</guid>
        <description>The Imperial College Hockey Club (ICHC) hosted a bar night at Vintage, formerly Chateau 6, on Thursday last week. The event was open to all students and served as a way for both students involved in sports and others to blow off some steam before the all-important Varsity games this March.
The event …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Does Computer Science hold the answer?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-does-computer-science-hold-the-answer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 11:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-does-computer-science-hold-the-answer/</guid>
        <description>Computer Science is an often misunderstood academic topic. Many people outside the field do not perceive the breadth and depth of research material that’s pumped out daily and how it affects our everyday lives. To observe its profound effect in the real world, we must first examine the theoretical. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Exhibition Road closes for grand opening
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-exhibition-road-closes-for-grand-opening/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2012 00:28:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,Philip Kent,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-3-exhibition-road-closes-for-grand-opening/</guid>
        <description>Following two years of construction, Exhibition Road closed last Wednesday for its grand opening led by the Mayor of London, Boris Johnson. ‘No parking’ signs were put up in advance and the event saw a day long closure marking the opening of the brand new signature road running through the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Faster Fast Fourier Transform found
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-faster-fast-fourier-transform-found/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 19:37:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-faster-fast-fourier-transform-found/</guid>
        <description>Researchers at MIT have discovered a new method of performing the Fast Fourier Transform algorithm which, in a large set of use cases, adds performance improvements. The MIT group submitted their paper, “Nearly Optimal Sparse Fourier Transform” to ArXiv on 12 January and presented their findings in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>SOPA: who got the last lulz?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-sopa-who-got-the-last-lulz/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 22:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-sopa-who-got-the-last-lulz/</guid>
        <description>You cannot censor the Internet. You cannot subpoena a hashtag. You cannot arrest an idea. You CAN expect us.” These are the words of decentralised hacktivist online group Anonymous, tweeted as they launched a hailstorm of Distributed Denial of Service (DDOS) attacks on various websites just hours …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>RCSU launches Science Challenge 2012
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-rcsu-launches-science-challenge-2012/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 22:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-rcsu-launches-science-challenge-2012/</guid>
        <description>The Royal College of Science Union (RCSU) launched the Science Challenge 2012 on Tuesday 18 January after holding an event that saw students turn out in force. The launch event, held in the Sir Alexander Fleming building, revealed the questions which this year&amp;rsquo;s Science Challenge revolve …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Permission granted for Fisher Hall development
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-permission-granted-for-fisher-hall-development/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 22:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-permission-granted-for-fisher-hall-development/</guid>
        <description>The topic of Fisher Hall’s closure in Evelyn Gardens has been revived after a planning permission request from the college aiming to shift the building’s use from Halls of Residence to Care Housing was granted. The request, put forth by both Imperial College and The Wellcome Trust, was approved on …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LHC finds its first new particle
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-lhc-finds-its-first-new-particle/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 22:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-12-lhc-finds-its-first-new-particle/</guid>
        <description>Over the Christmas holidays, CERN’s Large Hadron Collider (LHC) in Geneva reported its first particle discovery since opening in 2009. Named Chi_b (3P), the particle was recorded by ATLAS, one of four detectors within the LHC, and is a more excited state of the Chi particle.
Chi particles are part …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Plans to digitise Newton&#39;s handwritten Principia going ahead
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-24-plans-to-digitise-newtons-handwritten-principia-going-ahead/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2011 22:48:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-24-plans-to-digitise-newtons-handwritten-principia-going-ahead/</guid>
        <description>Cambridge University is to give the public access to Sir Isaac Newton&amp;rsquo;s own annotated copy of the Principia Mathematica online, along with several of his other papers. Newton, born on Christmas Day in 1642, shares credit with Gottfried Leibniz for the developments in integral and differential …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lasers may hold key to cryptography
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-lasers-may-hold-key-to-cryptography/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 20:54:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-lasers-may-hold-key-to-cryptography/</guid>
        <description>“The generation of random numbers is too important to be left to chance.” This was the title of a 1970 article by recognised expert in pseudo-random number generation Robert R Coveyou. There are many controversies surrounding the various algorithms used to generate numbers with the illusion of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let it snow, let it snow...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-let-it-snow-let-it-snow/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 20:38:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Oakes,Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-let-it-snow-let-it-snow/</guid>
        <description>Snowflakes start out life as small particles of dust in a high up cloud. Water freezes around the dust particles, forming tiny ice crystals. At first, the ice crystals grow slowly, developing flat sides known as facets. At this stage they are hexagonal prisms, with eight sides or facets – two shaped …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science Challenge winners announced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-science-challenge-winners-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 21:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-science-challenge-winners-announced/</guid>
        <description>The Royal College of Science Union (RCSU) held a formal dinner for alumni and the Science Challenge 2011 winners on Thursday 24 November. The Science Challenge competition is an annual, national scientific essay writing competition aiming to encourage scientific debate, reasoning and the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Facebook is making the world even smaller
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-facebook-is-making-the-world-even-smaller/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 19:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-facebook-is-making-the-world-even-smaller/</guid>
        <description>Facebook has conducted a joint study which suggests that there are on average 3.74 degrees of separation between users on the popular social networking website. The study, joint between Facebook’s data scientist Lars Backstrom and four researchers from the University of Milan, found that the number …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wavefunction may be real after all
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-wavefunction-may-be-real-after-all/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 20:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-wavefunction-may-be-real-after-all/</guid>
        <description>Scientists at Imperial College London have presented a theorem which suggests that the wavefunction is a physical object. The paper, which emphasises that the quantum state cannot be interpreted statistically, was submitted on November 14 and has potential to shake the foundations of quantum theory. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Quantum information
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-quantum-information/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 20:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-quantum-information/</guid>
        <description>Two developing technologies have been touted to mark the emergence of new quantum systems. Published in the journal Science last month, the fields of plasmonics and nanophotonics promise to speed up the advent of quantum information systems, which are capable of achieving processing powers that are …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tearing apart the vacuum of space
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-tearing-apart-the-vacuum-of-space/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 21:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-tearing-apart-the-vacuum-of-space/</guid>
        <description>Physicists are proposing an experiment that will require the world’s most powerful laser. The Extreme Light Infrastructure (ELI) Ultra-High Field Facility is touted to produce a laser so powerful that it would be able to pull together the fabric of space, vacuums.
A vacuum is generally believed to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Finals reveal Imperial University Challenge team
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-finals-reveal-imperial-university-challenge-team/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 19:48:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-finals-reveal-imperial-university-challenge-team/</guid>
        <description>Internal contests for Imperial’s University Challenge selection took place last week in the Blackett lab, with the initial tryouts on Thursday 3 November seeing attendance figures upwards of 130 students hoping to get onto the team. Sixty questions sent in by the show were asked in the space of an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Float like a social butterfly
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-float-like-a-social-butterfly/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 21:43:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-float-like-a-social-butterfly/</guid>
        <description>You may notice a story I ran in the Science section last week regarding a study which linked the amount of Facebook friends to the size of an individual’s grey matter. It is interesting to note that there have been many studies which have correlated changing brain structures to internet usage. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Council talk Balls and bars
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-council-talk-balls-and-bars/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 19:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Maciej Matuszewski,Navid Nabijou,Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-council-talk-balls-and-bars/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Union held its second Council meeting of the term on Monday 31 October, with all full members of Council attending for the first time. A variety of papers revolving around ongoing issues were brought forward with resolution reached for some.
Summer Ball Debrief
Serious issues about …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Study links Facebook friends with brain regions
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-28-study-links-facebook-friends-with-brain-regions/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 00:16:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-28-study-links-facebook-friends-with-brain-regions/</guid>
        <description>A study by UCL researchers suggests that the size of certain brain regions in an individual may be linked to their number of Facebook friends. The researchers found a strong correlation between the number of friends and the amount of grey matter in regions including the amygdala, the right superior …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>CGCU Dinner brings in the engineers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-cgcu-dinner-brings-in-the-engineers/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 20:12:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-cgcu-dinner-brings-in-the-engineers/</guid>
        <description>The City &amp;amp; Guilds College Union (CGCU) held their Welcome Dinner event along with an afterparty, on Tuesday 25 October at Café De Paris, marking their flagship event. The party attracted over 600 students, testing the 700 capacity of Café De Paris, with a three course dinner starting from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Could the American university system work here?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-could-the-american-university-system-work-here/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 22:59:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexandra Nowbar,Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-could-the-american-university-system-work-here/</guid>
        <description>Yes - Alexander Karapetian
We shouldn’t be so quick to react negatively towards the recent intention to change towards the American style system of having a Grade Point Average (GPA) by UCL. Students under the UK classification system are often under great pressures to attain a degree with 2:1 or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>RCSU Autumn Ball a hit for freshers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-rcsu-autumn-ball-a-hit-for-freshers/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 20:09:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-rcsu-autumn-ball-a-hit-for-freshers/</guid>
        <description>A barrage of freshers descended on Opal Bar in Embankment on Wednesday for the Royal College of Science Union’s (RCSU) Autumn Ball, where the faculty hosted their first major event of the year. Promising three free drinks, student prices throughout the night and rides across London on a vintage fire …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Scientists&#39; responsibilities outlined
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-scientists-responsibilities-outlined/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 09:47:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-scientists-responsibilities-outlined/</guid>
        <description>The General Assembly of the International Council for Science (ICSU) have recently recognised guidelines regarding the responsibilities and universal values which should be considered by scientists. The new wording of the Principle of Universality of Science, a prerequisite to membership of the ICSU …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cells captured in highest detail
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-cells-captured-in-highest-detail/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 09:39:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-cells-captured-in-highest-detail/</guid>
        <description>Researchers from Imperial College teamed up with the University of Oxford were able to reveal how white blood cells kill diseased tissue using deadly granules in more detail than ever before. The findings were published in the Public Library of Science (PLoS) and outline the use of optical laser …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stolen medic mascot scandal
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-stolen-medic-mascot-scandal/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 00:08:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-stolen-medic-mascot-scandal/</guid>
        <description>Luke Kanczes, President of the Royal College of Science Union (RCSU) successfully stole the Imperial College School of Medicine Students&amp;rsquo; Union&amp;rsquo;s (ICSMSU) Phoenix mascot head earlier this week with RCSU Vice-President Paul Beaumont in a mascotry scandal that continues today. The RCSU …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>While you were away...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-9-30-while-you-were-away/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2011 11:02:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Kelly Oakes,Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-9-30-while-you-were-away/</guid>
        <description>While you’ve been busy travelling the world, waiting for term to start, the staff at Imperial have been pushing the boundaries of human knowledge. The keen students amongst you may be aware of what headlines Imperial has been making over the last few months. But for those of you whose New Scientist …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Registration chaos for Business School courses
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-registration-chaos-for-business-school-courses/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 19:13:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-registration-chaos-for-business-school-courses/</guid>
        <description>The registration system for optional course modules in Business In Science, Engineering &amp;amp; Technology (BEST) was hit with problems on Monday. The Departmental Student System (DSS) used for registering optional modules in courses across college was swamped with connection requests as students …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Department of Mathematics top in Europe for research
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-department-of-mathematics-top-in-europe-for-research/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 19:43:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-department-of-mathematics-top-in-europe-for-research/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College has been ranked as having the most influential mathematics research of any institution in Europe by a recent chart created by Thomson-Reuters. Ranked 13th for top institutions in mathematics, above any non-US institution overall, Imperial is listed as having 777 papers with 5,369 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Former Rector sacked from board
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-former-rector-sacked-from-board/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 19:25:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-former-rector-sacked-from-board/</guid>
        <description>Sir Richard Sykes, a former Rector of Imperial College, is one of two people to have be ousted in a boardroom coup within the Eurasian Natural Resources Company (ENRC) two weeks ago. The former chairman of GlaxoSmithKline and now ex-deputy chairman of the Kazakh mining company was removed from the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tory MP implicated in Conservative Society tour charge
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-tory-mp-implicated-in-conservative-society-tour-charge/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 18:53:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-tory-mp-implicated-in-conservative-society-tour-charge/</guid>
        <description>Greg Hands, MP for Chelsea and Fulham and parliamentary private secretary to George Osborne, is alleged to have been involved in the prohibited sale of tickets for a tour of the Houses of Parliament by the Conservative Society at Imperial.
Politicalscrapbook.net, which describes its content as “left …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Enthusiasts create Steve Jobs birthday website
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-enthusiasts-create-steve-jobs-birthday-website/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 20:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-enthusiasts-create-steve-jobs-birthday-website/</guid>
        <description>The time was 4am on the 23rd of February. A relatively large coursework deadline loomed over the heads of Department of Computing students Gabriel Lorin and Raoul Gabriel Urma, but this was not what they were pulling an all nighter for. Having purchased server equipment and spent since noon the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Further disruption for Computing students
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-further-disruption-for-computing-students/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 20:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-further-disruption-for-computing-students/</guid>
        <description>Following the recent root level security breach in the Department of Computing (DoC), sources have informed Felix that the Computing Support Group (CSG) endeavoured to successfully patch all affected physical lab machines, rendering them safe to access and free from keylogging or other malicious …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>1300 lose home directory access
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-1300-lose-home-directory-access/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 21:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-1300-lose-home-directory-access/</guid>
        <description>A problem arising while moving user data between server disks last week resulted in the temporary outage of over 1300 student and staff profiles. The problem began on the morning of Monday 21st February, when staff and students found that their home directory was empty and that they had no profile …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Video games just aren’t as good as they used to be
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-video-games-just-arent-as-good-as-they-used-to-be/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 12:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-video-games-just-arent-as-good-as-they-used-to-be/</guid>
        <description>I have a younger sibling. He&amp;rsquo;s quite the games enthusiast. Whenever I visit home, I notice some new console videogame being played on the TV and I&amp;rsquo;m often greeted with an explanation of the gameplay. I can&amp;rsquo;t help but notice, however, that commitment to single games has weakened …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Department of Computing server hacked
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-department-of-computing-server-hacked/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 11:47:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-department-of-computing-server-hacked/</guid>
        <description>The Department of Computing (DoC) has suffered a security breach on their main shell server, named shell1, which provides secure shell access to the lab machines from outside the department. On the 24th of February, the College’s ICT Service Desk issued an email to DoC students informing them of a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PhD funding woes hit Business School
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-phd-funding-woes-hit-business-school/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 19:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-phd-funding-woes-hit-business-school/</guid>
        <description>A group of five PhD students have expressed complaints after they encountered issues with funding from the Imperial College Business School. The students, ranging from second to third years on the Graduate Teaching Assistant (GTA) scholarship scheme complained that they were expected to perform …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lord Kerr resigns after six years as Imperial Council Chair
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-lord-kerr-resigns-after-six-years-as-imperial-council-chair/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 18:11:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-lord-kerr-resigns-after-six-years-as-imperial-council-chair/</guid>
        <description>Lord Kerr, Chairman of the Imperial College Council for over six years, intends to step down in the Summer, a staff briefing indicated. The briefing included an announcement inviting members of the College to encourage people they know as suitable candidates to express interest.
John Olav Kerr, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Biology Professor awarded Weldon Prize
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-biology-professor-awarded-weldon-prize/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 21:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-biology-professor-awarded-weldon-prize/</guid>
        <description>Professor Russell S. Lande, a Royal Society researcher from the Division of Biology at Imperial, has been awarded the Weldon Memorial Prize for 2010. The prize, known as the Weldon Memorial Prize and Medal, is awarded annually by the University of Oxford and is named in honor of Walter Frank Raphael …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Pro-Rector announced
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-new-pro-rector-announced/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 21:47:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-new-pro-rector-announced/</guid>
        <description>New senior medical leadership positions have been announced in a bid to strengthen integration with the UK’s first Academic Health Science Centre (AHSC). Professor Stephen Smith, Principal of the Faculty of Medicine and Chief Executive of the Imperial College Healthcare NHS Trust, is to become Pro …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Firefox add-on leaves private student data open to snoopers
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-firefox-add-on-leaves-private-student-data-open-to-snoopers/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 19:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-firefox-add-on-leaves-private-student-data-open-to-snoopers/</guid>
        <description>Wireless network security has very often been the subject of criticism, and a proof of concept tool released two weeks ago called FireSheep outlined how a combination of security problems on websites and wireless networks can result in the disclosure of personal information. Felix was able to use …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lord Browne points to higher fees
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-lord-browne-points-to-higher-fees/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 19:07:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rory Fenton,Alexander Karapetian,Anna Perman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-lord-browne-points-to-higher-fees/</guid>
        <description>Universities should be unlimited in charging fees to students, the Browne review of university funding has recommended. The influential review, released early this week, outlined various proposals and potential changes in higher education funding to the government, including lifting the current cap …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Microsoft Partners With Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-28-microsoft-partners-with-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 16:07:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-28-microsoft-partners-with-imperial/</guid>
        <description>The Imperial College Business School has been selected as the lead academic partner for Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Innovation Outreach Programme (IOP), following an agreement which came to light during a Global Investment Conference held by the Prime Minister. The role will make Imperial&amp;rsquo;s innovation, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Guilds President found
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-12-new-guilds-president-found/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 16:23:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-12-new-guilds-president-found/</guid>
        <description>Following the departure of Kirsty Patterson, former CGCU President, the City and Guilds College Union held elections to appoint a new President and Guildsheet Editor. The elections attracted respective candidates Dan Lundy and Richard Bennett, who attained their positions unopposed.
Guildsheet is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>KCL Slash Humanities
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-7-kcl-slash-humanities/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2010 03:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-7-kcl-slash-humanities/</guid>
        <description>King&amp;rsquo;s College London faces controversy and fierce opposition as they announce plans to make cuts in the School of Arts and Humanities, including the firing of several internationally renowned academics.
KCL&amp;rsquo;s Department of Philosophy are outraged pending the forced retirement of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ultimate Imperial Storm Field Trip
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-7-ultimate-imperial-storm-field-trip/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2010 03:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-2-7-ultimate-imperial-storm-field-trip/</guid>
        <description>Five teams of Imperial students who entered BP&amp;rsquo;s Ultimate Field Trip competition are through to the semi finals, in which they will compete by presenting their ideas on tackling the carbon challenge to a panel of BP experts. The fifteen students are competing for the opportunity to receive a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sir Keith O&#39;Nions Steps Up
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-14-sir-keith-onions-steps-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 17:58:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Alexander Karapetian,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-1-14-sir-keith-onions-steps-up/</guid>
        <description>Sir Keith O&amp;rsquo;Nions has taken over the position of Acting Rector at Imperial following the resignation of Sir Roy Anderson. O&amp;rsquo;Nions began his role at the start of the New Year and sent out an introductory E-mail on the 11th giving students some background information and positive hopes for …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
