<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/aida_manzano_kharman/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/aida_manzano_kharman/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Do we need Women’s Day?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-do-we-need-women-s-day/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aida Manzano-Kharman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-do-we-need-women-s-day/</guid>
        <description>Why do we need a day to celebrate women? In truth if you think about the concept of a day to celebrate women, it sounds almost absurd, women are so crucial to humankind that a one-day celebration doesn’t even come close to acknowledging how important women are. That’s one way of seeing it, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The last domino to fall</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-the-last-domino-to-fall/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aida Manzano-Kharman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-the-last-domino-to-fall/</guid>
        <description>Amongst the seemingly ever rising far right movement in Europe, despite all the tumultuous events that have been occurring in Spain recently, the rise of an extreme right party was not something that Spanish and European citizens predicted as happening anytime soon. And yet nonetheless, Vox was the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Yemen: The big kids’ playground</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-yemen-the-big-kids-playground/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aida Manzano-Kharman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-yemen-the-big-kids-playground/</guid>
        <description>As of March 2018 the death toll in Yemen has surpassed 40,000 casualties. Save The Children reports that at least 50,000 children have died in 2017 alone, and to this day and counting the amount of displaced refugees is well over 2 million.
The civil war in Yemen has been raging on since 2015, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Catalonia’s new democracy – where can we go from here? </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-catalonia-s-new-democracy-where-can-we-go-from-here/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aida Manzano-Kharman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-04-26-catalonia-s-new-democracy-where-can-we-go-from-here/</guid>
        <description>Article 1.2 of the preliminary title of the Spanish Constitution states: “National sovereignty resides in the Spanish people, from whom the powers of the State emanate.” In essence, the distribution of power in Spain is dictated from the bottom upwards, in accordance to the will of the Spanish …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Balfour Declaration: a century on</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-the-balfour-declaration-a-century-on/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aida Manzano-Kharman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-the-balfour-declaration-a-century-on/</guid>
        <description>When people hear about Palestine and Israel, they usually know ‘something’s going on there’ but few seem to understand what exactly is happening, and most importantly how the conflict originated. There are many factors, but it is widely agreed that the Palestinian-Israeli conflict can be traced back …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Catalonia faces a uncertain future after an independence vote riddled with irregularities</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-catalonia-faces-a-uncertain-future-after-an-independence-vote-riddled-with-irregularities/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Aida Manzano-Kharman,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-12-13-catalonia-faces-a-uncertain-future-after-an-independence-vote-riddled-with-irregularities/</guid>
        <description>Do you want Cataluña to be an independent state in the form of a republic? This was the question posed to the 5,313,564 inhabitants of Cataluña, of which an overwhelming 90% voted “yes”, with a turnout of 42.3%.
While it is true that the right to self-determination is a fundamental human right, and …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
