<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/fa608/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/fa608/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Too few women and no change in sight
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-24-too-few-women-and-no-change-in-sight/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 23:24:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-24-too-few-women-and-no-change-in-sight/</guid>
        <description>If you like your Felix lighthearted, you may want to turn the page, because this article is anything but. The seeds of my piece were planted when I heard that one of my friends was planning to attend CodeF, a Google networking event ‘exclusively for female computer scientists’ attending top …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Perfection, at a premium
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-perfection-at-a-premium/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 21:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-perfection-at-a-premium/</guid>
        <description>I’m quite ambivalent when it comes to the relative merits of operating systems and the devices they run on. The Mac vs. PC debate has been stumbling along for almost as long as I can remember, and much of what can be said has been said, many times over. Suffering the minor misfortune of having to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kindling dissatisfaction
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-kindling-dissatisfaction/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 21:46:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-kindling-dissatisfaction/</guid>
        <description> I was one of the 1.2 million adults in Britain gifted an Amazon Kindle this Christmas, and as far as presents go it’s probably my favourite so far. Using the device has been a dream, and it has made the 20 hours I spent stuck flying in economy class this winter many magnitudes more enjoyable. There …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Facebook: all shared out?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-facebook-all-shared-out/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 19:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-1-facebook-all-shared-out/</guid>
        <description>I expect most of you have noticed the new items that have started appearing in your Facebook feeds: Spotify playlists of music that your friends are listening to and news articles from a whole host of national and international papers. They are part of the ‘OpenGraph’ scheme that Facebook has been …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Engineering tomorrow’s humanity
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-engineering-tomorrows-humanity/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 18:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-engineering-tomorrows-humanity/</guid>
        <description>Every week in here at Technology, we try and peek a few weeks into the future, to tell you what might be the best new technology of the coming season or the device that you’re going to be saving up for. The far future is often best left to science fiction; technological predictions about the future …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Livescribe: A smart choice for lectures
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-livescribe-a-smart-choice-for-lectures/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 23:07:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-livescribe-a-smart-choice-for-lectures/</guid>
        <description>I have to admit that when I first picked up Livescribe’s Echo Smartpen I was more than a little skeptical, for good reason. I’ve seen electronic note-taking aids from my first year at Imperial, and there’s good reason why the Union Shop does such good business at the start of term: it will take a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>iPhone 4S debuts to mixed reactions
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-iphone-4s-debuts-to-mixed-reactions/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 10:42:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-iphone-4s-debuts-to-mixed-reactions/</guid>
        <description>Tuesday evening brought us Tim Cook’s first keynote as Apple’s outright CEO, but that wasn’t the largest change as Apple turned away from its huge yearly update of the iPhone to instead offer punters an incrementally upgraded version, the iPhone 4S.
Key features on the new phone include an upgrade …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Felix Tech Guide 2011
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-9-30-the-felix-tech-guide-2011/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2011 12:00:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Chris Bowers,Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-9-30-the-felix-tech-guide-2011/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to Imperial! You’ve done well to make it here; for the next few years you will get to experience extreme levels of stress, a rapidly receding hairline and the effects of excess Red Bull consumption (seizure, in the case of one of my housemates).
Despite this, there’s much to be said for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>‘Everything everywhere’ a reality?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-everything-everywhere-a-reality/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 20:35:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-everything-everywhere-a-reality/</guid>
        <description>As summer draws nearer and the spring round of exhibitions and trade fairs draws to a close, there’s a lot of shiny new technology to look forward to over the next few months. Driving the latest round of products is the incessant slide towards perpetual connectivity: be it mobile, tablet, laptop or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Windows 8 preview promises app bonanza
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-12-windows-8-preview-promises-app-bonanza/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 15:48:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-12-windows-8-preview-promises-app-bonanza/</guid>
        <description>After weeks of speculation and leaks regarding the next version of Microsoft’s flagship software, Windows 8 was previewed this week at the Computex Expo.
Most striking about the new operating system was the user interface, which has dropped the traditional Start menu and desktop combination in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>O2 has best mobile broadband says Ofcom
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-o2-has-best-mobile-broadband-says-ofcom/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 18:47:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-o2-has-best-mobile-broadband-says-ofcom/</guid>
        <description>Looking to switch mobile connections and can’t go without a regular dose of Facebook and Twitter? Ofcom’s latest report would suggest that you head to your nearest O2 store. The company came out on top in a study of major mobile providers in the UK, loading pages faster than any of 3, Vodafone, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Skype pushes unwanted software to users
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-skype-pushes-unwanted-software-to-users/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 18:44:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-skype-pushes-unwanted-software-to-users/</guid>
        <description>Skype users might want to keep an eye out when installing updates on their system after users noticed that the application was attempting to foist software from another company on them. Skype was found requesting access to an application called ‘easybitsgo.exe’, produced by EasyBits, a company …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>After Spotify, what next?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-after-spotify-what-next/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 19:08:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-after-spotify-what-next/</guid>
        <description>Ever since Spotify Open limited users to 10 hours of free music and 5 plays per track, I’ve been on the hunt for alternative streaming services that offer something similar to its huge library and smooth browsing experience. If you’re searching too, here are my experiences.
Of all the streaming …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Driverless cars on the way
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-driverless-cars-on-the-way/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 05:59:27 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-driverless-cars-on-the-way/</guid>
        <description>If iPads and eReaders don’t make the journey into university feel futuristic enough, meet their hair-raisingly modern companion, the driverless car.
Nothing more than a pipe dream for decades, Google has spent the last few months showing off it’s fleet of driverless Prii (that, shockingly enough, is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Have your cake and eat it too
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-have-your-cake-and-eat-it-too/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 08:21:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-have-your-cake-and-eat-it-too/</guid>
        <description>This Easter heralded a slew of new tablet announcements, and the brightest of the latest generation of iPad contenders finally brought some variety and innovation to the tablet market. One of the best of these was the Eee Pad Transformer, a device that combines ASUS’s netbook prowess and a bit of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>iPad 2 blows away rivals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-ipad-2-blows-away-rivals/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 21:19:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-ipad-2-blows-away-rivals/</guid>
        <description>If preliminary reactions are anything to go by, it appears that Apple might have pulled another winner out of the bag with the newly released successor to the original iPad. The fully upgraded model has been garnering some serious attention from reviewers over the week, with the almost unanimous …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Crime on your street mapped
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-crime-on-your-street-mapped/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-crime-on-your-street-mapped/</guid>
        <description>Two burglaries and a case of vehicle crime – not your an average night out in a rough part of London, but a description of the crime in my street in the last month according to the police’s latest initiative, www.police.uk. The site, which allows you to enter a postcode and retrieve detailed crime …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AI geek bests human rivals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-ai-geek-bests-human-rivals/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 20:07:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-24-ai-geek-bests-human-rivals/</guid>
        <description>If you have an issue with a silicon based master race, you might want to start hunting around for a welcoming hippie commune, because things just got serious. In three rounds of the American game show Jeopardy, based on participants mastering wordplay to answer general knowledge questions, a pair of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Murdoch launches Daily magazine for iPad
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-murdoch-launches-daily-magazine-for-ipad/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 20:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-murdoch-launches-daily-magazine-for-ipad/</guid>
        <description>Faced with declining paper revenues and stiff competition from free online alternatives, Rupert Murdoch’s News Corporation made a bold foray into online publishing last Wednesday with the release of their subscription-based iPad-only publication The Daily. The Daily is one of a handful of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Egypt in complete internet blackout
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-egypt-in-complete-internet-blackout/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 20:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-egypt-in-complete-internet-blackout/</guid>
        <description>In the backdrop of the dramatic demonstrations sweeping Egypt, another battle is being fought for the control of internet and communication lines in the country as the government tries to prevent protesters from organising and the local media from distributing images and videos of the events to an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Facebook in address privacy u-turn
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-facebook-in-address-privacy-u-turn/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 19:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-facebook-in-address-privacy-u-turn/</guid>
        <description>Facebook was forced to beat a hasty retreat over the previous week as plans to allow third party access to user phone numbers and addresses caused strong concerns among security experts, even before the feature was fully rolled out. Less than 72 hours after a blog post announced the new …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Top tech to keep your eye on in 2011
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-top-tech-to-keep-your-eye-on-in-2011/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 20:38:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-top-tech-to-keep-your-eye-on-in-2011/</guid>
        <description>The Motorola Xoom
Motorola’s Xoom has been winning accolades from far and wide after it’s launch at CES. Boasting a feature set that puts Apple’s iPad in the shade, the tablet is a sure sign that tablet manufacturers are no longer looking towards Cupertino for inspiration.
In the processing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>CES 2011 - Las Vegas
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-ces-2011-las-vegas/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 20:34:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-ces-2011-las-vegas/</guid>
        <description>Every year, the CES exhibition out in the deserts of Las Vegas promises an interesting foresight into the gadgets and technologies that are going to be big over the year, and this year was no exception. While this year’s CES continued where the last exhibition left off, focusing on handheld and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>American embarrassment as more documents leaked about Iraq war
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-american-embarrassment-as-more-documents-leaked-about-iraq-war/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 19:37:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-american-embarrassment-as-more-documents-leaked-about-iraq-war/</guid>
        <description>Wikileaks is in the news again this week after releasing approximately 400,000 formerly classified documents relating to the war in Iraq.
The biggest revelation from the document dump is the fact that the American government has seemingly admitted to far fewer civilian casualties than they actually …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Android goes Froyo-tastic
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-6-3-android-goes-froyo-tastic/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 15:16:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Feroz Abdul Salam,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-6-3-android-goes-froyo-tastic/</guid>
        <description>When Google announced the Android mobile operating system in late 2007, the reaction it received was at best, lukewarm. Coming only a few months after the release of the iPhone OS, which had taken consumer markets by storm, most analysts were cautious about the announcement despite the fact that the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
