<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/lj810/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/lj810/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>A spot of magical realism in the kitchen
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-a-spot-of-magical-realism-in-the-kitchen/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 19:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucie Jichova,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-27-a-spot-of-magical-realism-in-the-kitchen/</guid>
        <description>Colombian coffee is savoured all over the world, but the cuisine of this country has not been exported as widely. Colombians are a nation of highly energetic, sociable people who know how to enjoy a good party. And they certainly enjoy parties that involve eating. Their cuisine is hearty and varied. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The brand spanking new Bloomberg Assessment Test
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-the-brand-spanking-new-bloomberg-assessment-test/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 20:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucie Jichova,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-the-brand-spanking-new-bloomberg-assessment-test/</guid>
        <description>The other day, you might have received an email from the Careers Advisory Service informing you that Imperial is one of the lucky universities selected to test-drive a new Bloomberg Assessment Test (BAT) for free. “Hurry now! In the future, there will be a fee for taking this test,” it said. First …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brasa: a place your date will get a good grilling
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-brasa-a-place-your-date-will-get-a-good-grilling/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 19:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucie Jichova,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-brasa-a-place-your-date-will-get-a-good-grilling/</guid>
        <description>This week, Felix returns to Fulham to review Brasa, the restaurant attached to the recently opened Broadway Bar &amp;amp; Grill which we wrote about a few weeks ago. Since our last visit, Brasa has acquired its own sign above the door, sending out the “Hello we exist!” message to passers-by, although …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Curry at naan o’clock: the real deal about curries
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-curry-at-naan-oclock-the-real-deal-about-curries/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 20:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucie Jichova,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-curry-at-naan-oclock-the-real-deal-about-curries/</guid>
        <description>A visit to a typical curry house in England would lead one to believe that understanding curry is pretty straightforward. A choice of three types of meat (chicken, lamb, or prawns) with some vegetables (tomatoes, onions, peas, and sometimes even, oh my God, pineapple), all swimming in the same …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fulham’s newest venture: Broadway Bar and Grill
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-fulhams-newest-venture-broadway-bar-and-grill/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 21:10:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lucie Jichova,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-11-fulhams-newest-venture-broadway-bar-and-grill/</guid>
        <description>“How formal is this place you are taking me to?” my friend Apu called to ask before meeting me at the newly opened Broadway Bar &amp;amp; Grill on Fulham Road. “I don’t think it’s too formal. Relax,” I told him. “Okay, let me ask it this way: Is it a shirt place, or a t-shirt place?” he replied. …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
