<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ng611/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/ng611/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Scrapping over Scalia
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-scrapping-over-scalia/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 11:29:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nathaniel Gallop,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-scrapping-over-scalia/</guid>
        <description>Love him, hate him, agree or disagree with him, it is undeniable that US supreme Court Justice Antonin Scalia was one of the most divisive and outspoken American political figures of this generation. A gifted jurist and bastion of American conservatism, his aggressive style of questioning and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Religion should be a private matter
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-9-religion-should-be-a-private-matter/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 19:52:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nathaniel Gallop,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-2-9-religion-should-be-a-private-matter/</guid>
        <description>I was seven years old when I first self-identified as an atheist.
I remember the setting vividly. I was in a social studies class in the second grade. My teacher – the American education system’s answer to Margaret Thatcher, albeit with less charm – was explaining the concept of religious diversity …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Taekwondo emerge victorious for second year running
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-taekwondo-emerge-victorious-for-second-year-running/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 20:42:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nathaniel Gallop,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-taekwondo-emerge-victorious-for-second-year-running/</guid>
        <description>The 10th anniversary of the Imperial College Taekwondo society got off to an explosive start over this past weekend, with the hosting of the third annual Imperial College Open Taekwondo Competition.
The competition has grown at an incredible rate since its inception in 2012, this year attracting …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who is accountable for the death of Michael Brown?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-who-is-accountable-for-the-death-of-michael-brown/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 18:29:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nathaniel Gallop,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-12-4-who-is-accountable-for-the-death-of-michael-brown/</guid>
        <description>For the past week, the town of Ferguson, Missouri has been racked with a continuous stream of protests and riots following the Grand Jury’s decision to not indict Officer Darren Wilson in the case of the shooting of Michael Brown. The outcome of the investigation has attracted widespread criticism …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The retirement of Dapper Laughs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-20-the-retirement-of-dapper-laughs/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 20:54:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nathaniel Gallop,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-20-the-retirement-of-dapper-laughs/</guid>
        <description>Ten days ago, controversial internet sensation Daniel O’Reilly appeared on an exclusive Newsnight interview to announce the retirement of his comedic persona, Dapper Laughs.
For connoisseurs of quality humour the nation over, it is a welcome end to what has been a meteoric rise of internet stardom …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Or maybe it won’t be that great after all
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-17-or-maybe-it-wont-be-that-great-after-all/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 18:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nathaniel Gallop,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-17-or-maybe-it-wont-be-that-great-after-all/</guid>
        <description>INTERSTELLAR
Director: Christopoher Nolan
Screenplay: Christopher Nolan, Jonathan Nolan
Cast: Matthew McConaughey, Anne Hathaway, Michael Caine, Jessica Chastain, John Lithgow, Casey Affleck, Ellen Burstyn, Wes Bentley
Rating: 3&amp;frasl;5
Interstellar is to Nolan what Sandinista! was to the Clash; a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Midterms: Why every red cloud has a blue lining
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-the-midterms-why-every-red-cloud-has-a-blue-lining/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 18:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nathaniel Gallop,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-the-midterms-why-every-red-cloud-has-a-blue-lining/</guid>
        <description>The votes have been cast, the results are in, and the outcome is far from unexpected. The Democrats have been unceremoniously kicked out of Capitol Hill.
For Obama, Clinton, and their supporters, the impending cession of control of both the House and Senate to the Republican Party has been akin to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Should we accept reporting of factual errors?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-should-we-accept-reporting-of-factual-errors/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 18:23:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nathaniel Gallop,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-11-6-should-we-accept-reporting-of-factual-errors/</guid>
        <description>So if you’ve been reading the news recently, you’ll surely be aware of the impending apocalypse sweeping Western Africa and soon enough, we are assured, the rest of the world.
I know, I can hardly wait myself.
I am, of course, referring to the recent outbreak of Ebola, which has recently claimed its …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>IC Taekwondo produce strong showing
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-ic-taekwondo-produce-strong-showing/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 04:45:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Nathaniel Gallop,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2014-1-17-ic-taekwondo-produce-strong-showing/</guid>
        <description>Last weekend saw Ethos sports centre nearly full to capacity as over one hundred and sixty competitors descended on Imperial College to take part in the Imperial College Open.
Now in its second year, the Imperial College Open has become a major event in the competitive year for many university …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
