<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jack_mitchell/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jack_mitchell/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial make their mark at BUCS Indoors Athletics</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-imperial-make-their-mark-at-bucs-indoors-athletics/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Mitchell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-08-imperial-make-their-mark-at-bucs-indoors-athletics/</guid>
        <description>Between the 15th and 17th of February, a team of Imperial’s finest athletes set off for BUCS Indoors in Sheffield.
This is the first big event of the athletics calendar and is attended by the best university athletes from across the country. It provides a great chance for athletes to gain experience …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LUCA Outdoors Championships II – revenge of ICXCAC</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-luca-outdoors-championships-ii-revenge-of-icxcac/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Mitchell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-luca-outdoors-championships-ii-revenge-of-icxcac/</guid>
        <description>LUCA outdoors – take two. Taking place at Lee Valley stadium on 28th April, this was an incredible event for ICXCAC and turned out to be our most successful ever athletics meet, in large part due to the enormous number of athletes that signed up to be part of the action.
The day began with a bang, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICXCAC head to the LUCA outdoors competition</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-icxcac-head-to-the-luca-outdoors-competition/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Mitchell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-03-icxcac-head-to-the-luca-outdoors-competition/</guid>
        <description>The sun was shining, and despite the early start for many, the ICXCAC team was smiling. Why? It was time for the LUCA (London Universities and Colleges Athletics) outdoors athletics series, beginning at Parliament Hill athletics track. On 15th April, the first meeting kicked off, with competitors …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICXCAC elites set off to the BUCS indoor competition</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-23-icxcac-elites-set-off-to-the-bucs-indoor-competition/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jack Mitchell,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-23-icxcac-elites-set-off-to-the-bucs-indoor-competition/</guid>
        <description>BUCS indoors. The first big event of the athletics season was upon us. Our thirteen-strong team of elite athletes jetted off to the Northern lands of Sheffield for a full weekend of cheering, racing, and, of course, dancing the night away. Held at the English Institute of Sport, the championships …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
