<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/icanon/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/icanon/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Hong Kong: Home No More</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-hong-kong-home-no-more/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-29-hong-kong-home-no-more/</guid>
        <description>Hong Kong. An asphalt jungle lit by neon lights. The brutal trek up the Tiger’s Head and down towards the beaches of Discovery Bay. A mere cog in the global economy machinery. For me it was all that and more. But somehow six thousand miles away from the city I called home, I’ve now come to realise I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>RE: “An opinion on the Hong Kong issue” – a Reality Check</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-08-11-response-to-an-opinion-on-Hong-Kong-a-reality-check/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-08-11-response-to-an-opinion-on-Hong-Kong-a-reality-check/</guid>
        <description>Have you ever read a piece of writing so factually inaccurate that you feel physically compelled to reply to it? That was the exact scenario in which I found myself after picking up a copy of Felix last Friday afternoon.
The article in the 1ST of November issue called ‘An opinion on the Hong Kong …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Opinion on the Hong Kong Issue</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-opinion-hong-kong-issue/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-11-01-opinion-hong-kong-issue/</guid>
        <description>The Hong Kong protests have been going on for 4 months now, with no end in sight. What started as a peaceful protest against the extradition bill has evolved (or devolved, depending on your perspective) into an often-violent movement against Beijing. Personally, I am both confused, amused and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Son</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-the-son/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-09-27-the-son/</guid>
        <description>The Son completes a loosely related trilogy in which each standalone play focuses on a member of the family. The first, The Father, examines the effects of dementia, and The Mother discusses middle-aged angst and loneliness. This final play’s focus is, teen depression. Nicolas, two years ago a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Black girl in STEM</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-a-black-girl-in-stem/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-a-black-girl-in-stem/</guid>
        <description>Where I’m from, the colour of my skin didn’t make me “the minority”, nor did being a female determine my academic success. Where I’m from, it was quite commonly joked about that the girls were smarter and more mature than the boys because, after all, “behind every successful man is a strong woman …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial pays working student late, again</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-imperial-pays-working-student-late-again/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-03-15-imperial-pays-working-student-late-again/</guid>
        <description>For the third time in six months, Imperial departments have failed to pay students who work for them on a part time basis on time. Students working on all day workshops around the pay date were informally told that they may have not be paid on time, and that it was their responsibility to follow it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Supervision Story</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-supervision-story/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-supervision-story/</guid>
        <description>The PhD student – supervisor relationship is a strange one; it is rare that in a workplace you would have a single boss for three to four years or have the flexibility to come into work at 11am and have the freedom to take three hours for lunch if you so wish. Then again, a PhD isn’t a normal job; …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The long road to recovery</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-the-long-road-to-recovery/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-25-the-long-road-to-recovery/</guid>
        <description>This isn’t what I expected recovery to look like. For over ten years, I’ve battled with an eating disorder, and I’m starting to realise that recovery might not have an end to it. For now, it seems like it’s a dynamic process, with an equilibrium that shifts left or right depending on the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Creative Green</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-a-creative-green/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-a-creative-green/</guid>
        <description>Hi there,
*
I am a bin
Your humble biographer
Wherever I may be
Beside the kitchen sink yawning in the morning to catch your cereal packet or an unwashed peanut butter jar
*
Standing on the landing at University you pass me everyday occasionally greet me with a screwed up tissue.
*
At lunchtime I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Have you ever experienced discrimination?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-have-you-ever-experienced-discrimination/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-have-you-ever-experienced-discrimination/</guid>
        <description>Have you ever felt unintentionally, casually or subtly discriminated against within the college environment? What happened? How did it make you feel? How did it affect you in the long run? Felix is trying to start a conversation to better understand the impact this has on people by compiling some …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Supervision Story - February </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-supervision-story-1/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-supervision-story-1/</guid>
        <description>Dialogue. I believe that in the thorough yet enjoyable experience that the PhD can be, we all go through times of self-doubt and questioning. Not only about the research itself, but about our own capabilities and the, sometimes, fearful prospect of having to finish. I am glad to have a supportive …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Women in STEM: Report from a conference</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-women-in-stem-report-from-a-conference/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-25-women-in-stem-report-from-a-conference/</guid>
        <description>I was at a conference and a guy from a research centre approached me. Initially our conversation was on research but then he asked if I would like to go to a bar with him after the gala dinner. He looked at me in an erotic way that made me feel very uncomfortable. I told him that I couldn’t go with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Meat-free Mondays: are they okay?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-meat-free-mondays-are-they-okay/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-meat-free-mondays-are-they-okay/</guid>
        <description>What possible change on campus this new year could spur so many people to respond with anger? What possible subject, requiring no effort on most anyone’s part could cause hordes to descend upon Imperial’s most popular social media platform at Imperial College Exposed to express their outrage? Of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Supervision Story - December</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-supervision-story-december/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-04-27-supervision-story-december/</guid>
        <description>My experience as a postgraduate research student at Imperial was in complete contrast to my expectations.
A diligent and hardworking student, I was accustomed to high-level problem solving, difficult tasks, proposing and defending arguments and manipulating complex data and ideas. Eager for the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is feminism still relevant?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-is-feminism-still-relevant/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-is-feminism-still-relevant/</guid>
        <description>At this point, you’re probably tired of hearing, seeing, listening to and arguing about feminism. I’m not too big of a fan of the word either so please don’t go ballistic just yet. Read on, try to keep an open mind, which I know is crazy hard, but how ’bout we try for just one sec?
Things are better …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wishing You an Appy New Year in London</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-wishing-you-an-appy-new-year-in-london/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-wishing-you-an-appy-new-year-in-london/</guid>
        <description>Whether you are new to London or you’ve always lived here, the collecton of apps in this article consists of apps many Londoners use daily, and many more you may be unaware of. Either way, they are sure to help you out if you haven’t used them before.
Citymapper
If you are new to London or even if …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Secret Tory: A Behind the Scenes Look at the Annual Tory Conference</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-the-secret-tory-a-behind-the-scenes-look-at-the-annual-tory-conference/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-23-the-secret-tory-a-behind-the-scenes-look-at-the-annual-tory-conference/</guid>
        <description>I will be frank – I am an undecided voter. I wanted to make an informed decision so I did the sane thing – I bought a media pass and packed my bags for the International Conference Centre (ICC) in Birmingham. The Conference was enlightening… it certainly changed my perspective of the Conservative …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Abandoná a tu Diego Rivera</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-abandon-a-tu-diego-rivera/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-abandon-a-tu-diego-rivera/</guid>
        <description>At the beginning of a relationship there is passion, not love. Love is built upon passion, but it doesn’t necessarily exist after passion. Some people are mature and caring enough to be able to build the love, some are not: it is as simple as that. To love someone, you must love yourself first: you …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This year Union Council has been completely toxic – it’s time for change</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-this-year-union-council-has-been-completely-toxic-it-s-time-for-change/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-this-year-union-council-has-been-completely-toxic-it-s-time-for-change/</guid>
        <description>From a particular perspective, Imperial College Union is an organisation which has always been defined by negativity. After all, students wouldn’t be motivated to make things better if they thought that things were already good enough. Usually, this negativity is channelled into productivity; the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s time to break the cycle of foreign interventions</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-it-s-time-to-break-the-cycle-of-foreign-interventions/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-05-18-it-s-time-to-break-the-cycle-of-foreign-interventions/</guid>
        <description>The olden days of warfare, of shrewd generals commanding their gallant troops into majestic battles, are long gone. The guerres du jour are served as drawn out, low-intensity meat grinders across land, sea, and air, augmented by a generous portion of ideological – and perhaps, one could say, memetic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A letter to the new sabbs</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-a-letter-to-the-new-sabbs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-a-letter-to-the-new-sabbs/</guid>
        <description>Dear New Sabbatical Officers,
If you’re reading this before the results drop, good luck. If they’ve already happened, congratulations! You’ve all worked extremely hard to get here – many of you had strong opponents, and even those who didn’t still took campaigning seriously. Well done.
I’m writing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In The Whites…</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-in-the-whites/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-02-in-the-whites/</guid>
        <description>Acting is about inhabiting another person’s life. When stories explore universal themes – most of Shakespeare fits this category – few would disagree that an actor can give an insightful performance in these stories, regardless of their ethnic background.
The appeal of “colour blind” casting, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rape law, rape culture, and what Imperial can do about it</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-23-rape-law-rape-culture-and-what-imperial-can-do-about-it/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-23-rape-law-rape-culture-and-what-imperial-can-do-about-it/</guid>
        <description>Did you know that the police estimated that upwards of 95,000 rapes take place each year in England and Wales? And yet the Crown Prosecution Service (CPS) only managed to convict a rapist in 2991 cases in 2016&amp;frasl;17 – that’s only 3%. The police estimated that upwards of 517,000 sexual offences …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Should we think more about our consumption habits?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-12-should-we-think-more-about-our-consumption-habits/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-12-should-we-think-more-about-our-consumption-habits/</guid>
        <description>When I am shopping I can feel different parts of my brain whirring away. The parts I use for systematic problem solving take a break and instead it is a desperate rush to find the most sticker-coated, cheapest and most appealing supplies for the week ahead. It is impossible, it seems, to truly …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The State of Israel</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-the-state-of-israel/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-01-26-the-state-of-israel/</guid>
        <description>In last week’s Felix, members of the Imperial College Friends of Palestine wrote an article entitled ‘Palestine: apartheid, ethnic-cleansing and discrimination’. It was a well-written piece, arguing against an earlier Felix article defending the Balfour declaration, itself a response to an earlier …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ethos Gym does not need to expand</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-ethos-gym-does-not-need-to-expand/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-24-ethos-gym-does-not-need-to-expand/</guid>
        <description>Let’s assume your claimthat exercise being good for mental health is true, and that it is Imperial’s duty to deal with this problem.
Ok. So Imperial needs to get more people to exercise. Anyone who has been to the gym at Ethos knows that at least 50% of the treadmills are being walked on, and at …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Self-help books are absolutely terrible, and I’ll fight them to the death</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-self-help-books-are-absolutely-terrible-and-i-ll-fight-them-to-the-death/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-11-03-self-help-books-are-absolutely-terrible-and-i-ll-fight-them-to-the-death/</guid>
        <description>In my three years at Imperial I have had many opportunities to be triggered by Felix’s Comment section — Brexit, two general elections, and numerous terrorist attacks have produced articles that managed to properly rustle my jimmies. The piece in last week’s issue, however, extolling the virtues of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Should medics go to Heaven?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-should-medics-go-to-heaven/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-10-27-should-medics-go-to-heaven/</guid>
        <description>The question, “Is it ever acceptable for straight people in large groups to congregate in an LGBT+ space?” is a contentious issue, and – in recent media – a divisive one. I’d like to make my position perfectly clear: there is something incredibly special about gay venues; something which, I believe, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Writing mental illness off as a personality quirk is dangerous</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-writing-mental-illness-off-as-a-personality-quirk-is-dangerous/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:44:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-7-28-writing-mental-illness-off-as-a-personality-quirk-is-dangerous/</guid>
        <description>Two weeks ago, I read an article in felix posing the question: “Are we medicalising personality?” The author argues that self-diagnosis of a mental health problem can be risky. I agree. They argue that convincing yourself you have a mental illness when you don’t, can make you miserable. I agree. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to dump someone (you met in Metric and subsequently fell in love with)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-how-to-dump-someone-you-met-in-metric-and-subsequently-fell-in-love-with/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 16:16:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Theresa Davey,Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-how-to-dump-someone-you-met-in-metric-and-subsequently-fell-in-love-with/</guid>
        <description> You were weak. Despite our foolproof guides on how to have a one night stand (in Metric), ‘How to have a one night stand (in Metric)’, and how not to fall in love with someone (from Metric), ‘How not to fall in love with someone (from Metric)’, you went ahead and fell in love with someone (from …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It&#39;s not rational to be scared of terrorism
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-its-not-rational-to-be-scared-of-terrorism/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 14:57:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-9-its-not-rational-to-be-scared-of-terrorism/</guid>
        <description>Every time there’s a terrorist attack, the more skittish of my friends set about panicking. Marking themselves safe on Facebook, making dramatic social media posts, and generally creating the hysteria and alarm that follows a terrorist attack.
If a chemical weapon had been used, or if the numbers …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The near-peg experience
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-the-near-peg-experience/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 13:53:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-6-2-the-near-peg-experience/</guid>
        <description>I went home last week for a few days over the bank holiday. As always when I go home, I opened up Tinder and began to swipe. I mostly use it as a way to keep track of who from school is single, but sometimes use it to shark on hot students and locals.
I swiped right on a few people before I ran out …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The counselling service does not work as advertised
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-19-the-counselling-service-does-not-work-as-advertised/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 15:05:28 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-19-the-counselling-service-does-not-work-as-advertised/</guid>
        <description>Everyone gets stressed at uni at some point. If you don’t, I applaud your Jedi level of inner peace. But for the rest of us mere mortals, it hits at some point. Because it affects everyone, I just assumed that what I was feeling was normal, that my course was always going to be a tough one and it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s not my job to please your girlfriend
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-its-not-my-job-to-please-your-girlfriend/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 16:31:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-5-15-its-not-my-job-to-please-your-girlfriend/</guid>
        <description>I don’t like being cheated on. You probably don’t either. In fact I’d go so far as to say that no one likes being cheated on. Unless you’re into cuckolding but that’s a whole other story. Last time I got cheated on it made me feel betrayed and angry not only at my partner, but also at the other …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is the Union fixing the leadership elections?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-is-the-union-fixing-the-leadership-elections/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 13:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-is-the-union-fixing-the-leadership-elections/</guid>
        <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a well known fact that if you’re one of the beautiful people, you’re more likely to be successful in the Union elections. But as well as having beauty be a requirement, there is also a culture of successful candidates being chosen from above.
To say that the Union (and by that I mean the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An ode to my roommate, whom I love
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-an-ode-to-my-roommate-whom-i-love/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 13:49:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-24-an-ode-to-my-roommate-whom-i-love/</guid>
        <description>I love my roommate. Quite the statement, isn’t it?
I love the way she never turns off the lights and always turns the desk light on when I go to sleep (even though I do it too). I think it’s her way of making sure that I get my light dose for my photosynthetic processes.
I love how she makes a lot …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Love is the drug you can’t get enough of
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-love-is-the-drug-you-cant-get-enough-of/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 15:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Theresa Davey,Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-love-is-the-drug-you-cant-get-enough-of/</guid>
        <description> Let’s be real. Love is a drug. It inhibits our ability to think clearly, turns us into terrible people, and makes us do stupid things. Face it, it’s far more harmful than a few hours gurning at the weekend. But just like with drugs, there are different kinds of highs, and so now, in honour of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is being a sabb bad for your health?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-is-being-a-sabb-bad-for-your-health/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 14:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-17-is-being-a-sabb-bad-for-your-health/</guid>
        <description>Year on year, the process of the Union elections cherry-picks those who are some of the most vulnerable to lead us as sabbatical officers.
This makes sense – those who have experienced difficulties during their time at Imperial are the ones who know the system, and the ones who are most likely to be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Being non-binary at Imperial is not fun
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-being-non-binary-at-imperial-is-not-fun/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 14:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-being-non-binary-at-imperial-is-not-fun/</guid>
        <description>There is a misconception held by many queer secondary school students that universities are very progressive and tolerant places. The It gets better project is all but built on this idea promoted by society that it’s okay if times are tough now, because one day you will escape your small town. You …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The NHS has no idea what it&#39;s doing when it comes to trans patients
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-the-nhs-has-no-idea-what-its-doing-when-it-comes-to-trans-patients/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 13:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-the-nhs-has-no-idea-what-its-doing-when-it-comes-to-trans-patients/</guid>
        <description>One of the most disconcerting things you can experience when visiting the doctor is seeing your GP open up Internet Explorer and start googling. As a nervous transgender teenager, I was completely terrified. GPs are meant to be a first point of contact for the general population; somebody we turn to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Coming out was an attempt to find myself
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-coming-out-was-an-attempt-to-find-myself/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 13:44:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-10-coming-out-was-an-attempt-to-find-myself/</guid>
        <description>I was a special kid (the lonely and isolated type, always lost in their thoughts). Around the age of five, I remember first hearing about homosexuality and even though it was not quite described as a ‘bad thing’, I still associated it with something to be afraid of. I told myself “with my luck, it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Starving anxiety into submission | Anorexia
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-starving-anxiety-into-submission-anorexia/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 18:07:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-2-3-starving-anxiety-into-submission-anorexia/</guid>
        <description>I thought the only way I could dull my anxiety was starving it. If I was dizzy and needed to concentrate hard on staying upright, there was no space left to worry. Before long I’d reach a comfortable haze, unable to carry a thought for more than a few seconds. The emptiness inside my stomach made …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How not to fall in love with someone (from Metric)
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-how-not-to-fall-in-love-with-someone-from-metric/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 15:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Lef Apostolakis,Theresa Davey,Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2017-1-20-how-not-to-fall-in-love-with-someone-from-metric/</guid>
        <description> This is a follow up to our piece ‘How to have a one night stand (in Metric)’. For those of you who somehow missed it, we provided a tried-and-tested plan of action designed to get you laid after a night in Metric. This plan was meant to get you in and out without leaving any trace. But expectedly, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>No one helped. No one understood.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-no-one-helped-no-one-understood/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 14:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-11-11-no-one-helped-no-one-understood/</guid>
        <description>I don’t know if this is the place to share my story, but with so many sexual assault happenings being opened up and spoken about, I feel like I should say something.
They go to Imperial. They were a friend, someone who provided comfort and companionship. I never wanted anything sexual to occur …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Drunk consent is not consent. My rape story
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-drunk-consent-is-not-consent-my-rape-story/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 22:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-31-drunk-consent-is-not-consent-my-rape-story/</guid>
        <description>This week the coat I lost on the night I was raped found its way back to me.
Having languished, dirty and unloved, at the back of a cupboard in a house I occasionally visited for parties, it was unearthed in a start-of-year clean and returned to me. I had been there a year and a half ago for a club …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stop silencing those who speak out about sexual assault
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-21-stop-silencing-those-who-speak-out-about-sexual-assault/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 12:51:36 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-21-stop-silencing-those-who-speak-out-about-sexual-assault/</guid>
        <description> The “conversation” going on right now is essentially the lived experience of most sexual assault survivors
 I’m so tired. There is a general consensus right now in the media that 2016 has been, for lack of a better word, a shitshow. But as a person who has experienced sexual assault, the last week …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ten things I hate about you
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-7-ten-things-i-hate-about-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 17:32:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Felix Editor,Theresa Davey,Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-10-7-ten-things-i-hate-about-you/</guid>
        <description> We’ve come to the end of Freshers’ Week, and maybe you’ve had a bit too much fun. We’ve all been there, made mistakes, and done things that we live to regret with the bad-boy (or girl) hall senior who seems so mature and experienced. Regardless of how, when, or why, many people all over Imperial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Does anyone benefit from #sabblife?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-does-anyone-benefit-from-sabblife/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 08:56:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-17-does-anyone-benefit-from-sabblife/</guid>
        <description>Sabbatical officers at every university are the same. They’re all self-important, egotistical, and narcissistic, with an inflated sense of the importance of their role. They enter this multi-generational circle-jerk of sabbs, stroking each other’s egos and sucking each other’s dicks, both literally …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why is Imperial so ugly?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-why-is-imperial-so-ugly/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 08:21:42 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-why-is-imperial-so-ugly/</guid>
        <description>Hello Imperial, we need to talk.
In previous volumes, this journal has been dedicated to burning issues of the day: junior doctors’ working conditions, the cost of living for students, union bureaucracy, and clarion call to vote (this 23rd of June). Nevertheless, there is an issue fundamental to our …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>EU myths debunked
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-eu-myths-debunked/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 08:19:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-10-eu-myths-debunked/</guid>
        <description>The claim: The EU open-borders policy puts strain on the UK and makes it harder for non-Europeans to settle in the UK.
The facts: According to a report by the Migration Observatory in 2011, 95% of net migration to the UK was that of non-EU nationals.
The EU has no power over UK immigration policies …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mars under the magnifying glass
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-mars-under-the-magnifying-glass/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 09:17:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-mars-under-the-magnifying-glass/</guid>
        <description>I get angry waiting for Google Maps to load on my iPhone and I tell this to Jan-Peter Muller, Professor of Image Understanding and Remote Sensing at the Department of Space and Climate Physics at UCL. He looks as if he’s experienced a similar thing. “If you think 3G or GPRS is bad, try processing an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can we stop talking over women?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-can-we-stop-talking-over-women/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 09:03:32 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),Christopher Worsfold,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-can-we-stop-talking-over-women/</guid>
        <description>We’ve all been there – you finish your exams and suddenly there’s a deep hole, a lack of purpose in your life. What else was I to do but pick up Felix and read Arnold Tan’s “message to feminists”.
In his article, Arnold gave his view on the feminist movement, articulating his own helpful …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who are we to vote on EU membership?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-who-are-we-to-vote-on-eu-membership/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 09:02:34 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-6-3-who-are-we-to-vote-on-eu-membership/</guid>
        <description>As the date of the EU referendum approaches, we are being flooded with Remain vs Exit articles on all media. However, this is NOT going to be another advocating piece. In fact, I am wondering why one even gets to vote on such an issue at all.
Before you label me an authoritarian-totalitarian-fascist …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What makes a good GUM clinic?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-what-makes-a-good-gum-clinic/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 09:01:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-what-makes-a-good-gum-clinic/</guid>
        <description>Apparently I engage in risky sexual behaviour. This means that like the good millennial I am, I have to periodically get tested to make sure that I&amp;rsquo;m free from the nasties that make sex a little less fun and a little more infectious (and not in a good way). Although there are many sexual …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to have sex in halls
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-how-to-have-sex-in-halls/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 09:00:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-how-to-have-sex-in-halls/</guid>
        <description>With exams finishing and the sun coming out, Imperial is a hive of frenzied sexual activity, as inhibitions are shed in anticipation of the long summer break. But if you live in a shared room in halls, it strongly limits the privacy available for the exciting sexual encounters that we’re all …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Virtual reality porn is a game-changer
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-virtual-reality-porn-is-a-game-changer/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 08:58:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-5-13-virtual-reality-porn-is-a-game-changer/</guid>
        <description>When Palmer Luckey kickstarted the virtual reality revolution in 2012 I doubt he expected that one of primary uses of his new technology would be pornography. We’ve seen smartphones change the way we watched porn, and VR is set to do the same. While 3D porn itself is nothing new (it’s been around …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I’m a slut and proud
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-im-a-slut-and-proud/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:45:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-im-a-slut-and-proud/</guid>
        <description>This article was published as part of FELIX&amp;rsquo;s Sex Survey launch. Do the survey here.
I’ve been called a slut more times than I can count, both as an insult and as a compliment. Whilst some people recoil from the notion of a sexually empowered female, many celebrate us girls who openly love …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Iconic sex toys that changed the world
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-iconic-sex-toys-that-changed-the-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 10:43:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-4-29-iconic-sex-toys-that-changed-the-world/</guid>
        <description> This article was published as part of FELIX&amp;rsquo;s Sex Survey launch. Do the survey here.
If there’s one thing that I’ve learnt over the course of my adult life, it’s how to get myself off, and I don’t think there’s any shame in admitting that. In recent years, more and more women have begun …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Being a virgin isn’t a big deal anymore
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-being-a-virgin-isnt-a-big-deal-anymore/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 11:47:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-being-a-virgin-isnt-a-big-deal-anymore/</guid>
        <description>This article was published as part of FELIX&amp;rsquo;s Sex Survey launch. Do the survey here.
Out of all my friends I was set to be one of the first to lose it, and by it I mean my virginity.
I don’t really know why. I guess it’s just because I had a series of boyfriends, quite a few guy friends and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We need to talk about contraception
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-we-need-to-talk-about-contraception/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 11:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-18-we-need-to-talk-about-contraception/</guid>
        <description>This article was published as part of FELIX&amp;rsquo;s Sex Survey launch. Do the survey here.
In the UK, we’re lucky enough to have access to free contraception, regardless of who you are. The NHS provides 15 different methods, ranging from the provision of free condoms, to implanted devices, to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I had sex in the tunnels under Imperial
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-15-i-had-sex-in-the-tunnels-under-imperial/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 09:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-3-15-i-had-sex-in-the-tunnels-under-imperial/</guid>
        <description> Heads were banged, and knees were scraped
 This article was published as part of FELIX&amp;rsquo;s Sex Survey launch. Do the survey here.
It was a bright, sunny day in the summer of 2014. The renovation of the West Basement of Beit was well underway, and amidst the flurry of activity, I discovered some …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Financial Worlds Conference
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-new-financial-worlds-conference/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 12:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-26-new-financial-worlds-conference/</guid>
        <description>On 17th February 2016, the 5th New Financial Worlds Conference was successfully held at the state-of-the-art Bloomberg Auditorium in London.
The day was split between Investment Banking and Global Markets. The diverse range of speakers left attendees with an unparalleled understanding of the two …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Things you’re desperate to ask your Muslim lab partner
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-things-youre-desperate-to-ask-your-muslim-lab-partner/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 11:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2016-2-19-things-youre-desperate-to-ask-your-muslim-lab-partner/</guid>
        <description> Muslims are probably one of the easiest groups of people to identify from the way we dress, girls being more obvious than guys. As Muslims we find that there’s a lot of confusion about why we do certain things and people speculate because they’re too scared to ask in case we get offended. Contrary …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How it feels when your home country goes to the polls
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-how-it-feels-when-your-home-country-goes-to-the-polls/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 13:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-how-it-feels-when-your-home-country-goes-to-the-polls/</guid>
        <description>When talking about how it feels to live abroad, the conversation tends to revolve around the things you miss, such as family members, the weather, or food. But, if your home country is in a state of change and turmoil, the hardest thing about being away is having to live through certain events …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jeremy hunts for a solution to junior doctor drama
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-jeremy-hunts-for-a-solution-to-junior-doctor-drama/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 13:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-11-6-jeremy-hunts-for-a-solution-to-junior-doctor-drama/</guid>
        <description>Health Secretary Jeremy Hunt has offered junior doctors an 11% basic pay rise, having cut the hours classified as &amp;lsquo;unsociable&amp;rsquo; meaning that some will actually get a pay cut of as much as 15%. In an attempt to convince junior doctors not to take strike action, he’s conveying the message …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cruising through Colchagua (Valley)</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-1-cruising-through-colchagua-valley/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2015 17:38:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-6-1-cruising-through-colchagua-valley/</guid>
        <description>A couple of months ago I was just like you: I’d crafted what I thought at the time was the perfect route through South America, cruising merrily along the gringo trail, diverting occasionally for the miscellaneous hidden gems I’d heard about through the grapevine. But as it turned out there were …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Summer Ball Headliner ‘Slap Happy’
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-21-summer-ball-headliner-slap-happy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2015 23:03:46 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-21-summer-ball-headliner-slap-happy/</guid>
        <description>This year’s Summer Ball headliner was announced a couple of weeks ago, via the somewhat protracted method of a quiz – where the first letter of five somewhat transparently James Bond themed questions allowed students to spell out the artist’s name.
How successful this method of engaging with the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Volunteer Experience: Working away in Chile’s Colchagua Valley</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-4-volunteer-experience-working-away-in-chiles-colchagua-valley/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 16:35:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-5-4-volunteer-experience-working-away-in-chiles-colchagua-valley/</guid>
        <description>I’m sure you’re all depressingly familiar with the concept of unpaid internships by now: roll in with a smile, do a little grunt work, leave with a frown, only to be replaced by the next person on the unending list of the exploited. WorkAway.info is a little different. In exchange for a mere 25 …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Art History From A New Perspective
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-art-history-from-a-new-perspective/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 13:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-art-history-from-a-new-perspective/</guid>
        <description>I recently came across an opinion piece in Art Review magazine that discussed the crisis of the contemporary within art, particularly focussing on the difficulty in finding a suitable label for the art of the present day. With ‘modern’ art confined to a temporality at the beginning of the 20th …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The White Square — An LSD Rhapsody
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-the-white-square-an-lsd-rhapsody/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 12:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-25-the-white-square-an-lsd-rhapsody/</guid>
        <description>Have I just made the stupidest mistake of my life?” I wondered as the white square dissolved in my mouth and passed down my throat. I reassured myself, the whole thing was thought through and the plan was bullet proof. I stepped out of the bathroom and an usher passed a few angry words in my …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This purist likes their tea and biscuits kept separate
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-this-purist-likes-their-tea-and-biscuits-kept-separate/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 19:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-9-this-purist-likes-their-tea-and-biscuits-kept-separate/</guid>
        <description>Gentle reader, I’m certain that I am only the latest in a long line of commentators to compare two of the greatest influences in our British lives: tea and sex. While these might initially appear to have as much in common as, say, fashion sense and Islamic State, there’s a great deal of common …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The best and worst of student election videos
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-4-the-best-and-worst-of-student-election-videos/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2015 18:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-3-4-the-best-and-worst-of-student-election-videos/</guid>
        <description>At this time of year we start to see the typical seasonal changes come into effect: the days are starting to get longer, the temperature is starting to rise, and a plethora of cringey election videos have been released, featuring shockingly awful musical covers, unnervingly unfunny inside jokes, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Up in Ubud: Dabbling the delights in Bali’s undisputed cultural capital</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-up-in-ubud-dabbling-the-delights-in-balis-undisputed-cultural-capital/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 19:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-up-in-ubud-dabbling-the-delights-in-balis-undisputed-cultural-capital/</guid>
        <description> Bali: the four letters roll eloquently off the tongue, and immediately conjure up images of beautiful beaches, bronze bods, and bottled Bintang. But a stone’s throw – literally one hour by shuttle bus – into the island’s core teleports you to a different kind of paradise: the kind that featured …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The gospel accoring to Zouk</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-the-gospel-accoring-to-zouk/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 18:53:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2015-1-23-the-gospel-accoring-to-zouk/</guid>
        <description>By the time it came around to ZoukOut I’d been on the road for several months, a continuing holiday trend throughout my time at Imperial that’s led to me missing almost every major music festival since I started uni. This year was supposed to be different but, alas, my optimistic KaZantipplans …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Commonwealth: Beginning of the End?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-commonwealth-beginning-of-the-end/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 16:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-24-commonwealth-beginning-of-the-end/</guid>
        <description>As the controversial 23rd Commonwealth Governmental meeting in Colombo closed earlier this week there was widespread feeling that the Commonwealth has suffered a huge dent in its credibility. In March 2013 (for the first time in its history) the Commonwealth set out a new charter emphasising the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Some guys just can’t handle La Paz</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-some-guys-just-cant-handle-la-paz/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 23:53:10 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-10-12-some-guys-just-cant-handle-la-paz/</guid>
        <description> Bolivia isn’t exactly a fresh addition to the Latin American gringo trail – it features heavily in countless itineraries (indeed, I even ran into an old Felix editor whilst there) – yet it’s managed to retain an essence of individuality whilst neighbouring countries have started to subside. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Execution of a 12-Year-Old Boy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-the-execution-of-a-12-year-old-boy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 10:34:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-22-the-execution-of-a-12-year-old-boy/</guid>
        <description>It is a war that has produced some of humanity’s most shocking and depraved images. But the new photographic evidence, released by Channel 4 News last Monday, is perhaps the most disturbing yet. The first photo shows Balachandran Prabakaran, the 12-year-old son of a Tamil Tiger, being held captive …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>King Krule: Live
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-king-krule-live/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 23:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),Padraic Calpin,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-1-king-krule-live/</guid>
        <description>King Krule, a lonely rider of the current music scene, the only one that is really talking about being in pain (his own words), is the alias of an 18-year old South Londoner, Archie Marshall, accompanied on stage by a bassist, drummer, saxophonist and guitarist. Archie first caught people’s eye last …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cruising up the backwaters</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-25-cruising-up-the-backwaters/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 18:15:21 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-25-cruising-up-the-backwaters/</guid>
        <description>As the saying goes: even a poor-quality photo taken on a beaten digital camera can tell a thousand brilliant words. Or something like that. If the accompanying photograph doesn’t appeal to you then hopefully the remainder of this article will inspire you to take a trip.
The destination in question …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Hundred in the Hands are back in the fold</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-23-the-hundred-in-the-hands-are-back-in-the-fold/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 16:27:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-23-the-hundred-in-the-hands-are-back-in-the-fold/</guid>
        <description>Following what appeared to be an indefinite hiatus after the release of their eponymous debut in 2010, The Hundred in the Hands are back on the scene. And while that said debut managed to rapidly rack up favourable reviews from the likes of Pitchfork and Metacritic, it looks as though we can expect …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Summer festival ambitions</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-summer-festival-ambitions/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 18:50:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-summer-festival-ambitions/</guid>
        <description>I’m sure we all agree that much of the British festival scene is in tatters. Sure, if you’re willing to deviate from the likes of Reading you might catch some acts that are a little (read: endlessly) more interesting than Kasabian, but ultimately you’ll probably still be forking out far too much …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sri Lanka&#39;s Killing Fields
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-13-sri-lankas-killing-fields/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2012 15:44:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-13-sri-lankas-killing-fields/</guid>
        <description>On Wednesday 14th March, Channel 4 will broadcast ‘Sri Lanka’s Killing Fields: War Crimes Unpunished’ at 10.55 pm. The program is a sequel to the critically acclaimed and RTS-award winning documentary released last year, under a similar title, which shocked and horrified viewers worldwide. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to the jungle</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-welcome-to-the-jungle/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 21:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-welcome-to-the-jungle/</guid>
        <description>By the time I hit Kerala I was more than ready for it: with Rajasthan’s dusty forts a distant memory I was ready to hit up something a little more tropical. That’s the incredible thing about Kerala: after a short and breezy (read: forty hour and mosquito-infested) coastal train down from the north, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Learn to think better of teaching</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-learn-to-think-better-of-teaching/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 23:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-learn-to-think-better-of-teaching/</guid>
        <description>Three out of four secondary school students are not taught physics by a specialist physics teacher. 16% of those eligible for school meals make it to university. Independent schools, however, manage to send 96% of theirs to higher education. These points are raised by Teach First (whose mission is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sri Lanka’s silent genocide
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-sri-lankas-silent-genocide/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 22:43:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-sri-lankas-silent-genocide/</guid>
        <description>On Monday 21st November and Tuesday 22nd November Imperial’s International Tamil Society organised and ran a successful Breaking the Silence Campaign. They are one of eight different universities in London participating in the campaign. Their stalls quickly became overwhelmed with inquisitive …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jaipur: up, up and away</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-jaipur-up-up-and-away/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 20:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-jaipur-up-up-and-away/</guid>
        <description>Having been on the road for a while at this point in time, I’d lost all sense of a sleeping pattern: probably for the best when facing a 4:30 start. After overcoming that bitter morning sensation we peered from our hostel window to see what appeared to be a hot-rod straight out of Kill Bill: we …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The real benefit cheats</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-18-the-real-benefit-cheats/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 00:55:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-18-the-real-benefit-cheats/</guid>
        <description>Welfare can be a controversial issue these days, invoking heated debate.
It is often said that the hard-working majority are forced to pay taxes for the idle few benefit-scroungers who don’t pull their weight. In these economic times, many have wondered whether these payments should be cut.
Trouble …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Gallivanting the golden sands of gorgeous Goa</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-gallivanting-the-golden-sands-of-gorgeous-goa/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 20:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-3-gallivanting-the-golden-sands-of-gorgeous-goa/</guid>
        <description>Let’s be honest about it, the existing beach scene has very much gone to the dogs: Ibiza is past its expiry date, Koh Phangan is being sucked into that same black hole (thanks, The Hangover Part II), and Malia-napa-luf is far too saturated with sleaze for me to waste my time with a rant. My point is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is Democracy the best policy?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-is-democracy-the-best-policy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 22:57:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-is-democracy-the-best-policy/</guid>
        <description>Many people have argued that democracy is actually one of the most radical ideas in political history. To treat people as equals with equal votes sits well with most people today. We can also see the effects of ideas like these in the West in the last 300 years or so with mass education, rising …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The media&#39;s inevitable right wing slant</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-14-the-medias-inevitable-right-wing-slant/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 10:35:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-14-the-medias-inevitable-right-wing-slant/</guid>
        <description>We live in democracies where we hold those in power to account using elections. To help us make informed choices about our society there are many kinds of media on the market whose job it is to tell us all the bad stuff and to suggest solutions to them. The idea is that this will build a public …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Acclimatising to incredible India</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-acclimatising-to-incredible-india/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 13:10:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-acclimatising-to-incredible-india/</guid>
        <description>When I first touched down in New Delhi I have to say I was a tad deceived. Having skimmed my trusty Lonely Planet, I was expecting the Paharganj area to be a bustling Th Khao San à la Bangkok, but was greeted with something else entirely. I suppose I have my own ignorance to thank; I’d been told …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sadly no simple single solution
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-13-sadly-no-simple-single-solution/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2011 13:28:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-13-sadly-no-simple-single-solution/</guid>
        <description>This article was originally published on Friday 15 October 2010.
After three hours of questioning and “security checks” it was with some relief that our group finally left the bowels of Ben Gurion airport and stepped out into the warm Mediterranean night. Soon after arriving at our first destination …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ton Rai Plai Dee</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-ton-rai-plai-dee/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 19:53:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-ton-rai-plai-dee/</guid>
        <description>ASCETIC
Too much time to play the cynic, Glad to be your biggest critic, Lacking purpose and direction, But keen to give all my affection.
I do mean every word I say, But definitions change each day, Calm down dearest, no need to worry, When I’m gone you won’t be sorry.
KHAO SAN BLUES
My hands they …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get out and see it while you still can</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-27-get-out-and-see-it-while-you-still-can/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 15:29:18 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-27-get-out-and-see-it-while-you-still-can/</guid>
        <description>Recently Nazareth (no, not the Jesus one), a small town in the Amazon region of Colombia announced that tourists are no longer allowed to visit: the tens of thousands that visit each year are providing little for the economy and their presence is having detrimental effects on both local scenery and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>World Cup woes for the residents of Rio</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-8-world-cup-woes-for-the-residents-of-rio/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2011 13:28:45 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-8-world-cup-woes-for-the-residents-of-rio/</guid>
        <description>2014 will no doubt arrive in the blink of an eye and it’ll be time again for that most glorious of sporting events. And with rocketing temperatures, minimal living costs and the nearby Copacabana beach boasting hot latina girls wearing next to nothing, what better venue for the World Cup than Rio’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fuck Buttons is the music scene’s saviour</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-fuck-buttons-is-the-music-scenes-saviour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 08:59:25 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-fuck-buttons-is-the-music-scenes-saviour/</guid>
        <description>HMV Forum, Kentish Town Thursday 21st April
In a decade unfortunately masked by the lousy sounds of David Guetta and The Black Eyed Peas, we should be praying to the likes of Fuck Buttons as our rare saving grace. If you’ve been living in the chart bubble let me bring you up to speed: the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tricked by Facebook fraudster</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-4-25-tricked-by-facebook-fraudster/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2011 17:20:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-4-25-tricked-by-facebook-fraudster/</guid>
        <description>With her big bright eyes, a selfless desire to help those in need, and an unrivalled passion for the sounds of obscure bands you’d have to Google just to maintain conversation, Demi Atkinson certainly ticked all the boxes. And to your average Imperial fresher, confined to our beloved South Ken …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Has the Media failed Science?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-has-the-media-failed-science/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 20:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-has-the-media-failed-science/</guid>
        <description>This year’s BioSoc debate, held last Thursday in the Sir Alexander Fleming Building, turned out a huge success. The provocative debate title ‘Has the Media failed Science?’, albeit a little misleading to the speakers who were expecting some fierce opposition, was always going to invoke some great …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Thailand’s essentials uncovered</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-thailands-essentials-uncovered/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 06:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-3-thailands-essentials-uncovered/</guid>
        <description>The lowdown: The track is well beaten, but this certainly doesn’t detract from its charm. From the plush northern hills, down through the urban centre through to the islands of paradise, Thailand has something for all.
Culture: Thais are very friendly, laid back but energetic people. Always be …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Digital books kindle unease</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-digital-books-kindle-unease/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 20:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Anonymous (IC),</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-17-digital-books-kindle-unease/</guid>
        <description>Tyrants and autocrats have always understood that literacy, learning, books and newspapers are potentially dangerous. They can put independent and even rebellious ideas in the heads of their subjects.
Frederick Douglass, a former slave who taught himself to read, recalled being found with books by …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
