<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/eh508/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/eh508/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Triathlon Club Take on the BUCS Chilly Duathlon to End 2013.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-11-triathlon-club-take-on-the-bucs-chilly-duathlon-to-end-2013/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 00:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edward A J Hallett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-12-11-triathlon-club-take-on-the-bucs-chilly-duathlon-to-end-2013/</guid>
        <description>With the biggest turn out the triathlon club has ever seen, twenty five athletes travelled in an entourage of cars, minibus and van down the M4. The term was to culminate on Sunday 24th at the 2013 BUCS Duathlon at Castle Combe.
This fast pace race sees competitors circumnavigate the famous Castle …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial win at Hillingdon Duathlon
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-imperial-win-at-hillingdon-duathlon/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 11:50:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edward A J Hallett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-15-imperial-win-at-hillingdon-duathlon/</guid>
        <description>Memories of a completely crappy rain-filled start to November were dried up in a flash as Sunday came around and the skies cleared for the 2013 Hillingdon Autumn Duathlon. The local race is a favourite among the club with a few podiums last year and a win courtesy of Swiss international Jean-Claude …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>TriIC sprint to the finish
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-triic-sprint-to-the-finish/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 17:54:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edward A J Hallett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-16-triic-sprint-to-the-finish/</guid>
        <description>This year saw a record number of TriIC members travel to St Mary’s school in Calne for the 2013 BUCS Sprint Championships. It was a stunning morning, the perfect set up for a full day ahead of racing and sunning ourselves on the grass. Eighteen people worked together in the Tetris challenge of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Triathlon climb Castle Combe
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-triathlon-climb-castle-combe/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 23:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edward A J Hallett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-29-triathlon-climb-castle-combe/</guid>
        <description>This was the race we’d looked forward to: the only BUCS competition this term and a highlight of the calendar. With five hundred people competing, it is the biggest duathlon event in the country. Hosted at the iconic Castle Combe race track, athletes get to fly around a track that has held motoring …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Triathalon Dominate Podium
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-triathalon-dominate-podium/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 22:22:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Edward A J Hallett,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-triathalon-dominate-podium/</guid>
        <description>On what felt like the coldest morning of the year so far, a selection of Imperial Triathlon members met while it was still dark to ride off towards Paddington, and to the first race on our calendar. The team was severely dented with four members dropping out at the last minute due to falling down …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
