<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jn104/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/jn104/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>No Cinderella, you shan&#39;t go to the Summer Ball
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-5-no-cinderella-you-shant-go-to-the-summer-ball/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 23:48:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jovan Nedic,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-5-no-cinderella-you-shant-go-to-the-summer-ball/</guid>
        <description>The Summer Ball, a chance for staff and students to celebrate the end of their exams (sorry Chemistry, Biochemistry, and Biology), the end of another academic year, and for some, the end of university life, has always been a highlight of the Imperial social calendar. However, when the details of the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>So close yet so far
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-25-so-close-yet-so-far/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2011 15:05:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jovan Nedic,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-25-so-close-yet-so-far/</guid>
        <description>Following a hard fought victory over Swansea in the semis, Imperial Men’s Lacrosse faced up against Leeds Met Carnegie in the BUCS Trophy final in Sheffield on the 17th March. Leeds had narrowly beaten Birmingham in their semi and, having lost against Birmingham 20-0 two years previously, Imperial …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nine in a row for Medicals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-nine-in-a-row-for-medicals/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 21:52:03 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jovan Nedic,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-nine-in-a-row-for-medicals/</guid>
        <description>A strong start by Imperial was not enough to keep the Medicals at bay at this year’s Varsity, as they went on to win their ninth successive JPR Williams Cup.
From the kick-off, Imperial were determined to show that they were a force to be reckoned with, running with pace and intensity at the Medical …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sports training could be hit
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-sports-training-could-be-hit/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 21:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jovan Nedic,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-sports-training-could-be-hit/</guid>
        <description>The College’s proposals to extend the working day would have several implications in terms of the available time for extra-curricular sporting activity.
Although some might find Imperial’s location within London an advantage, for the sports teams the significant distance to the grounds and the added …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don’t extend College hours
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-dont-extend-college-hours/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 19:49:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jovan Nedic,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-dont-extend-college-hours/</guid>
        <description>It appears that the College has yet again taken a somewhat narrow-minded view on their latest venture, extending the working day for not only the students, but the staff as well. Forget the fact that they will have to ask staff to work longer hours, which might be a whole other bag of problems, but …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>South Africa train at Ethos
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-south-africa-train-at-ethos/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 20:47:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jovan Nedic,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-south-africa-train-at-ethos/</guid>
        <description>The South African rugby team followed in the footsteps of their Southern Hemisphere colleagues, New Zealand, and trained at Ethos on Thursday morning in preparation for their match against the Barbarians this coming weekend.
The team arrived by coach and practiced their lineouts beside the rock …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Varsity moves to The Stoop
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-varsity-moves-to-the-stoop/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 18:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jovan Nedic,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-varsity-moves-to-the-stoop/</guid>
        <description>After several months of negotiations and rumours, Sport Imperial were able to confirm that the JPR Williams Cup match will move to The Stoop, home of rugby premiership side Harlequins.
The new three year deal will see Imperial’s and the Medicals’ best rugby teams fight it out for the JPR Williams …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All Blacks visit Ethos
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-all-blacks-visit-ethos/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 18:42:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jovan Nedic,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-all-blacks-visit-ethos/</guid>
        <description>The New Zealand Rugby Union team, commonly known as the All Blacks across the world, came for a quick visit and training session in Ethos on Monday afternoon. According to Sport Imperial, the team did not wanting to publicise their visit; despite this, the sports centre was swamped with enthusiastic …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Imperial Ninjas triumph against Kyoto 1st XV
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-7-2-imperial-ninjas-triumph-against-kyoto-1st-xv/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 11:17:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jovan Nedic,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-7-2-imperial-ninjas-triumph-against-kyoto-1st-xv/</guid>
        <description> Kyoto University RFC 1st XV 19 Imperial College Union RFC 1st XV 61
###
The Imperial Ninjas kicked off their tour of Japan with a match against Kyoto Imperial University. Having arrived in Japan the day before, the players were sleep deprived, jet lagged and hungover. Add the hot and humid Japanese …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Alldridge to return home from Japan Tour
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-7-2-alldridge-to-return-home-from-japan-tour/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 01:01:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jovan Nedic,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-7-2-alldridge-to-return-home-from-japan-tour/</guid>
        <description>Imperial College Union Rugby Football Club have suffered their first major injury on tour.
Jamie Alldridge, 22, suffered an injury to his wrist after a rather unfortunate fall during a game, and has been advised by doctors from Kyoto&amp;rsquo;s Second Red Cross Hospital to return to England for medical …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ICURFC Barbarians hampered by hangover
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-7-1-icurfc-barbarians-hampered-by-hangover/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2010 02:01:04 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jovan Nedic,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-7-1-icurfc-barbarians-hampered-by-hangover/</guid>
        <description>Kyoto University RFC 2nd XV 34 Imperial College Union RFC 2nd XV 19
After 24 hours travelling and one short nights sleep, for most (a number of senior players decided to set an example by making an impact on the Kyoto night scene. Some action was achieved although there were some discrepancy about …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Decade, New Venue, Same Story
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-4-18-new-decade-new-venue-same-story/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2010 17:11:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jovan Nedic,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-4-18-new-decade-new-venue-same-story/</guid>
        <description>IMPERIAL MEDICALS 29 IMPERIAL COLLEGE 13
Two tries by Man of the Match James Sharples at a buzzing Old Deer Park Stadium on Wednesday night saw that the Imperial Medicals retained the JPR Williams Cup for the eighth consecutive year.
College had the upper hand going into the game, having beaten and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sports of Yesteryear: Sparkes Cup
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-4-18-sports-of-yesteryear-sparkes-cup/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2010 17:09:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jovan Nedic,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-4-18-sports-of-yesteryear-sparkes-cup/</guid>
        <description>Everyone knows, or at least will know by within the next few weeks, that every year the Imperial School of Medicine take on the rest of the College in the annual Varsity Matches, with the culmination being the JPR Williams Cup between the two 1st XV sides in front of a packed crowd. For the rugby …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sports of Yesteryear: Rector&#39;s Cup
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-4-18-sports-of-yesteryear-rectors-cup/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2010 16:50:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Jovan Nedic,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-4-18-sports-of-yesteryear-rectors-cup/</guid>
        <description>Blood, sweat and beers. If there were ever three words that would describe the Rector&amp;rsquo;s Cup, they would be it. Last week, we discovered the wonder that was Morphy Day and how it was a sporting and social highlight for half a century. But what of the other events? This week, we delve into the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
