<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/juan_rubio_gorrochategui/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/juan_rubio_gorrochategui/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Oxygen: the generator of life</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-oxygen-the-generator-of-life/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-06-21-oxygen-the-generator-of-life/</guid>
        <description>When your peaceful summer nap is interrupted by the constant buzzing of a fly, do not think of it as the predetermined behaviour of a bothersome insect, but that of a many-times-removed cousin. Most animal phyla (the major groups under which the animal kingdom is divided, based originally in their …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Air pollution in London: where are we now?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-air-pollution-in-london-where-are-we-now/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-10-air-pollution-in-london-where-are-we-now/</guid>
        <description>It is not an exaggeration to say that pollution is one of London’s biggest challenges for the foreseeable future. While it is true that the situation is not as concerning as 70 years ago, when the pea soup-like Great Smog killed 4000 people in less than a week, the current pollution cloud that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Spanish socialists win big in a fragmented parliament while the far-right gets representation for the first time</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-spanish-socialists-win-big-in-a-fragmented-parliament-while-the-far-right-gets-representation-for-the-first-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-05-03-spanish-socialists-win-big-in-a-fragmented-parliament-while-the-far-right-gets-representation-for-the-first-time/</guid>
        <description>Prime Minister Pedro Sánchez’s Spanish Socialist Workers Party (PSOE in Spanish) won a commanding victory in the general election held last Sunday in Spain. Despite being far from wining an absolute majority of seats, something that rarely happens due to the relatively proportional voting system and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lefty YouTubers event draws large crowds </title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-lefty-youtubers-event-draws-large-crowds/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-02-08-lefty-youtubers-event-draws-large-crowds/</guid>
        <description>Shout out to Something Awful forum poster SuperMechaGodzilla, who, in 2013, posted a Communist analysis of the film Prometheus, and basically radicalised me on the spot”. This was the answer of Harry Brewis (Hbomberguy) to the question on how he was introduced to leftism. With such a starting shot, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The man who shocked the world</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-the-man-who-shocked-the-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2019-01-18-the-man-who-shocked-the-world/</guid>
        <description>Three years ago last week, David Robert Jones passed away at the age of 69. I remember it perfectly, as it was the day I had my first exam as an Imperial undergraduate. The night before I had been listening to Blackstar, the surprise avant-garde album that he had released only two days earlier, and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nothing but Mayhem</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-nothing-but-mayhem/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-12-07-nothing-but-mayhem/</guid>
        <description>Theresa May’s survival ability is something to behold. She could be half-jokingly compared to the character of the Black Knight in Monty Python’s Holy Grail who kept fighting King Arthur even after losing his four limbs. In an ironic twist, her constant resilience mirrors that of Labour leader …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>American Midterms: Tactical Defeat, Strategic Victory for the Democrats</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-american-midterms-tactical-defeat-strategic-victory-for-the-democrats/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-11-16-american-midterms-tactical-defeat-strategic-victory-for-the-democrats/</guid>
        <description>Last Tuesday, Americans went to the poll to vote for a third of their Senators, all their Representatives, 36 governors and most state senators and state representatives in the country. The Felix readership probably knows the two main takeaways: while the Democrats were successful in their attempt …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jamal, the Martyr</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-jamal-the-martyr/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-26-jamal-the-martyr/</guid>
        <description>In 1170, four English knights murdered the archbishop of Canterbury, Thomas Beckett, following the orders of king Henry II. The assassination of Beckett had ramifications that reached continental Europe, and less than two years after his death he was declared a saint by the Church. Henry had to …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>War at the world</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-war-at-the-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-22-war-at-the-world/</guid>
        <description>What difference does half a degree make? It doesn’t seem like much, right? After all, you don’t notice if the water in your sink has gone from 35 ºC to 35.5 ºC when you are washing the dishes. But half a degree is much more important than what you may think. It is the difference between being able …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bolsonaro Wins the First Round: Brazil Goes Balls Up</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-15-bolsonaro-wins-the-first-round-brazil-goes-balls-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-15-bolsonaro-wins-the-first-round-brazil-goes-balls-up/</guid>
        <description>South American countries have usually been ignored by the Western media, with few exceptions. On the few occasions the continent was reported by our news organisations, its nations were painted as permanently failed states ravaged by civil war, dictators and death squads. This picture ignores the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>May, you live in interesting times</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-may-you-live-in-interesting-times/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-10-29-may-you-live-in-interesting-times/</guid>
        <description>In 2015, David Cameron achieved by surprise what no other Conservative leader had accomplished since 1992: he returned to Westminster with a majority of six. The Tories had warned the electorate of a ‘coalition of chaos’ arising around Ed Miliband if voters returned again a hung parliament. Three …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First new stereoisomer type in 50 years, claim chemists</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-first-new-stereoisomer-type-in-50-years-claim-chemists/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-first-new-stereoisomer-type-in-50-years-claim-chemists/</guid>
        <description>Chemists at both Shanghai University and the University of Sydney have announced the discovery of the first new kind of molecular stereoisomer in half a century. For those who have never heard of this term, stereoisomers are molecules that share the same molecular formula (i.e. contain the same …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In defence of the Syrian Democratic Forces</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-in-defence-of-the-syrian-democratic-forces/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-06-19-in-defence-of-the-syrian-democratic-forces/</guid>
        <description>Several weeks ago, I wrote a comment piece for this paper that advocated Western support to the organization known as SDF (Syrian Democratic Forces), a group I described as: “an organization which has an ideology that combines libertarian socialism, gender equality, respect for ethnic minorities, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Words and genes</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-words-and-genes/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-03-09-words-and-genes/</guid>
        <description>Language and genetics do not usually go hand in hand in human history. Languages are, if anything, an instrument for domination – the epitome of international prestige as well as commercial and political supremacy. As the scholar of Yiddish Max Weinreich once said: “a language is a dialect with an …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>No Olive Branch for Rojava – what happens after the Turkish intervention in Syria?</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-no-olive-branch-for-rojava-what-happens-after-the-turkish-intervention-in-syria/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Juan Rubio Gorrochategui,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2018-02-16-no-olive-branch-for-rojava-what-happens-after-the-turkish-intervention-in-syria/</guid>
        <description>While Western audiences were being entertained by the latest Trump antics and the recent developments in the seemingly interminable process that is Brexit, the last three weeks saw the beginning of a new phase in the Syrian Civil War. Now ISIS has lost its territorial power base and has disappeared …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
