<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rjd08/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/rjd08/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Looking back at Pride and Prejudice
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-looking-back-at-pride-and-prejudice/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 01:24:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-looking-back-at-pride-and-prejudice/</guid>
        <description>Pride and Prejudice by Jane Austen was first published in 1813. It hardly belongs on the latest bestsellers chart so why have I landed on this book, now? A few reasons. One, it’s one of those classic books that you always promise yourself that you’ll read (but never do). Indeed, I’ve put off reading …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The writer of Spring
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-the-writer-of-spring/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 21:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-15-the-writer-of-spring/</guid>
        <description>Every year, societies like DramSoc and MTSoc find new ways to impress me. You would not think that in a university filled with scientists, engineers and medics, the students would be that interested in theatre. However, these clubs are more than interested, they are good at it too, finding new ways …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Helping to raise a latte for equality
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-7-helping-to-raise-a-latte-for-equality/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 19:53:00 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-7-helping-to-raise-a-latte-for-equality/</guid>
        <description>First off, I’m not a natural coffee drinker. Fair enough, unless your mother had a very peculiar physiology while breast-feeding, none of us are natural coffee drinkers. My point is, if given a choice, I would rather pick a pot of peppermint tea than choose a cafetiere of cappuccino. This puts me in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The puzzling problem with ponderings
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-the-puzzling-problem-with-ponderings/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 06:36:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-18-the-puzzling-problem-with-ponderings/</guid>
        <description>I’m in the grips of a dilemma. Oh dear.
But yet I’m strangely glad: I like being in trouble; I like having a problem to solve. This may sound odd. After all, if I’m content with my situation, is there even a problem at all? Technically, no. But I’m not content with my situation, that’s why there’s a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Curse of the dead man at world’s stranger tides
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-curse-of-the-dead-man-at-worlds-stranger-tides/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 20:26:39 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-curse-of-the-dead-man-at-worlds-stranger-tides/</guid>
        <description>The Pirates! In an Adventure with Scientists!
Directors Peter Lord, Jeff Newitt Screenwriter Gidoen Defoe Cast (voice) Hugh Grant, Salma Hayek, Jeremy Piven
My girlfriend sometimes says that I’m just a big kid sometimes. That doesn’t bother me – kids get all the really cool stuff. After going to see …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I am not a hipster – it’s too mainstream
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-i-am-not-a-hipster-its-too-mainstream/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 20:10:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-i-am-not-a-hipster-its-too-mainstream/</guid>
        <description>Firstly, let me clarify – I am not a hipster.
I feel compelled to begin with that statement because after reading this article, you may come to the conclusion that I am a hipster. I assure you I am not. You will not catch me wearing an inordinate amount of wool, or styling thick-rimmed glasses in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Will this book crash and burn?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-will-this-book-crash-and-burn/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 18:39:07 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-will-this-book-crash-and-burn/</guid>
        <description>My friend read this and raved about it to me. Quickly sold (mainly by the main character’s name, Hiro Protagonist), I vowed I’d read it as soon as I could. That was in high school. Some ten years later, I’ve finally got around to it.
Snow Crash, by Neil Stephenson, was written in 1992, so even when …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All hail the crime-fighting Hobo
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-all-hail-the-crime-fighting-hobo/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 20:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-all-hail-the-crime-fighting-hobo/</guid>
        <description>Hobo with a Shotgun
Director Jason Elsener Screenwriters Rob Cotterill, Niv Fichman, Paul Gross, Frank Siracusa Cast Rutger Hauer
Some films are bad. Some films are so bad they’re good. And there are some films which are so bad, they’re awesome. ​
The plot is neatly summarised in the title. The Hobo …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I have a smartphone: progress at last
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-i-have-a-smartphone-progress-at-last/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2012 19:51:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-23-i-have-a-smartphone-progress-at-last/</guid>
        <description>I recently joined the twenty-first century and got a new phone.
Actually, that’s not quite accurate. As well as servicing my telecommunicative needs, it also has a whole array of shiny doodads and gizmos. It has a camera with the resolution to individually identify the hairs in Karl Marx’s beard …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Link’s latest epic escapade
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-links-latest-epic-escapade/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 22:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-links-latest-epic-escapade/</guid>
        <description>So I finally completed The Legend of Zelda: Skyward Sword last night.
Zelda has always been a passion for me, even within my geeky realm of video games. I was blown away by the beauty of Ocarina of Time when I first saw it and with each new game, a new fix for my addiction. So when I heard Skyward …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A possible high society
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-a-possible-high-society/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 23:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-a-possible-high-society/</guid>
        <description>Please do not read the following if you do not like controversial material.
The debate over the legalisation of drugs has wittered on for as long as we’ve had drugs, or at least laws about them. Those of you who think that drugs are dangerous for the public at large will probably give good arguments …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pigs – our friends and maybe our equals
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-pigs-our-friends-and-maybe-our-equals/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 23:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-26-pigs-our-friends-and-maybe-our-equals/</guid>
        <description>Getting home one day, I was met with an unwelcome, albeit familiar, sight. The living room looked like a bomb had gone off and the rubble had been picked over by looters. In the kitchen, scores of mice were defending the ceramic mountain range by the sink from an amorphous and strangely sentient …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>There&#39;s something about Christmas
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-theres-something-about-christmas/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 22:23:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-theres-something-about-christmas/</guid>
        <description>The entire final quarter of the year snowballs towards the 25th of December with the unstoppable momentum of an avalanche on a skateboard. Even by November, the excitement runs at fever pitch levels. In fact, there is a spike in A&amp;amp;E admissions that coincides with the first screening of the Coca …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>All aboard the nostalgia train
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-all-aboard-the-nostalgia-train/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 22:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-24-all-aboard-the-nostalgia-train/</guid>
        <description>There are many ways to travel and I like to think that I’ve experienced most of them. Each one has its own charm, best suited to different needs and situations; from the humdrum of buses to the out-of-this-world splendour of airplanes, and, for the adventurous among you, the awesome majesty of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cats and babies
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-cats-and-babies/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 21:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-17-cats-and-babies/</guid>
        <description>The fact that I’m still alive is surprising to say the least.
Every day, my life is a constant struggle against the innumerable dangers that surround me. Some are obvious; cycling to college focuses the sum hatred of all commuters on my little two wheels. My home is no safer; I actually pay for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Portrait of the Cook as a Young Man
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-4-the-portrait-of-the-cook-as-a-young-man/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 16:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-4-the-portrait-of-the-cook-as-a-young-man/</guid>
        <description>Looking back with the aged eyes of a fourth year, I can reflect on my experiences here and divise a pattern, common to all who pass through these halls. As a child, food was just food. Food was also delicious. In university, food is still delicious but it is suddenly so much more complicated. For …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Did you know I once saw John Cleese in a curry house?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-did-you-know-i-once-saw-john-cleese-in-a-curry-house/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 23:12:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-20-did-you-know-i-once-saw-john-cleese-in-a-curry-house/</guid>
        <description>This one sentence can kick-off a near-endless conversation of who saw who, where and doing what. Like them or loathe them, celebrities do get people talking. Off the top of my head, I can’t think of any other use they might have. Every day it gets easier to gossip – not just because of The News of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fun in the sun
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-fun-in-the-sun/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 01:43:47 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-fun-in-the-sun/</guid>
        <description>Did you have a nice summer? You did? That’s nice.
As for myself, I, like many people travelled far away for a spell in prison. Alright, it may be more accurately described as a holiday in the sun, but as I lay there on my sun/cell-bed, I couldn’t help musing over the similarities.
For one thing: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The clock is ticking
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-9-30-the-clock-is-ticking/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2011 10:16:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-9-30-the-clock-is-ticking/</guid>
        <description>Mesdames et messieurs, meine damen und herren, ladies and gentlemen, bienvenue, wilkommen and of course, welcome – to Imperial College.
Please wipe your feet.
I am addressing the Freshers amongst you. To returning second years and above, welcome back. We can reminisce about our summers in the Union …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A pat on the back for humanity
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-a-pat-on-the-back-for-humanity/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 20:51:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-23-a-pat-on-the-back-for-humanity/</guid>
        <description>I’m not one for blowing my own trumpet, but sometimes when I look down on this sprawling metropolis of science and soccer, of museums and Metro newspapers, I think we can feel a modicum of pride. I’m not talking about just London though. It’s everyone, the whole human race! When I think about what …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Looking for a better book to read
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-looking-for-a-better-book-to-read/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 20:46:01 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-looking-for-a-better-book-to-read/</guid>
        <description>I have always been an avid reader, ever since a young age. I’m not picky either – as long as I have something papery in my hands, I’m glad to read it. I’ll read – and enjoy – mostly anything.
I say mostly because try as I might, I just couldn’t enjoy Looking for Mrs Dextrose by Nick Griffiths. The …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don’t forget to remember...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-dont-forget-to-remember/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 20:32:11 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-16-dont-forget-to-remember/</guid>
        <description>I’m a bit embarrassed. Y’see, you’ve caught me at quite an inopportune moment. I was going to write this letter on something important, I’m sure of that. The only thing is&amp;hellip; I can’t remember what I was going to write about. You don’t happen to know, do you? Wait! Hah, got it! Memory, that’s …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Design Flaws
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-design-flaws/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 18:13:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-9-design-flaws/</guid>
        <description>When they said that you see a bright light when you die, you did not realise that it was actually a 60 watt desk-lamp.
You also did not know just how fast cars could go round that bend, or how easily shopping can get broken when it is hit. Like bottles, boxes of eggs&amp;hellip;human bodies.
“Am I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Planning the unexpected
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-planning-the-unexpected/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 19:27:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-6-2-planning-the-unexpected/</guid>
        <description>It’s late. My eyes are red from fear and concentration. The only light in the room comes from my desk lamp as I burn the midnight oil, stooped over my desk. The floor around me is littered with scrumpled wads of paper. Discarded ideas. Each one would have worked, they would have worked fine. But …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Extra dimensions of service
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-extra-dimensions-of-service/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 23:44:48 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-26-extra-dimensions-of-service/</guid>
        <description>I’m sure you’ve suffered the same experience. You’re at a restaurant, the food you’ve ordered has arrived and you tuck in. Thirty seconds later, a waiter will come across and obsequiously ask if everything is alright. Since there hasn’t been the time for anything to go wrong, you nod politely and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Memory overload
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-memory-overload/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 05:49:56 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-memory-overload/</guid>
        <description>I hope ope you all had a nice break over Easter. I certainly hope it was better than mine. Foolishly, I fell ill.
It began with a bit of a runny nose and I thought it was nothing. Then I started running a temperature and I just could not catch my breath. By the third day, I felt like death with a …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to be British, apparently
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-how-to-be-british-apparently/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 08:39:50 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-how-to-be-british-apparently/</guid>
        <description>There was a wedding last Friday. One of slightly more importance than normal. Did you see it? I’m afraid I missed it. Which was a shame because I had a personal invitation to Westminster Abbey but a very important engagement came up at the last moment. There was a wall that had been recently painted …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Discovering this weird world
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-discovering-this-weird-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 21:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-17-discovering-this-weird-world/</guid>
        <description>The other day I saw something strange and wonderful. I was walking along the street, happily minding my own business, and happened to stop at a junction. All normal so far. Then, a lorry stopped beside me – a FedEx lorry with the FedEx logo emblazoned all over. And that was when I saw it; inside the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Up is the new down
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-up-is-the-new-down/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2011 20:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-10-up-is-the-new-down/</guid>
        <description>Someone once told me that dogs can’t look up. After the serendipitous, albeit not entirely legal acquisition of several dogs and the systematic placing of bones, dog food, and even cats on formidably high shelving, I at last determined that this was utter bollocks. But it got me thinking. Dogs can …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Alive and kicking
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-alive-and-kicking/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 20:57:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-3-1-alive-and-kicking/</guid>
        <description>I’d like to share with you, if I may, an episode from my life as medical student. No, stop, don’t run away! It’s not that bad, I swear. There may even be a moral at the end of it.
You begin Medicine learning dry facts and theories but the emphasis on these largely evaporates by the time you reach …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dating tips? From this guy?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-dating-tips-from-this-guy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 21:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-dating-tips-from-this-guy/</guid>
        <description>Of all the highlights that come with every lap the Earth makes around the Sun, Valentine’s Day I think is the trickiest. For some, it’s plain tiresome, as all media seem to gravitate around hearts and puppies and little naked children with wings. On any other day, these things would rarely feature …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Apocalypse Now... please?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-apocalypse-now-please/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 20:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-3-apocalypse-now-please/</guid>
        <description>If popular culture has taught me anything (and I like to think it has), it is that we are most likely to perish as a species in a thermonuclear fire-storm or a zombie pandemic. Though radically different, these apocalypses involve a great deal of mass panic before the dying starts. As such, there …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The importance of being idle
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-the-importance-of-being-idle/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 21:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-20-the-importance-of-being-idle/</guid>
        <description>For a long time, I’ve tried to live life in the fast lane – even occasionally overtaking on the central reservation – but it’s only recently that I’ve come to realise why.
Even when I was young, my parents would complain that I had ants in my pants. Apart from a rather unfortunate picnic, that …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2011: A Space Odyssey... I wish
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-2011-a-space-odyssey-i-wish/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 21:21:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-13-2011-a-space-odyssey-i-wish/</guid>
        <description>Happy New Year to you all! It’s nice to know that, as a species, we’ve managed to make it through another year without destroying ourselves. Well done.
There can be no doubt now that we are living in the future. We have, by some people’s (anachronistic) standards, supercomputers that we can carry in …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Minced pies in June? If only!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-minced-pies-in-june-if-only/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 21:37:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-minced-pies-in-june-if-only/</guid>
        <description>What’s the point in Christmas?
Before you start, I should make it clear I don’t have a personal grudge – or Grinch – against the festive season. Far from it – this whole month fills me with a child-like joy that eagerly effervesces with each opened advent calendar door. It would take strong …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flee! Flee the St John Ambulance service!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-flee-flee-the-st-john-ambulance-service/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 21:46:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-2-flee-flee-the-st-john-ambulance-service/</guid>
        <description>Before coming to London, my friends and family loaded me up with good advice. A common theme running through these kernels of sagacity was that London is a very dangerous place – something I won’t even try and refute.
With every month that I stay and study here, I can feel the years sloughing off my …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The F-word. Not that one
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-the-f-word-not-that-one/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2010 21:58:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-25-the-f-word-not-that-one/</guid>
        <description>Before you begin to read, please excuse the crumbs.
I love to snack while I write. I’m not picky; from the humble chocolate digestive, perfectly married with a nice cup of tea; to a sandwich in the small hours, filled with whatever in the fridge doesn’t move when I touch it; to an entire roast …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Photos can make us immortal
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-photos-can-make-us-immortal/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 22:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-18-photos-can-make-us-immortal/</guid>
        <description>I was back home the other day, clearing out the attic, where, inexplicably, a great deal of my dearest childhood possessions had wound up; cherished dolls, knitted by a late grandmother; industrious railway tracks by Brio and Tomy; and enough Lego to fill a skip. I was conflicted. On the one hand, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Chairman of the bored
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-chairman-of-the-bored/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 19:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-chairman-of-the-bored/</guid>
        <description>They say that when a man is bored of London, he is bored of life. If this is true, I should take a running leap off Hammersmith Bridge in my solid concrete Hushpuppies – however, no matter how boring life may get, I’m certain that the alternative is even more so. To clarify, of course I’m not bored …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Union presents tuition fees policy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-union-presents-tuition-fees-policy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 19:59:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-union-presents-tuition-fees-policy/</guid>
        <description>It seems like a lifetime ago now when, on the 12th October, Lord Browne finally published his review of higher education funding. Already, it is a topic that has been endlessly deconstructed and analysed and which every student in Imperial and the UK feels strongly about.
Two weeks have passed since …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pigeons of prey
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-pigeons-of-prey/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 19:46:44 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-pigeons-of-prey/</guid>
        <description>It was a very ordinary day when I realised I was a superhero.
I was walking through Hyde Park with nowhere in particular to be. As I was by myself, I granted my tongue the freedom to do as it wished. It entertained itself with a delightful series of clicks and clucks as I walked.
I stopped – I had …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In praise of cultural theft
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-in-praise-of-cultural-theft/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 18:57:14 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-in-praise-of-cultural-theft/</guid>
        <description>As I dodge knife-wielding pigeons and Underground commuters, disgruntled by the sheer virtue of being awake, on my way in to college from the outer fringes of the capital (and civilisation), I remember with fondness my first year here, spent in the sheltered haven of Prince’s Gardens.
It was the one …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Taking an unwelcome break
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-taking-an-unwelcome-break/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 20:03:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-14-taking-an-unwelcome-break/</guid>
        <description>Since I live in Cardiff and Imperial is in London, I am well-versed in the pages of English countryside that is the M4 corridor. Queues around Newport, chevrons outside of Bristol, roadworks just past Reading, I’m better than any SatNav. As well as speed cameras, lane narrowing and caravans, there …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What’s wrong with camping? Everything...
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-7-whats-wrong-with-camping-everything/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 22:57:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-7-whats-wrong-with-camping-everything/</guid>
        <description>I don’t know what you got up to with your summer. Maybe you went home, met up with some old friends and took it easy. Maybe you took off around the world in a glamorous jet-set holiday. Maybe you engaged in a whirlwind fling of summer romance (like a forest-fire, it was short-lived but passionate …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reynolds Bar given new lease of life with summer refurbishment
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-7-reynolds-bar-given-new-lease-of-life-with-summer-refurbishment/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 22:22:09 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-7-reynolds-bar-given-new-lease-of-life-with-summer-refurbishment/</guid>
        <description>While a lot of attention has been focussed on the refurbishment of Metric and FiveSixEight - as they will soon be called - renovations have also been taking place in the Reynolds Bar, the spiritual home of ICSM in Charing Cross Hospital.
Redecorating has been much gentler than at the Union, with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Freshers’ Tip #29: Avoid leopards
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-1-freshers-tip-29-avoid-leopards/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 22:44:54 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Rhys Davies,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-1-freshers-tip-29-avoid-leopards/</guid>
        <description>A big hello to those of you picking up Felix for the very first time. And a very good day to you! You are at the beginning of one of the most exciting, terrifying&amp;hellip; and certainly unique periods of your life. University. London. People. It gives me a buzz just thinking about it. To prepare you …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
