<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Felix</title>
    <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/lap08/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Felix</description>
    <atom:link href="https://old.felixonline.co.uk/authors/lap08/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The chaos of colony collapse disorder
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-the-chaos-of-colony-collapse-disorder/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 09:43:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-11-1-the-chaos-of-colony-collapse-disorder/</guid>
        <description>The modern-day bee is in a bit of a sticky situation, and we’re not talking about honey.
It was published in PLoS One last week that scientists discovered a mass-extinction of one bee group, Xylocopinae, at around the same time the dinosaurs punched out of the biological timeline. This extinction is …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Commute your way to good health
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-8-6-commute-your-way-to-good-health/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2013 09:36:49 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-8-6-commute-your-way-to-good-health/</guid>
        <description>Who needs Ethos when you’ve got the London Underground? New research from Imperial College London and University College London shows that actively travelling to work (cycling, brisk walking or even using public transport) confers more health benefits than you’d initially suspect.
Most people …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A cut above the rest?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-7-23-a-cut-above-the-rest/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2013 17:28:23 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-7-23-a-cut-above-the-rest/</guid>
        <description>It sounds like something Apple would produce, not a team of Imperial researchers: the iKnife, the surgical device that can ‘sniff out’ cancer.
The iKnife (Intelligent Knife) has been doing the rounds this week, stirring up a fair amount of hype. It works almost in real time, has demonstrated a 100% …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Banishing your demons
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-banishing-your-demons/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 22:50:35 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-13-banishing-your-demons/</guid>
        <description>Statistically, approximately one in every 100 of us will develop schizophrenia over the course of our lifetimes. Schizophrenia is one of the more commonly known mental disorders, but also one that remains somewhat of a mystery to non-sufferers. Whilst the Greek root of the word schizophrenia, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flicking off the fear switch
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-5-flicking-off-the-fear-switch/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 16:10:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-6-5-flicking-off-the-fear-switch/</guid>
        <description>“You asked me once, what was in Room 101. I told you that you knew the answer already. Everyone knows it. The thing that is in Room 101 is the worst thing in the world.”
Room 101: a setting from Orwell’s Nineteen Eighty-Four, the room where everyone’s worst fear is contained. For the protagonist …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Science Bites: Why does cut grass smell?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-29-science-bites-why-does-cut-grass-smell/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 17:30:17 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-29-science-bites-why-does-cut-grass-smell/</guid>
        <description>Causing tissue damage to grass by cutting it causes it to release volatile organic compounds, collectively known as green leaf volatiles (GLVs). One effect of GLV release is to attract predatory insects to defend the plant, though how effective they’d be against a lawnmower is another question. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Helter skelter helicenes
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-8-helter-skelter-helicenes/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 16:36:43 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-5-8-helter-skelter-helicenes/</guid>
        <description>Dr Matthew Fuchter is a Senior Lecturer in Synthetic and Medicinal chemistry at Imperial College London. In close collaboration with Dr Alasdair Campbell from the department of Physics Dr Fuchter and his research group have dedicated some of their research to OLEDs and a group of molecules known as …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Choccy and the dangers towards doggies
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-choccy-and-the-dangers-towards-doggies/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 01:03:57 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-choccy-and-the-dangers-towards-doggies/</guid>
        <description>Chocolate is well known to be toxic to dogs – but why?
Cocoa,the basic ingredient of chocolate, contains a compound known as theobromine (which doesn’t actually contain any bromine), a mild stimulant. In general the darker the chocolate the higher the theobromine concentration.
Upon ingestion, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Resistance on the Rise
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-resistance-on-the-rise/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 01:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-3-15-resistance-on-the-rise/</guid>
        <description>As any good Imperial student knows antibiotic resistant bacteria are a growing threat to human health. The threat has been heightened once again by a recent report produced by the government’s chief medical officer, calling the problem a “ticking timebomb”.
Professor Dame Sally Davies published the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>May the farce be with you, young one
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-28-may-the-farce-be-with-you-young-one/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 23:38:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-28-may-the-farce-be-with-you-young-one/</guid>
        <description>“No. I am your father,” is a line that has gone down in film history. It is at this point that Luke Skywalker finally confronts Darth Vader, his arch enemy, and, as we find out from that immortal line, his biological father. Would the moment have been ruined by an eager audience yelling out “OH NO …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Valve games into films? Sign me up!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-valve-games-into-films-sign-me-up/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 14:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-2-13-valve-games-into-films-sign-me-up/</guid>
        <description>It has to be said that films based on video games don’t tend to get critically praised. Browsing Wikipedia shows that the highest Rotten Tomatoes score one has ever achieved is 43%, which is less than impressive. They are not, in general, the kind of films I pay to see.
But things might well change. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fund cancer research, gain immortality. Maybe.
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-fund-cancer-research-gain-immortality-maybe/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 22:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2013-1-10-fund-cancer-research-gain-immortality-maybe/</guid>
        <description>Ad5[CgA-E1A-miR122]PTD isn’t a catchy name. But, for just one million pounds, Ad5[CgA-E1A-miR122]PTD (Ad5 for short) could be renamed — after you.
But why would anyone want this seemingly pointless honour? A Swedish research team modified Ad5, a basic adenovirus, so that it ‘eats cancer’. More …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Waka waka waka? Pac-Man: The Sequel
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-waka-waka-waka-pac-man-the-sequel/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 01:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-12-7-waka-waka-waka-pac-man-the-sequel/</guid>
        <description>At one point it was just Mimas, one of Saturn’s 62 moons, that looked like 80’s gaming legend Pac-Man. Now Tethys, another Saturnian natural satellite, becomes the second.
The unusual pattern, recorded using NASA’s Cassini probe’s thermal imager, was first spotted on Mimas in 2010, with the warmer …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Colour change test for HIV
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-colour-change-test-for-hiv/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 12:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-11-9-colour-change-test-for-hiv/</guid>
        <description>Biomedical engineers at Imperial College London have developed a cheap new method of detecting ultralow concentrations of HIV and some cancers, with the results visualised via a colour changing solution. This colour change is visible to the naked eye.
The test relies upon a solution that changes …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fishing for the facts
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-fishing-for-the-facts/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 11:56:31 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-10-5-fishing-for-the-facts/</guid>
        <description>&amp;lsquo;Only 100 adult cod in North Sea’; ‘Just 100 cod left in North Sea’; ‘Just 100 mature fish in North Sea’ are but three of the headlines published by The Sunday Times, The Telegraph Online, and The Sun respectively, a little over two weeks ago. One is not required to be a fisherman or marine …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>SCP-173: -- personnel KIA, survivors left gruesomely -------- by -------------
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-scp-173-personnel-kia-survivors-left-gruesomely-by-/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 20:23:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-14-scp-173-personnel-kia-survivors-left-gruesomely-by-/</guid>
        <description>Any class D personnel are to stop reading this article immediately. Further reading with result in immediate termination.
Many of you won’t be familiar with the SCP (Secure, Contain, Protect) Foundation, a wiki dedicated to the cataloging a huge range of fictional paranormal objects. These range …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Has the time come to accept insect cuisine?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-3-has-the-time-come-to-accept-insect-cuisine/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2012 16:10:41 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-6-3-has-the-time-come-to-accept-insect-cuisine/</guid>
        <description>Grasshopper steak, anyone? If that doesn’t tickle your fancy, how about an ant lollipop? Though these ideas may sound revolting, entomophagy, the consumption of insects, may well become more popular in the Western world as fish stocks dwindle and rising population reduces the space available for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Remote-controlled insulin production
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-remote-controlled-insulin-production/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 20:14:53 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-remote-controlled-insulin-production/</guid>
        <description>Researchers in New York have engineered a way to non-invasively trigger gene activation in live animals using nanoparticles and radio waves, a method that may, in the future, be used to remotely control genes in humans for medical purposes.
Current methods of activating cells are unwieldy at best: …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The horror of the modern day horror
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-the-horror-of-the-modern-day-horror/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 19:31:08 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-10-the-horror-of-the-modern-day-horror/</guid>
        <description>Regular readers might know I’ve covered a few horror games in my time – Amnesia: The Dark Descent, Dead Rising 2, Dead Space 2, Limbo, and how could I fail to mention Baron Wittard: Nemesis of Ragnarok (a game as scary as a furious kitten). I’ve also played a good few games I haven’t written about. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A very Odd-World indeed
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-a-very-odd-world-indeed/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 18:45:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-5-3-a-very-odd-world-indeed/</guid>
        <description>It’s a shame Oddworld Inhabitants, an American game company founded way back when I was just knee-high to a grasshopper, stopped making games. Why? Because they made some pretty kick-ass stuff, that’s why. So kick-ass in fact that many modern-day game developers could learn a thing or two from them. …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Games by Angelina: Artificial Intelligence and game design
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-games-by-angelina-artificial-intelligence-and-game-design/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 20:35:24 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-15-games-by-angelina-artificial-intelligence-and-game-design/</guid>
        <description>Laurence: So, first question, for someone who’s never heard of Angelina, how would you best describe it? Mike: Angelina is just a piece of software, exactly like any other kind of application on your computer. It needs a lot more resources to run, and what it essentially does is I set a few …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Can&#39;t pay, won&#39;t pay, must see
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-cant-pay-wont-pay-must-see/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 20:29:34 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-8-cant-pay-wont-pay-must-see/</guid>
        <description>Once more I managed to wangle my way into watching DramSoc’s second spring term production, Can’t Pay? Won’t Pay!, Nobel laureate Dario Fo’s 1974 farcical comedy, involving pseudo-pregnant woman, confused husbands and a suspiciously similar-looking string of police inspectors and undertakers. I was …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Enron to a winner
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-enron-to-a-winner/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2012 22:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-3-1-enron-to-a-winner/</guid>
        <description>Last week I requested a gilded invitation to see DramSoc’s latest spring term play ENRON before it went on stage. Whilst I did get my invite I didn’t get it on gold leaf coated paper, the stingy gits. In spite of this I went to see the cast perform on Tuesday, with no idea what to expect, despite …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Virtual dating for those despondent Valentines
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-virtual-dating-for-those-despondent-valentines/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 21:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-virtual-dating-for-those-despondent-valentines/</guid>
        <description>Alyx Vance (HL2 Series)
From: City 17 The Good:_ Feisty yet incredibly practical action girl with energy and brains to spare._ The Bad: Packs heat. On no account leave the relationship on a sour note. Mr Right: Prefers the strong, silent nerdy type. Having a PhD in theoretical physics is a plus.
If …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Better read than Dead
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-better-read-than-dead/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 21:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-16-better-read-than-dead/</guid>
        <description>Death is a real nuisance. You can’t move, you can’t see, you can’t – well, let’s be honest here, you can’t do much at all. The best you can manage is a bit of basic decomposition, but it’s not really something to brag about (not that you can talk anyway). On the plus side though, you do get some …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Modern medicine
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-modern-medicine/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 22:54:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-modern-medicine/</guid>
        <description>You might not immediately assume DNA sequencing technology and human medicine go hand in hand, but you’d be wrong. Research currently being carried out by scientists involved in the Human Genome Project is having a huge impact on 21st century medicine.
In a lecture on February 2, organised by the …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Total Annihilation totally annihilates boredom
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-total-annihilation-totally-annihilates-boredom/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 22:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-9-total-annihilation-totally-annihilates-boredom/</guid>
        <description>Oh, so you were expecting a review on a new game? What new game? January and February are hell for game reviews; nothing’s being churned out by the video game companies. So instead, I’m going to take the time to wind the clock back and review a game I played when I was eleven. It was brilliant then …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Putting a pause on influenza research
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-putting-a-pause-on-influenza-research/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 19:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-2-2-putting-a-pause-on-influenza-research/</guid>
        <description>Research involving a virulent mutant strain of the influenza A virus has been temporarily halted over fears of potential bioterrorism and accidental release.
It is widely recognized by scientists and laypeople alike that influenza continues to pose a great threat to global health, even rivalling …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Problem of Piracy
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-the-problem-of-piracy/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 20:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2012-1-19-the-problem-of-piracy/</guid>
        <description>Some readers may well be familiar with the acronyms SOPA and PIPA, both of which have been bounded about in the news over the last few months or so. They stand for the Stop Online Piracy Act and the closely related Protect IP (Intellectual Property) Act. Both are bills that are currently being …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Top Picks from 2011
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-the-top-picks-from-2011/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 21:22:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,Michael Cook,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-12-8-the-top-picks-from-2011/</guid>
        <description>Michael Cook goes for Team Fortress 2
Team Fortress 2 is not a new release for 2011. But the renaissance it underwent over the last 12 months means it might as well be treated as such. A huge number of new ideas have been ploughed into this game, and it remains as fresh, vibrant and playful as it …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>COD: MW3 theft shocks world
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-cod-mw3-theft-shocks-world/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 22:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-11-10-cod-mw3-theft-shocks-world/</guid>
        <description>So I guess some of you were expecting a Modern Warfare 3 review, right? I barely have enough money to subsist on dry bread and so little free time that I can only sleep for half an hour each day, so you expect me to purchase and play COD: MW3? I guess a man can dream. If you’re all good little girls …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Good riddance, Gaddafi
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-28-good-riddance-gaddafi/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 00:31:29 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-28-good-riddance-gaddafi/</guid>
        <description>Unless you’ve been living under a rock, or hiding out in a sewer for the last week, you’ll know that everyone’s favourite Northern African whack job Muammar Gaddafi is dead. To this I say – good riddance. I shall miss you about as much as I do my ingrown toenail.
Now, unless you’re a Libyan rebel, …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Free-to-Play? Watch your language
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-free-to-play-watch-your-language/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 23:25:52 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-27-free-to-play-watch-your-language/</guid>
        <description>Free-to-play games are exactly what they say on the tin – video games that don’t cost money to play. If this is what they truly were then I could wrap this article up right now, but unfortunately the rule ‘there’s no such thing as a free lunch’ still remains unbroken. Here’s why.
I picked up on this …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Byron means Burger
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-byron-means-burger/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 11:54:58 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-byron-means-burger/</guid>
        <description>“I want to keep fighting because it is the only thing that keeps me out of the hamburger joints. If I don’t fight, I’ll eat this planet.” Take this George Foreman quote, replace ‘fight’ with ‘study’ and ‘hamburger joints’ with ‘Byron’ and it’s instantly applicable to me. Well, sort of. OK, not …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>DLC - To pay, or not to pay?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-dlc-to-pay-or-not-to-pay/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 10:28:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-21-dlc-to-pay-or-not-to-pay/</guid>
        <description>So, a little over a week ago Valve brought out a fairly large update for their flagship game Team Fortress 2. So what? Ignoring the fact that TF2 is now over four years old and still receiving content updates which it celebrated this time last year when microtransactions were first introduced into …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Minecraft: so much more than just Lego for nerds
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-minecraft-so-much-more-than-just-lego-for-nerds/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 22:41:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-13-minecraft-so-much-more-than-just-lego-for-nerds/</guid>
        <description>Yesterday one of my friends asked me – what’s the deal with Minecraft? I tried to explain it to them, but to no avail. So here’s try two – in print form. Maybe I’ll enlighten this time around…
It’s easy to say what Minecraft (by developers Mojang) is – an open-world sandbox game with no goal in mind …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An ex-po-citing Expo
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-an-ex-po-citing-expo/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 12:19:06 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-10-7-an-ex-po-citing-expo/</guid>
        <description>I guess now’s the time for me to offer a late (but warm) welcome to all the freshers who’ve stumbled onto the Games section. I would’ve written for the Freshers&amp;rsquo; Issue, but I was too busy doing more important stuff like working on my rock-hard abs, jet skiing in the Caribbean and seducing …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flower power in your pocket
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-flower-power-in-your-pocket/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 04:31:40 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-20-flower-power-in-your-pocket/</guid>
        <description>I cannot stand writing articles. There, I said it.
You know why I detest penning these things? It is because once a week I have to get off my lazy behind, I have to stop playing games and I have to churn out something for you lot to read. In general, the more I enjoy a game the more hate-filled I …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Are video games a waste of time?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-are-video-games-a-waste-of-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 19:05:57 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Omar Hafeez-Bore,Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-12-are-video-games-a-waste-of-time/</guid>
        <description>I guess so – Laurence Pope
This was always going to be a difficult piece to write, since the answer to the above question could be summed up succinctly in a single syllable – yes. Unfortunately, my editor isn’t particularly happy with one word articles, so I suppose I’d better make something out of …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Portal 2? Like Portal but better, dummy!
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-portal-2-like-portal-but-better-dummy/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 14:59:38 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-5-6-portal-2-like-portal-but-better-dummy/</guid>
        <description>Hello Felix readers, Cave Johnson here, founder and CEO of Aperture Science. Now I’m sure you’re all wondering, “Cave, why are you writing about Portal 2? Why are you breaking the fourth wall?” I’ll tell you why, it’s because I’m Cave Johnson and I don’t let silly little things like rules and …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Old Games Revisited: GTA 2
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-old-games-revisited-gta-2/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 20:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-28-old-games-revisited-gta-2/</guid>
        <description>Alright folks, it’s time to sit back and take a great big hit from the nostalgia bong. Today we’re going to be travelling back in time to when the Grand Theft Auto series was actually good and take a look at GTA2.
OK, I’d better clarify that statement before the slew of hate mail. The GTA series …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Magicka: A mad, mixed bag of tricks
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-magicka-a-mad-mixed-bag-of-tricks/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 20:36:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-10-magicka-a-mad-mixed-bag-of-tricks/</guid>
        <description>Ahh, cosplay. There’s nothing I like more than putting on my robe and wizard hat, striding round the Queen’s Lawn and waving about my enormous magical staff, casting spells of such power that mere mortals can only gasp in awe. Then, some killjoy policeman arrests me for public indecency, or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dead Space 2: New aliens, same ol&#39; frights
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-4-dead-space-2-new-aliens-same-ol-frights/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 16:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-2-4-dead-space-2-new-aliens-same-ol-frights/</guid>
        <description>In the immortal words of John McClane: “How can the same shit happen to the same guy twice?” In this case the ‘shit’ is another alien infection and the ‘guy’ is everyone’s favourite space engineer, Isaac Clarke (lose a thousand nerd points if you miss the reference).
Yes, dear old Isaac is back once …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Super Meat Boy: is it as delicious as they say?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-super-meat-boy-is-it-as-delicious-as-they-say/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 20:23:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2011-1-27-super-meat-boy-is-it-as-delicious-as-they-say/</guid>
        <description>Three things are required to complete a game like Super Meat Boy successfully: The first is a sturdy keyboard or controller, the second is a level of patience few devout Zen Buddhists can ever hope to attain and the third is more free time than your average Arts or Media Studies student. Whilst I’m …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stuck for gift ideas for your pet gamer?
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-stuck-for-gift-ideas-for-your-pet-gamer/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 19:57:17 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-12-9-stuck-for-gift-ideas-for-your-pet-gamer/</guid>
        <description>Do YOU LIKE GAMES? Do your FRIENDS like games? Do you even HAVE any friends? If you answered YES to these questions then READ ON.
With the Christmas season approaching, it’s time to start looking for presents, and why waste time wrapping boxes when you could use Steam to deliver your expensive (or …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It’s raining games! Cloud gaming hits TVs
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-26-its-raining-games-cloud-gaming-hits-tvs/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2010 14:58:37 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-26-its-raining-games-cloud-gaming-hits-tvs/</guid>
        <description>Hear me now, peasants, with your antiquated computers, bowls of gruel and embarrassing outdated fashion sense! No longer are you quite so inferior to the glorious PC gaming master races with their diamond studded octo-core processors, water cooled graphics cards and jewel-encrusted laser mice, for …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The next revolution in gaming has arrived
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-15-the-next-revolution-in-gaming-has-arrived/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 18:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-15-the-next-revolution-in-gaming-has-arrived/</guid>
        <description>Kinect, Microsoft’s most recent peripheral for the Xbox 360, is set to arrive in UK stores by the time your eyes are roving over this article. There’s been a fair bit of hype and excitement pertaining to Microsoft’s latest gadget, but is it really justified? Is Kinect the greatest thing since sliced …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Polynomial proves maths isn’t fun
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-polynomial-proves-maths-isnt-fun/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2010 18:27:48 +0000</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-11-4-polynomial-proves-maths-isnt-fun/</guid>
        <description>The Polynomial – Space Of The Music, far from being just a mathematical expression, is a 3D music action game in which you pilot a space ship through a brightly coloured universe that pulsates along to currently playing song.
The premise is simple: you select a certain music track, and the game will …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Felix’s guide to surviving the zombie apocalypse
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-felixs-guide-to-surviving-the-zombie-apocalypse/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 19:19:51 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-28-felixs-guide-to-surviving-the-zombie-apocalypse/</guid>
        <description>So we all know the zombie apocalypse is coming at some point, most likely arising from some combination of a genetically modified virus, a dodgy business venture and a mad Imperial graduate. When it does strike, what on Earth do you do? No idea? Well, after days of careful thought I’ve come up with …</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Graphic survival horror: the forgotten genre
</title>
        <link>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-graphic-survival-horror-the-forgotten-genre/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 19:33:22 +0100</pubDate>
        
          <author>Laurence Pope,</author>
        
        <guid>https://old.felixonline.co.uk/articles/2010-10-21-graphic-survival-horror-the-forgotten-genre/</guid>
        <description>Amnesia: The Dark Descent is a graphic adventure survival horror game that had me swapping out trousers on a regular basis, and I shall endeavour to convey why this little-known gem is so worthy of attention. First though, a little introduction to Frictional Games, and the current state of the …</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
